<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Conservatism &amp; Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/conservatism-right-of-centre-democratic-ideologies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/conservatism-right-of-centre-democratic-ideologies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Conservatism &amp; Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/conservatism-right-of-centre-democratic-ideologies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</title>
		<link>/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR </p>
<p>                     When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch a cable news network in 1996, American politics and media changed forever. With a remarkable level of detail and insight, Vanity Fair magazine reporter Gabriel Sherman puts Ailes&#8217;s unique genius on display, along with the outsize personalities&#8211;Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Sean Hannity, Megyn Kelly, Sarah Palin, Karl Rove, Glenn Beck, Mike Huckabee, Gretchen Carlson, Bill Shine, and others&#8211;who have helped Fox News play a defining role in the great social and political controversies of the past two decades. From the Clinton-Lewinsky scandal to the Bush-Gore recount, from the war in Iraq to the Tea Party attack on the Obama presidency, Roger Ailes developed an unrivaled power to sway the national agenda. Even more, he became the indispensable figure in conservative America and the man any Republican politician with presidential aspirations had to court. </p>
<p>                     How did this man become the master strategist of our political landscape? In revelatory detail, Sherman chronicles the rise of Ailes, a frail kid from an Ohio factory town who, through sheer willpower, the flair of a showman, fierce corporate politicking, and a profound understanding of the priorities of middle America, built the most influential television news empire of our time. </p>
<p>                     Drawing on hundreds of interviews with Fox News insiders past and present, Sherman documents Ailes&#8217;s tactical acuity as he battled the press, business rivals, and countless real and perceived enemies inside and outside Fox. Sherman takes us inside the morning meetings in which Ailes and other high-level executives strategized Fox&#8217;s presentation of the news to advance Ailes&#8217;s political agenda; provides behind-the-scenes details of Ailes&#8217;s crucial role as finder and shaper of talent, including his sometimes rocky relationships with Fox News stars such as O&#8217;Reilly, Hannity, and Carlson; and probes Ailes&#8217;s fraught partnership with his equally brash and mercurial boss, Rupert Murdoch. </p>
<p>                     Roger Ailes&#8217;s life is a story worthy of Citizen Kane. Featuring an afterword about Ailes&#8217;s epic downfall during the extraordinary 2016 election, The Loudest Voice in the Room is an extraordinary feat of reportage with a compelling human drama at its heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Politically Incorrect Guide to Western Civilization &#8211; Anthony Esolen</title>
		<link>/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-western-civilization-anthony-esolen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-western-civilization-anthony-esolen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everything you should know&#8211;but PC professors won&#8217;t teach&#8211;about Western heritage. Western civilization is the envy of the globe. It has given to the world universally accepted understandings of human rights (rooted in Judeo-Christian principles), created standards for art, music, and literature that have never been equaled, and originated political and social systems that have spread [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-western-civilization-anthony-esolen/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to Western Civilization &#8211; Anthony Esolen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything you should know&#8211;but PC professors won&#8217;t teach&#8211;about Western heritage. </p>
<p>                     Western civilization is the envy of the globe. It has given to the world universally accepted understandings of human rights (rooted in Judeo-Christian principles), created standards for art, music, and literature that have never been equaled, and originated political and social systems that have spread all across the planet. </p>
<p>                     Political correctness now obscures these and other truths about Western civilization. Leftists and Islamic jihadists find common cause in assailing Western &#8220;colonialism,&#8221; &#8220;imperialism,&#8221; and &#8220;racism&#8221; as its defining characteristics. Guilt-ridden Western leaders and public figures speak of their cultural patrimony in disparaging terms they would never dare to use about a non-Western culture. And in universities, &#8220;multicultural&#8221;-minded professors flatter students into believing they have nothing really to learn from Sophocles or Shakespeare. </p>
<p>                     But now, Professor Anthony Esolen&#8211;one of the team-teachers of Providence College&#8217;s esteemed Development of Western Civilization Core Curriculum&#8211;has risen to the West&#8217;s defense. The Politically Incorrect Guide(TM) to Western Civilization takes on the prevailing liberal assumptions that make Western civilization the universal whipping boy for today&#8217;s global problems &#8211; and introduces you to the significant events, individuals, nations, ideas, and artistic achievements that make Western civilization the greatest the world has ever known. </p>
<p>                     Today, defending the West has become an urgent imperative: if we don&#8217;t value what we have and what we have inherited, we will surely lose it. The Politically Incorrect Guide(tm) to Western Civilization is an essential sourcebook for that defense.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-western-civilization-anthony-esolen/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to Western Civilization &#8211; Anthony Esolen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution &#8211; Larry Schweikart</title>
		<link>/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American War Of Independence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The truth about the American Revolution is under attack. Despite what you may have learned in school, it wasn&#8217;t a rich slaveholder&#8217;s war fought to maintain white privilege. In fact, the War of Independence wasn&#8217;t about maintaining any status quo&#8211;it was the world&#8217;s first successful bottom-up revolution by the people, ushering in a new dawn [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution &#8211; Larry Schweikart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The truth about the American Revolution is under attack. Despite what you may have learned in school, it wasn&#8217;t a rich slaveholder&#8217;s war fought to maintain white privilege. In fact, the War of Independence wasn&#8217;t about maintaining any status quo&#8211;it was the world&#8217;s first successful bottom-up revolution by the people, ushering in a new dawn of liberty that history had never seen before. But with left-wingers dominating the teaching of history, where can you go for the true story of the unprecedented events that made the United States the worlds greatest nation? </p>
<p>                     Now bestselling historian Larry Schweikart has teamed up with author Dave Dougherty to write the ground-breaking patriotic history you&#8217;ve always wanted to read about the foundation of our unique nation. The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution reveals:<br />
                     Four key factors that applied only in America, making it impossible to replicate the Revolution anywhere else  Why it matters that the Patriot ghting force was overwhelmingly Scotch-Irish  The key role of Protestantism: which denominations tended to become Patriots, and which Tories How Americans were different from the Europeans and English even at the outset of the Revolution  How the casualties of the deadliest war in American history are routinely underreported  How our Revolution became a model for hundreds of others&#8211;that all failed<br />
                     Schweikart and Dougherty take on the left-wing myths&#8211;starting with the Marxist narrative of the Revolution in Howard Zinn&#8217;s nearly ubiquitous A People&#8217;s History of the United States&#8211;and uncover the truth about America&#8217;s beginning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution &#8211; Larry Schweikart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Rednecks &#038; White Liberals : Hope, Mercy, Justice and Autonomy in the American Health Care System &#8211; Thomas Sowell</title>
		<link>/black-rednecks-white-liberals-hope-mercy-justice-and-autonomy-in-the-american-health-care-system-thomas-sowell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-rednecks-white-liberals-hope-mercy-justice-and-autonomy-in-the-american-health-care-system-thomas-sowell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This explosive new book challenges many of the long-prevailing assumptions about blacks, about Jews, about Germans, about slavery, and about education. Plainly written, powerfully reasoned, and backed with a startling array of documented facts, Black Rednecks and White Liberals takes on not only the trendy intellectuals of our times but also such historic interpreters of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-rednecks-white-liberals-hope-mercy-justice-and-autonomy-in-the-american-health-care-system-thomas-sowell/">Black Rednecks &#038; White Liberals : Hope, Mercy, Justice and Autonomy in the American Health Care System &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This explosive new book challenges many of the long-prevailing assumptions about blacks, about Jews, about Germans, about slavery, and about education. Plainly written, powerfully reasoned, and backed with a startling array of documented facts, Black Rednecks and White Liberals takes on not only the trendy intellectuals of our times but also such historic interpreters of American life as Alexis de Tocqueville and Frederick Law Olmsted. In a series of long essays, this book presents an in-depth look at key beliefs behind many mistaken and dangerous actions, policies, and trends. It presents eye-opening insights into the historical development of the ghetto culture that is today wrongly seen as a unique black identity&#8211;a culture cheered on toward self-destruction by white liberals who consider themselves &#8220;friends&#8221; of blacks. An essay titled &#8220;The Real History of Slavery&#8221; presents a jolting re-examination of that tragic institution and the narrow and distorted way it is too often seen today. The reasons for the venomous hatred of Jews, and of other groups like them in countries around the world, are explored in an essay that asks, &#8220;Are Jews Generic?&#8221;<br />
                    Misconceptions of German history in general, and of the Nazi era in particular, are also re-examined. So too are the inspiring achievements and painful tragedies of black education in the United States. &#8220;Black Rednecks and White Liberals&#8221; is the capstone of decades of outstanding research and writing on racial and cultural issues by Thomas Sowell.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-rednecks-white-liberals-hope-mercy-justice-and-autonomy-in-the-american-health-care-system-thomas-sowell/">Black Rednecks &#038; White Liberals : Hope, Mercy, Justice and Autonomy in the American Health Care System &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</title>
		<link>/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate. Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate.    </p>
<p>                    Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence to challenge the idea that different economic outcomes can be explained by any one factor, be it discrimination, exploitation, or genetics. This revised and enlarged edition also analyzes the human consequences of the prevailing social vision of these disparities and the policies based on that vision&#8211;from educational disasters to widespread crime and violence.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dangerous &#8211; Milo Yiannopoulos</title>
		<link>/dangerous-milo-yiannopoulos/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dangerous-milo-yiannopoulos/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The liberal media machine did everything they could to keep this book out of your hands. Now, finally, DANGEROUS, the most controversial book of the decade, is tearing down safe spaces everywhere.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerous-milo-yiannopoulos/">Dangerous &#8211; Milo Yiannopoulos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The liberal media machine did everything they could to keep this book out of your hands. Now, finally, DANGEROUS, the most controversial book of the decade, is tearing down safe spaces everywhere.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerous-milo-yiannopoulos/">Dangerous &#8211; Milo Yiannopoulos</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Politically Incorrect Guide to Socialism &#8211; Kevin D Williamson</title>
		<link>/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-socialism-kevin-d-williamson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-socialism-kevin-d-williamson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stalin&#8217;s gulag, impoverished North Korea, collapsing Cuba&#8230;it&#8217;s hard to name a dogma that has failed as spectacularly as socialism. And yet leaders around the world continue to subject millions of people to this dysfunctional, violence-prone ideology. In The Politically Incorrect Guide(TM) to Socialism, Kevin Williamson reveals the fatal flaw of socialism&#8211;that efficient, complex economies simply [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-socialism-kevin-d-williamson/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to Socialism &#8211; Kevin D Williamson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stalin&#8217;s gulag, impoverished North Korea, collapsing Cuba&#8230;it&#8217;s hard to name a dogma that has failed as spectacularly as socialism. And yet leaders around the world continue to subject millions of people to this dysfunctional, violence-prone ideology. </p>
<p>                    In The Politically Incorrect Guide(TM) to Socialism, Kevin Williamson reveals the fatal flaw of socialism&#8211;that efficient, complex economies simply can&#8217;t be centrally planned. But even in America, that hasn&#8217;t stopped politicians and bureaucrats from planning, to various extents, the most vital sectors of our economy: public education, energy, and the most arrogant central-planning effort of them all, Obama&#8217;s healthcare plan. </p>
<p>                    In this provocative book, Williamson unfolds the grim history of socialism, showing how the ideology has spawned crushing poverty, devastating famines, and horrific wars. Lumbering from one crisis to the next, leaving a trail of economic devastation and environmental catastrophe, socialism has wreaked more havoc, caused more deaths, and impoverished more people than any other ideology in history&#8211;especially when you include the victims of fascism, which Williamson notes is simply a variant of socialism. </p>
<p>                    Williamson further demonstrates: </p>
<p>                    Why, contrary to popular belief, socialism in theory is no better than socialism in practice<br />
                    Why socialism can&#8217;t exist without capitalism<br />
                    How the energy powerhouse of Venezuela, under socialism, has become an economic basket case subject to rationing and blackouts<br />
                    How socialism, not British colonialism, plunged the bountiful economy of India into stagnation and dysfunction&#8211;and how capitalism is rescuing it<br />
                    Why socialism is inextricably linked to communism </p>
<p>                    If you thought socialism went into the dustbin of history with the collapse of the Soviet Union, think again. Socialism is alive and kicking, and it&#8217;s already spread further than you know.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-socialism-kevin-d-williamson/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to Socialism &#8211; Kevin D Williamson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019</p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.</p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.</p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.</p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?</p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A LITHUB BOOK OF THE DECADE. The US is one of the largest democracies in the world &#8211; or is it? America is experiencing an age of profound economic inequality. Employee protections have been decimated, and state welfare is virtually non-existent, while hedge fund billionaires are grossly under-taxed and big businesses make astounding profits at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/">Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A LITHUB BOOK OF THE DECADE.    </p>
<p>                    The US is one of the largest democracies in the world &#8211; or is it?    </p>
<p>                    America is experiencing an age of profound economic inequality. Employee protections have been decimated, and state welfare is virtually non-existent, while hedge fund billionaires are grossly under-taxed and big businesses make astounding profits at the expense of the environment and of their workers.    </p>
<p>                    How did this come about, and who were the driving forces behind it?    </p>
<p>                    In this powerful and meticulously researched work of investigative journalism, New Yorker staff writer Jane Mayer exposes the network of billionaires trying to buy the US electoral system &#8211; and succeeding. Led by libertarian industrialists the Koch brothers, they believe that taxes are a form of tyranny and that government oversight of business is an assault on freedom. Together, they have spent hundreds of millions of dollars influencing politicians and voters, and hijacking American democracy for their own ends.    </p>
<p>                    Dark Money brilliantly illuminates a shady corner of US politics. It is essential reading for anybody interested in the future of democracy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/">Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Liars, Leakers, and Liberals : The Case Against the Anti-Trump Conspiracy &#8211; Judge Jeanine Pirro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/liars-leakers-and-liberals-the-case-against-the-anti-trump-conspiracy-judge-jeanine-pirro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/liars-leakers-and-liberals-the-case-against-the-anti-trump-conspiracy-judge-jeanine-pirro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At this point in American history, we are the victims of a liberal sabotage of the presidency unlike anything we&#8217;ve ever witnessed. Nevertheless President Trump continues to fight every day to keep his promise to Make America Great Again. Today that bold idea has already led to a conservative judge on the Supreme Court, tax [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/liars-leakers-and-liberals-the-case-against-the-anti-trump-conspiracy-judge-jeanine-pirro-abridged/">Liars, Leakers, and Liberals : The Case Against the Anti-Trump Conspiracy &#8211; Judge Jeanine Pirro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At this point in American history, we are the victims of a liberal sabotage of the presidency unlike anything we&#8217;ve ever witnessed.  Nevertheless President Trump continues to fight every day to keep his promise to Make America Great Again. Today that bold idea has already led to a conservative judge on the Supreme Court, tax reform, and deregulation that has unleashed an economy stronger than anyone could have imagined.    </p>
<p>                    But there are dark forces that seek to obstruct and undermine the president and reverse the results of the 2016 presidential election.  They are part of a wide-ranging conspiracy that would seem incredible if it weren&#8217;t being perpetrated openly.  Driven by ambition, blinded by greed, and bound by a common goal &#8212; to unseat the 45th President of the United States &#8212; this cabal is determined to maintain its wrongful hold on national political power.    </p>
<p>                    Fox News host Jeanine Pirro uncovers the elements of this conspiracy, including:<br />
                    &#8220;Fake news&#8221; propaganda,Law enforcement corruption at the highest levels,National security leaks by the intelligence community,Bureaucratic resistance to lawful and constitutional executive orders issued by the duly elected president,Crooked deals with foreign governments by U.S. officials sworn to defend our Constitution.<br />
                    It&#8217;s about time the American public knows the truth about the plot to bring down the Trump presidency. By the time you&#8217;ve finished this book, you&#8217;ll agree with Judge Pirro that the only way to stop these hoodlums is to Take Them Out in Cuffs!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/liars-leakers-and-liberals-the-case-against-the-anti-trump-conspiracy-judge-jeanine-pirro-abridged/">Liars, Leakers, and Liberals : The Case Against the Anti-Trump Conspiracy &#8211; Judge Jeanine Pirro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH     </p>
<p>                    The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, and Obama&#8217;s America.      </p>
<p>                     What is the big lie of the Democratic Party? That conservatives&#8211;and President Donald Trump in particular&#8211;are fascists. Nazis, even. In a typical comment, MSNBC host Rachel Maddow says the Trump era is reminiscent of what it was like when Hitler first became chancellor.     </p>
<p>                     But in fact, this audacious lie is a complete inversion of the truth. Yes, there is a fascist threat in America&#8211;but that threat is from the Left and the Democratic Party. The Democratic left has an ideology virtually identical with fascism and routinely borrows tactics of intimidation and political terror from the Nazi Brownshirts.     </p>
<p>                     To cover up their insidious fascist agenda, Democrats loudly accuse President Trump and other Republicans of being Nazis&#8211;an obvious lie, considering the GOP has been fighting the Democrats over slavery, genocide, racism and fascism from the beginning.     </p>
<p>                     Now, finally, Dinesh D&#8217;Souza explodes the Left&#8217;s big lie. He expertly exonerates President Trump and his supporters, then uncovers the Democratic Left&#8217;s long, cozy relationship with Nazism: how the racist and genocidal acts of early Democrats inspired Adolf Hitler&#8217;s campaign of death; how fascist philosophers influenced the great 20th century lions of the American Left; and how today&#8217;s anti-free speech, anti-capitalist, anti-religious liberty, pro-violence Democratic Party is a frightening simulacrum of the Nazi Party.     </p>
<p>                     Hitler coined the term the big lie to describe a lie that the great masses of the people will fall for precisely because of how bold and monstrous the lie is. In The Big Lie, D&#8217;Souza shows that the Democratic Left&#8217;s orchestrated campaign to paint President Trump and conservatives as Nazis to cover up its own fascism is, in fact, the biggest lie of all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Triggered : How the Left Thrives on Hate and Wants to Silence Us &#8211; Donald Trump, Jr. (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/triggered-how-the-left-thrives-on-hate-and-wants-to-silence-us-donald-trump-jr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Censorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/triggered-how-the-left-thrives-on-hate-and-wants-to-silence-us-donald-trump-jr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Triggered, Donald Trump, Jr. will expose all the tricks that the left uses to smear conservatives and push them out of the public square, from online &#8220;shadow banning&#8221; to fake accusations of &#8220;hate speech.&#8221; No topic is spared from political correctness. This is the book that the leftist elites don&#8217;t want you to read! [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/triggered-how-the-left-thrives-on-hate-and-wants-to-silence-us-donald-trump-jr-abridged/">Triggered : How the Left Thrives on Hate and Wants to Silence Us &#8211; Donald Trump, Jr. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Triggered, Donald Trump, Jr. will expose all the tricks that the left uses to smear conservatives and push them out of the public square, from online &#8220;shadow banning&#8221; to fake accusations of &#8220;hate speech.&#8221; No topic is spared from political correctness. This is the book that the leftist elites don&#8217;t want you to read!     </p>
<p>                    Trump, Jr. will write about the importance of fighting back and standing up for what you believe in. From his childhood summers in Communist Czechoslovakia that began his political thought process, to working on construction sites with his father, to the major achievements of President Trump&#8217;s administration, Donald Trump, Jr. spares no details and delivers a book that focuses on success and perseverance, and proves offense is the best defense.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/triggered-how-the-left-thrives-on-hate-and-wants-to-silence-us-donald-trump-jr-abridged/">Triggered : How the Left Thrives on Hate and Wants to Silence Us &#8211; Donald Trump, Jr. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For more than a year, Hillary Clinton has laid out an ambitious agenda to improve the lives of the American people and make the country stronger and safer. Stronger Together presents that agenda in full, relating stories from the American people and outlining the Clinton/Kaine campaign&#8217;s plans on everything from apprenticeships to the Zika virus, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/">Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For more than a year, Hillary Clinton has laid out an ambitious agenda to improve the lives of the American people and make the country stronger and safer. Stronger Together presents that agenda in full, relating stories from the American people and outlining the Clinton/Kaine campaign&#8217;s plans on everything from apprenticeships to the Zika virus, including:<br />
                     -Building an economy that works for everyone.<br />
                     -Making investment in good-paying jobs, including infrastructure, manufacturing, clean energy and small business.<br />
                     -Making debt-free college a reality and tackling the student debt crisis.<br />
                     -A course of action to defeat global terrorist networks and support allies.<br />
                     -Breaking down the barriers that hold Americans back by reforming a broken immigration system, ending mass incarceration, protecting voting rights, and fixing the campaign finance system.<br />
                     -Putting families first through universal, affordable health care; paid family and medical leave, and affordable child care.<br />
                        Stronger Together offers specific solutions and a bold vision for building a more perfect union.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/">Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Right Side of History : How Reason and Moral Purpose Made the West Great &#8211; Ben Shapiro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Intolerance, Persecution & Conflict]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Issues & Debates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! Human beings have never had it better than we have it now in the West. So why are we on the verge of throwing it all away? In 2016, New York Times bestselling author Ben Shapiro spoke at the University of California-Berkeley. Hundreds of police officers were required to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/">The Right Side of History : How Reason and Moral Purpose Made the West Great &#8211; Ben Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!    </p>
<p>                    Human beings have never had it better than we have it now in the West. So why are we on the verge of throwing it all away?    </p>
<p>                    In 2016, New York Times bestselling author Ben Shapiro spoke at the University of California-Berkeley. Hundreds of police officers were required to protect his speech. What was so frightening about Shapiro? He came to argue that Western civilization is in the midst of a crisis of purpose and ideas; that we have let grievances replace our sense of community and political expediency limit our individual rights; that we are teaching our kids that their emotions matter more than rational debate; and that the only meaning in life is arbitrary and subjective.    </p>
<p>                    As a society, we are forgetting that almost everything great that has ever happened in history happened because of people who believed in both Judeo-Christian values and in the Greek-born power of reason. In The Right Side of History, Shapiro sprints through more than 3,500 years, dozens of philosophers, and the thicket of modern politics to show how our freedoms are built upon the twin notions that every human being is made in God&#8217;s image and that human beings were created with reason capable of exploring God&#8217;s world.    </p>
<p>                    We can thank these values for the birth of science, the dream of progress, human rights, prosperity, peace, and artistic beauty. Jerusalem and Athens built America, ended slavery, defeated the Nazis and the Communists, lifted billions from poverty, and gave billions more spiritual purpose.     </p>
<p>                    Yet we are in the process of abandoning Judeo-Christian values and Greek natural law, watching our civilization collapse into age-old tribalism, individualistic hedonism, and moral subjectivism. We believe we can satisfy ourselves with intersectionality, scientific materialism, progressive politics, authoritarian governance, or nationalistic solidarity.    </p>
<p>                    We can&#8217;t.    </p>
<p>                    The West is special, and in The Right Side of History, Ben Shapiro bravely explains how we have lost sight of the moral purpose that drives each of us to be better, the sacred duty to work together for the greater good,.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/">The Right Side of History : How Reason and Moral Purpose Made the West Great &#8211; Ben Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public. Unfreedom of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public.     </p>
<p>                    Unfreedom of the Press is not just another book about the press. In &#8220;Levin&#8217;s finest work&#8221; (Breitbart), he shows how those entrusted with news reporting today are destroying freedom of the press from within-not through actions of government officials, but with its own abandonment of reportorial integrity and objective journalism.    </p>
<p>                    With the depth of historical background for which his books are renowned, Levin takes you on a journey through the early American patriot press, which proudly promoted the principles set forth in the Declaration of Independence and the Constitution. This is followed by the early decades of the Republic during which newspapers around the young country were open and transparent about their fierce allegiance to one political party or another.    </p>
<p>                    It was only at the start of the Progressive Era and the 20th century that the supposed &#8220;objectivity of the press&#8221; first surfaced, leaving us where we are today: with a partisan party-press overwhelmingly aligned with a political ideology but hypocritically engaged in a massive untruth as to its real nature.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal: to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221; major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal:  to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221;  major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair way.     </p>
<p>                    Breitbart burst on to the national media scene thanks to his coverage of  the ACORN controversy, where a local ACORN community group leader was videotaped giving business advice to a &#8220;gentleman&#8221; who ran a prostitution ring. When the major news media at first tried to bury the story, Breitbart used his extraordinary marketing savvy to make sure the story got full national attention.     </p>
<p>                    More recently, Congressman Anthony Weiner took on Breitbart, claiming that scurrilous photos of Weiner were being sent on the internet by the conservative right. In a new chapter in RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart details how &#8220;Weinergate&#8221; was entirely the personal fault of Congressman Weiner, and how Weiner derailed his own promising career by trying to implicate Breitbart and conservative journalists.    </p>
<p>                    In short, RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart talks about the key issues that Americans face, how he has aligned himself with the Tea Party, and how one needs to deal with the liberal news world head on. Along the way, he details his early years, working with Matt Drudge, the Huffington Post, and so on, and how Breitbart developed his unique style of launching key websites to help get the word out to conservatives all over.     </p>
<p>                    A rollicking and controversial read, Breitbart will certainly raise your blood pressure, one way or another.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! Washington insiders operate by a proven credo: When a Peter Schweizer book drops, duck and brace for impact. For over a decade, the work of six-time New York Times bestselling investigative reporter Peter Schweizer has sent shockwaves through the political universe. Clinton Cash revealed the Clintons&#8217; international money flow, exposed global [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/">Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!    </p>
<p>                    Washington insiders operate by a proven credo: When a Peter Schweizer book drops, duck and brace for impact.    </p>
<p>                    For over a decade, the work of six-time New York Times bestselling investigative reporter Peter Schweizer has sent shockwaves through the political universe.    </p>
<p>                    Clinton Cash revealed the Clintons&#8217; international money flow, exposed global corruption, and sparked an FBI investigation. Secret Empires exposed bipartisan corruption and launched congressional investigations. And Throw Them All Out and Extortion prompted passage of the STOCK Act. Indeed, Schweizer&#8217;s &#8220;follow the money&#8221; bombshell revelations have been featured on the front pages of the New York Times and the Wall Street Journal, and regularly appear on national news programs, including 60 Minutes.    </p>
<p>                    Now Schweizer and his team of seasoned investigators turn their focus to the nation&#8217;s top progressives-politicians who strive to acquire more government power to achieve their political ends.    </p>
<p>                    Can they be trusted with more power?    </p>
<p>                    In Profiles in Corruption, Schweizer offers a deep-dive investigation into the private finances, and secrets deals of some of America&#8217;s top political leaders. And, as usual, he doesn&#8217;t disappoint, with never-before-reported revelations that uncover corruption and abuse of power-all backed up by a mountain of corporate documents and legal filings from around the globe. Learn about how they are making sweetheart deals, generating side income, bending the law to their own benefits, using legislation to advance their own interests, and much more.    </p>
<p>                    Profiles in Corruption contains tomorrow&#8217;s headlines.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/">Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this highly anticipated follow-up to his blockbuster New York Times bestseller The Amateur, former New York Times Magazine editor-in-chief Edward Klein delves into the rocky relationship between the Obamas and the Clintons. An old-school reporter with incredible insider contacts, Klein reveals just how deep the rivalry between the Obamas and the Clintons runs, with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/">Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this highly anticipated follow-up to his blockbuster New York Times bestseller The Amateur, former New York Times Magazine editor-in-chief Edward Klein delves into the rocky relationship between the Obamas and the Clintons. An old-school reporter with incredible insider contacts, Klein reveals just how deep the rivalry between the Obamas and the Clintons runs, with details on closed-door meetings buttressed by hundreds of interviews. Blood Feud is a stunning expose of the animosity, jealousy, and competition between America&#8217;s two most powerful political couples.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/">Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Opinion & Polls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans. &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate. You have nowhere to go. You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221; &#8211;From the Introduction In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate.<br />
                     You have nowhere to go.<br />
                     You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;From the Introduction     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools: How a Selfish Ruling Class is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution, Tucker Carlson tells the truth about the new American elites, a group whose power and wealth has grown beyond imagination even as the rest of the country has withered. The people who run America now barely interact with it. They fly on their own planes, ski on their own mountains, watch sporting events far from the stands in sky boxes. They have total contempt for you.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;They view America the way a private equity firm sizes up an aging conglomerate,&#8221; Carlson writes, &#8220;as something outdated they can profit from. When it fails, they&#8217;re gone.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools,  Tucker Carlson offers a blistering critique of our new overlords. Traditional liberals are gone, he writes. The patchouli-scented hand-wringers who worried about whales and defended free speech have been replaced by globalists who hide their hard-edged economic agenda behind the smokescreen of identity politics. They&#8217;ll outsource your job while lecturing you about transgender bathrooms. Left and right, Carlson says, are no longer meaningful categories in America. &#8220;The rift is between those who benefit from the status quo, and those who don&#8217;t.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     Our leaders are fools, Carlson concludes, &#8220;unaware that they are captains of a sinking ship.&#8221; But in the signature and witty style that viewers of Tucker Carlson Tonight have come to enjoy, his book answers the all-important question: How do we put the country back on course?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strangers In Their Own Land : Anger and Mourning on the American Right &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Strangers in Their Own Land, the renowned sociologist Arlie Hochschild embarks on a thought-provoking journey from her liberal hometown of Berkeley, California, deep into Louisiana bayou country &#8211; a stronghold of the conservative right. As she gets to know people who strongly oppose many of the ideas she famously champions, Hochschild nevertheless finds common [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">Strangers In Their Own Land : Anger and Mourning on the American Right &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Strangers in Their Own Land, the renowned sociologist Arlie Hochschild embarks on a thought-provoking journey from her liberal hometown of Berkeley, California, deep into Louisiana bayou country &#8211; a stronghold of the conservative right. As she gets to know people who strongly oppose many of the ideas she famously champions, Hochschild nevertheless finds common ground and quickly warms to the people she meets, people whose concerns are actually ones that all Americans share: the desire for community, the embrace of family, and hopes for their children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">Strangers In Their Own Land : Anger and Mourning on the American Right &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nationalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism. Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections. In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism.    </p>
<p>                    Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections.    </p>
<p>                    In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist and commentator Rick Wilson delivers &#8220;a searingly honest, bitingly funny, comprehensive answer to the question we find ourselves asking most mornings: &#8216;What the hell is going on?&#8217; (Chicago Tribune). The Guardian hails Everything Trump Touches Dies, saying it gives, &#8220;more unvarnished truths about Donald Trump than anyone else in the American political establishment has offered. Wilson never holds back.&#8221; Rick mercilessly exposes the damage Trump has done to the country, to the Republican Party, and to the conservative movement that has abandoned its principles for the worst President in American history.    </p>
<p>                    Wilson unblinkingly dismantles Trump&#8217;s deceptions and the illusions to which his supporters cling, shedding light on the guilty parties who empower and enable Trump in Washington and in the media. He calls out the race-war dead-enders who hitched a ride with Trump, the alt-right basement dwellers who worship him, and the social conservatives who looked the other way. Publishers Weekly calls it, &#8220;a scathing, profane, unflinching, and laugh-out-loud funny rebuke of Donald Trump and his presidency.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    No left-winger, Wilson is a lifelong conservative who delivers his withering critique of Trump from the right. A leader of the Never Trump movement, he warned from the start that Trump would destroy the lives and reputations of everyone in his orbit, and Everything Trump Touches Dies is a deft chronicle the tragicomic political story of our time. From the early campaign days through the shock of election night, to the inconceivable train-wreck of Trump&#8217;s first year. Rick Wilson provides not only an insightful analysis of the Trump administration, but also an optimistic path forward for the GOP, the conservative movement, and the country.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hilarious, smartly written, and usually spot-on&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews), Everything Trump Touches Dies is perfect for those on either side of the aisle who need a dose of unvarnished reality, a good laugh, a strong cocktail, and a return to sanity in American politics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019    </p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.    </p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.    </p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.    </p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?    </p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Suicide of the West : How the Rebirth of Tribalism, Nationalism, and Socialism Is Destroying American Democracy &#8211; Jonah Goldberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/suicide-of-the-west-how-the-rebirth-of-tribalism-nationalism-and-socialism-is-destroying-american-democracy-jonah-goldberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/suicide-of-the-west-how-the-rebirth-of-tribalism-nationalism-and-socialism-is-destroying-american-democracy-jonah-goldberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent argument that America and other democracies are in peril because they have lost the will to defend the values and institutions that sustain freedom and prosperity. Now updated with a new preface! &#8220;Epic and debate-shifting.&#8221;&#8211;David Brooks, New York Times Only once in the last 250,000 years have humans [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/suicide-of-the-west-how-the-rebirth-of-tribalism-nationalism-and-socialism-is-destroying-american-democracy-jonah-goldberg-abridged/">Suicide of the West : How the Rebirth of Tribalism, Nationalism, and Socialism Is Destroying American Democracy &#8211; Jonah Goldberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent argument that America and other democracies are in peril because they have lost the will to defend the values and institutions that sustain freedom and prosperity. Now updated with a new preface!    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Epic and debate-shifting.&#8221;&#8211;David Brooks, New York Times  Only once in the last 250,000 years have humans stumbled upon a way to lift ourselves out of the endless cycle of poverty, hunger, and war that defines most of history. If democracy, individualism, and the free market were humankind&#8217;s destiny, they should have appeared and taken hold a bit earlier in the evolutionary record. The emergence of freedom and prosperity was nothing short of a miracle.  As Americans we are doubly blessed, because the radical ideas that made the miracle possible were written not just into the Constitution but in our hearts, laying the groundwork for our uniquely prosperous society. Those ideas are:  &#8211; Our rights come from God, not from the government. <br />
                     &#8211; The government belongs to us; we do not belong to it. <br />
                     &#8211; The individual is sovereign. We are all captains of our own souls, not bound by the circumstances of our birth. <br />
                     &#8211; The fruits of our labors belong to us.  In the last few decades, these political virtues have been turned into vices. As we are increasingly taught to view our traditions as a system of oppression, exploitation, and privilege, the principles of liberty and the rule of law are under attack from left and right. For the West to survive, we must renew our sense of gratitude for what our civilization has given us and rediscover the ideals and habits of the heart that led us out of the bloody muck of the past&#8211;or back to the muck we will go.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/suicide-of-the-west-how-the-rebirth-of-tribalism-nationalism-and-socialism-is-destroying-american-democracy-jonah-goldberg-abridged/">Suicide of the West : How the Rebirth of Tribalism, Nationalism, and Socialism Is Destroying American Democracy &#8211; Jonah Goldberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
