<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sales &amp; Marketing Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sales-marketing-management/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sales-marketing-management/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sales &amp; Marketing Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sales-marketing-management/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin</title>
		<link>/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re either a Purple Cow or you&#8217;re not. You&#8217;re either remarkable or invisible. Make your choice. What do Apple, Starbucks, Dyson and Pret a Manger have in common? How do they achieve spectacular growth, leaving behind former tried-and-true brands to gasp their last? The old checklist of P&#8217;s used by marketers &#8211; Pricing, Promotion, Publicity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin/">Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re either a Purple Cow or you&#8217;re not. You&#8217;re either remarkable or invisible. Make your choice.    </p>
<p>                    What do Apple, Starbucks, Dyson and Pret a Manger have in common? How do they achieve spectacular growth, leaving behind former tried-and-true brands to gasp their last? The old checklist of P&#8217;s used by marketers &#8211; Pricing, Promotion, Publicity &#8211; aren&#8217;t working anymore. The golden age of advertising is over. It&#8217;s time to add a new P &#8211; the Purple Cow.    </p>
<p>                    Purple Cow describes something phenomenal, something counterintuitive and exciting and flat-out unbelievable. In his new bestseller, Seth Godin urges you to put a Purple Cow into everything you build, and everything you do, to create something truly noticeable. It&#8217;s a manifesto for anyone who wants to help create products and services that are worth marketing in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s business classic This is Marketing.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin/">Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising. For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising.     </p>
<p>                     For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup founder, a small business owner, or part of a large corporation.     </p>
<p>                     No matter what your product or service, this book will help you reframe how it&#8217;s presented to the world, in order to meaningfully connect with people who want it. Seth employs his signature blend of insight, observation, and memorable examples to teach you:    </p>
<p>                     * How to build trust and permission with your target market.<br />
                     * The art of positioning&#8211;deciding not only who it&#8217;s for, but who it&#8217;s not for.<br />
                     * Why the best way to achieve your goals is to help others become who they want to be.<br />
                     * Why the old approaches to advertising and branding no longer work.<br />
                     * The surprising role of tension in any decision to buy (or not).<br />
                     * How marketing is at its core about the stories we tell ourselves about our social status.    </p>
<p>                     You can do work that matters for people who care. This book shows you the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This Is Marketing is a very accessible way into Godin&#8217;s thinking&#8230;. Godin writes in pacy, jargon-free prose and this book is interesting and useful for anyone who wants an insight into how, and why, we buy things or change our habits in any way.&#8221; &#8211; The Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s Purple Cow, a true business classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Marketing Revolution : Seize Control of Your Market in Five Key Steps &#8211; Dane Brookes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/content-marketing-revolution-seize-control-of-your-market-in-five-key-steps-dane-brookes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/content-marketing-revolution-seize-control-of-your-market-in-five-key-steps-dane-brookes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Content Marketing Revolution boldly guides you through five proven steps that will help your business to attract more customers, close more sales and excite brand loyalty. Whether you&#8217;re a marketing manager, an entrepreneur or an S&#038;P Index CEO, this book provides a step-by-step guide to planning, executing and monitoring a killer content marketing strategy. Gone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-marketing-revolution-seize-control-of-your-market-in-five-key-steps-dane-brookes-abridged/">Content Marketing Revolution : Seize Control of Your Market in Five Key Steps &#8211; Dane Brookes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Content Marketing Revolution boldly guides you through five proven steps that will help your business to attract more customers, close more sales and excite brand loyalty. Whether you&#8217;re a marketing manager, an entrepreneur or an S&#038;P Index CEO, this book provides a step-by-step guide to planning, executing and monitoring a killer content marketing strategy. Gone are the days when traditional marketing messages had critical power on buying decisions. Instead, customers now want to make empowered decisions based on useful information, valuable engagements and brand affinity. This book will help you to quickly adapt to the demise of traditional marketing and position your brand as a market leader in the &#8216;content age&#8217;. Content marketing expert, Dane Brookes, shares his secrets and battle tactics, along with everything you need to know to seize control of your market by giving your customers exactly what they want, before they even realise it. Entertainingly written, this book is packed with practical tips, proven strategies, and case studies that demonstrate how some of the most successful brands in the world like Red Bull, Four Seasons and Open University are nurturing customers with highly-relevant content. The book also includes contributions from leading content experts, including Olivier award-winning writer, Mark Davies Markham and Philips&#8217; Digital Editor in Chief, Matt Warnock (Foreword). It&#8217;s time to declare war on your competitors and revolutionise your place in the market. Expert reviews: &#8220;Dane Brookes inspiringly guides you through the five key steps to success. This book is a must for marketers of all levels.&#8221; &#8211; Mark Langshaw, Journalist at Digital Spy &#8220;Dane Brookes is amongst the new breed of true content marketers. By following his advice in this book, you&#8217;ll be able to devise a solid content strategy, with insights into how you can test, measure and improve.&#8221; &#8211; Matt Warnock, Digital Editor in Chief at Philips &#8220;Content Marketing Revolution is the new bible for business owners. If you want to dominate your market, this is your starting point.&#8221; &#8211; Debora Fougere, Emmy &#038; Peabody Award-Winning TV Producer &#8220;If you&#8217;re looking to build a marketing strategy that actually works, this book contains the instructions.&#8221; &#8211; Jo Banks, Author &#038; Business Consultant</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-marketing-revolution-seize-control-of-your-market-in-five-key-steps-dane-brookes-abridged/">Content Marketing Revolution : Seize Control of Your Market in Five Key Steps &#8211; Dane Brookes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China&#8217;s Super Consumers : What 1 Billion Customers Want and How to Sell it to Them &#8211; Savio Chan, Michael Zakkour (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chinese Consumers are Changing The World Understand Them and Sell To Them China has transformed itself from a feudal economy in the 19th century, to Mao and Communism in the 20th century, to the largest consumer market in the world by the early 21st century. China&#8217;s Super Consumers explores the extraordinary birth of consumerism in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/">China&#8217;s Super Consumers : What 1 Billion Customers Want and How to Sell it to Them &#8211; Savio Chan, Michael Zakkour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chinese Consumers are Changing The World Understand Them and Sell To Them China has transformed itself from a feudal economy in the 19th century, to Mao and Communism in the 20th century, to the largest consumer market in the world by the early 21st century. China&#8217;s Super Consumers explores the extraordinary birth of consumerism in China and explains who these super consumers are. China&#8217;s Super Consumers offers an in-depth explanation of what&#8217;s inside the minds of Chinese consumers and explores what they buy, where they buy, how they buy, and most importantly why they buy. The book is filled with real-world stories of the foreign and domestic companies, leading brands, and top executives who have succeeded in selling to this burgeoning marketplace. This remarkable book also takes you inside the boardrooms of the people who understand Chinese consumers and have had success in the Chinese market.<br />
                    * A hands-on resource for succeeding in the Chinese marketplace * Filled with real-world stories of companies who have made an impact in China * Discover what the Chinese consumer wants and how to deliver the goods * Written by Savio Chan and Michael Zakkour, two leading experts on the Chinese market This book is an invaluable resource for anyone who wants a clear understanding of how China&#8217;s Super Consumers are changing the world and how to sell to them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/">China&#8217;s Super Consumers : What 1 Billion Customers Want and How to Sell it to Them &#8211; Savio Chan, Michael Zakkour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes, it makes more sense to lose today in order to win tomorrow. What do you do when you know what you want, but you have no idea how to get it? &#8216;The greatest negotiation book of all time.&#8217; Inc. Magazine ________________ Never walk away. Learn to listen, then learn to understand, then learn to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/">Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes, it makes more sense to lose today in order to win tomorrow. What do you do when you know what you want, but you have no idea how to get it?    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The greatest negotiation book of all time.&#8217; Inc. Magazine<br />
                     ________________                           </p>
<p>                     Never walk away. Learn to listen, then learn to understand, then learn to win.    </p>
<p>                    Negotiation is part of every human encounter, and most of us do it badly. Whether dealing with family, a business, or diplomacy, people often fail to meet their goals in every country and context. They focus on power and &#8220;win-win&#8221; instead of relationships and perceptions. They don&#8217;t find enough things to trade. They think others should be rational when they should be dealing with emotions. They get distracted from their goals.    </p>
<p>                    In this revolutionary and seminal bestselling book, leading negotiation practitioner, coach and professor Stuart Diamond shows how emotional intelligence, perceptions, cultural diversity and collaboration produce four times as much value as old-school, conflictive, power, leverage and logic. Drawing on thirty-plus years of research involving 30,000 people across 45 countries &#8211; ranging from political and corporate leaders to administrative assistants, lawyers, housewives, students, and labourers &#8211; he outlines specific, practical and better ways to deal with others. To this, he adds his 40-year experience as a corporate executive, Harvard-trained attorney, and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist.    </p>
<p>                    Getting More is based on Professor Diamond&#8217;s award-winning negotiations course at The Wharton Business School, where it has been the most sought-after course by students for almost two decades. It contains a powerful toolkit that can be used in any situation: with kids and jobs, travel and shopping, business, politics, relationships, cultures, partners and competitors. His advice is brought to life in an accessible and entertaining manner through the stories of hundreds of people who have used the toolkit with great success.<br />
                    ________________    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;From advising on how to negotiate with terrorists, to industrial disputes, to children, Diamond&#8217;s twelve rules of negotiation promise to open new doors every day.&#8217; Radio One    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Practical, immediately applicable and highly effective.&#8217; Evan Wittenberg, co-founder of TRUE and former Head of Global Leadership Development at Google    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I rely on Stuart Diamond&#8217;s negotiation tools every day.&#8217; Christian Hernandez, venture capitalist and former Head of International Business Development at Facebook</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/">Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Truth, Lies, and Advertising : The Art of Account Planning &#8211; Jon Steel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Account planning exists for the sole purpose of creating advertising that truly connects with consumers. While many in the industry are still dissecting consumer behavior, extrapolating demographic trends, developing complex behavioral models, and measuring Pavlovian salivary responses, Steel advocates an approach to consumer research that is based on simplicity, common sense, and creativity&#8211;an approach that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/">Truth, Lies, and Advertising : The Art of Account Planning &#8211; Jon Steel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Account planning exists for the sole purpose of creating advertising that truly connects with consumers. While many in the industry are still dissecting consumer behavior, extrapolating demographic trends, developing complex behavioral models, and measuring Pavlovian salivary responses, Steel advocates an approach to consumer research that is based on simplicity, common sense, and creativity&#8211;an approach that gains access to consumers&#8217; hearts and minds, develops ongoing relationships with them, and, most important, embraces them as partners in the process of developing and advertising. A witty, erudite raconteur and teacher, Steel describes how successful account planners work in partnership with clients, consumer, and agency creatives. He criticizes research practices that, far from creating relationships, drive a wedge between agencies and the people they aim to persuade; he suggests new ways of approaching research to cut through the BS and get people to show their true selves; and he shows how the right research, when translated into a motivating and inspiring brief, can be the catalyst for great creative ideas.<br />
                    He draws upon his own experiences and those of colleagues in the United States and abroad to illustrate those points, and includes examples of some of the most successful campaigns in recent years, including Polaroid, Norwegian Cruise Line, Porsche, Isuzu, &#8220;got milk?&#8221; and others. The message of this book is that well-thought-out account planning results in better, more effective marketing and advertising for both agencies and clients. And also makes an evening in front of the television easier to bear for the population at large.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/">Truth, Lies, and Advertising : The Art of Account Planning &#8211; Jon Steel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dream Teams : Working Together Without Falling Apart &#8211; Shane Snow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dream-teams-working-together-without-falling-apart-shane-snow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dream-teams-working-together-without-falling-apart-shane-snow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An adventure into the very human science of making breakthroughs together.&#8217; &#8211; Charles Duhigg, Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist and author of The Power of Habit The best groups are more than the sum of their parts &#8211; but why does teamwork so often fail to fulfill this promise? Award-winning entrepreneur and journalist Shane Snow takes us [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dream-teams-working-together-without-falling-apart-shane-snow-abridged/">Dream Teams : Working Together Without Falling Apart &#8211; Shane Snow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An adventure into the very human science of making breakthroughs together.&#8217; &#8211; Charles Duhigg, Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist and author of The Power of Habit    </p>
<p>                    The best groups are more than the sum of their parts &#8211; but why does teamwork so often fail to fulfill this promise?     </p>
<p>                    Award-winning entrepreneur and journalist Shane Snow takes us on an extraordinary tour of the hidden science of team dynamics, revealing the counterintuitive reasons that some groups break out while far too many break down.    </p>
<p>                    Examining history-making groups like the Wu Tang Clan and the Russian national hockey side alongside teams whose failures have had lasting impact, Snow reveals the answers, and what the rest of us can learn from the rare teams that do the impossible together. In this stimulating, pacey adventure through history, neuroscience, psychology, sports and business, Snow explores the secrets of the best teams the world has to offer.     </p>
<p>                    You&#8217;ll discover:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; How ragtag teams &#8211; from soccer clubs to startups to gangs of pirates &#8211; beat the odds throughout history    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Why DaimlerChrysler flopped while the Wu-Tang Clan succeeded, and the surprising factor behind most failed mergers, marriages, and partnerships    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; What the Wright Brothers&#8217; daily arguments can teach us about group problem solving    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; The true stories of pioneering women in law enforcement, unlikely civil rights collaborators, and underdog armies that did the incredible together    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; The team players behind great social movements in history, and the science of becoming open-minded.    </p>
<p>                    Provocative and entertaining, Dream Teams is a landmark work that will change the way we think about progress and collaboration.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dream-teams-working-together-without-falling-apart-shane-snow-abridged/">Dream Teams : Working Together Without Falling Apart &#8211; Shane Snow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selling With Noble Purpose : How to Drive Revenue and Do Work That Makes You Proud &#8211; Lisa Earle McLeod, Elizabeth Lotardo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/selling-with-noble-purpose-how-to-drive-revenue-and-do-work-that-makes-you-proud-lisa-earle-mcleod-elizabeth-lotardo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/selling-with-noble-purpose-how-to-drive-revenue-and-do-work-that-makes-you-proud-lisa-earle-mcleod-elizabeth-lotardo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Don&#8217;t let anyone tell you that you have to choose between making money and making a difference. Selling With Noble Purpose: How to Drive Revenue and Do Work That Makes You Proud, 2nd Edition is an update of the acclaimed book that changed the game in sales. Using real-world data, compelling stories and psychological research, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selling-with-noble-purpose-how-to-drive-revenue-and-do-work-that-makes-you-proud-lisa-earle-mcleod-elizabeth-lotardo-abridged/">Selling With Noble Purpose : How to Drive Revenue and Do Work That Makes You Proud &#8211; Lisa Earle McLeod, Elizabeth Lotardo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Don&#8217;t let anyone tell you that you have to choose between making money and making a difference.      </p>
<p>                     Selling With Noble Purpose: How to Drive Revenue and Do Work That Makes You Proud, 2nd Edition is an update of the acclaimed book that changed the game in sales. Using real-world data, compelling stories and psychological research, Selling With Noble Purpose explains why salespeople who genuinely understand how they can make a difference to customers outsell those who only focus on internal targets and quotas.        </p>
<p>                     Sales leadership experts McLeod and Lotardo reveal how a Noble Sales Purpose (NSP) can drive a team to outstanding sales numbers.  Whether you&#8217;re an executive, manager or aspiring sales leader, you&#8217;ll discover how to find your own Noble Sales Purpose and create a sales force of True Believers.   This new edition covers:     </p>
<p>                    How firms overcome ferocious competition and how you can do the same<br />
                    Why sales organizations with a clear NSP outperform traditional sales teams<br />
                    How to avoid the trap of behaving like a transactional salesperson<br />
                    Why well-intended leaders often unknowingly erode purpose and differentiation<br />
                    How to use your NSP to increase customer engagement<br />
                    Why an NSP gives you clarity during times of uncertainty     </p>
<p>                     In an era where organizations often believe that money is the primary way to motivate salespeople, Selling with Noble Purpose offers and exciting and sustainable alternative.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selling-with-noble-purpose-how-to-drive-revenue-and-do-work-that-makes-you-proud-lisa-earle-mcleod-elizabeth-lotardo-abridged/">Selling With Noble Purpose : How to Drive Revenue and Do Work That Makes You Proud &#8211; Lisa Earle McLeod, Elizabeth Lotardo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sales Management. Simplified. : The Straight Truth About Getting Exceptional Results from Your Sales Team &#8211; Mike Weinberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sales-management-simplified-the-straight-truth-about-getting-exceptional-results-from-your-sales-team-mike-weinberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sales-management-simplified-the-straight-truth-about-getting-exceptional-results-from-your-sales-team-mike-weinberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Packed with examples and anecdotes,?Sales Management. Simplified.?offers a proven formula for prospecting, developing, and closing deals-in your time, on your terms. Why do sales organizations fall short? Every day, expert consultants like Mike Weinberg are called on by companies to find the answer &#8211; and it&#8217;s one that may surprise you. Typically, the issue lies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sales-management-simplified-the-straight-truth-about-getting-exceptional-results-from-your-sales-team-mike-weinberg-abridged/">Sales Management. Simplified. : The Straight Truth About Getting Exceptional Results from Your Sales Team &#8211; Mike Weinberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Packed with examples and anecdotes,?Sales Management. Simplified.?offers a proven formula for prospecting, developing, and closing deals-in your time, on your terms.    </p>
<p>                    Why do sales organizations fall short? Every day, expert consultants like Mike Weinberg are called on by companies to find the answer &#8211; and it&#8217;s one that may surprise you. Typically, the issue lies not with the sales team but with how it is being led. Through their attitude and actions, senior executives and sales managers unknowingly undermine performance.    </p>
<p>                    Weinberg tells it straight by calling out the problems plaguing sales forces and the costly mistakes made by even the best-intentioned sales managers. The good news is that with the right guidance, results can be transformed.    </p>
<p>                    In Sales Management. Simplified., Weinberg teaches managers how to:    </p>
<p>                    Implement a simple framework for sales leadership<br />
                    Foster a healthy, high-performance sales culture<br />
                    Conduct productive meetings<br />
                    Put the right people in the right roles<br />
                    Retain top producers and remediate underperformers<br />
                    Point salespeople at the proper targets    </p>
<p>                    Blending blunt, practical advice with funny stories from the field, Sales Management. Simplified. delivers the tools every sales manager needs to succeed.    </p>
<p>                    Managing sales doesn&#8217;t have to be complicated, and the solution starts with you!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sales-management-simplified-the-straight-truth-about-getting-exceptional-results-from-your-sales-team-mike-weinberg-abridged/">Sales Management. Simplified. : The Straight Truth About Getting Exceptional Results from Your Sales Team &#8211; Mike Weinberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Strategic Selling : The Unique Sales System Proven Successful by the World&#8217;s Best Companies &#8211; Robert B Miller, Stephen E Heiman, Tad Tuleja (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-new-strategic-selling-the-unique-sales-system-proven-successful-by-the-worlds-best-companies-robert-b-miller-stephen-e-heiman-tad-tuleja-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-strategic-selling-the-unique-sales-system-proven-successful-by-the-worlds-best-companies-robert-b-miller-stephen-e-heiman-tad-tuleja-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn from one of the bestselling books on sales ever published, which has cemented itself as the must-read for any sales or marketing professional, written by leaders at Miller Heiman &#8211; the global lead in sales and development. Strategic Selling presented the idea of selling as a joint venture, introducing the influential concept of &#8216;win-win&#8217; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-strategic-selling-the-unique-sales-system-proven-successful-by-the-worlds-best-companies-robert-b-miller-stephen-e-heiman-tad-tuleja-abridged/">The New Strategic Selling : The Unique Sales System Proven Successful by the World&#8217;s Best Companies &#8211; Robert B Miller, Stephen E Heiman, Tad Tuleja (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn from one of the bestselling books on sales ever published, which has cemented itself as the must-read for any sales or marketing professional, written by leaders at Miller Heiman &#8211; the global lead in sales and development.     </p>
<p>                    Strategic Selling presented the idea of selling as a joint venture, introducing the influential concept of &#8216;win-win&#8217; and making it one of the bestselling books on sales ever published. The response to &#8216;win-win&#8217; was immediate and fundamentally changed sales and marketing with its rejection of manipulative tactics, in turn positioning Miller Heiman as a global leader with the most prestigious client list in the industry.    </p>
<p>                    Now, learn from the latest, third edition of this genuine business classic with The New Strategic Selling which confronts the rapidly changing world of B2B sales including:<br />
                    &#8211; Real-world examples<br />
                    &#8211; Strategies for confronting the competition<br />
                    &#8211; New content on the most common challenges and questions from the Miller Heiman workshop     </p>
<p>                    The New Strategic Selling remains essential reading for any sales directors, managers or executives in any type of company and industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-strategic-selling-the-unique-sales-system-proven-successful-by-the-worlds-best-companies-robert-b-miller-stephen-e-heiman-tad-tuleja-abridged/">The New Strategic Selling : The Unique Sales System Proven Successful by the World&#8217;s Best Companies &#8211; Robert B Miller, Stephen E Heiman, Tad Tuleja (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave New Work : Are You Ready to Reinvent Your Organization? &#8211; Aaron Dignan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s stopping you from doing the best work of your life? The way we work is broken. It takes forever to get anything done. Meetings and emails are incessant. Bureaucracy stifles talent and creativity. Is this really the best we can do? Aaron Dignan teaches companies how to eliminate red tape, tap into collective intelligence, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/">Brave New Work : Are You Ready to Reinvent Your Organization? &#8211; Aaron Dignan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s stopping you from doing the best work of your life?    </p>
<p>                    The way we work is broken. It takes forever to get anything done. Meetings and emails are incessant. Bureaucracy stifles talent and creativity.  Is this really the best we can do?    </p>
<p>                    Aaron Dignan teaches companies how to eliminate red tape, tap into collective intelligence, and rethink long-held traditions that no longer make sense. In Brave New Work, he shows you how to revolutionize the way you, your team and your company works forever.     </p>
<p>                    *         Have fewer but better meetings<br />
                    *         Create a culture of honesty, transparency and trust<br />
                    *         Cut down on rules to be more efficient<br />
                    *         Be more agile and adaptive<br />
                    *         Reignite passion and energy throughout your organisation    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Clear, powerful and urgent, it&#8217;s a must read for anyone who cares about where they work and how they work&#8221; &#8211; Seth Godin, author of This is Marketing and Purple Cow</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/">Brave New Work : Are You Ready to Reinvent Your Organization? &#8211; Aaron Dignan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fanatical Prospecting : The Ultimate Guide to Opening Sales Conversations and Filling the Pipeline by Leveraging Social Selling, Telephone, Email, Text, and Cold Calling &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword by Mike Weinberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ditch the failed sales tactics, fill your pipeline, and crush your number Fanatical Prospecting gives salespeople, sales leaders, entrepreneurs, and executives a practical, eye-opening guide that clearly explains the why and how behind the most important activity in sales and business development prospecting. The brutal fact is the number one reason for failure in sales [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/">Fanatical Prospecting : The Ultimate Guide to Opening Sales Conversations and Filling the Pipeline by Leveraging Social Selling, Telephone, Email, Text, and Cold Calling &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword by Mike Weinberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ditch the failed sales tactics, fill your pipeline, and crush your number  Fanatical Prospecting gives salespeople, sales leaders, entrepreneurs, and executives a practical, eye-opening guide that clearly explains the why and how behind the most important activity in sales and business development prospecting.  The brutal fact is the number one reason for failure in sales is an empty pipe and the root cause of an empty pipeline is the failure to consistently prospect. By ignoring the muscle of prospecting, many otherwise competent salespeople and sales organizations consistently underperform. Step by step, Jeb Blount outlines his innovative approach to prospecting that works for real people, in the real world, with real prospects. Learn how to keep the pipeline full of qualified opportunities and avoid debilitating sales slumps by leveraging a balanced prospecting methodology across multiple prospecting channels. This book reveals the secrets, techniques, and tips of top earners.<br />
                    You ll learn: * Why the 30-Day Rule is critical for keeping the pipeline full * Why understanding the Law of Replacement is the key to avoiding sales slumps * How to leverage the Law of Familiarity to reduce prospecting friction and avoid rejection * The 5 C s of Social Selling and how to use them to get prospects to call you * How to use the simple 5 Step Telephone Framework to get more appointments fast * How to double call backs with a powerful voice mail technique * How to leverage the powerful 4 Step Email Prospecting Framework to create emails that compel prospects to respond * How to get text working for you with the 7 Step Text Message Prospecting Framework * And there is so much more! Fanatical Prospecting is filled with the high-powered strategies, techniques, and tools you need to fill your pipeline with high quality opportunities. In the most comprehensive book ever written about sales prospecting, Jeb Blount reveals the real secret to improving sales productivity and growing your income fast. You ll gain the power to blow through resistance and objections, gain more appointments, start more sales conversations, and close more sales.<br />
                    Break free from the fear and frustration that is holding you and your team back from effective and consistent prospecting. It&#8217;s time to get off the feast or famine sales roller-coaster for good!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/">Fanatical Prospecting : The Ultimate Guide to Opening Sales Conversations and Filling the Pipeline by Leveraging Social Selling, Telephone, Email, Text, and Cold Calling &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword by Mike Weinberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Predictable Revenue &#8211; Aaron Ross, Marylou Tyler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/predictable-revenue-aaron-ross-marylou-tyler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/predictable-revenue-aaron-ross-marylou-tyler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Called &#8220;The Sales Bible of Silicon Valley&#8221;&#8230;discover the sales specialization system and outbound sales process that, in just a few years, helped add $100 million in recurring revenue to Salesforce.com, almost doubling their enterprise growth&#8230;with zero cold calls. This is NOT just another book about how to cold call or close deals. This is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/predictable-revenue-aaron-ross-marylou-tyler-abridged/">Predictable Revenue &#8211; Aaron Ross, Marylou Tyler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Called &#8220;The Sales Bible of Silicon Valley&#8221;&#8230;discover the sales specialization system and outbound sales process that, in just a few years, helped add $100 million in recurring revenue to Salesforce.com, almost doubling their enterprise growth&#8230;with zero cold calls. This is NOT just another book about how to cold call or close deals. This is an entirely new kind of sales system for CEOs, entrepreneurs and sales VPs to help you build a sales machine. What does it take for your sales team to generate as many highly-qualified new leads as you want, create predictable revenue, and meet your financial goals without your constant focus and attention? Predictable Revenue has the answers!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/predictable-revenue-aaron-ross-marylou-tyler-abridged/">Predictable Revenue &#8211; Aaron Ross, Marylou Tyler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How I Raised Myself From Failure to Success in Selling &#8211; Frank Bettger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-i-raised-myself-from-failure-to-success-in-selling-frank-bettger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-i-raised-myself-from-failure-to-success-in-selling-frank-bettger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What are the selling secrets that raised Frank Bettger from initial failure to unparalleled success, and fame, as one of the highest paid salesmen in America? Encouraged to tell his story by admiring colleague Dale Carnegie, Bettger reveals his proven success formula so that you too can work magic with sales &#8211; and multiply your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-i-raised-myself-from-failure-to-success-in-selling-frank-bettger-abridged/">How I Raised Myself From Failure to Success in Selling &#8211; Frank Bettger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are the selling secrets that raised Frank Bettger from initial failure to unparalleled success, and fame, as one of the highest paid salesmen in America? Encouraged to tell his story by admiring colleague Dale Carnegie, Bettger reveals his proven success formula so that you too can work magic with sales &#8211; and multiply your income and happiness a thousandfold! Inside you will find instructive examples and step-by-step guidelines on how to develop the style, spirit, and techniques of a first-rate salesperson. No matter what you sell, your on-the-job performance and profits will increase dramatically when you apply Bettger&#8217;s keen insights on: * The power of enthusiasm * How to conquer fear * The key word for turning a sceptical client into an enthusiastic buyer * The quickest way to win confidence * How to deliver a winning sales talk * Seven golden rules for closing a sale</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-i-raised-myself-from-failure-to-success-in-selling-frank-bettger-abridged/">How I Raised Myself From Failure to Success in Selling &#8211; Frank Bettger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Top professional speaker and sales trainer Brian Tracy found that his most important breakthrough was the discovery that it is the &#8220;psychology of selling&#8221; that is more important than the techniques and methods of selling. Learn how to double and triple your sales in any market. It&#8217;s a promise of prosperity that sales guru Brian [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/">The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Top professional speaker and sales trainer Brian Tracy found that his most important breakthrough was the discovery that it is the &#8220;psychology of selling&#8221; that is more important than the techniques and methods of selling.    </p>
<p>                    Learn how to double and triple your sales in any market. It&#8217;s a promise of prosperity that sales guru Brian Tracy has seen fulfilled again and again.    </p>
<p>                    More salespeople have become millionaires by listening to and applying his ideas than from any other sales training process ever developed.    </p>
<p>                    In Psychology of Selling, Tracy teaches you:    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The inner game of sales and selling&#8221;<br />
                    How to eliminate the fear of rejection<br />
                    How to build unshakeable confidence    </p>
<p>                    Tracy shows how salespeople must learn to control their thoughts, feelings and actions to make themselves more effective.    </p>
<p>                    Psychology of Selling gives you a series of ideas, methods, strategies, and techniques that you can use immediately to make more sales, faster and easier than ever before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/">The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A classic.-Jay Conrad Levinson, author of Guerrilla Marketing Now in paperback, the bestselling business playbook that introduced a simple framework for turbocharging any organization. What if you could create the finest, most profitable and best-run version of your business without wasting precious dollars on a thousand different strategies? Legendary sales expert Chet Holmes says you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/">Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A classic.-Jay Conrad Levinson, author of Guerrilla Marketing     </p>
<p>                    Now in paperback, the bestselling business playbook that introduced a simple framework for turbocharging any organization.     </p>
<p>                     What if you could create the finest, most profitable and best-run version of your business without wasting precious dollars on a thousand different strategies? Legendary sales expert Chet Holmes says you can. All you need is to focus on twelve key areas of improvement&#8211;and practice them over and over with pigheaded discipline.     </p>
<p>                     The Ultimate Sales Machine is essential reading for anyone who wants to transform their organization into a high-performing, moneymaking force. By spending just an hour per week on crucial aspects of your business&#8211;from sales and marketing to management and hiring&#8211;you can systematically improve how your business operates. With practical tools, real-life examples, and proven strategies presented in Holmes&#8217; signature tell-it-like-it-is style, this book will show you how to:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Teach your team to work smarter, not harder<br />
                     &#8211; Get more bang from your marketing for less<br />
                     &#8211; Perfect every sales interaction by working on sales, not just in sales<br />
                     &#8211; Land your dream clients     </p>
<p>                    For every CEO, manager, and business owner who wants to take their organization to the next level, The Ultimate Sales Machine will put you and your company on the path to success&#8211;and help you stay there!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/">Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re either a Purple Cow or you&#8217;re not. You&#8217;re either remarkable or invisible. Make your choice. What do Apple, Starbucks, Dyson and Pret a Manger have in common? How do they achieve spectacular growth, leaving behind former tried-and-true brands to gasp their last? The old checklist of P&#8217;s used by marketers &#8211; Pricing, Promotion, Publicity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin-abridged/">Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re either a Purple Cow or you&#8217;re not. You&#8217;re either remarkable or invisible. Make your choice.    </p>
<p>                    What do Apple, Starbucks, Dyson and Pret a Manger have in common? How do they achieve spectacular growth, leaving behind former tried-and-true brands to gasp their last? The old checklist of P&#8217;s used by marketers &#8211; Pricing, Promotion, Publicity &#8211; aren&#8217;t working anymore. The golden age of advertising is over. It&#8217;s time to add a new P &#8211; the Purple Cow.    </p>
<p>                    Purple Cow describes something phenomenal, something counterintuitive and exciting and flat-out unbelievable. In his new bestseller, Seth Godin urges you to put a Purple Cow into everything you build, and everything you do, to create something truly noticeable. It&#8217;s a manifesto for anyone who wants to help create products and services that are worth marketing in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s business classic This is Marketing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin-abridged/">Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Building a StoryBrand : Clarify Your Message So Customers Will Listen &#8211; Donald Miller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/building-a-storybrand-clarify-your-message-so-customers-will-listen-donald-miller-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/building-a-storybrand-clarify-your-message-so-customers-will-listen-donald-miller-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than half-a-million business leaders have discovered the power of the StoryBrand Framework, created by New York Times best-selling author and marketing expert Donald Miller. And they are making millions. If you use the wrong words to talk about your product, nobody will buy it. Marketers and business owners struggle to effectively connect with their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-a-storybrand-clarify-your-message-so-customers-will-listen-donald-miller-abridged/">Building a StoryBrand : Clarify Your Message So Customers Will Listen &#8211; Donald Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than half-a-million business leaders have discovered the power of the StoryBrand Framework, created by New York Times best-selling author and marketing expert Donald Miller. And they are making millions.    </p>
<p>                    If you use the wrong words to talk about your product, nobody will buy it. Marketers and business owners struggle to effectively connect with their customers, costing them and their companies millions in lost revenue.    </p>
<p>                    In a world filled with constant, on-demand distractions, it has become near-impossible for business owners to effectively cut through the noise to reach their customers, something Donald Miller knows first-hand. In this book, he shares the proven system he has created to help you engage and truly influence customers.    </p>
<p>                    The StoryBrand process is a proven solution to the struggle business leaders face when talking about their companies. Without a clear, distinct message, customers will not understand what you can do for them and are unwilling to engage, causing you to lose potential sales, opportunities for customer engagement, and much more.    </p>
<p>                    In Building a StoryBrand, Donald Miller teaches marketers and business owners to use the seven universal elements of powerful stories to dramatically improve how they connect with customers and grow their businesses.    </p>
<p>                    His proven process has helped thousands of companies engage with their existing customers, giving them the ultimate competitive advantage. Building a StoryBrand does this by teaching you:    </p>
<p>                    The seven universal story points all humans respond to;<br />
                    The real reason customers make purchases;<br />
                    How to simplify a brand message so people understand it; and<br />
                    How to create the most effective messaging for websites, brochures, and social media.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you are the marketing director of a multibillion-dollar company, the owner of a small business, a politician running for office, or the lead singer of a rock band, Building a StoryBrand will forever transform the way you talk about who you are, what you do, and the unique value you bring to your customers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-a-storybrand-clarify-your-message-so-customers-will-listen-donald-miller-abridged/">Building a StoryBrand : Clarify Your Message So Customers Will Listen &#8211; Donald Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buyer Personas : How to Gain Insight into your Customer&#8217;s Expectations, Align your Marketing Strategies, and Win More Business &#8211; Adele Revella (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buyer-personas-how-to-gain-insight-into-your-customers-expectations-align-your-marketing-strategies-and-win-more-business-adele-revella-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buyer-personas-how-to-gain-insight-into-your-customers-expectations-align-your-marketing-strategies-and-win-more-business-adele-revella-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>See your offering through the buyer&#8217;s eyes for more effective marketing Buyer Personas is the marketer&#8217;s actionable guide to learning what your buyer wants and how they make decisions. Written by the world&#8217;s leading authority on buyer personas, this book provides comprehensive coverage of a compelling new way to conduct buyer studies, plus practical advice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyer-personas-how-to-gain-insight-into-your-customers-expectations-align-your-marketing-strategies-and-win-more-business-adele-revella-abridged/">Buyer Personas : How to Gain Insight into your Customer&#8217;s Expectations, Align your Marketing Strategies, and Win More Business &#8211; Adele Revella (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>See your offering through the buyer&#8217;s eyes for more effective marketing Buyer Personas is the marketer&#8217;s actionable guide to learning what your buyer wants and how they make decisions. Written by the world&#8217;s leading authority on buyer personas, this book provides comprehensive coverage of a compelling new way to conduct buyer studies, plus practical advice on adopting the buyer persona approach to measurably improve marketing outcomes. Readers will learn how to segment their customer base, investigate each customer type, and apply a radically more relevant process of message selection, content creation, and distribution through the channels that earn the buyers&#8217; trust. Rather than relying on generic data or guesswork to determine what the buyer wants, the buyer persona approach allows companies to ask the buyer directly and obtain more precise and actionable guidance. Buyer personas are composite pictures of the people who buy solutions, services or products, crafted through a unique type of interview with the people the marketer wants to influence.<br />
                    This book provides step-by-step guidance toward implementing the buyer persona approach, with the advice of an internationally-respected expert. * Learn who buys what, and why * Understand your buyer&#8217;s goals and how you can address them * Tailor your marketing activities to your buyer&#8217;s expectations * See the purchase through the customer&#8217;s eyes A recent services industry survey reports that 52 percent of their marketers have buyer personas, and another 28 percent expect to add them within the next two years but only 14.6 percent know how to use them. To avoid letting such a valuable tool go to waste, access the expert perspective in Buyer Personas, and craft a more relevant marketing strategy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyer-personas-how-to-gain-insight-into-your-customers-expectations-align-your-marketing-strategies-and-win-more-business-adele-revella-abridged/">Buyer Personas : How to Gain Insight into your Customer&#8217;s Expectations, Align your Marketing Strategies, and Win More Business &#8211; Adele Revella (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UnMarketing : Everything Has Changed and Nothing is Different &#8211; Scott Stratten, Alison Stratten (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unmarketing-everything-has-changed-and-nothing-is-different-scott-stratten-alison-stratten-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unmarketing-everything-has-changed-and-nothing-is-different-scott-stratten-alison-stratten-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>UnMarket to build trust and make lifelong customers! In 2009, Scott Stratten and Alison Stratten wrote the bestselling UnMarketing: Stop Marketing, Start Engaging and began a journey that would take them around the world sharing their message of engagement with corporations, entrepreneurs, and students.They are now back with this second edition, because Everything has Changed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmarketing-everything-has-changed-and-nothing-is-different-scott-stratten-alison-stratten-abridged/">UnMarketing : Everything Has Changed and Nothing is Different &#8211; Scott Stratten, Alison Stratten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>UnMarket to build trust and make lifelong customers! In 2009, Scott Stratten and Alison Stratten wrote the bestselling UnMarketing: Stop Marketing, Start Engaging and began a journey that would take them around the world sharing their message of engagement with corporations, entrepreneurs, and students.They are now back with this second edition, because Everything has Changed and Nothing is Different, with all the brilliance of the first edition, plus new content and commentary to reflect the rapidly changing landscape we all live, buy, and work in today. For generations, marketing has been hypocritical. We&#8217;ve been taught to market to others in ways we hate being marketed to (cold-calling, flyers, ads, etc.). So why do we still keep trying the same stale marketing moves? UnMarketing shows you how to unlearn the old ways and consistently attract and engage the right customers. You&#8217;ll stop just pushing out your message and praying that it sticks somewhere. Potential and current customers want to be listened to, validated, and have a platform to be heard-especially online.<br />
                    With UnMarketing, you&#8217;ll create a relationship with your customers, and make yourself the logical choice for their needs. We know you&#8217;ve been told to act like other people, talk like other people, and market like all the people, but it is time for you to unlearn everything and start to UnMarket yourself. UnMarketing includes the latest information on: Idea Creation, Viral Marketing and Video, Marketing to Millennials, Authenticity, Transparency and Immediacy, Ethics and Affiliates, Social Media Platforming, UnPodcasting, Word of Mouth, Customer Service, Consumer Advocacy and Leadership. With examples of what to do, and what not to do, from small business right up to worldwide corporations in areas such as real estate, travel, service, retail, and B2B.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmarketing-everything-has-changed-and-nothing-is-different-scott-stratten-alison-stratten-abridged/">UnMarketing : Everything Has Changed and Nothing is Different &#8211; Scott Stratten, Alison Stratten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coaching Salespeople into Sales Champions : A Tactical Playbook for Managers and Executives &#8211; Keith Rosen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/coaching-salespeople-into-sales-champions-a-tactical-playbook-for-managers-and-executives-keith-rosen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/coaching-salespeople-into-sales-champions-a-tactical-playbook-for-managers-and-executives-keith-rosen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How many salespeople (and managers) are not realizing their fullest potential? What stands in the way to greater performance isn&#8217;t something they don&#8217;t have but something they don&#8217;t get consistently: effective coaching . Unfortunately; most managers don&#8217;t deliver consistent, effective coaching or have the coaching skills needed to make a long term, positive impact on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coaching-salespeople-into-sales-champions-a-tactical-playbook-for-managers-and-executives-keith-rosen-abridged/">Coaching Salespeople into Sales Champions : A Tactical Playbook for Managers and Executives &#8211; Keith Rosen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How many salespeople (and managers) are not realizing their fullest potential? What stands in the way to greater performance isn&#8217;t something they don&#8217;t have but something they don&#8217;t get consistently: effective coaching  . Unfortunately; most managers don&#8217;t deliver consistent, effective coaching or have the coaching skills needed to make a long term, positive impact on their salespeople&#8217;s performance. They act as Chief Problem Solvers and get far too involved in fixing their people&#8217;s problems; then get frustrated about their salespeople&#8217;s inability to improve. Coaching Salespeople into Sales Champions provides a proven coaching framework used by the world&#8217;s leading sales organizations so that managers can confidently facilitative powerful, engaging coaching conversations that help you reach your business objectives &#8212; faster and win more sales today.<br />
                    Winner of  6 International Best Book Awards , this book has already been endorsed by dozens of top sales organizations such as Microsoft, Oracle, Google, American Express, IBM, PepsiCo, The New York Rangers, The New York Knicks and thought leaders including Brian Tracy, Ziglar, Tom Hopkins, Denis Waitley and Tony Alessandra, Tony Parinello and Jill Konrath as the number one book on sales coaching and management coach training.  Sales training alone is not enough  . Your people can&#8217;t always diagnose their own skill deficiencies, nor can they coach themselves out of a slump. Managers focus on spreadsheets and treat symptoms instead of  uncovering the root cause , so similar problems persist. Good coaching taps into people&#8217;s individuality and motivation, builds confidence &#038; fosters deeper accountability. Four main barriers to effective coaching that inhibits consistent sales growth are: 1.  Managers focus on what&#8217;s going on (unproductive behaviors/activity) but don&#8217;t uncover exactly why it&#8217;s happening. As such, they fail to get to the  root cause  of a situation, which results in costly, time consuming repetitive conversations. 2.<br />
                    Managers coach in their own image (&#8220;It worked for me&#8221;) instead of tapping into people&#8217;s individuality. 3.  Managers are compelled to provide the quick answers rather than empower people to create their own solutions  . 4.  Managers are typically good at strategy but often struggle with being a strategic communicator  . That is, delivering a compelling, engaging message that creates  authentic buy in and commitment  around any changes or new initiatives. The solution to winning more sales isn&#8217;t more sales training but better coaching.  Good coaching embeds and sustains the behavioral changes you want in your people that generates desired, sustained long term results. When managers become better coaches and learn how to coach their people around best practices and core competencies, it makes your sales training stick. Coaching then becomes your  competitive edge  to foster long term, positive changes in behavior. With Keith Rosen&#8217;s award winning book, you&#8217;ll get your salespeople and managers to perform better &#8212; guaranteed.<br />
                    The top leaders know how to coach their teams by using a tactical coaching model that is easy to deploy on a consistent basis in order to protect and maximize the potential of the company&#8217;s greatest investment, their people. Coaching Salespeople into Sales Champions is what executives and managers need to develop their own executive sales coaching skills and strategy; the missing discipline amongst leadership. This book will teach managers how to  boost sales efficiency, quickly turnaround an underperformer, eliminate hours from your workload and integrate a proven, step by step internal coaching framework to most effectively hire and retain top talent.  This book is for any sales manager, executive and business owner looking to maximize team productivity through executive sales coaching. You will discover how to master your coaching skills and deploy an internal coaching program, enabling you to : Conduct an effective deal/pipeline review that and  improves forecast accuracy  and uncovers new selling opportunities.  Make the transition from high performing salesperson to high performing sales manager  .<br />
                    Handle difficult conversations, and difficult employees without collateral damage or being held hostage by your people.  Create  alignment  with people you have to influence (partners, stakeholders, non-directs, peers, account executives, PAMs)  Position coaching to create a  positive  perception and eliminate any resistance people may feel around being coached.  Coach and consistently motivate the top, mid and underperformer &#8212; with great confidence.  Utilize a proven coaching framework to impact performance  immediately . ( L.E.A.D.S.  Coaching Framework(t);)  Master the language of leaders, The Art of Enrollment to create buy in and deeper engagement without pushback.  Conduct effective observation sessions and deliver feedback that leads to a positive change in behavior  .  Stop micro-managing and eliminate the heavy burden of dependency that traditional management styles create.  Make the shift from a fear based, reactionary, toxic culture to a  coaching culture  that fosters full accountability  .</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coaching-salespeople-into-sales-champions-a-tactical-playbook-for-managers-and-executives-keith-rosen-abridged/">Coaching Salespeople into Sales Champions : A Tactical Playbook for Managers and Executives &#8211; Keith Rosen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 1% Windfall : How Successful Companies Use Price to Profit and Grow &#8211; Rafi Mohammed (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Mathematics & Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In &#8220;The Art of Pricing&#8221;, Rafi Mohammed gave readers advice on setting prices. In this essential follow up, he takes them to the next level, teaching them how to use price as a competitive strategy. A study of the Global 1200 found that if companies increased prices by just 1 percent, their average operating profits [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/">The 1% Windfall : How Successful Companies Use Price to Profit and Grow &#8211; Rafi Mohammed (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In &#8220;The Art of Pricing&#8221;, Rafi Mohammed gave readers advice on setting prices. In this essential follow up, he takes them to the next level, teaching them how to use price as a competitive strategy. A study of the Global 1200 found that if companies increased prices by just 1 percent, their average operating profits would increase by 11 percent. Using small incremental changes in price, Fortune 200 companies would see enormous growth in percentage of profit: Amazon, 40 percent; Aramark, 30 percent; Archer Daniels Midland, 19 percent; AMR, 68 percent; Boeing, 19 percent; Ingram Micro, 83 percent; McKesson, 82 percent; Wal Mart, 22 percent. Unfortunately, most companies have no clue how to capitalise on the direct link between pricing and profits. But how do executives and managers set the right price? Underpinned by sound empirical research and real-life anecdotes &#8220;The 1% Windfall&#8221; addresses this fundamental question, offering guidelines any company-whether a multi-national conglomerate, a small business, or even a non-profit can follow to create a comprehensive pricing strategy for any product and service.<br />
                    In addition, these techniques and tools apply equally to offensive and defensive solutions whether a company wants to keep ahead of the competition, avert a slump in a recession, or offset the impact of inflation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/">The 1% Windfall : How Successful Companies Use Price to Profit and Grow &#8211; Rafi Mohammed (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Objections : The Ultimate Guide for Mastering The Art and Science of Getting Past No &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword by Mark Hunter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/objections-the-ultimate-guide-for-mastering-the-art-and-science-of-getting-past-no-jeb-blount-foreword-by-mark-hunter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/objections-the-ultimate-guide-for-mastering-the-art-and-science-of-getting-past-no-jeb-blount-foreword-by-mark-hunter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are few one-size-fits-all solutions in sales. Context matters. Complex sales are different from one-call closes. B2B is different than B2C. Prospects, territories, products, industries, companies, and sales processes are all different. There is little black and white in the sales profession. Except for objections. There is democracy in objections. Every salesperson must endure many [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/objections-the-ultimate-guide-for-mastering-the-art-and-science-of-getting-past-no-jeb-blount-foreword-by-mark-hunter-abridged/">Objections : The Ultimate Guide for Mastering The Art and Science of Getting Past No &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword by Mark Hunter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are few one-size-fits-all solutions in sales. Context matters. Complex sales are different from one-call closes. B2B is different than B2C. Prospects, territories, products, industries, companies, and sales processes are all different. There is little black and white in the sales profession.    </p>
<p>                     Except for objections. There is democracy in objections. Every salesperson must endure many NOs in order to get to YES.     </p>
<p>                     Objections don&#8217;t care or consider:    </p>
<p>                    Who you are<br />
                    What you sell<br />
                    How you sell<br />
                    If you are new to sales or a veteran<br />
                    If your sales cycle is long or short &#8211; complex or transactional    </p>
<p>                     For as long as salespeople have been asking buyers to make commitments, buyers have been throwing out objections. And, for as long as buyers have been saying no, salespeople have yearned for the secrets to getting past those NOs.    </p>
<p>                     Following in the footsteps of his blockbuster bestsellers Fanatical Prospecting and Sales EQ, Jeb Blount&#8217;s Objections is a comprehensive and contemporary guide that engages your heart and mind.    </p>
<p>                     In his signature right-to-the-point style, Jeb pulls no punches and slaps you in the face with the cold, hard truth about what&#8217;s really holding you back from closing sales and reaching your income goals. Then he pulls you in with examples, stories, and lessons that teach powerful human-influence frameworks for getting past NO &#8211; even with the most challenging objections.    </p>
<p>                     What you won&#8217;t find, though, is old school techniques straight out of the last century. No bait and switch schemes, no sycophantic tie-downs, no cheesy scripts, and none of the contrived closing techniques that leave you feeling like a phony, destroy relationships, and only serve to increase your buyers&#8217; resistance.    </p>
<p>                     Instead, you&#8217;ll learn a new psychology for turning-around objections and proven techniques that work with today&#8217;s more informed, in control, and skeptical buyers. Inside the pages of Objections, you&#8217;ll gain deep insight into:    </p>
<p>                    How to get past the natural human fear of NO and become rejection proof<br />
                    The science of resistance and why buyers throw out objections<br />
                    Human influence frameworks that turn you into a master persuader<br />
                    The key to avoiding embarrassing red herrings that derail sales calls<br />
                    How to leverage the &#8220;Magical Quarter of a Second&#8221; to instantly gain control of your emotions when you get hit with difficult objections<br />
                    Proven objection turn-around frameworks that give you confidence and control in virtually every sales situation<br />
                    How to easily skip past reflex responses on cold calls and when prospecting<br />
                    How to move past brush-offs to get to the next step, increase pipeline velocity, and shorten the sales cycle<br />
                    The 5 Step Process for Turning Around Buying Commitment Objections and closing the sale<br />
                    Rapid Negotiation techniques that deliver better terms and higher prices    </p>
<p>                     As you dive into these powerful insights, and with each new chapter, you&#8217;ll gain greater and greater confidence in your ability to face and effectively handle objections in any selling situation. And, with this new-found confidence, your success and income will soar.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/objections-the-ultimate-guide-for-mastering-the-art-and-science-of-getting-past-no-jeb-blount-foreword-by-mark-hunter-abridged/">Objections : The Ultimate Guide for Mastering The Art and Science of Getting Past No &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword by Mark Hunter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Challenger Sale : Taking Control of the Customer Conversation &#8211; Matthew Dixon, Brent Adamson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-challenger-sale-taking-control-of-the-customer-conversation-matthew-dixon-brent-adamson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-challenger-sale-taking-control-of-the-customer-conversation-matthew-dixon-brent-adamson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The need to understand what top-performing reps are doing that their average performing colleagues are not drove Matthew Dixon, Brent Adamson, and their colleagues at Corporate Executive Board to investigate the skills, behaviors, knowledge, and attitudes that matter most for high performance. And what they discovered may be the biggest shock to conventional sales wisdom [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-challenger-sale-taking-control-of-the-customer-conversation-matthew-dixon-brent-adamson-abridged/">The Challenger Sale : Taking Control of the Customer Conversation &#8211; Matthew Dixon, Brent Adamson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The need to understand what top-performing reps are doing that their average performing colleagues are not drove Matthew Dixon, Brent Adamson, and their colleagues at Corporate Executive Board to investigate the skills, behaviors, knowledge, and attitudes that matter most for high performance. And what they discovered may be the biggest shock to conventional sales wisdom in decades. Based on an exhaustive study of thousands of sales reps across multiple industries and geographies, &#8220;The Challenger Sale&#8221; argues that classic relationship building is a losing approach, especially when it comes to selling complex, large-scale business-to-business solutions. The authors&#8217; study found that every sales rep in the world falls into one of five distinct profiles, and while all of these types of reps can deliver average sales performance, only one &#8211; the Challenger &#8211; delivers consistently high performance. Instead of bludgeoning customers with endless facts and features about their company and products, Challengers approach customers with unique insights about how they can save or make money. They tailor their sales message to the customer&#8217;s specific needs and objectives.<br />
                    Rather than acquiescing to the customer&#8217;s every demand or objection, they are assertive, pushing back when necessary and taking control of the sale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-challenger-sale-taking-control-of-the-customer-conversation-matthew-dixon-brent-adamson-abridged/">The Challenger Sale : Taking Control of the Customer Conversation &#8211; Matthew Dixon, Brent Adamson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sales Bible, New Edition : The Ultimate Sales Resource &#8211; Jeffrey Gitomer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sales-bible-new-edition-the-ultimate-sales-resource-jeffrey-gitomer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sales-bible-new-edition-the-ultimate-sales-resource-jeffrey-gitomer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sales Bible softbound NEW EDITION WITH SOCIAL MEDIA ANSWERS Global sales authority Jeffrey Gitomer&#8217;s bestselling classic, The Sales Bible, has been updated and appended in this new edition, offering you the ultimate sales methods and strategies that really work every day, in real-world selling situations. With over 200,000 copies of the previous editions sold, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sales-bible-new-edition-the-ultimate-sales-resource-jeffrey-gitomer-abridged/">The Sales Bible, New Edition : The Ultimate Sales Resource &#8211; Jeffrey Gitomer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sales Bible softbound NEW EDITION WITH SOCIAL MEDIA ANSWERS Global sales authority Jeffrey Gitomer&#8217;s bestselling classic, The Sales Bible, has been updated and appended in this new edition, offering you the ultimate sales methods and strategies that really work every day, in real-world selling situations. With over 200,000 copies of the previous editions sold, The Sales Bible was listed as one of &#8220;The Ten Books Every Salesperson Should Own and Read&#8221; by the Dale Carnegie Sales Advantage Program. Jeffrey Gitomer&#8217;s column, &#8220;Sales Moves,&#8221; and blog, &#8220;SalesBlog.com&#8221; are read by more than four million people every week. His customers include Coca-Cola, BMW, Kimpton Hotels, Hilton, Wells Fargo Bank, IBM, Enterprise Rent-A-Car, Hewlett Packard, and hundreds of others. The Sales Bible is your personal, trusted, authoritative resource to reach your sales potential and shine like a star. Accept no substitutes. Here are a few highlights: * The 10.5<br />
                    Commandments of Selling * Generate leads and close sales in any market environment * Find 25 proven ways to set hard-to-get appointments * Use top-down selling to fill your sales pipeline with prospects who are ready to buy now * Ask the right questions to make more sales in half the time * How to use the top social media platforms to create inbound leads and prove value The Sales Bible has helped tens of thousands of salespeople all over the world reach their potential and close the deal and it can help you. So what are you waiting for?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sales-bible-new-edition-the-ultimate-sales-resource-jeffrey-gitomer-abridged/">The Sales Bible, New Edition : The Ultimate Sales Resource &#8211; Jeffrey Gitomer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behind the Cloud : The Untold Story of How Salesforce.com Went from Idea to Billion-Dollar Company-and Revolutionized an Industry &#8211; Marc Benioff, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behind-the-cloud-the-untold-story-of-how-salesforce-com-went-from-idea-to-billion-dollar-company-and-revolutionized-an-industry-marc-benioff-carlye-adler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behind-the-cloud-the-untold-story-of-how-salesforce-com-went-from-idea-to-billion-dollar-company-and-revolutionized-an-industry-marc-benioff-carlye-adler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How did salesforce.com grow from a start up in a rented apartment into the world&#8217;s fastest growing software company in less than a decade? For the first time, Marc Benioff, the visionary founder, chairman and CEO of salesforce.com, tells how he and his team created and used new business, technology, and philanthropic models tailored to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behind-the-cloud-the-untold-story-of-how-salesforce-com-went-from-idea-to-billion-dollar-company-and-revolutionized-an-industry-marc-benioff-carlye-adler-abridged/">Behind the Cloud : The Untold Story of How Salesforce.com Went from Idea to Billion-Dollar Company-and Revolutionized an Industry &#8211; Marc Benioff, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How did salesforce.com grow from a start up in a rented apartment into the world&#8217;s fastest growing software company in less than a decade? For the first time, Marc Benioff, the visionary founder, chairman and CEO of salesforce.com, tells how he and his team created and used new business, technology, and philanthropic models tailored to this time of extraordinary change. Showing how salesforce.com not only survived the dotcom implosion of 2001, but went on to define itself as the leader of the cloud computing revolution and spark a $46-billion dollar industry, Benioff&#8217;s story will help business leaders and entrepreneurs stand out, innovate better, and grow faster in any economic climate. In Behind the Cloud, Benioff shares the strategies that have inspired employees, turned customers into evangelists, leveraged an ecosystem of partners, and allowed innovation to flourish.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behind-the-cloud-the-untold-story-of-how-salesforce-com-went-from-idea-to-billion-dollar-company-and-revolutionized-an-industry-marc-benioff-carlye-adler-abridged/">Behind the Cloud : The Untold Story of How Salesforce.com Went from Idea to Billion-Dollar Company-and Revolutionized an Industry &#8211; Marc Benioff, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
