<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Christian Life &amp; Practice Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/christian-life-practice/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/christian-life-practice/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Christian Life &amp; Practice Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/christian-life-practice/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chicken Soup for the Soul: Runners : 31 Stories on Starting Out, Running Therapy, and Camaraderie &#8211; Jack Canfield</title>
		<link>/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-runners-31-stories-on-starting-out-running-therapy-and-camaraderie-jack-canfield/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Christian Testimony & Popular Inspirational Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-runners-31-stories-on-starting-out-running-therapy-and-camaraderie-jack-canfield/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When runners aren&#8217;t running, they are talking about running, planning their next run, shopping for running. This book contains stories from runners, telling their stories to other runners about. running — how it has changed their lives, their bodies, and their spirits. Runners will love these inspirational stories of fellow runners challenging themselves, recovering from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-runners-31-stories-on-starting-out-running-therapy-and-camaraderie-jack-canfield/">Chicken Soup for the Soul: Runners : 31 Stories on Starting Out, Running Therapy, and Camaraderie &#8211; Jack Canfield</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When runners aren&#8217;t running, they are talking about running, planning their next run, shopping for running. This book contains stories from runners, telling their stories to other runners about. running — how it has changed their lives, their bodies, and their spirits. Runners will love these inspirational stories of fellow runners challenging themselves, recovering from injuries, and staying motivated.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-runners-31-stories-on-starting-out-running-therapy-and-camaraderie-jack-canfield/">Chicken Soup for the Soul: Runners : 31 Stories on Starting Out, Running Therapy, and Camaraderie &#8211; Jack Canfield</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unmasking The Devil &#8211; John Ramirez</title>
		<link>/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Satanist-Turned-Evangelist Gives You the Inside Strategy to Defeat the Devil&#8217;s Plans! Many people, even Christians, deny the devil&#8217;s power. John Ramirez doesn&#8217;t have that luxury&#8211;he experienced the prince of darkness up close and personal. In the impoverished streets of the South Bronx, John Ramirez found &#8220;acceptance&#8221; from a family of witches and warlocks. These practitioners [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/">Unmasking The Devil &#8211; John Ramirez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Satanist-Turned-Evangelist Gives You the Inside Strategy to Defeat the Devil&#8217;s Plans!</p>
<p>                     Many people, even Christians, deny the devil&#8217;s power. John Ramirez doesn&#8217;t have that luxury&#8211;he experienced the prince of darkness up close and personal.</p>
<p>                     In the impoverished streets of the South Bronx, John Ramirez found &#8220;acceptance&#8221; from a family of witches and warlocks. These practitioners of dark arts trained him to be a high-ranking satanic priest&#8211;a story told in his first book, Out of the Devil&#8217;s Cauldron. However, everything changed when he met the living Christ.</p>
<p>                     In Unmasking the Devil, John Ramirez shares an insider view of how satan operates so you can avoid his traps and learn how to:<br />
                     discern between the voice of God that directs to victory and satan&#8217;s voice that leads to destruction.close the demonic doors satan uses to enter your life: entertainment, unhealthy relationships, greed, and false religion.activate the spiritual weapons of prayer, intercession, and Scripture to render hell powerless over your life.recognize how the spirits of Jezebel and Delilah attempt to infiltrate the church, create disunity, and render God&#8217;s people powerless.<br />
                     No army goes into battle without first knowing the tactics of their enemy. Receive behind-the-scene glimpses of satan&#8217;s strategies and equip yourself to live victoriously over the powers of darkness! </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Spiritual warfare is a must for every Christian if they are going to survive in the coming years,&#8221; says John Ramirez. &#8220;It&#8217;s time to stop playing patty-cake with the devil and learn how to put hell on notice.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/">Unmasking The Devil &#8211; John Ramirez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus : How the Jewish Words of Jesus Can Change Your Life &#8211; Lois Tverberg</title>
		<link>/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aspects Of Religion (non-Christian)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus, Lois Tverberg challenges readers to follow their Rabbi more closely by reexamining his words in the light of their Jewish context. Doing so will provide a richer, deeper understanding of his ministry, compelling us to live differently, to become more Christ-like. We&#8217;ll begin to understand why his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/">Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus : How the Jewish Words of Jesus Can Change Your Life &#8211; Lois Tverberg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus, Lois Tverberg challenges readers to follow their Rabbi more closely by reexamining his words in the light of their Jewish context. Doing so will provide a richer, deeper understanding of his ministry, compelling us to live differently, to become more Christ-like. We&#8217;ll begin to understand why his first Jewish disciples abandoned everything to follow him, to live out his commands.    </p>
<p>                    Our modern society, with its individualism and materialism, is very different than the tight-knit, family-oriented setting Jesus lived and taught in. What wisdom can we glean from his Eastern, biblical attitude toward life? How can knowing Jesus within this context shed light on his teachings for us today?    </p>
<p>                    In Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus we&#8217;ll journey back in time to eavesdrop on the conversations that arose among the rabbis of Jesus&#8217; day, and consider how hearing Rabbi Jesus with the ears of a first-century disciple can bring new meaning to our faith. And we&#8217;ll listen to Jewish thinkers through the ages, discovering how ideas that germinated in Jesus&#8217; time have borne fruit. Doing so will yield fresh, practical insights for following our Rabbi&#8217;s teachings from a Jewish point of view.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/">Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus : How the Jewish Words of Jesus Can Change Your Life &#8211; Lois Tverberg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let God Change Your Life &#8211; Greg Laurie</title>
		<link>/let-god-change-your-life-greg-laurie/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-god-change-your-life-greg-laurie/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Evangelist Greg Laurie calls all Christians back to radical New Testament living in his latest offering, Let God Change Your Life. Imagine what it would have been like to be a follower of Jesus; first-century Christians walked away from their old lives just to be where He was. What they learned, sitting at His feet, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-god-change-your-life-greg-laurie/">Let God Change Your Life &#8211; Greg Laurie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Evangelist Greg Laurie calls all Christians back to radical New Testament living in his latest offering, Let God Change Your Life. Imagine what it would have been like to be a follower of Jesus; first-century Christians walked away from their old lives just to be where He was. What they learned, sitting at His feet, was discipleship. And when His work on earth was done, first-century Christians took His words and example and spread out, teaching the gospel to everyone. The good news is that we, too, can participate in this lifestyle. Laurie drills it down in three simple ideas: get to know Jesus, follow His plan for discipleship, and use it to tell others what we know. Laurie&#8217;s tone is clear, direct, and biblical.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-god-change-your-life-greg-laurie/">Let God Change Your Life &#8211; Greg Laurie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Covenant with My Eyes &#8211; Bob Sorge</title>
		<link>/a-covenant-with-my-eyes-bob-sorge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Men]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-covenant-with-my-eyes-bob-sorge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This books sounds a bold call to the highest consecration in our sexuality. Get ready for a unique book that is apprehending, prudent, and empowering. Based on Bob&#8217;s own experience with Job 31:1, this book extends an invitation to actually make a covenant vow before God with our eyes. Written for all ages, men and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-covenant-with-my-eyes-bob-sorge/">A Covenant with My Eyes &#8211; Bob Sorge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This books sounds a bold call to the highest consecration in our sexuality. Get ready for a unique book that is apprehending, prudent, and empowering. Based on Bob&#8217;s own experience with Job 31:1, this book extends an invitation to actually make a covenant vow before God with our eyes. Written for all ages, men and women alike, this book excavates from the ancient spirituality of the book of Job the master key to consecration and illuminates its relevance to us today. The careful writing style will make you feel safe recommending this book even to teens.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-covenant-with-my-eyes-bob-sorge/">A Covenant with My Eyes &#8211; Bob Sorge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Murder of Jesus &#8211; John F. MacArthur</title>
		<link>/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bible Studies: For Individual Or Small Group Study]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The pieces are in place. The curtain rises for the final act. God is about to die. An unprecedented conspiracy of injustice, cruelty, and religious and political interests sentenced a man guilty of no crimes to the most barbaric method of execution ever devised. The victim was no mere man. Jesus was God in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/">The Murder of Jesus &#8211; John F. MacArthur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The pieces are in place. The curtain rises for the final act. God is about to die.    </p>
<p>                    An unprecedented conspiracy of injustice, cruelty, and religious and political interests sentenced a man guilty of no crimes to the most barbaric method of execution ever devised. The victim was no mere man. Jesus was God in the flesh. The Creator of life died.    </p>
<p>                    How did such a thing come to be? Who were the onlookers, the players, the fakes, frauds, and heroes? What was it like in the Upper Room that night, in the shadows of Gethsemane, or in the Praetorium awaiting Pilate&#8217;s verdict? What is the meaning of the last words Jesus uttered as He gasped for breath on the cross? What if all the facts you now so well could come alive in your ind and heart as a living story, rather than as a 2000-year-old ancient account?    </p>
<p>                    By piecing together the narrative from the perspective of the participants, John MacArthur invites you to relive the most awesome injustice in the history of man, the unparalleled triumph of the sovereignty of God, and the passion of Christ.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/">The Murder of Jesus &#8211; John F. MacArthur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A witty, compelling guide to raising open-minded and morally grounded kids in these crazy times, with an approach that&#8217;s rooted in science, psychology, and faith &#8220;Groundbreaking, profound, frank and friendly.&#8221;&#8211;Wendy Mogel, PhD, author of The Blessing of a Skinned Knee NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY LIBRARY JOURNAL When Rev. Molly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/">Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A witty, compelling guide to raising open-minded and morally grounded kids in these crazy times, with an approach that&#8217;s rooted in science, psychology, and faith     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Groundbreaking, profound, frank and friendly.&#8221;&#8211;Wendy Mogel, PhD, author of The Blessing of a Skinned Knee     </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY LIBRARY JOURNAL     </p>
<p>                    When Rev. Molly Baskette and Dr. Ellen O&#8217;Donnell first met, they were both new mothers seeking parenting wisdom. They read a lot of books on the topic, but none of them contained practical suggestions that would help their families psychologically and spiritually while maintaining their progressive values: How do we teach the art of forgiving and serving others? How do we raise kids who are tolerant, curious, and honorable? And what about the sex talk?     </p>
<p>                    Taking matters into their own hands, Baskette and O&#8217;Donnell began creating actionable steps addressing these questions and more. This book is the fruit of their many conversations begun long ago during the daycare carpool, from angsty moments to hallelujahs.     </p>
<p>                    In Bless This Mess, readers will gain constructive tools as they learn how to talk to their children about social justice, money, God, ethics, bullying, disabilities, sexuality, and their bodies. Parents will also glean insights on how to serve others with joy, give generously and gratefully, and&#8211;perhaps most important&#8211;learn how to stop being so afraid all the damn time, even while raising kids in an increasingly chaotic and often scary world. With real-life examples, relatable personal stories, and strategies tailored to the toddler, preteen, or teenager, Bless This Mess guides parents of children at all stages of their development.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/">Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Failing Forward : Turning Mistakes into Stepping Stones for Success &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/failing-forward-turning-mistakes-into-stepping-stones-for-success-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/failing-forward-turning-mistakes-into-stepping-stones-for-success-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>America&#8217;s most trusted leadership expert will transform your attitude and belief about failure and empower you to make positive changes in your life to achieve your full potential. Are some people born to achieve anything they want while others struggle? Call them lucky, blessed, or possessors of the Midas touch. What is the real reason [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/failing-forward-turning-mistakes-into-stepping-stones-for-success-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">Failing Forward : Turning Mistakes into Stepping Stones for Success &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>America&#8217;s most trusted leadership expert will transform your attitude and belief about failure and empower you to make positive changes in your life to achieve your full potential.    </p>
<p>                    Are some people born to achieve anything they want while others struggle? Call them lucky, blessed, or possessors of the Midas touch. What is the real reason for their success? Is it family background, wealth, greater opportunities, high morals, an easy childhood?    </p>
<p>                    New York Times best-selling author John C. Maxwell has the answer: The difference between average people and achieving people is their perception of and response to failure.    </p>
<p>                    Most people are never prepared to deal with failure. Maxwell says that if you are like him, coming out of school, you feared it, misunderstood it, and ran away from it. But Maxwell has learned to make failure his friend, and he can teach you to do the same.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I want to help you learn how to confidently look the prospect of failure in the eye and move forward anyway,&#8221; says Maxwell. &#8220;Because in life, the question is not if you will have problems, but how you are going to deal with them. Stop failing backward and start failing forward!&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/failing-forward-turning-mistakes-into-stepping-stones-for-success-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">Failing Forward : Turning Mistakes into Stepping Stones for Success &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Work : A Proven Path to Discovering What You Were Meant to Do &#8211; Jeff Goins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-work-a-proven-path-to-discovering-what-you-were-meant-to-do-jeff-goins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-work-a-proven-path-to-discovering-what-you-were-meant-to-do-jeff-goins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jeff Goins, a brilliant new voice counting Seth Godin and Jon Acuff among his fans, explains how to abandon the status quo and live a life that matters with true passion and purpose. The path to your life&#8217;s work is difficult and risky, even scary, which is why few finish the journey. This is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-work-a-proven-path-to-discovering-what-you-were-meant-to-do-jeff-goins-abridged/">The Art of Work : A Proven Path to Discovering What You Were Meant to Do &#8211; Jeff Goins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jeff Goins, a brilliant new voice counting Seth Godin and Jon Acuff among his fans, explains how to abandon the status quo and live a life that matters with true passion and purpose.    </p>
<p>                    The path to your life&#8217;s work is difficult and risky, even scary, which is why few finish the journey. This is a book about discovering your life&#8217;s work, that treasure of immeasurable worth we all long for. It&#8217;s about the task you were born to do.         </p>
<p>                    As Jeff Goins explains, the search begins with passion but does not end there. Only when our interests connect with the needs of the world do we begin living for a larger purpose. Those who experience this intersection experience something exceptional and enviable. Though it is rare, such a life is attainable by anyone brave enough to try.     </p>
<p>                    Through personal experience, compelling case studies, and current research on the mysteries of motivation and talent, Jeff shows readers how to find their vocation and what to expect along the way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-work-a-proven-path-to-discovering-what-you-were-meant-to-do-jeff-goins-abridged/">The Art of Work : A Proven Path to Discovering What You Were Meant to Do &#8211; Jeff Goins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get Out of your Head : The One Thought that Can Shift Our Chaotic Minds &#8211; Jennie Allen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/get-out-of-your-head-the-one-thought-that-can-shift-our-chaotic-minds-jennie-allen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Christian Testimony & Popular Inspirational Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/get-out-of-your-head-the-one-thought-that-can-shift-our-chaotic-minds-jennie-allen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; You can choose hope in the midst of chaos. The visionary behind the million-strong IF: Gathering challenges you to exercise your God-given power to shift negative thinking patterns and take back control of your thoughts and emotions. &#8220;A must-have resource for anyone looking to get control of their thoughts.&#8221;&#8211;Lysa TerKeurst, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-out-of-your-head-the-one-thought-that-can-shift-our-chaotic-minds-jennie-allen-abridged/">Get Out of your Head : The One Thought that Can Shift Our Chaotic Minds &#8211; Jennie Allen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; You can choose hope in the midst of chaos. The visionary behind the million-strong IF: Gathering challenges you to exercise your God-given power to shift negative thinking patterns and take back control of your thoughts and emotions.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A must-have resource for anyone looking to get control of their thoughts.&#8221;&#8211;Lysa TerKeurst, #1 New York Times bestselling author and president of Proverbs 31 Ministries     </p>
<p>                    CHRISTIAN BOOK AWARD FINALIST &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY COSMOPOLITAN     </p>
<p>                    Are your thoughts holding you captive? I&#8217;ll never be good enough. Other people have better lives than I do. God couldn&#8217;t really love me. Jennie Allen knows what it&#8217;s like to swirl in a spiral of destructive thoughts, but she also knows we don&#8217;t have to stay stuck in toxic thinking patterns.     </p>
<p>                    As she discovered in her own life, God built a way for us to escape that downward spiral. Freedom comes when we refuse to be victims to our thoughts and realize we have already been equipped with power from God to fight and win the war for our minds.     </p>
<p>                    In Get Out of Your Head,  Jennie inspires and equips us to transform our emotions, our outlook, and even our circumstances by taking control of our thoughts. Our enemy is determined to get in our heads to make us feel helpless, overwhelmed, and incapable of making a difference for the kingdom of God. But when we submit our minds to Christ, the promises and goodness of God flood our lives in remarkable ways.     </p>
<p>                    It starts in your head. And from there, the possibilities are endless.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-out-of-your-head-the-one-thought-that-can-shift-our-chaotic-minds-jennie-allen-abridged/">Get Out of your Head : The One Thought that Can Shift Our Chaotic Minds &#8211; Jennie Allen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Road Back to You : An Enneagram Journey to Self-Discovery &#8211; Ian Morgan Cron, Suzanne Stabile (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over 750,000 Copies Sold Worldwide! Foreword INDIES Book of the Year Awards Finalist Missio Alliance Essential Reading List Ignorance is bliss-except in self-awareness. What you don&#8217;t know about yourself can hurt you and your relationships-and even keep you in the shallows with God. Do you want help figuring out who you are and why you&#8217;re [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/">The Road Back to You : An Enneagram Journey to Self-Discovery &#8211; Ian Morgan Cron, Suzanne Stabile (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over 750,000 Copies Sold Worldwide!    </p>
<p>                                Foreword INDIES Book of the Year Awards Finalist    </p>
<p>                    Missio Alliance Essential Reading List<br />
                             Ignorance is bliss-except in self-awareness.<br />
                    What you don&#8217;t know about yourself can hurt you and your relationships-and even keep you in the shallows with God. Do you want help figuring out who you are and why you&#8217;re stuck in the same ruts?<br />
                    The Enneagram is an ancient personality typing system with an uncanny accuracy in describing how human beings are wired, both positively and negatively. In The Road Back to You Ian Morgan Cron and Suzanne Stabile forge a unique approach-a practical, comprehensive way of accessing Enneagram wisdom and exploring its connections with Christian spirituality for a deeper knowledge of ourselves, compassion for others, and love for God.<br />
                    Witty and filled with stories, this book allows you to peek inside each of the nine Enneagram types, keeping you turning the pages long after you have read the chapter about your own number. Not only will you learn more about yourself, but you will also start to see the world through other people&#8217;s eyes, understanding how and why people think, feel, and act the way they do.<br />
                    Beginning with changes you can start making today, the wisdom of the Enneagram can help take you further along into who you really are-leading you into places of spiritual discovery you would never have found on your own, and paving the way to the wiser, more compassionate person you want to become.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/">The Road Back to You : An Enneagram Journey to Self-Discovery &#8211; Ian Morgan Cron, Suzanne Stabile (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Purpose Driven Life &#8211; Rick Warren (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-purpose-driven-life-rick-warren-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-purpose-driven-life-rick-warren-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rick Warren, founding pastor of Saddleback Church in Lake Forest, California, one of America&#8217;s largest and best-known churches, shows you how to lead a Purpose-Driven Life. This Miniature Edition (TM) will help you understand why you are alive and God&#8217;s amazing plan for you- both here and now, and for eternity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-purpose-driven-life-rick-warren-abridged/">The Purpose Driven Life &#8211; Rick Warren (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rick Warren, founding pastor of Saddleback Church in Lake Forest, California, one of America&#8217;s largest and best-known churches, shows you how to lead a Purpose-Driven Life. This Miniature Edition (TM) will help you understand why you are alive and God&#8217;s amazing plan for you- both here and now, and for eternity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-purpose-driven-life-rick-warren-abridged/">The Purpose Driven Life &#8211; Rick Warren (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The More of Less: Finding the Life you Want Under Everything you Own &#8211; Joshua Becker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-more-of-less-finding-the-life-you-want-under-everything-you-own-joshua-becker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-more-of-less-finding-the-life-you-want-under-everything-you-own-joshua-becker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Don&#8217;t Settle for More Most of us know we own too much stuff. We feel the weight and burden of our clutter, and we tire of cleaning and managing and organizing. While excess consumption leads to bigger houses, faster cars, fancier technology, and cluttered homes, it never brings happiness. Rather, it results in a desire [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-more-of-less-finding-the-life-you-want-under-everything-you-own-joshua-becker-abridged/">The More of Less: Finding the Life you Want Under Everything you Own &#8211; Joshua Becker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Don&#8217;t Settle for More    </p>
<p>                     Most of us know we own too much stuff. We feel the weight and burden of our clutter, and we tire of cleaning and managing and organizing.     </p>
<p>                     While excess consumption leads to bigger houses, faster cars, fancier technology, and cluttered homes, it never brings happiness. Rather, it results in a desire for more. It redirects our greatest passions to things that can never fulfill. And it distracts us from the very life we wish we were living.     </p>
<p>                     Live a better life with less.     </p>
<p>                     In The More of Less, Joshua Becker helps you&#8230;     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Recognize the life-giving benefits of owning less<br />
                     &#8211; Realize how all the stuff you own is keeping you from pursuing your dreams<br />
                     &#8211; Craft a personal, practical approach to decluttering your home and life<br />
                     &#8211; Experience the joys of generosity<br />
                     &#8211; Learn why the best part of minimalism isn&#8217;t a clean house, it&#8217;s a full life     </p>
<p>                     The beauty of minimalism isn&#8217;t in what it takes away. It&#8217;s in what it gives.     </p>
<p>                    Make Room in Your Life for What You Really Want     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Maybe you don&#8217;t need to own all this stuff.&#8221; After a casual conversation with his neighbor on Memorial Day 2008, Joshua Becker realized he needed a change. He was spending far too much time organizing possessions, cleaning up messes, and looking for more to buy.     </p>
<p>                    So Joshua and his wife decided to remove the nonessential possessions from their home and life. Eventually, they sold, donated, or discarded over 60 percent of what they owned. In exchange, they found a life of more freedom, more contentment, more generosity, and more opportunity to pursue the things that mattered most.     </p>
<p>                    The More of Less delivers an empowering plan for living more by owning less. With practical suggestions and encouragement to personalize your own minimalist style, Joshua Becker shows you why minimizing possessions is the best way to maximize life.     </p>
<p>                    Are you ready for less cleaning, less anxiety, and less stress in your life? Simplicity isn&#8217;t as complicated as you think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-more-of-less-finding-the-life-you-want-under-everything-you-own-joshua-becker-abridged/">The More of Less: Finding the Life you Want Under Everything you Own &#8211; Joshua Becker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Return to Love : Reflections on the Principles of &#8220;a Course in Miracles&#8221; &#8211; Marianne Williamson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-return-to-love-reflections-on-the-principles-of-a-course-in-miracles-marianne-williamson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chakras, Auras & Spiritual Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stationery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-return-to-love-reflections-on-the-principles-of-a-course-in-miracles-marianne-williamson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Back by popular demand &#8212; and newly updated by the author &#8212; the mega-bestselling spiritual guide in which Marianne Williamson shares her reflections on A Course in Miracles and her insights on the application of love in the search for inner peace. Williamson reveals how we each can become a miracle worker by accepting God [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-return-to-love-reflections-on-the-principles-of-a-course-in-miracles-marianne-williamson-abridged/">A Return to Love : Reflections on the Principles of &#8220;a Course in Miracles&#8221; &#8211; Marianne Williamson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Back by popular demand &#8212; and newly updated by the author &#8212; the mega-bestselling spiritual guide in which Marianne Williamson shares her reflections on A Course in Miracles and her insights on the application of love in the search for inner peace.    </p>
<p>                    Williamson reveals how we each can become a miracle worker by accepting God and by the expression of love in our daily lives. Whether psychic pain is in the area of relationships, career, or health, she shows us how love is a potent force, the key to inner peace, and how by practicing love we can make our own lives more fulfilling while creating a more peaceful and loving world for our children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-return-to-love-reflections-on-the-principles-of-a-course-in-miracles-marianne-williamson-abridged/">A Return to Love : Reflections on the Principles of &#8220;a Course in Miracles&#8221; &#8211; Marianne Williamson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Name of God is Mercy &#8211; Pope Francis, Translated by Oonagh Stransky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-name-of-god-is-mercy-pope-francis-translated-by-oonagh-stransky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Leaders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Roman Catholicism, Roman Catholic Church]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-name-of-god-is-mercy-pope-francis-translated-by-oonagh-stransky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Name of God is Mercy, Pope Francis&#8217; exploration on the universal theme of mercy, is a spiritual inspiration to both followers of Christianity and non-Christians around the world. Drawing on his own experience as a priest and shepherd, Pope Francis discusses mercy, a subject of central importance in his religious teaching and testimony, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-name-of-god-is-mercy-pope-francis-translated-by-oonagh-stransky-abridged/">The Name of God is Mercy &#8211; Pope Francis, Translated by Oonagh Stransky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Name of God is Mercy, Pope Francis&#8217; exploration on the universal theme of mercy, is a spiritual inspiration to both followers of Christianity and non-Christians around the world.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own experience as a priest and shepherd, Pope Francis discusses mercy, a subject of central importance in his religious teaching and testimony, and in addition sums up other ideas &#8211; reconciliation, the closeness of God &#8211; that comprise the heart of his papacy. Written in conversation with Vatican expert and La Stampa journalist Andrea Tornielli, The Name of God is Mercy is directed at everyone, inside or outside of the Catholic Church, seeking meaning in life, a road to peace and reconciliation, or the healing of physical or spiritual wounds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-name-of-god-is-mercy-pope-francis-translated-by-oonagh-stransky-abridged/">The Name of God is Mercy &#8211; Pope Francis, Translated by Oonagh Stransky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition : A Proven Plan for Financial Fitness &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-total-money-makeover-classic-edition-a-proven-plan-for-financial-fitness-dave-ramsey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funding Of Education & Student Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-total-money-makeover-classic-edition-a-proven-plan-for-financial-fitness-dave-ramsey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to build a budget that actually works for you? Are you ready to transform your relationship with money? This New York Times bestseller has already helped millions of people learn how to develop everyday money-saving habits with the help of America&#8217;s favorite finance coach, Dave Ramsey. By now, you&#8217;ve already heard all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-total-money-makeover-classic-edition-a-proven-plan-for-financial-fitness-dave-ramsey-abridged/">The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition : A Proven Plan for Financial Fitness &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to build a budget that actually works for you? Are you ready to transform your relationship with money? This New York Times bestseller has already helped millions of people learn how to develop everyday money-saving habits with the help of America&#8217;s favorite finance coach, Dave Ramsey.    </p>
<p>                    By now, you&#8217;ve already heard all of the nutty get-rich-quick schemes and the fiscal diet fads that leave you with a lot of quirky ideas but not a penny in your pocket. If you&#8217;re tired of the lies and sick of the false promises, Dave is here to provide practical, long-term help. The Total Money Makeover is the simplest, most straightforward game plan for completely changing your finances. And, best of all, these principles are based on results, not pie-in-the-sky fantasies. This is the financial reset you&#8217;ve been looking for.    </p>
<p>                    The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition will give you the tools and the encouragement you need to:    </p>
<p>                    Design a sure-fire plan for paying off all debt&#8211;from your cars to your home and everything in between<br />
                    Break bad habits and make lasting changes when it comes to your relationship with money<br />
                    Recognize the 10 most dangerous money myths<br />
                    Secure a healthy nest egg for emergencies and set yourself up for retirement<br />
                    Become financially healthy for life    </p>
<p>                    This edition of The Total Money Makeover includes new, expanded &#8220;Dave Rants&#8221; that tackle marriage conflict, college debt, and so much more. Each copy of The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition also includes brand new back-of-the-book resources to help you make Total Money Makeover your new reality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-total-money-makeover-classic-edition-a-proven-plan-for-financial-fitness-dave-ramsey-abridged/">The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition : A Proven Plan for Financial Fitness &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Should We Then Live? : The Rise and Decline of Western Thought and Culture &#8211; Francis A. Schaeffer, Foreword by Lane T. Dennis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-should-we-then-live-the-rise-and-decline-of-western-thought-and-culture-francis-a-schaeffer-foreword-by-lane-t-dennis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Ministry & Pastoral Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Social Thought & Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-should-we-then-live-the-rise-and-decline-of-western-thought-and-culture-francis-a-schaeffer-foreword-by-lane-t-dennis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Special 50th anniversary L&#8217;Abri Fellowship edition. Schaeffer&#8217;s seminal work which analyzed the reasons for modern society&#8217;s state of affairs and presented living a Christ-centered life as the only viable alternative</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-should-we-then-live-the-rise-and-decline-of-western-thought-and-culture-francis-a-schaeffer-foreword-by-lane-t-dennis-abridged/">How Should We Then Live? : The Rise and Decline of Western Thought and Culture &#8211; Francis A. Schaeffer, Foreword by Lane T. Dennis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Special 50th anniversary L&#8217;Abri Fellowship edition. Schaeffer&#8217;s seminal work which analyzed the reasons for modern society&#8217;s state of affairs and presented living a Christ-centered life as the only viable alternative</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-should-we-then-live-the-rise-and-decline-of-western-thought-and-culture-francis-a-schaeffer-foreword-by-lane-t-dennis-abridged/">How Should We Then Live? : The Rise and Decline of Western Thought and Culture &#8211; Francis A. Schaeffer, Foreword by Lane T. Dennis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Work the System (Fourth Edition) : The Simple Mechanics of Making More and Working Less &#8211; Sam Carpenter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/work-the-system-fourth-edition-the-simple-mechanics-of-making-more-and-working-less-sam-carpenter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/work-the-system-fourth-edition-the-simple-mechanics-of-making-more-and-working-less-sam-carpenter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Work The System aims to convince people to change their fundamental perception of the world around them from a vision of an impenetrable, amorphous conglomeration, to one made up of individual linear systems, each of which can be improved and perfected. The reader is guided through the process of &#8221;getting&#8221; this new vision, and then [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/work-the-system-fourth-edition-the-simple-mechanics-of-making-more-and-working-less-sam-carpenter-abridged/">Work the System (Fourth Edition) : The Simple Mechanics of Making More and Working Less &#8211; Sam Carpenter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Work The System aims to convince people to change their fundamental perception of the world around them from a vision of an impenetrable, amorphous conglomeration, to one made up of individual linear systems, each of which can be improved and perfected. The reader is guided through the process of &#8221;getting&#8221; this new vision, and then through the specifics of applying it. It&#8217;s simple, believable, and mechanical; not mystical or theoretical.    </p>
<p>                    Work the System will show business leaders and professionals how to achieve a positive macro result by looking at their business and work on a micro level &#8211; by analysing and refining each of the systems that are already in place. Readers will learn how to tweak this network of systems to maximize profits, create client loyalty, and develop autonomous employees. The strategies will also help individuals improve their performance and decrease the stress of being overtaxed or disorganized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/work-the-system-fourth-edition-the-simple-mechanics-of-making-more-and-working-less-sam-carpenter-abridged/">Work the System (Fourth Edition) : The Simple Mechanics of Making More and Working Less &#8211; Sam Carpenter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Faith : A Journey for All &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/faith-a-journey-for-all-jimmy-carter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Christian Testimony & Popular Inspirational Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/faith-a-journey-for-all-jimmy-carter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful and personal reflection, a New York Times bestseller, President Jimmy Carter contemplates how faith has sustained him in happiness and disappointment and considers how we may find it in our own lives. All his life, President Jimmy Carter has been a courageous exemplar of faith. Now he shares the lessons he learned. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/faith-a-journey-for-all-jimmy-carter-abridged/">Faith : A Journey for All &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful and personal reflection, a New York Times bestseller, President Jimmy Carter contemplates how faith has sustained him in happiness and disappointment and considers how we may find it in our own lives.     </p>
<p>                    All his life, President Jimmy Carter has been a courageous exemplar of faith. Now he shares the lessons he learned. He writes, &#8220;The issue of faith arises in almost every area of human existence, so it is important to understand its multiple meanings. In this book, my primary goal is to explore the broader meaning of faith, its far-reaching effect on our lives, and its relationship to past, present, and future events in America and around the world. The religious aspects of faith are also covered, since this is how the word is most often used, and I have included a description of the ways my faith has guided and sustained me, as well as how it has challenged and driven me to seek a closer and better relationship with people and with God.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Quoting eminent Protestant theologians, in Faith President Carter describes his belief in religious freedom, moral politics, and the place of prayer in his daily life. He examines faith&#8217;s many meanings, he describes how to accept it, live it, how to doubt and find faith again. This is a serious and moving reflection from one of America&#8217;s most admired and respected citizens.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/faith-a-journey-for-all-jimmy-carter-abridged/">Faith : A Journey for All &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Right Side of History : How Reason and Moral Purpose Made the West Great &#8211; Ben Shapiro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Intolerance, Persecution & Conflict]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Issues & Debates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! Human beings have never had it better than we have it now in the West. So why are we on the verge of throwing it all away? In 2016, New York Times bestselling author Ben Shapiro spoke at the University of California-Berkeley. Hundreds of police officers were required to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/">The Right Side of History : How Reason and Moral Purpose Made the West Great &#8211; Ben Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!    </p>
<p>                    Human beings have never had it better than we have it now in the West. So why are we on the verge of throwing it all away?    </p>
<p>                    In 2016, New York Times bestselling author Ben Shapiro spoke at the University of California-Berkeley. Hundreds of police officers were required to protect his speech. What was so frightening about Shapiro? He came to argue that Western civilization is in the midst of a crisis of purpose and ideas; that we have let grievances replace our sense of community and political expediency limit our individual rights; that we are teaching our kids that their emotions matter more than rational debate; and that the only meaning in life is arbitrary and subjective.    </p>
<p>                    As a society, we are forgetting that almost everything great that has ever happened in history happened because of people who believed in both Judeo-Christian values and in the Greek-born power of reason. In The Right Side of History, Shapiro sprints through more than 3,500 years, dozens of philosophers, and the thicket of modern politics to show how our freedoms are built upon the twin notions that every human being is made in God&#8217;s image and that human beings were created with reason capable of exploring God&#8217;s world.    </p>
<p>                    We can thank these values for the birth of science, the dream of progress, human rights, prosperity, peace, and artistic beauty. Jerusalem and Athens built America, ended slavery, defeated the Nazis and the Communists, lifted billions from poverty, and gave billions more spiritual purpose.     </p>
<p>                    Yet we are in the process of abandoning Judeo-Christian values and Greek natural law, watching our civilization collapse into age-old tribalism, individualistic hedonism, and moral subjectivism. We believe we can satisfy ourselves with intersectionality, scientific materialism, progressive politics, authoritarian governance, or nationalistic solidarity.    </p>
<p>                    We can&#8217;t.    </p>
<p>                    The West is special, and in The Right Side of History, Ben Shapiro bravely explains how we have lost sight of the moral purpose that drives each of us to be better, the sacred duty to work together for the greater good,.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/">The Right Side of History : How Reason and Moral Purpose Made the West Great &#8211; Ben Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stitches : A Handbook on Meaning, Hope, and Repair &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stitches-a-handbook-on-meaning-hope-and-repair-anne-lamott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Institutions & Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stitches-a-handbook-on-meaning-hope-and-repair-anne-lamott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What do we do when life lurches out of balance? How can we reconnect to one another and to what&#8217;s sustaining, when evil and catastrophe seem inescapable? These questions lie at the heart of Stitches, Anne Lamott&#8217;s follow-up to her New York Times-bestselling work, Help, Thanks, Wow. In this book, she explores how we find [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stitches-a-handbook-on-meaning-hope-and-repair-anne-lamott-abridged/">Stitches : A Handbook on Meaning, Hope, and Repair &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What do we do when life lurches out of balance? How can we reconnect to one another and to what&#8217;s sustaining, when evil and catastrophe seem inescapable?    </p>
<p>                    These questions lie at the heart of Stitches, Anne Lamott&#8217;s follow-up to her New York Times-bestselling work, Help, Thanks, Wow. In this book, she explores how we find meaning and peace in these loud and frantic times; where we start again after personal and public devastation; how we recapture wholeness after loss; and how we locate our true identities in this frazzled age. We begin, Lamott says, by collecting the ripped sheets of our emotional and spiritual fabric and sewing them back together &#8211; one stitch at a time.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s in these stitches that the quilt of life begins, and embedded in them are strength, warmth, humour and humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stitches-a-handbook-on-meaning-hope-and-repair-anne-lamott-abridged/">Stitches : A Handbook on Meaning, Hope, and Repair &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Imperfect Courage: Live a Life of Purpose by Leaving Comfort and Going Anyway &#8211; Jessica Honegger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/imperfect-courage-live-a-life-of-purpose-by-leaving-comfort-and-going-anyway-jessica-honegger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/imperfect-courage-live-a-life-of-purpose-by-leaving-comfort-and-going-anyway-jessica-honegger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Want to make a move but scared to leave your comfort zone? Go anyway. &#8220;Jessica&#8217;s perspective of global sisterhood and the power of lifting each other up in the midst of fear and scarcity is exactly what we need today. This book is both an invitation and a challenge to bravely show up for ourselves, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imperfect-courage-live-a-life-of-purpose-by-leaving-comfort-and-going-anyway-jessica-honegger-abridged/">Imperfect Courage: Live a Life of Purpose by Leaving Comfort and Going Anyway &#8211; Jessica Honegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Want to make a move but scared to leave your comfort zone? Go anyway.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Jessica&#8217;s perspective of global sisterhood and the power of lifting each other up in the midst of fear and scarcity is exactly what we need today. This book is both an invitation and a challenge to bravely show up for ourselves, for the people we love, and for the strangers that we will one day call family. I say, Amen!&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;Brené Brown, Ph.D., Author of the #1 New York Times bestseller Braving the Wilderness     </p>
<p>                     In Imperfect Courage, the founder of the popular fair trade jewelry brand Noonday Collection shares her story of starting the rapid-growing business that impacts over 4,500 artisans in vulnerable communities across the globe&#8211;and invites readers on a journey of transformation, challenging them to trade their comfort zones for a life of impact and adventure.    </p>
<p>                     In 2015, Inc. magazine recognized Noonday Collection as one of the fastest-growing companies in America. But years earlier, as Jessica Honegger stood at a pawn-shop counter in Austin, Texas, and handed over her grandmother&#8217;s gold jewelry, her goal was much more personal: to fund the adoption of her Rwandan son, Jack, by selling artisan-made jewelry.     </p>
<p>                     This first step launched an unexpected side-hustle that would grow into Noonday Collection. Jessica embarked on this new journey and teamed up with her first artisan partner, Jalia, a Ugandan jewelry maker. She saw the meaningful impact Noonday brought to Jalia&#8217;s community and knew it was the right move.     </p>
<p>                     Fear crept into Jessica&#8217;s heart as she realized her success, or failure, meant the same for Jalia. But refusing to let fear hinder her goals, Jessica found the necessary (if imperfect) courage she needed along the way&#8211;the courage to leave comfort and embrace a life of risk and impact.     </p>
<p>                     Discover Your Imperfect Courage<br />
                     In Imperfect Courage, Jessica takes you by the hand and invites you to trade your comfort zone for a life of impact and meaning.     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; First, she invites you to draw a circle of compassion around yourself and leads you through some soul-searching aimed at setting you free from shame.<br />
                     &#8211; Next, she challenges all of us to come together, dare to be vulnerable with one another, and commit to building a culture of collaboration.<br />
                     &#8211; Finally, Jessica calls on you to broaden your circle of compassion to embrace the entire globe&#8211;and to bring your beautifully imperfect courage to a world that needs you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imperfect-courage-live-a-life-of-purpose-by-leaving-comfort-and-going-anyway-jessica-honegger-abridged/">Imperfect Courage: Live a Life of Purpose by Leaving Comfort and Going Anyway &#8211; Jessica Honegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 5 Levels of Leadership : Proven Steps to Maximize Your Potential &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-5-levels-of-leadership-proven-steps-to-maximize-your-potential-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Christian Testimony & Popular Inspirational Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-5-levels-of-leadership-proven-steps-to-maximize-your-potential-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>True leadership isn&#8217;t a matter of having a certain job or title. In fact, being chosen for a position is only the first of the five levels every effective leader achieves. In his seminal work, leadership guru John Maxwell presents readers with the five stages of leadership and explains how to maximize each one to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-levels-of-leadership-proven-steps-to-maximize-your-potential-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">The 5 Levels of Leadership : Proven Steps to Maximize Your Potential &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>True leadership isn&#8217;t a matter of having a certain job or title. In fact, being chosen for a position is only the first of the five levels every effective leader achieves. In his seminal work, leadership guru John Maxwell presents readers with the five stages of leadership and explains how to maximize each one to become more influential, respected and successful: 1. Position &#8211; People follow because they have to. 2. Permission &#8211; People follow because they want to. 3. Production &#8211; People follow because of what you have done for the organization. 4. People Development &#8211; People follow because of what you have done for them personally. 5. Pinnacle &#8211; People follow because of who you are and what you represent.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-levels-of-leadership-proven-steps-to-maximize-your-potential-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">The 5 Levels of Leadership : Proven Steps to Maximize Your Potential &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Next Right Thing : A Simple, Soulful Practice for Making Life Decisions &#8211; Emily P. Freeman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-next-right-thing-a-simple-soulful-practice-for-making-life-decisions-emily-p-freeman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-next-right-thing-a-simple-soulful-practice-for-making-life-decisions-emily-p-freeman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nothing gets our attention like an unmade decision: Should I accept the new position? Which schooling choice is best for my kids? How can I support my aging parents? When we have a decision to make and the answer isn&#8217;t clear, what we want more than anything is peace, clarity, and a nudge in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-right-thing-a-simple-soulful-practice-for-making-life-decisions-emily-p-freeman-abridged/">The Next Right Thing : A Simple, Soulful Practice for Making Life Decisions &#8211; Emily P. Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nothing gets our attention like an unmade decision: Should I accept the new position? Which schooling choice is best for my kids? How can I support my aging parents? When we have a decision to make and the answer isn&#8217;t clear, what we want more than anything is peace, clarity, and a nudge in the right direction.     </p>
<p>                    If you have trouble making decisions, because of either chronic hesitation you&#8217;ve always lived with or a more recent onset of decision fatigue, Emily P. Freeman offers a fresh way of practicing familiar but often forgotten advice: simply do the next right thing. With this simple, soulful practice, it is possible to clear the decision-making chaos, quiet the fear of choosing wrong, and find the courage to finally decide without regret or second-guessing.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re in the midst of a major life transition or are weary of the low-grade anxiety that daily life can bring, Emily helps create space for your soul to breathe so you can live life with God at a gentle pace and discern your next right thing in love.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-right-thing-a-simple-soulful-practice-for-making-life-decisions-emily-p-freeman-abridged/">The Next Right Thing : A Simple, Soulful Practice for Making Life Decisions &#8211; Emily P. Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody, Always : Becoming Love in a World Full of Setbacks and Difficult People &#8211; Bob Goff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if we stopped avoiding the difficult people in our lives and committed to simply loving everybody? What happens when we give away love like we&#8217;re made of it? In Everybody, Always, Bob Goff&#8217;s joyful New York Times bestselling follow-up to Love Does, you&#8217;ll discover the secret to living without fear, constraint, or worry. Bob [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/">Everybody, Always : Becoming Love in a World Full of Setbacks and Difficult People &#8211; Bob Goff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What if we stopped avoiding the difficult people in our lives and committed to simply loving everybody? What happens when we give away love like we&#8217;re made of it? In Everybody, Always, Bob Goff&#8217;s joyful New York Times bestselling follow-up to Love Does, you&#8217;ll discover the secret to living without fear, constraint, or worry.     </p>
<p>                    Bob teaches us that the path toward the outsized, unfettered, liberated existence we all long for is found in one simple truth: love people, even the difficult ones, without distinction and without limits.    </p>
<p>                    In Everybody, Always, Bob shows us the simple truths about life that have the power to shift our mindset forever:    </p>
<p>                    Jesus uses our blind spots to reveal himself to us<br />
                    It&#8217;s easy to love kind, lovely, humble people, but you have to tackle fear in order to love people who are difficult<br />
                    What we do with our love will become the conversations we have with God<br />
                    Dark and scary places are filled with beautiful people who need our unconditional love<br />
                    Extravagant love has extraordinary power to change lives, including our own    </p>
<p>                    Driven by Bob&#8217;s trademark storytelling, this book reveals the wisdom Bob learned&#8211;often the hard way&#8211;about what it means to love without inhibition, insecurity, or restriction. From finding the right friends to discovering the upside of failure, Everybody, Always points the way to embodying love by doing the unexpected, the intimidating, the seemingly impossible.    </p>
<p>                    Whether losing his shoes while skydiving solo or befriending a Ugandan witch doctor, Bob steps into life with a no-limits embrace of others that is as infectious as it is extraordinarily ordinary. Everybody, Always reveals how we can do the same.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/">Everybody, Always : Becoming Love in a World Full of Setbacks and Difficult People &#8211; Bob Goff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 3 MILLION COPIES SOLD Do you ever suspect that everyone else has life figured out and you don&#8217;t have a clue? If so, Rachel Hollis has something to tell you: that&#8217;s a lie. If you have ever said any of these things to yourself . . . Something [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/">Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 3 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    Do you ever suspect that everyone else has life figured out and you don&#8217;t have a clue? If so, Rachel Hollis has something to tell you: that&#8217;s a lie.    </p>
<p>                    If you have ever said any of these things to yourself . . .    </p>
<p>                    Something else will make me happy.<br />
                    I&#8217;m not a good mom.<br />
                    I will never get past this.<br />
                    I am defined by my weight.<br />
                    I should be further along by now.    </p>
<p>                    . . . then you could benefit from the unflinching faith and rock-hard tenacity Rachel Hollis has in store for you. In this challenging but conversational book, Rachel exposes the twenty lies and misconceptions that too often hold us back from living joyfully and productively, lies we&#8217;ve told ourselves so often we don&#8217;t even hear them anymore.    </p>
<p>                    Rachel is real and talks about real issues. More than that, she reveals the specific practical strategies that helped her move past them. In the process, she encourages, entertains, and even kicks a little butt, all to convince you to do whatever it takes to get real and become the joyous, confident woman you were meant to be. Because you really can live with passion and hustle &#8211; and give yourself grace without giving up.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/">Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Now Shall We Live? &#8211; Charles Colson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-now-shall-we-live-charles-colson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Ministry & Pastoral Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Social Thought & Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-now-shall-we-live-charles-colson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2000 Gold Medallion Award winner! Christianity is more than a personal relationship with Jesus Christ. It is also a worldview that not only answers life&#8217;s basic questions&#8211;Where did we come from, and who are we? What has gone wrong with the world? What can we do to fix it?&#8211;but also shows us how we should [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-now-shall-we-live-charles-colson-abridged/">How Now Shall We Live? &#8211; Charles Colson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2000 Gold Medallion Award winner!<br />
                    Christianity is more than a personal relationship with Jesus Christ. It is also a worldview that not only answers life&#8217;s basic questions&#8211;Where did we come from, and who are we? What has gone wrong with the world? What can we do to fix it?&#8211;but also shows us how we should live as a result of those answers. How Now Shall We Live? gives Christians the understanding, the confidence, and the tools to confront the world&#8217;s bankrupt worldviews and to restore and redeem every aspect of contemporary culture: family, education, ethics, work, law, politics, science, art, music. This book will change every Christian who reads it. It will change the church in the new millennium.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-now-shall-we-live-charles-colson-abridged/">How Now Shall We Live? &#8211; Charles Colson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading : The Delights and Dilemmas of the Reading Life &#8211; Anne Bogel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/id-rather-be-reading-the-delights-and-dilemmas-of-the-reading-life-anne-bogel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/id-rather-be-reading-the-delights-and-dilemmas-of-the-reading-life-anne-bogel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For so many people, reading isn&#8217;t just a hobby or a way to pass the time&#8211;it&#8217;s a lifestyle. Our books shape us, define us, enchant us, and even sometimes infuriate us. Our books are a part of who we are as people, and we can&#8217;t imagine life without them. I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/id-rather-be-reading-the-delights-and-dilemmas-of-the-reading-life-anne-bogel-abridged/">I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading : The Delights and Dilemmas of the Reading Life &#8211; Anne Bogel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For so many people, reading isn&#8217;t just a hobby or a way to pass the time&#8211;it&#8217;s a lifestyle. Our books shape us, define us, enchant us, and even sometimes infuriate us. Our books are a part of who we are as people, and we can&#8217;t imagine life without them.    </p>
<p>                    I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading is the perfect literary companion for everyone who feels that way. In this collection of charming and relatable reflections on the reading life, beloved blogger and author Anne Bogel leads readers to remember the book that first hooked them, the place where they first fell in love with reading, and all of the moments afterward that helped make them the reader they are today. Known as a reading tastemaker through her popular podcast What Should I Read Next?, Bogel invites book lovers into a community of like-minded people to discover new ways to approach literature, learn fascinating new things about books and publishing, and reflect on the role reading plays in their lives.    </p>
<p>                    The perfect gift for the bibliophile in everyone&#8217;s life, I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading will command an honored place on the overstuffed bookshelves of any book lover.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/id-rather-be-reading-the-delights-and-dilemmas-of-the-reading-life-anne-bogel-abridged/">I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading : The Delights and Dilemmas of the Reading Life &#8211; Anne Bogel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ruthless Elimination of Hurry : How to stay emotionally healthy and spiritually alive in the chaos of the modern world &#8211; John Mark Comer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ruthless-elimination-of-hurry-how-to-stay-emotionally-healthy-and-spiritually-alive-in-the-chaos-of-the-modern-world-john-mark-comer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spiritualism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ruthless-elimination-of-hurry-how-to-stay-emotionally-healthy-and-spiritually-alive-in-the-chaos-of-the-modern-world-john-mark-comer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Who are you becoming? That was the question nagging pastor and author John Mark Comer. By outward metrics, everything appeared successful. But inwardly, things weren&#8217;t pretty. So he turned to a trusted mentor for guidance and heard these words: &#8216;Ruthlessly eliminate hurry from your life. Hurry is the great enemy of the spiritual life.&#8217; It [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ruthless-elimination-of-hurry-how-to-stay-emotionally-healthy-and-spiritually-alive-in-the-chaos-of-the-modern-world-john-mark-comer-abridged/">The Ruthless Elimination of Hurry : How to stay emotionally healthy and spiritually alive in the chaos of the modern world &#8211; John Mark Comer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who are you becoming? That was the question nagging pastor and author John Mark Comer. By outward metrics, everything appeared successful. But inwardly, things weren&#8217;t pretty. So he turned to a trusted mentor for guidance and heard these words: &#8216;Ruthlessly eliminate hurry from your life. Hurry is the great enemy of the spiritual life.&#8217; It wasn&#8217;t the response he expected, but it continues to be the answer he needs.    </p>
<p>                    Too often we treat the symptoms of toxicity in our modern world instead of trying to pinpoint the cause. A growing number of voices are pointing at hurry, or busyness as a root of much evil. Within the pages of this book, you&#8217;ll find a compelling emotional and spiritual case against hurry and in favour of a slower, simpler way of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ruthless-elimination-of-hurry-how-to-stay-emotionally-healthy-and-spiritually-alive-in-the-chaos-of-the-modern-world-john-mark-comer-abridged/">The Ruthless Elimination of Hurry : How to stay emotionally healthy and spiritually alive in the chaos of the modern world &#8211; John Mark Comer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hallelujah Anyway : Rediscovering Mercy &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hallelujah-anyway-rediscovering-mercy-anne-lamott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hallelujah-anyway-rediscovering-mercy-anne-lamott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Anne Lamott is my Oprah.&#8221; -Chicago Tribune The New York Times bestseller from the author of Dusk, Night, Dawn, Almost Everything and Bird by Bird, a powerful exploration of mercy and how we can embrace it. &#8220;Mercy is radical kindness,&#8221; Anne Lamott writes in her enthralling and heartening book, Hallelujah Anyway. It&#8217;s the permission you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hallelujah-anyway-rediscovering-mercy-anne-lamott-abridged/">Hallelujah Anyway : Rediscovering Mercy &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Anne Lamott is my Oprah.&#8221; -Chicago Tribune    </p>
<p>                    The New York Times bestseller from the author of Dusk, Night, Dawn, Almost Everything and Bird by Bird, a powerful exploration of mercy and how we can embrace it.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Mercy is radical kindness,&#8221; Anne Lamott writes in her enthralling and heartening book, Hallelujah Anyway. It&#8217;s the permission you give others-and yourself-to forgive a debt, to absolve the unabsolvable, to let go of the judgment and pain that make life so difficult.    </p>
<p>                    In Hallelujah Anyway: Rediscovering Mercy Lamott ventures to explore where to find meaning in life. We should begin, she suggests, by &#8220;facing a great big mess, especially the great big mess of ourselves.&#8221; It&#8217;s up to each of us to recognize the presence and importance of mercy everywhere-&#8220;within us and outside us, all around us&#8221;-and to use it to forge a deeper understanding of ourselves and more honest connections with each other. While that can be difficult to do, Lamott argues that it&#8217;s crucial, as &#8220;kindness towards others, beginning with myself, buys us a shot at a warm and generous heart, the greatest prize of all.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Full of Lamott&#8217;s trademark honesty, humor and forthrightness, Hallelujah Anyway is profound and caring, funny and wise-a hopeful book of hands-on spirituality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hallelujah-anyway-rediscovering-mercy-anne-lamott-abridged/">Hallelujah Anyway : Rediscovering Mercy &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
