<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sociolinguistics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sociolinguistics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sociolinguistics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sociolinguistics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sociolinguistics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Reader, Come Home : The Reading Brain in a Digital World &#8211; Maryanne Wolf (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed Proust and the Squid follows up with a lively, ambitious, and deeply informative book that considers the future of the reading brain and our capacity for critical thinking, empathy, and reflection as we become increasingly dependent on digital technologies. A decade ago, Maryanne Wolf&#8217;s Proust and the Squid revealed what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/">Reader, Come Home : The Reading Brain in a Digital World &#8211; Maryanne Wolf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed Proust and the Squid follows up with a lively, ambitious, and deeply informative book that considers the future of the reading brain and our capacity for critical thinking, empathy, and reflection as we become increasingly dependent on digital technologies.    </p>
<p>                    A decade ago, Maryanne Wolf&#8217;s Proust and the Squid revealed what we know about how the brain learns to read and how reading changes the way we think and feel. Since then, the ways we process written language have changed dramatically with many concerned about both their own changes and that of children. New research on the reading brain chronicles these changes in the brains of children and adults as they learn to read while immersed in a digitally dominated medium.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing deeply on this research, this book comprises a series of letters Wolf writes to us&#8211;her beloved readers&#8211;to describe her concerns and her hopes about what is happening to the reading brain as it unavoidably changes to adapt to digital mediums. Wolf raises difficult questions, including: Will children learn to incorporate the full range of deep reading processes that are at the core of the expert reading brain?Will the mix of a seemingly infinite set of distractions for children&#8217;s attention and their quick access to immediate, voluminous information alter their ability to think for themselves?With information at their fingertips, will the next generation learn to build their own storehouse of knowledge, which could impede the ability to make analogies and draw inferences from what they know?Will all these influences change the formation in children and the use in adults of slower cognitive processes like critical thinking, personal reflection, imagination, and empathy that comprise deep reading and that influence both how we think and how we live our lives?How can we preserve deep reading processes in future iterations of the reading brain?    </p>
<p>                    Concerns about attention span, critical reasoning, and over-reliance on technology are never just about children&#8211;Wolf herself has found that, though she is a reading expert, her ability to read deeply has been impacted as she has become increasingly dependent on screens.    </p>
<p>                    Wolf draws on neuroscience, literature, education, and philosophy and blends historical, literary, and scientific facts with down-to-earth examples and warm anecdotes to illuminate complex ideas that culminate in a proposal for a biliterate reading brain. Provocative and intriguing, Reader, Come Home is a roadmap that provides a cautionary but hopeful perspective on the impact of technology on our brains and our most essential intellectual capacities&#8211;and what this could mean for our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/">Reader, Come Home : The Reading Brain in a Digital World &#8211; Maryanne Wolf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities. In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities.     </p>
<p>                    In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our language carries secrets about our feelings, our self-concept, and our social intelligence. Our most forgettable words, such as pronouns and prepositions, can be the most revealing: their patterns are as distinctive as fingerprints.     </p>
<p>                    Using innovative analytic techniques, Pennebaker X-rays everything from John McCain&#8217;s tweets to the Federalist Papers. Who would have predicted that the high school student who uses too many verbs in her college admissions essay is likely to make lower grades in college? Or that a world leader&#8217;s use of pronouns could reliably presage whether he will lead his country into war? You&#8217;ll learn what Lady Gaga and William Butler Yeats have in common, and how Ebenezer Scrooge&#8217;s syntax hints at his self-deception and repressed emotion in this sprightly, surprising tour of what our words are saying-whether we mean them to or not.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Stuff of Thought : Language as a Window into Human Nature &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-stuff-of-thought-language-as-a-window-into-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-stuff-of-thought-language-as-a-window-into-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Stuff of Thought: Language as a Window into Human Nature, Steven Pinker looks at how the relationship between words and thoughts can help us understand who we are. Why do so many swear words involve topics like sex, bodily functions or the divine? Why do some children&#8217;s names thrive while others fall out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stuff-of-thought-language-as-a-window-into-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Stuff of Thought : Language as a Window into Human Nature &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Stuff of Thought: Language as a Window into Human Nature, Steven Pinker looks at how the relationship between words and thoughts can help us understand who we are.    </p>
<p>                      Why do so many swear words involve topics like sex, bodily functions or the divine? Why do some children&#8217;s names thrive while others fall out of favour? Why do we threaten and bribe and seduce in such elaborate, often comical ways? How can a choice of metaphor damn a politician or start a war? And why do we rarely say what we actually mean?     </p>
<p>                      Language, as Steven Pinker shows, is at the heart of our lives, and through the way we use it &#8211; whether to inform, persuade, entertain or manipulate &#8211; we can glimpse the very essence of what makes us human.     </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Awesome&#8217;<br />
                      Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Highly entertaining &#8230; funny and thought-provoking&#8217;<br />
                      The Times    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Anyone interested in language should read The Stuff of Thought &#8230; moments of genuine revelation and some very good jokes&#8217;<br />
                      Mark Haddon, Sunday Telegraph Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;No one writes about language as clearly as Steven Pinker, and this is his best book yet&#8217;<br />
                      David Crystal, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                      Steven Pinker is the Johnstone Family Professor in the Department of Psychology at Harvard University. Until 2003, he taught in the Department of Brain and Cognitive Sciences at MIT. He conducts research on language and cognition, writes for publications such as The New York Times, Time and Slate, and is the author of six books, including The Language Instinct, How the Mind Works and The Blank Slate.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stuff-of-thought-language-as-a-window-into-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Stuff of Thought : Language as a Window into Human Nature &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
