<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sports Psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sports-psychology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sports-psychology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sports Psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sports-psychology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Mindful Athlete : Secrets to Peak Performance &#8211; George Mumford (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-mindful-athlete-secrets-to-peak-performance-george-mumford-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mindful-athlete-secrets-to-peak-performance-george-mumford-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;George helped me understand the art of mindfulness. To be neither distracted or focused, rigid or flexible, passive or aggressive. I learned just to be. &#8211;Kobe Bryant Michael Jordan credits George Mumford with transforming his on-court leadership of the Bulls, helping Jordan lead the team to six NBA championships. Mumford also helped Kobe Bryant, Andrew [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mindful-athlete-secrets-to-peak-performance-george-mumford-abridged/">The Mindful Athlete : Secrets to Peak Performance &#8211; George Mumford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;George helped me understand the art of mindfulness. To be neither distracted or focused, rigid or flexible, passive or aggressive. I learned just to be. &#8211;Kobe Bryant    </p>
<p>                    Michael Jordan credits George Mumford with transforming his on-court leadership of the Bulls, helping Jordan lead the team to six NBA championships. Mumford also helped Kobe Bryant, Andrew Bynum, and Lamar Odom and countless other NBA players turn around their games. A widely respected public speaker and coach, Mumford is sharing his own story and the strategies that have made these athletes into stars in The Mindful Athlete: The Secret to Pure Performance. His proven, gentle but groundbreaking mindfulness techniques can transform the performance of anyone with a goal, be they an Olympian, weekend warrior, executive, hacker, or artist.     </p>
<p>                    When Michael Jordan left the Chicago Bulls to play baseball in 1993, the team was in crisis. Coach Phil Jackson, a long-time mindfulness practitioner, contacted Dr. Kabat-Zinn to find someone who could teach mindfulness techniques to the struggling team&#8211;someone who would have credibility and could speak the language of his players. Kabat-Zinn led Jackson to Mumford and their partnership began. Mumford has worked with Jackson and each of the eleven teams he coached to become NBA champions. His roster of champion clients has since blossomed way beyond basketball to include corporate executives, Olympians, and athletes in many different sports.     </p>
<p>                    With a charismatic teaching style that combines techniques of engaged mindfulness with lessons from popular culture icons such as Yoda, Indiana Jones, and Bruce Lee, Mumford tells illuminating stories about his larger than life clients. His writing is down-to-earth and easy to understand and apply. The Mindful Athlete is an engrossing story and an invaluable resource for anyone looking to elevate their game, no matter what the pursuit, and includes a foreword by Phil Jackson.     </p>
<p>                    Self-consciousness is when you&#8217;re focused on how you&#8217;re doing instead of what you&#8217;re doing. We have to learn how to push and challenge ourselves, but not in an insensitive way. Honing your performance really comes down to being comfortable with being uncomfortable.&#8211;George Mumford</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mindful-athlete-secrets-to-peak-performance-george-mumford-abridged/">The Mindful Athlete : Secrets to Peak Performance &#8211; George Mumford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Champions Think : In Sports and in Life &#8211; Dr. Bob Rotella, With Bob Cullen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-champions-think-in-sports-and-in-life-dr-bob-rotella-with-bob-cullen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Climbing & Mountaineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Golf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-champions-think-in-sports-and-in-life-dr-bob-rotella-with-bob-cullen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed sports psychologist Bob Rotella has advised everyone from professional golfers to NBA superstars to business executives on how to flourish under pressure and overcome challenges. &#8220;Rotella&#8217;s philosophy is astonishingly simple&#8230;his success rate&#8230;is phenomenal&#8221; (The New York Times). Now, for the first time, he&#8217;s distilled his decades of in-depth research and practical experience into a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-champions-think-in-sports-and-in-life-dr-bob-rotella-with-bob-cullen-abridged/">How Champions Think : In Sports and in Life &#8211; Dr. Bob Rotella, With Bob Cullen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed sports psychologist Bob Rotella has advised everyone from professional golfers to NBA superstars to business executives on how to flourish under pressure and overcome challenges. &#8220;Rotella&#8217;s philosophy is astonishingly simple&#8230;his success rate&#8230;is phenomenal&#8221; (The New York Times). Now, for the first time, he&#8217;s distilled his decades of in-depth research and practical experience into a potential-unlocking guide for everyone, from businesspeople to athletes to parents.<br />
                         Most psychology is focused on trying to make abnormal people normal. Bob Rotella&#8217;s work is to make normal people exceptional. How Champions Think takes readers inside the minds of winners in many fields. It explores how to keep the mind from holding you back, whatever your physical gifts or other talents. It&#8217;s about how to make a commitment, how to persevere, how to deal with failure. It&#8217;s about how to train your mind to create a self-image that promotes confidence and accomplishment.<br />
                         Any successful life starts with how you see yourself. And with these pearls of wisdom from the nation&#8217;s preeminent sports psychologist, you can learn to achieve the success of your dreams. &#8220;Straightforward and simple&#8230;Do the math. Read Rotella&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-champions-think-in-sports-and-in-life-dr-bob-rotella-with-bob-cullen-abridged/">How Champions Think : In Sports and in Life &#8211; Dr. Bob Rotella, With Bob Cullen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Box Thinking : Marginal Gains and the Secrets of High Performance &#8211; Matthew Syed, Matthew Syed Consulting Ltd (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/black-box-thinking-marginal-gains-and-the-secrets-of-high-performance-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-box-thinking-marginal-gains-and-the-secrets-of-high-performance-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times No.1 Bestseller From the Bestselling Author of Bounce What links the Mercedes Formula One team with Google? What links Team Sky and the aviation industry? What connects James Dyson and David Beckham? They are all Black Box Thinkers. Black Box Thinking is a new approach to high performance, a means of finding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-box-thinking-marginal-gains-and-the-secrets-of-high-performance-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/">Black Box Thinking : Marginal Gains and the Secrets of High Performance &#8211; Matthew Syed, Matthew Syed Consulting Ltd (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times No.1 Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    From the Bestselling Author of Bounce    </p>
<p>                    What links the Mercedes Formula One team with Google?    </p>
<p>                    What links Team Sky and the aviation industry?    </p>
<p>                    What connects James Dyson and David Beckham?    </p>
<p>                    They are all Black Box Thinkers.    </p>
<p>                    Black Box Thinking is a new approach to high performance, a means of finding an edge in a complex and fast-changing world. It is not just about sport, but has powerful implications for business and politics, as well as for parents and students. In other words, all of us.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on a dizzying array of case studies and real-world examples, together with cutting-edge research on marginal gains, creativity and grit, Matthew Syed tells the inside story of how success really happens &#8211; and how we cannot grow unless we are prepared to learn from our mistakes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-box-thinking-marginal-gains-and-the-secrets-of-high-performance-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/">Black Box Thinking : Marginal Gains and the Secrets of High Performance &#8211; Matthew Syed, Matthew Syed Consulting Ltd (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Endure : Mind, Body and the Curiously Elastic Limits of Human Performance &#8211; Alex Hutchinson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/endure-mind-body-and-the-curiously-elastic-limits-of-human-performance-alex-hutchinson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Track & Field Sports, Athletics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/endure-mind-body-and-the-curiously-elastic-limits-of-human-performance-alex-hutchinson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book is AMAZING!&#8217; &#8211; MALCOLM GLADWELL &#8216;If you want to gain insight into the mind of great athletes, adventurers, and peak performers then prepare to be enthralled by Alex Hutchinson&#8217;s Endure.&#8217; &#8211; BEAR GRYLLS How high or far or fast can humans go? And what about individual potential: what defines a person&#8217;s limits? From [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/endure-mind-body-and-the-curiously-elastic-limits-of-human-performance-alex-hutchinson-abridged/">Endure : Mind, Body and the Curiously Elastic Limits of Human Performance &#8211; Alex Hutchinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book is AMAZING!&#8217; &#8211; MALCOLM GLADWELL    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;If you want to gain insight into the mind of great athletes, adventurers, and peak performers then prepare to be enthralled by Alex Hutchinson&#8217;s Endure.&#8217; &#8211; BEAR GRYLLS    </p>
<p>                              How high or far or fast can humans go? And what about individual potential: what defines a person&#8217;s limits? From running a two-hour marathon to summiting Mount Everest, we&#8217;re fascinated by the extremes of human endurance, constantly testing both our physical and psychological limits.    </p>
<p>                              In Endure Alex Hutchinson, Ph.D., reveals why our individual limits may be determined as much by our head and heart, as by our muscles. He presents an overview of science&#8217;s search for understanding human fatigue, from crude experiments with electricity and frogs&#8217; legs to sophisticated brain imaging technology. Going beyond the traditional mechanical view of human limits, he instead argues that a key element in endurance is how the brain responds to distress signals-whether heat, or cold, or muscles screaming with lactic acid-and reveals that we can train to improve brain response.    </p>
<p>                              An elite distance runner himself, Hutchinson takes us to the forefront of the new sports psychology &#8211; brain electrode jolts, computer-based training, subliminal messaging &#8211; and presents startling new discoveries enhancing the performance of athletes today, showing us how anyone can utilize these tactics to bolster their own performance &#8211; and get the most out of their bodies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/endure-mind-body-and-the-curiously-elastic-limits-of-human-performance-alex-hutchinson-abridged/">Endure : Mind, Body and the Curiously Elastic Limits of Human Performance &#8211; Alex Hutchinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chasing Excellence : A Story About Building the World&#8217;s Fittest Athlete &#8211; Ben Bergeron (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chasing-excellence-a-story-about-building-the-worlds-fittest-athlete-ben-bergeron-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Track & Field Sports, Athletics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chasing-excellence-a-story-about-building-the-worlds-fittest-athlete-ben-bergeron-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CrossFit trainer Ben Bergeron has helped build the world&#8217;s fittest athletes, but he&#8217;s not like other coaches. He believes that greatness is not for the elite few; that winning is a result, not a goal; and that character, not talent, is what makes a true champion. His powerful philosophy can help anyone excel at all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chasing-excellence-a-story-about-building-the-worlds-fittest-athlete-ben-bergeron-abridged/">Chasing Excellence : A Story About Building the World&#8217;s Fittest Athlete &#8211; Ben Bergeron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CrossFit trainer Ben Bergeron has helped build the world&#8217;s fittest athletes, but he&#8217;s not like other coaches. He believes that greatness is not for the elite few; that winning is a result, not a goal; and that character, not talent, is what makes a true champion. His powerful philosophy can help anyone excel at all aspects of life.Using the dramatic competition between the top contenders at the 2016 Reebok CrossFit Games(R) as a background, Ben explores the step-by-step process of achieving excellence and the unique set of positive character traits necessary for leveling up to world-class. The mindset and methodology that have produced some of the greatest athletes in the world&#8217;s most gruelling sport can work equally well for golfers, lawyers, artists, entrepreneurs-anyone who&#8217;s willing to commit totally to becoming better than the best.By Chasing Excellence, you&#8217;ll discover how extraordinary it&#8217;s possible for you to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chasing-excellence-a-story-about-building-the-worlds-fittest-athlete-ben-bergeron-abridged/">Chasing Excellence : A Story About Building the World&#8217;s Fittest Athlete &#8211; Ben Bergeron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Your Brain on Sports : The Science of Underdogs, the Value of Rivalry, and What We Can Learn from the T-Shirt Cannon &#8211; L. Jon Wertheim, Sam Sommers (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-your-brain-on-sports-the-science-of-underdogs-the-value-of-rivalry-and-what-we-can-learn-from-the-t-shirt-cannon-l-jon-wertheim-sam-sommers-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sport & Leisure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-your-brain-on-sports-the-science-of-underdogs-the-value-of-rivalry-and-what-we-can-learn-from-the-t-shirt-cannon-l-jon-wertheim-sam-sommers-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is Your Brain on Sports is the book for sports fans searching for a deeper understanding of the games they watch and the people who play them. Sports Illustrated executive editor and bestselling author L. Jon Wertheim teams up with Tufts psychologist Sam Sommers to take readers on a wild ride into the inner [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-sports-the-science-of-underdogs-the-value-of-rivalry-and-what-we-can-learn-from-the-t-shirt-cannon-l-jon-wertheim-sam-sommers-abridged/">This Is Your Brain on Sports : The Science of Underdogs, the Value of Rivalry, and What We Can Learn from the T-Shirt Cannon &#8211; L. Jon Wertheim, Sam Sommers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is Your Brain on Sports is the book for sports fans searching for a deeper understanding of the games they watch and the people who play them. Sports Illustrated executive editor and bestselling author L. Jon Wertheim teams up with Tufts psychologist Sam Sommers to take readers on a wild ride into the inner world of sports. Through the prism of behavioral economics, neuroscience, and psychology, they reveal the hidden influences and surprising cues that inspire and derail us&#8211;on the field and in the stands&#8211;and by extension, in corporate board rooms, office settings, and our daily lives.     </p>
<p>                     In this irresistible narrative romp, Wertheim and Sommers usher us from professional football to the NBA to Grand Slam tennis, from the psychology of athletes self-handicapping their performance in the boxing ring or the World Series, to an explanation of why even the glimpse of a finish line can lift us beyond ordinary physical limits. They explore why Tom Brady and other starting NFL quarterbacks all seem to look like fashion models; why fans of teams like the Cubs, Mets, and any franchise from Cleveland love rooting for a loser; why the best players make the worst coaches; why hockey goons (and fans) would rather fight at home than on the road; and why the arena t-shirt cannon has something to teach us about human nature.     </p>
<p>                     In short, this book is an entertaining and thought-provoking journey into how psychology and behavioral science collide with the universe of wins-and-losses, coaching changes, underdogs, and rivalry games.     </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Boston Globe, Best Books of 2016, Sports</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-sports-the-science-of-underdogs-the-value-of-rivalry-and-what-we-can-learn-from-the-t-shirt-cannon-l-jon-wertheim-sam-sommers-abridged/">This Is Your Brain on Sports : The Science of Underdogs, the Value of Rivalry, and What We Can Learn from the T-Shirt Cannon &#8211; L. Jon Wertheim, Sam Sommers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Inner Game of Tennis : The Ultimate Guide to the Mental Side of Peak Performance &#8211; W Timothy Gallwey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-inner-game-of-tennis-the-ultimate-guide-to-the-mental-side-of-peak-performance-w-timothy-gallwey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-inner-game-of-tennis-the-ultimate-guide-to-the-mental-side-of-peak-performance-w-timothy-gallwey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Improve your game and discover your true potential by increasing your concentration, willpower and confidence. Described by Billie Jean King as her &#8216;tennis bible&#8217;, Timothy Gallwey&#8217;s multi-million bestseller, including an introduction from acclaimed sports psychologist Geoff Beattie, has been a phenomenon for players of all abilities since it was first published in 1972. Instead of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inner-game-of-tennis-the-ultimate-guide-to-the-mental-side-of-peak-performance-w-timothy-gallwey-abridged/">The Inner Game of Tennis : The Ultimate Guide to the Mental Side of Peak Performance &#8211; W Timothy Gallwey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Improve your game and discover your true potential by increasing your concentration, willpower and confidence.    </p>
<p>                    Described by Billie Jean King as her &#8216;tennis bible&#8217;, Timothy Gallwey&#8217;s multi-million bestseller, including an introduction from acclaimed sports psychologist Geoff Beattie, has been a phenomenon for players of all abilities since it was first published in 1972.    </p>
<p>                    Instead of concentrating on how to improve your technique, it starts from the understanding that &#8216;every game is composed of two parts, an outer game and an inner game&#8217;. The former is played against opponents on the court, but the latter is a battle within ourselves as we try and overcome self-doubt and anxiety. It is often won or lost before a ball has been hit.    </p>
<p>                      Gallwey&#8217;s revolutionary approach, built on a foundation of Zen thinking and humanistic psychology, will teach you how to develop your concentration, work on your gamesmanship and help you break bad habits. You will also learn how to trust yourself on the court and how to maintain clarity of mind throughout the match, giving you a clear psychological advantage over your opponent.    </p>
<p>                      Whether you are an amateur or a pro, The Inner Game of Tennis is essential reading for overcoming the self-doubt, nervousness, and lapses of concentration that can keep a player from winning. It is guaranteed to change the way you play tennis forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inner-game-of-tennis-the-ultimate-guide-to-the-mental-side-of-peak-performance-w-timothy-gallwey-abridged/">The Inner Game of Tennis : The Ultimate Guide to the Mental Side of Peak Performance &#8211; W Timothy Gallwey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sports Gene : Inside the Science of Extraordinary Athletic Performance &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sports-gene-inside-the-science-of-extraordinary-athletic-performance-david-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sports-gene-inside-the-science-of-extraordinary-athletic-performance-david-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller &#8211; with a new afterword about early specialization in youth sports &#8211; from the author of Range: Why Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World. The debate is as old as physical competition. Are stars like Usain Bolt, Michael Phelps, and Serena Williams genetic freaks put on Earth to dominate their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sports-gene-inside-the-science-of-extraordinary-athletic-performance-david-epstein-abridged/">The Sports Gene : Inside the Science of Extraordinary Athletic Performance &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller &#8211; with a new afterword about early specialization in youth sports &#8211; from the author of Range: Why Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World.     </p>
<p>                     The debate is as old as physical competition. Are stars like Usain Bolt, Michael Phelps, and Serena Williams genetic freaks put on Earth to dominate their respective sports? Or are they simply normal people who overcame their biological limits through sheer force of will and obsessive training?    </p>
<p>                     In this controversial and engaging exploration of athletic success and the so-called 10,000-hour rule, David Epstein tackles the great nature vs. nurture debate and traces how far science has come in solving it. Through on-the-ground reporting from below the equator and above the Arctic Circle, revealing conversations with leading scientists and Olympic champions, and interviews with athletes who have rare genetic mutations or physical traits, Epstein forces us to rethink the very nature of athleticism.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sports-gene-inside-the-science-of-extraordinary-athletic-performance-david-epstein-abridged/">The Sports Gene : Inside the Science of Extraordinary Athletic Performance &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boost! : How the Psychology of Sports Can Enhance Your Performance in Management and Work &#8211; Michael Bar-Eli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/boost-how-the-psychology-of-sports-can-enhance-your-performance-in-management-and-work-michael-bar-eli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boost-how-the-psychology-of-sports-can-enhance-your-performance-in-management-and-work-michael-bar-eli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To perform better in any situation &#8211; in your career, hobbies, relationships, or in any facet of your life &#8211; it is critical to develop psychological skills, which, just like physical abilities, can be taught, learned, and practiced. Both as individuals and as groups, we can tone these psychological skills and use them to heighten [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boost-how-the-psychology-of-sports-can-enhance-your-performance-in-management-and-work-michael-bar-eli-abridged/">Boost! : How the Psychology of Sports Can Enhance Your Performance in Management and Work &#8211; Michael Bar-Eli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To perform better in any situation &#8211; in your career, hobbies, relationships, or in any facet of your life &#8211; it is critical to develop psychological skills, which, just like physical abilities, can be taught, learned, and practiced. Both as individuals and as groups, we can tone these<br />
                    psychological skills and use them to heighten awareness, foster talents and technical abilities, and reach peak performance. Mental preparedness and psychological awareness are the keys to thriving in any environment.     </p>
<p>                    Few understand the importance of psychological skills better than the internationally recognized professor Michael Bar-Eli. As both a sports and organizational psychologist for more than 35 years, Bar-Eli has not only researched the science of performance but has also worked directly with elite<br />
                    athletes, coaches, and teams to help them improve their success on the court or field. Boost! takes the lessons he&#8217;s learned from sports psychology and translates them for leaders and managers at any stage in their career. With prescriptive advice, Bar-Eli illustrates how anyone can apply these<br />
                    lessons to better support and inspire co-workers and employees and create a sustainable, successful working environment and business.     </p>
<p>                    Boost! breaks down the complex behavioral science of getting ahead. Through original scientific research, unique case studies, and anecdotes from the world of sports and beyond, Bar-Eli explains the psychological underpinnings of human behavior and how we can harness this knowledge to perform at our<br />
                    highest levels, succeeding in our careers and personal lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boost-how-the-psychology-of-sports-can-enhance-your-performance-in-management-and-work-michael-bar-eli-abridged/">Boost! : How the Psychology of Sports Can Enhance Your Performance in Management and Work &#8211; Michael Bar-Eli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mind Gym &#8211; Gary Mack, David Casstevens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American Football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Baseball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Combat Sports & Self-defence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football (Soccer, Association Football)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Golf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gymnastics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ice-skating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multidiscipline Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olympic Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming & Diving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Track & Field Sports, Athletics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Volleyball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wrestling]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Mind Gym &#8220;Believing in yourself is paramount to success for any athlete. Gary&#8217;s lessons and David&#8217;s writing provide examples of the importance of the mental game.&#8221; &#8211;Ben Crenshaw, two-time Masters champion and former Ryder Cup captain &#8220;Mind Gym hits a home run. If you want to build mental muscle for the major leagues, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/">Mind Gym &#8211; Gary Mack, David Casstevens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Mind Gym    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Believing in yourself is paramount to success for any athlete. Gary&#8217;s lessons and David&#8217;s writing provide examples of the importance of the mental game.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Ben Crenshaw, two-time Masters champion and former Ryder Cup captain    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Mind Gym hits a home run. If you want to build mental muscle for the major leagues, read this book.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Ken Griffey Jr., Major League Baseball MVP    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I read Mind Gym on my way to the Sydney Olympics and really got a lot out of it. Gary has important lessons to teach, and you&#8217;ll find the exercises fun and beneficial.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Jason Kidd, NBA All-Star and Olympic gold-medal winner    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I love the book Mind Gym.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Madison Kocian, 2016 U.S. Women&#8217;s Gymnastics Team, 2015 Uneven Bars World Champion, as told to Us Weekly    </p>
<p>                    In Mind Gym, noted sports psychology consultant Gary Mack explains how your mind influences your performance on the field or on the court as much as your physical skill does, if not more so. Through forty accessible lessons and inspirational anecdotes from prominent athletes&#8211;many of whom he has worked with&#8211;you will learn the same techniques and exercises Mack uses to help elite athletes build mental &#8220;muscle.&#8221; Mind Gym will give you the &#8220;head edge&#8221; over the competition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/">Mind Gym &#8211; Gary Mack, David Casstevens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Captain Class : A New Theory of Leadership &#8211; Sam Walker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-captain-class-a-new-theory-of-leadership-sam-walker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-captain-class-a-new-theory-of-leadership-sam-walker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A bold new theory of leadership drawn from elite captains throughout sports&#8211;named one of the best business books of the year by CNBC, The New York Times, Forbes, strategy+business, The Globe and Mail, and Sports Illustrated &#8220;The book taught me that there&#8217;s no cookie-cutter way to lead. Leading is not just what Hollywood tells you. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-captain-class-a-new-theory-of-leadership-sam-walker-abridged/">The Captain Class : A New Theory of Leadership &#8211; Sam Walker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A bold new theory of leadership drawn from elite captains throughout sports&#8211;named one of the best business books of the year by CNBC, The New York Times, Forbes, strategy+business, The Globe and Mail,  and Sports Illustrated     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The book taught me that there&#8217;s no cookie-cutter way to lead. Leading is not just what Hollywood tells you. It&#8217;s not the big pregame speech. It&#8217;s how you carry yourself every day, how you treat the people around you, who you are as a person.&#8221;&#8211;Mitchell Trubisky, quarterback, Chicago Bears    </p>
<p>                    Now featuring analysis of the five-time Super Bowl champion New England Patriots and their captain, Tom Brady     </p>
<p>                    The seventeen most dominant teams in sports history had one thing in common: Each employed the same type of captain&#8211;a singular leader with an unconventional set of skills and tendencies. Drawing on original interviews with athletes, general managers, coaches, and team-building experts, Sam Walker identifies the seven core qualities of the Captain Class&#8211;from extreme doggedness and emotional control to tactical aggression and the courage to stand apart. Told through riveting accounts of pressure-soaked moments in sports history, The Captain Class will challenge your assumptions of what inspired leadership looks like.     </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Captain Class     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Wildly entertaining and thought-provoking . . . makes you reexamine long-held beliefs about leadership and the glue that binds winning teams together.&#8221;&#8211;Theo Epstein, president of baseball operations, Chicago Cubs     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;If you care about leadership, talent development, or the art of competition, you need to read this immediately.&#8221;&#8211;Daniel Coyle, author of The Culture Code     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The insights in this book are tremendous.&#8221;&#8211;Bob Myers, general manager, Golden State Warriors     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;An awesome book . . . I find myself relating a lot to its portrayal of the out-of the-norm leader.&#8221;&#8211;Carli Lloyd, co-captain, U.S. Soccer Women&#8217;s National Team     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A great read . . . Sam Walker used data and a systems approach to reach some original and unconventional conclusions about the kinds of leaders that foster enduring success. Most business and leadership books lapse into clichés. This one is fresh.&#8221;&#8211;Jeff Immelt, chairman and former CEO, General Electric      </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I can&#8217;t tell you how much I loved The Captain Class. It identifies something many people who&#8217;ve been around successful teams have felt but were never able to articulate. It has deeply affected my thoughts around how we build our culture.&#8221;&#8211;Derek Falvey, chief baseball officer, Minnesota Twins</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-captain-class-a-new-theory-of-leadership-sam-walker-abridged/">The Captain Class : A New Theory of Leadership &#8211; Sam Walker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Range : How Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/range-how-generalists-triumph-in-a-specialized-world-david-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/range-how-generalists-triumph-in-a-specialized-world-david-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating . . . If you&#8217;re a generalist who has ever felt overshadowed by your specialist colleagues, this book is for you&#8217; &#8211; Bill Gates The instant Sunday Times Top Ten and New York Times bestseller Shortlisted for the Financial Times/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award A Financial Times Essential Reads A powerful argument [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/range-how-generalists-triumph-in-a-specialized-world-david-epstein-abridged/">Range : How Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating . . . If you&#8217;re a generalist who has ever felt overshadowed by your specialist colleagues, this book is for you&#8217; &#8211; Bill Gates    </p>
<p>                    The instant Sunday Times Top Ten and New York Times bestseller<br />
                    Shortlisted for the Financial Times/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award<br />
                    A Financial Times Essential Reads    </p>
<p>                    A powerful argument for how to succeed in any field: develop broad interests and skills while everyone around you is rushing to specialize.     </p>
<p>                    From the &#8216;10,000 hours rule&#8217; to the power of Tiger parenting, we have been taught that success in any field requires early specialization and many hours of deliberate practice. And, worse, that if you dabble or delay, you&#8217;ll never catch up with those who got a head start.     </p>
<p>                    This is completely wrong.    </p>
<p>                    In this landmark book, David Epstein shows you that the way to succeed is by sampling widely, gaining a breadth of experiences, taking detours, experimenting relentlessly, juggling many interests &#8211; in other words, by developing range.    </p>
<p>                    Studying the world&#8217;s most successful athletes, artists, musicians, inventors and scientists, Epstein demonstrates why in most fields &#8211; especially those that are complex and unpredictable &#8211; generalists, not specialists are primed to excel. No matter what you do, where you are in life, whether you are a teacher, student, scientist, business analyst, parent, job hunter, retiree, you will see the world differently after you&#8217;ve read Range. You&#8217;ll understand better how we solve problems, how we learn and how we succeed. You&#8217;ll see why failing a test is the best way to learn and why frequent quitters end up with the most fulfilling careers.     </p>
<p>                    As experts silo themselves further while computers master more of the skills once reserved for highly focused humans, Range shows how people who think broadly and embrace diverse experiences and perspectives will increasingly thrive and why spreading your knowledge across multiple domains is the key to your success, and how to achieve it.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I loved Range&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Urgent and important. . . an essential read for bosses, parents, coaches, and anyone who cares about improving performance.&#8217; &#8211; Daniel H. Pink    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;So much crucial and revelatory information about performance, success, and education.&#8217; &#8211; Susan Cain, bestselling author of Quiet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/range-how-generalists-triumph-in-a-specialized-world-david-epstein-abridged/">Range : How Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
