<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Buddhist Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/buddhist-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/buddhist-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Buddhist Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/buddhist-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Radical Compassion : Learning to Love Yourself and Your World with the Practice of RAIN &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/radical-compassion-learning-to-love-yourself-and-your-world-with-the-practice-of-rain-tara-brach-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/radical-compassion-learning-to-love-yourself-and-your-world-with-the-practice-of-rain-tara-brach-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A powerful book that will free you from shame, fear, and negative self-beliefs. You will feel wiser, happier, and kinder after reading it&#8217; Haemin Sunim World-renowned meditation teacher Tara Brach shares a simple four-step practice to awaken compassion and release the grip of painful emotions: Recognize Allow Investigate Nurture Heartfelt and deeply practical, Radical Compassion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-compassion-learning-to-love-yourself-and-your-world-with-the-practice-of-rain-tara-brach-abridged/">Radical Compassion : Learning to Love Yourself and Your World with the Practice of RAIN &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A powerful book that will free you from shame, fear, and negative self-beliefs. You will feel wiser, happier, and kinder after reading it&#8217; Haemin Sunim     </p>
<p>                    World-renowned meditation teacher Tara Brach shares a simple four-step practice to awaken compassion and release the grip of painful emotions:    </p>
<p>                    Recognize<br />
                    Allow<br />
                    Investigate<br />
                    Nurture    </p>
<p>                    Heartfelt and deeply practical, Radical Compassion teaches us to find healing and freedom through the sources of love, courage and deep wisdom alive within us all.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Radical Compassion lays out a path of straightforward, accessible practices grounded in both modern brain science and ancient wisdom &#8230; a masterpiece&#8217; Rick Hanson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is a treasure from one of the most spiritual teachers of our time&#8217; Kristin Neff</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-compassion-learning-to-love-yourself-and-your-world-with-the-practice-of-rain-tara-brach-abridged/">Radical Compassion : Learning to Love Yourself and Your World with the Practice of RAIN &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Start Where You Are : How to Accept Yourself and Others &#8211; Pema Choedroen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/start-where-you-are-how-to-accept-yourself-and-others-pema-choedroen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/start-where-you-are-how-to-accept-yourself-and-others-pema-choedroen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Start Where You Are is an indispensable handbook for cultivating fearlessness and awakening a compassionate heart, from bestselling author Pema Choedroen. With insight and humour, she presents down-to-earth guidance on how to make friends with ourselves and develop genuine compassion towards others. This book shows how we can &#8216;start where we are&#8217; by embracing rather [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/start-where-you-are-how-to-accept-yourself-and-others-pema-choedroen-abridged/">Start Where You Are : How to Accept Yourself and Others &#8211; Pema Choedroen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Start Where You Are is an indispensable handbook for cultivating fearlessness and awakening a compassionate heart, from bestselling author Pema Choedroen. With insight and humour, she presents down-to-earth guidance on how to make friends with ourselves and develop genuine compassion towards others.    </p>
<p>                              This book shows how we can &#8216;start where we are&#8217; by embracing rather than denying the painful aspects of our lives.    </p>
<p>                              Pema Choedroen frames her teachings on compassion around fifty-nine traditional Tibetan Buddhist maxims, or slogans, such as: &#8216;Always apply a joyful state of mind&#8217;, &#8216;Always meditate on whatever provokes resentment&#8217; and &#8216;Be grateful to everyone&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                              Working with these slogans and through the practice of meditation, Start Where You Are shows how we can all develop the courage to work with our own inner pain and discover joy, well-being and confidence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/start-where-you-are-how-to-accept-yourself-and-others-pema-choedroen-abridged/">Start Where You Are : How to Accept Yourself and Others &#8211; Pema Choedroen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Advice Not Given : A Guide to Getting Over Yourself &#8211; Dr Mark Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/advice-not-given-a-guide-to-getting-over-yourself-dr-mark-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/advice-not-given-a-guide-to-getting-over-yourself-dr-mark-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our ego, and its accompanying sense of self-doubt, is one affliction we all share. And while our ego claims to have our best interests at heart, in its never-ending pursuit of attention and power, it sabotages the very goals it sets to achieve. In Advice Not Given, renowned psychiatrist and author Dr Mark Epstein reveals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/advice-not-given-a-guide-to-getting-over-yourself-dr-mark-epstein-abridged/">Advice Not Given : A Guide to Getting Over Yourself &#8211; Dr Mark Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our ego, and its accompanying sense of self-doubt, is one affliction we all share. And while our ego claims to have our best interests at heart, in its never-ending pursuit of attention and power, it sabotages the very goals it sets to achieve. In Advice Not Given, renowned psychiatrist and author Dr Mark Epstein reveals how Buddhism and Western psychotherapy both identify the ego as the limiting factor in our wellbeing and both come to the same conclusion: when we give the ego free rein, we suffer; but when it learns to let go, we are free.    </p>
<p>                    Our ego is at once our biggest obstacle and our greatest hope. We can be at its mercy or we can learn to mould it. Completely unique and practical, Epstein&#8217;s advice can be used by all, and will provide wise counsel in a confusing world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/advice-not-given-a-guide-to-getting-over-yourself-dr-mark-epstein-abridged/">Advice Not Given : A Guide to Getting Over Yourself &#8211; Dr Mark Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Love &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-love-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-love-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to Love is part of a charming series of books from Zen Master, Thich Nhat Hanh, exploring the essential foundations of mindful meditation and practise. How to Love shows that when we feel closer to our loved ones, we are also more connected to the world as a whole. Nhat Hanh brings his signature [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-love-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/">How To Love &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to Love is part of a charming series of books from Zen Master, Thich Nhat Hanh, exploring the essential foundations of mindful meditation and practise.     </p>
<p>                    How to Love shows that when we feel closer to our loved ones, we are also more connected to the world as a whole. Nhat Hanh brings his signature clarity, compassion and humour to the thorny question of how to love and distils one of our strongest emotions down to four essentials: you can only love another when you feel true love for yourself; love is understanding; understanding brings compassion; and deep listening and loving speech are key ways of showing our love.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-love-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/">How To Love &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Self, No Problem : How Neuropsychology is Catching Up to Buddhism &#8211; Chris Niebauer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-self-no-problem-how-neuropsychology-is-catching-up-to-buddhism-chris-niebauer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-self-no-problem-how-neuropsychology-is-catching-up-to-buddhism-chris-niebauer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While in grad school in the early 1990s, Chris Niebauer began to notice striking parallels between the latest discoveries in psychology, neuroscience, and the teachings of Buddhism, Taoism, and other schools of Eastern thought. When he presented his findings to a professor, his ideas were quickly dismissed as &#8220;pure coincidence, nothing more.&#8221; Fast-forward 20 years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-self-no-problem-how-neuropsychology-is-catching-up-to-buddhism-chris-niebauer-abridged/">No Self, No Problem : How Neuropsychology is Catching Up to Buddhism &#8211; Chris Niebauer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While in grad school in the early 1990s, Chris Niebauer began to notice striking parallels between the latest discoveries in psychology, neuroscience, and the teachings of Buddhism, Taoism, and other schools of Eastern thought. When he presented his findings to a professor, his ideas were quickly dismissed as &#8220;pure coincidence, nothing more.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Fast-forward 20 years later and Niebauer is a PhD and a tenured professor, and the Buddhist-neuroscience connection he found as a student is practically its own genre in the bookstore. But according to Niebauer, we are just beginning to understand the link between Eastern philosophy and the latest findings in psychology and neuroscience and what these assimilated ideas mean for the human experience.     </p>
<p>                    In this groundbreaking book, Niebauer writes that the latest research in neuropsychology is now confirming a fundamental tenet of Buddhism, what is called Anatta, or the doctrine of &#8220;no self.&#8221; Niebauer writes that our sense of self, or what we commonly refer to as the ego, is an illusion created entirely by the left side of the brain. Niebauer is quick to point out that this doesn&#8217;t mean that the self doesn&#8217;t exist but rather that it does so in the same way that a mirage in the middle of the desert exists, as a thought rather than a thing. His conclusions have significant ramifications for much of modern psychological modalities, which he says are spending much of their time trying to fix something that isn&#8217;t there.     </p>
<p>                    What makes this book unique is that Niebauer offers a series of exercises to allow the reader to experience this truth for him- or herself, as well as additional tools and practices to use after reading the book, all of which are designed to change the way we experience the world&#8211;a way that is based on being rather than thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-self-no-problem-how-neuropsychology-is-catching-up-to-buddhism-chris-niebauer-abridged/">No Self, No Problem : How Neuropsychology is Catching Up to Buddhism &#8211; Chris Niebauer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buddhism Plain and Simple &#8211; Steve Hagen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buddhism-plain-and-simple-steve-hagen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buddhism-plain-and-simple-steve-hagen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is a book about awareness &#8211; it&#8217;s about being &#8216;awake&#8217; and in touch with what is going on here and now. Practical and down-to-earth, it deals exclusively with the present, not with speculation, theory or belief in some far-off time and place. The teachings of the Buddha are plain and straightforward, and because they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buddhism-plain-and-simple-steve-hagen-abridged/">Buddhism Plain and Simple &#8211; Steve Hagen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a book about awareness &#8211; it&#8217;s about being &#8216;awake&#8217; and in touch with what is going on here and now. Practical and down-to-earth, it deals exclusively with the present, not with speculation, theory or belief in some far-off time and place. The teachings of the Buddha are plain and straightforward, and because they remain focused on the moment they are just as relevant now as they have ever been. BUDDHISM PLAIN AND SIMPLE is the book for anyone wanting to discover, or rediscover, the essence of Buddhism.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buddhism-plain-and-simple-steve-hagen-abridged/">Buddhism Plain and Simple &#8211; Steve Hagen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Radical Acceptance : Embracing Your Life With the Heart of a Buddha &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/radical-acceptance-embracing-your-life-with-the-heart-of-a-buddha-tara-brach-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/radical-acceptance-embracing-your-life-with-the-heart-of-a-buddha-tara-brach-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For many of us, feelings of deficiency are right around the corner. It doesn&#8217;t take much&#8211;just hearing of someone else&#8217;s accomplishments, being criticized, getting into an argument, making a mistake at work&#8211;to make us feel that we are not okay. Beginning to understand how our lives have become ensnared in this trance of unworthiness is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-acceptance-embracing-your-life-with-the-heart-of-a-buddha-tara-brach-abridged/">Radical Acceptance : Embracing Your Life With the Heart of a Buddha &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For many of us, feelings of deficiency are right around the corner. It doesn&#8217;t take much&#8211;just hearing of someone else&#8217;s accomplishments, being criticized, getting into an argument, making a mistake at work&#8211;to make us feel that we are not okay. Beginning to understand how our lives have become ensnared in this trance of unworthiness is our first step toward reconnecting with who we really are and what it means to live fully.<br />
                     &#8211;from Radical Acceptance     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Believing that something is wrong with us is a deep and tenacious suffering,&#8221; says Tara Brach at the start of this illuminating book. This suffering emerges in crippling self-judgments and conflicts in our relationships, in addictions and perfectionism, in loneliness and overwork&#8211;all the forces that keep our lives constricted and unfulfilled. Radical Acceptance offers a path to freedom, including the day-to-day practical guidance developed over Dr. Brach&#8217;s twenty years of work with therapy clients and Buddhist students.     </p>
<p>                     Writing with great warmth and clarity, Tara Brach brings her teachings alive through personal stories and case histories, fresh interpretations of Buddhist tales, and guided meditations. Step by step, she leads us to trust our innate goodness, showing how we can develop the balance of clear-sightedness and compassion that is the essence of Radical Acceptance. Radical Acceptance does not mean self-indulgence or passivity. Instead it empowers genuine change: healing fear and shame and helping to build loving, authentic relationships. When we stop being at war with ourselves, we are free to live fully every precious moment of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-acceptance-embracing-your-life-with-the-heart-of-a-buddha-tara-brach-abridged/">Radical Acceptance : Embracing Your Life With the Heart of a Buddha &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wherever You Go There You are &#8211; Jon Kabat-Zinn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No matter how busy you are, find quiet reflective moments in your life&#8211;and reduce your stress levels drastically&#8211;with this classic bestselling guide from a mindfulness expert. When Wherever You Go, There You Are was first published in 1994, no one could have predicted that the book would launch itself onto bestseller lists nationwide and sell [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/">Wherever You Go There You are &#8211; Jon Kabat-Zinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No matter how busy you are, find quiet reflective moments in your life&#8211;and reduce your stress levels drastically&#8211;with this classic bestselling guide from a mindfulness expert. When Wherever You Go, There You Are was first published in 1994, no one could have predicted that the book would launch itself onto bestseller lists nationwide and sell over 750,000 copies to date. Ten years later, the book continues to change lives. In honor of the book&#8217;s 10th anniversary, Hyperion is proud to be releasing the book with a new afterword by the author, and to share this wonderful book with an even larger audience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/">Wherever You Go There You are &#8211; Jon Kabat-Zinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
