<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Oncology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/oncology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/oncology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Oncology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/oncology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oncology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases. Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases.      </p>
<p>                    Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to identify the strategies and dosages for using food to transform your resilience and health in Eat to Beat Disease.     </p>
<p>                    We have radically underestimated our body&#8217;s power to transform and restore our health. Pioneering physician scientist, Dr. William Li, empowers readers by showing them the evidence behind over 200 health-boosting foods that can starve cancer, reduce your risk of dementia, and beat dozens of avoidable diseases. Eat to Beat Disease isn&#8217;t about what foods to avoid, but rather is a life-changing guide to the hundreds of healing foods to add to your meals that support the body&#8217;s defense systems, including: PlumsCinnamonJasmine teaRed wine and beerBlack BeansSan Marzano tomatoesOlive oilPacific oystersCheeses like Jarlsberg, Camembert and cheddarSourdough bread<br />
                    The book&#8217;s plan shows you how to integrate the foods you already love into any diet or health plan to activate your body&#8217;s health defense systems-Angiogenesis, Regeneration, Microbiome, DNA Protection, and Immunity-to fight cancer, diabetes, cardiovascular, neurodegenerative autoimmune diseases, and other debilitating conditions.     </p>
<p>                    Both informative and practical, Eat to Beat Disease explains the science of healing and prevention, the strategies for using food to actively transform health, and points the science of wellbeing and disease prevention in an exhilarating new direction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
