<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Environmental Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/environmental-economics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/environmental-economics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Environmental Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/environmental-economics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Information: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT    </p>
<p>                    We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need to be late.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master class &#8230; As a guide for perplexed Westerners, this book is very hard to beat &#8230; an honest, cohesive explanation for why the world is the way it is, without miracle cures or scapegoats&#8217; John Micklethwait, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; admirably honest &#8230; injects a badly needed dose of optimism into the modern debate&#8217; Gillian Tett, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;His main piece of advice for individuals, corporations, and countries is clear: Take a deep breath and adapt. This world isn&#8217;t going to wait for you&#8217; Fortune    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A humane and empathetic book&#8217; David Henkin, The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making the Modern World : Materials and Dematerialization &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Materials Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mechanical Engineering & Materials]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How much further should the affluent world push its material consumption? Does relative dematerialization lead to absolute decline in demand for materials? These and many other questions are discussed and answered in Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization. Over the course of time, the modern world has become dependent on unprecedented flows of materials. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Making the Modern World : Materials and Dematerialization &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How much further should the affluent world push its material consumption? Does relative dematerialization lead to absolute decline in demand for materials?  These and many other questions are discussed and answered in Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization. Over the course of time, the modern world has become dependent on unprecedented flows of materials. Now even the most efficient production processes and the highest practical rates of recycling may not be enough to result in dematerialization rates that would be high enough to negate the rising demand for materials generated by continuing population growth and rising standards of living. This book explores the costs of this dependence and the potential for substantial dematerialization of modern economies. Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization considers the principal materials used throughout history, from wood and stone, through to metals, alloys, plastics and silicon, describing their extraction and production as well as their dominant applications.<br />
                    The evolving productivities of material extraction, processing, synthesis, finishing and distribution, and the energy costs and environmental impact of rising material consumption are examined in detail. The book concludes with an outlook for the future, discussing the prospects for dematerialization and potential constrains on materials. This interdisciplinary text provides useful perspectives for readers with backgrounds including resource economics, environmental studies, energy analysis, mineral geology, industrial organization, manufacturing and material science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Making the Modern World : Materials and Dematerialization &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Drawdown : The Most Comprehensive Plan Ever Proposed to Roll Back Global Warming &#8211; Paul Hawken (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8211; New York Times bestseller &#8211; The 100 most substantive solutions to reverse global warming, based on meticulous research by leading scientists and policymakers around the world &#8220;At this point in time, the Drawdown book is exactly what is needed; a credible, conservative solution-by-solution narrative that we can do it. Reading it is an effective [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/">Drawdown : The Most Comprehensive Plan Ever Proposed to Roll Back Global Warming &#8211; Paul Hawken (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8211; New York Times bestseller &#8211;     </p>
<p>                    The 100 most substantive solutions to reverse global warming, based on meticulous research by leading scientists and policymakers around the world     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;At this point in time, the Drawdown book is exactly what is needed; a credible, conservative solution-by-solution narrative that we can do it. Reading it is an effective inoculation against the widespread perception of doom that humanity cannot and will not solve the climate crisis. Reported by-effects include increased determination and a sense of grounded hope.&#8221; &#8211;Per Espen Stoknes, Author, What We Think About When We Try Not To Think About Global Warming     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There&#8217;s been no real way for ordinary people to get an understanding of what they can do and what impact it can have. There remains no single, comprehensive, reliable compendium of carbon-reduction solutions across sectors. At least until now. . . . The public is hungry for this kind of practical wisdom.&#8221; &#8211;David Roberts, Vox    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is the ideal environmental sciences textbook&#8211;only it is too interesting and inspiring to be called a textbook.&#8221; &#8211;Peter Kareiva, Director of the Institute of the Environment and Sustainability, UCLA     </p>
<p>                    In the face of widespread fear and apathy, an international coalition of researchers, professionals, and scientists have come together to offer a set of realistic and bold solutions to climate change. One hundred techniques and practices are described here&#8211;some are well known; some you may have never heard of. They range from clean energy to educating girls in lower-income countries to land use practices that pull carbon out of the air. The solutions exist, are economically viable, and communities throughout the world are currently enacting them with skill and determination. If deployed collectively on a global scale over the next thirty years, they represent a credible path forward, not just to slow the earth&#8217;s warming but to reach drawdown, that point in time when greenhouse gases in the atmosphere peak and begin to decline. These measures promise cascading benefits to human health, security, prosperity, and well-being&#8211;giving us every reason to see this planetary crisis as an opportunity to create a just and livable world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/">Drawdown : The Most Comprehensive Plan Ever Proposed to Roll Back Global Warming &#8211; Paul Hawken (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
