<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>African History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/african-history/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/african-history/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>African History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/african-history/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Desert and the Sea : 977 Days Captive on the Somali Pirate Coast &#8211; Michael Scott Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-desert-and-the-sea-977-days-captive-on-the-somali-pirate-coast-michael-scott-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism, Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-desert-and-the-sea-977-days-captive-on-the-somali-pirate-coast-michael-scott-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Scott Moore, a journalist and the author of Sweetness and Blood, incorporates personal narrative and rigorous investigative journalism in this profound and revelatory memoir of his three-year captivity by Somali pirates-a riveting,thoughtful, and emotionally resonant exploration of foreign policy, religious extremism, and the costs of survival. In January 2012, having covered a Somali pirate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-desert-and-the-sea-977-days-captive-on-the-somali-pirate-coast-michael-scott-moore-abridged/">The Desert and the Sea : 977 Days Captive on the Somali Pirate Coast &#8211; Michael Scott Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Scott Moore, a journalist and the author of Sweetness and Blood, incorporates personal narrative and rigorous investigative journalism in this profound and revelatory memoir of his three-year captivity by Somali pirates-a riveting,thoughtful, and emotionally resonant exploration of foreign policy, religious extremism, and the costs of survival.    </p>
<p>                    In January 2012, having covered a Somali pirate trial in Hamburg for Spiegel Online International-and funded by a grant from the Pulitzer Center on Crisis Reporting-Michael Scott Moore traveled to the Horn of Africa to write about piracy and ways to end it. In a terrible twist of fate, Moore himself was kidnapped and subsequently held captive by Somali pirates. Subjected to conditions that break even the strongest spirits-physical injury, starvation, isolation, terror-Moore&#8217;s survival is a testament to his indomitable strength of mind. In September 2014, after 977 days, he walked free when his ransom was put together by the help of several US and German institutions, friends, colleagues, and his strong-willed mother.     </p>
<p>                    Yet Moore&#8217;s own struggle is only part of the story: The Desert and the Sea falls at the intersection of reportage, memoir, and history. Caught between Muslim pirates, the looming threat of Al-Shabaab, and the rise of ISIS, Moore observes the worlds that surrounded him-the economics and history of piracy; the effects of post-colonialism; the politics of hostage negotiation and ransom; while also conjuring the various faces of Islam-and places his ordeal in the context of the larger political and historical issues.               </p>
<p>                    A sort of Catch-22 meets Black Hawk Down, The Desert and the Sea is written with dark humor, candor, and a journalist&#8217;s clinical distance and eye for detail. Moore offers an intimate and otherwise inaccessible view of life as we cannot fathom it, brilliantly weaving his own experience as a hostage with the social, economic, religious, and political factors creating it. The Desert and the Sea is wildly compelling and a book that will take its place next to titles like Den of Lions and Even Silence Has an End.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-desert-and-the-sea-977-days-captive-on-the-somali-pirate-coast-michael-scott-moore-abridged/">The Desert and the Sea : 977 Days Captive on the Somali Pirate Coast &#8211; Michael Scott Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mighty Be Our Powers : How Sisterhood, Prayer, and Sex Changed a Nation at War &#8211; Carol Mithers, Leymah Gbowee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The winner of the Nobel Peace Prize shares her inspirational, powerful story of how a group of women working together created an unstoppable force that brought peace to Liberia. As a young woman, Leymah Gbowee was broken by the Liberian civil war, a brutal conflict that destroyed her country and claimed the lives of countless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/">Mighty Be Our Powers : How Sisterhood, Prayer, and Sex Changed a Nation at War &#8211; Carol Mithers, Leymah Gbowee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The winner of the Nobel Peace Prize shares her inspirational, powerful story of how a group of women working together created an unstoppable force that brought peace to Liberia.     </p>
<p>                     As a young woman, Leymah Gbowee was broken by the Liberian civil war, a brutal conflict that destroyed her country and claimed the lives of countless relatives and friends. Propelled by her realization that it is women and girls who suffer most during conflicts, she found the courage to turn her bitterness into action.     </p>
<p>                     She helped organize and then lead the Liberian Mass Action for Peace, which brought together Christian and Muslim women in a nonviolent movement that engaged in public protest, confronted Liberia&#8217;s ruthless president and rebel warlords, and even held a sex strike.     </p>
<p>                     With an army of women, Gbowee helped lead her nation to peace-and became an international leader who changed history, won the Nobel Peace Prize for her work, and fiercely advocates for girls&#8217; empowerment and leadership. Mighty Be Our Powers is the gripping chronicle of a journey from hopelessness to liberation that will touch all who dream of a better world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/">Mighty Be Our Powers : How Sisterhood, Prayer, and Sex Changed a Nation at War &#8211; Carol Mithers, Leymah Gbowee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Congo from Leopold to Kabila : A People&#8217;s History &#8211; Georges Nzongola-Ntalaja (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-congo-from-leopold-to-kabila-a-peoples-history-georges-nzongola-ntalaja-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-congo-from-leopold-to-kabila-a-peoples-history-georges-nzongola-ntalaja-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The people of the Congo have suffered from a particularly brutal colonial rule, American interference after independence, decades of robbery at the hands of the dictator Mobutu and periodic warfare which continues even now in the East of the country. But, as this insightful political history makes clear, the Congolese people have not taken these [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-congo-from-leopold-to-kabila-a-peoples-history-georges-nzongola-ntalaja-abridged/">The Congo from Leopold to Kabila : A People&#8217;s History &#8211; Georges Nzongola-Ntalaja (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The people of the Congo have suffered from a particularly brutal colonial rule, American interference after independence, decades of robbery at the hands of the dictator Mobutu and periodic warfare which continues even now in the East of the country. But, as this insightful political history makes clear, the Congolese people have not taken these multiple oppressions lying down and have fought over many years to establish democratic institutions at home and free themselves from foreign exploitation; indeed these are two aspects of a single project.    </p>
<p>                    Professor Nzongola-Ntalaja is one of his country&#8217;s leading intellectuals and his panoramic understanding of the personalities and events, as well as class, ethnic and other factors, make his book a lucid, radical and utterly unromanticized account of his countrymen&#8217;s struggle. His people&#8217;s defeat and the state&#8217;s post-colonial crisis are seen as resulting from a post-independence collapse of the anti-colonial alliance between the masses and the national leadership .    </p>
<p>                    This book is essential reading for understanding what is happening in the Congo and the Great Lakes region under the rule of the late President Kabila, and now his son. It will also stand as a milestone in how to write the modern political history of Africa.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-congo-from-leopold-to-kabila-a-peoples-history-georges-nzongola-ntalaja-abridged/">The Congo from Leopold to Kabila : A People&#8217;s History &#8211; Georges Nzongola-Ntalaja (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rift : A New Africa Breaks Free &#8211; Alex Perry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rift-a-new-africa-breaks-free-alex-perry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rift-a-new-africa-breaks-free-alex-perry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Taking the Great Rift Valley &#8211; the geological fault that will eventually tear Africa in two &#8211; as his central metaphor, Alex Perry explores the split between a resurgent Africa and a world at odds with its rise. Africa has long been misunderstood &#8211; and abused &#8211; by outsiders. Perry travelled the continent for most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rift-a-new-africa-breaks-free-alex-perry-abridged/">The Rift : A New Africa Breaks Free &#8211; Alex Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Taking the Great Rift Valley &#8211; the geological fault that will eventually tear Africa in two &#8211; as his central metaphor, Alex Perry explores the split between a resurgent Africa and a world at odds with its rise. Africa has long been misunderstood &#8211; and abused &#8211; by outsiders. Perry travelled the continent for most of a decade, meeting with entrepreneurs and warlords, professors and cocaine smugglers, presidents and jihadis, among many others.    </p>
<p>                    Opening with a devastating investigation into a largely unreported war crime in Somalia in 2011, he finds Africa at a moment of furious self-assertion. This is a remade continent, defiantly rising from centuries of oppression to become an economic and political titan: where cash is becoming a thing of the past, where astronomers are unlocking the origin of life and where, twenty-five years after Live Aid, Ethiopia&#8217;s first yuppies are traders on an electronic food exchange. Yet, as Africa finally wins the substance of its freedom, it must confront the three last false prophets of Islamists, dictators and aid workers, who would keep it in its bonds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rift-a-new-africa-breaks-free-alex-perry-abridged/">The Rift : A New Africa Breaks Free &#8211; Alex Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China&#8217;s Second Continent : How a Million Migrants Are Building a New Empire in Africa &#8211; Howard W. French (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Migration, Immigration & Emigration]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book Chinese immigrants of the recent past and unfolding twenty-first century are in search of the African dream. So explains indefatigable traveler Howard W. French, prize-winning investigative journalist and former New York Times bureau chief in Africa and China, in the definitive account of this seismic geopolitical development. China&#8217;s burgeoning [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/">China&#8217;s Second Continent : How a Million Migrants Are Building a New Empire in Africa &#8211; Howard W. French (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book     </p>
<p>                    Chinese immigrants of the recent past and unfolding twenty-first century are in search of the African dream. So explains indefatigable traveler Howard W. French, prize-winning investigative journalist and former New York Times bureau chief in Africa and China, in the definitive account of this seismic geopolitical development. China&#8217;s burgeoning presence in Africa is already shaping, and reshaping, the future of millions of people. From Liberia to Senegal to Mozambique, in creaky trucks and by back roads, French introduces us to the characters who make up China&#8217;s dogged emigrant population: entrepreneurs singlehandedly reshaping African infrastructure, and less-lucky migrants barely scraping by but still convinced of Africa&#8217;s opportunities. French&#8217;s acute observations offer illuminating insight into the most pressing unknowns of modern Sino-African relations: Why China is making these cultural and economic incursions into the continent; what Africa&#8217;s role is in this equation; and what the ramifications for both parties and their people&#8211;and the watching world&#8211;will be in the foreseeable future.     </p>
<p>                    One of the Best Books of the Year at &#8211; The Economist &#8211; The Guardian &#8211; Foreign Affairs</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/">China&#8217;s Second Continent : How a Million Migrants Are Building a New Empire in Africa &#8211; Howard W. French (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A History of Nigeria &#8211; Toyin Falola, Matthew M. Heaton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-history-of-nigeria-toyin-falola-matthew-m-heaton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-history-of-nigeria-toyin-falola-matthew-m-heaton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nigeria is Africa&#8217;s most populous country and the world&#8217;s eighth largest oil producer, but its success has been undermined in recent decades by ethnic and religious conflict, political instability, rampant official corruption and an ailing economy. Toyin Falola, a leading historian intimately acquainted with the region, and Matthew Heaton, who has worked extensively on African [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-history-of-nigeria-toyin-falola-matthew-m-heaton-abridged/">A History of Nigeria &#8211; Toyin Falola, Matthew M. Heaton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nigeria is Africa&#8217;s most populous country and the world&#8217;s eighth largest oil producer, but its success has been undermined in recent decades by ethnic and religious conflict, political instability, rampant official corruption and an ailing economy. Toyin Falola, a leading historian intimately acquainted with the region, and Matthew Heaton, who has worked extensively on African science and culture, combine their expertise to explain the context to Nigeria&#8217;s recent troubles through an exploration of its pre-colonial and colonial past, and its journey from independence to statehood. By examining key themes such as colonialism, religion, slavery, nationalism and the economy, the authors show how Nigeria&#8217;s history has been swayed by the vicissitudes of the world around it, and how Nigerians have adapted to meet these challenges. This book offers a unique portrayal of a resilient people living in a country with immense, but unrealized, potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-history-of-nigeria-toyin-falola-matthew-m-heaton-abridged/">A History of Nigeria &#8211; Toyin Falola, Matthew M. Heaton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strength in What Remains &#8211; Tracy Kidder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/strength-in-what-remains-tracy-kidder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/strength-in-what-remains-tracy-kidder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY: Los Angeles Times &#8211; San Francisco Chronicle -Chicago Tribune &#8211; The Christian Science Monitor &#8211; Publishers Weekly In Strength in What Remains, Tracy Kidder gives us the story of one man&#8217;s inspiring American journey and of the ordinary people who helped him, providing brilliant testament [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strength-in-what-remains-tracy-kidder-abridged/">Strength in What Remains &#8211; Tracy Kidder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY:<br />
                    Los Angeles Times &#8211; San Francisco Chronicle -Chicago Tribune &#8211; The Christian Science Monitor &#8211; Publishers Weekly     </p>
<p>                    In Strength in What Remains,  Tracy Kidder gives us the story of one man&#8217;s inspiring American journey and of the ordinary people who helped him, providing brilliant testament to the power of second chances. Deo arrives in the United States from Burundi in search of a new life. Having survived a civil war and genocide, he lands at JFK airport with two hundred dollars, no English, and no contacts. He ekes out a precarious existence delivering groceries, living in Central Park, and learning English by reading dictionaries in bookstores. Then Deo begins to meet the strangers who will change his life, pointing him eventually in the direction of Columbia University, medical school, and a life devoted to healing. Kidder breaks new ground in telling this unforgettable story as he travels with Deo back over a turbulent life and shows us what it means to be fully human.     </p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Named one of the Top 10 Nonfiction Books of the year by Time &#8211; Named one of the year&#8217;s &#8220;10 Terrific Reads&#8221; by O: The Oprah Magazine     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Extraordinarily stirring . . . a miracle of human courage.&#8221;&#8211;The Washington Post     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Absorbing . . . a story about survival, about perseverance and sometimes uncanny luck in the face of hell on earth. . . . It is just as notably about profound human kindness.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Important and beautiful . . . This book is one you won&#8217;t forget.&#8221;&#8211;Portland Oregonian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strength-in-what-remains-tracy-kidder-abridged/">Strength in What Remains &#8211; Tracy Kidder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
