<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Retail Sector Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/retail-sector/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/retail-sector/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Retail Sector Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/retail-sector/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Rule of Logistics : Walmart and the Architecture of Fulfillment &#8211; Jesse LeCavalier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rule-of-logistics-walmart-and-the-architecture-of-fulfillment-jesse-lecavalier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Building Construction & Materials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Buildings: Civic, Commercial, Industrial, Etc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rule-of-logistics-walmart-and-the-architecture-of-fulfillment-jesse-lecavalier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every time you wheel a shopping cart through one of Walmart&#8217;s more than 10,000 stores worldwide, or swipe your credit card or purchase something online, you enter a mind-boggling logistical regime. Even if you&#8217;ve never shopped at Walmart, its logistics have probably affected your life. The Rule of Logistics makes sense of its spatial and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rule-of-logistics-walmart-and-the-architecture-of-fulfillment-jesse-lecavalier-abridged/">The Rule of Logistics : Walmart and the Architecture of Fulfillment &#8211; Jesse LeCavalier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every time you wheel a shopping cart through one of Walmart&#8217;s more than 10,000 stores worldwide, or swipe your credit card or purchase something online, you enter a mind-boggling logistical regime. Even if you&#8217;ve never shopped at Walmart, its logistics have probably affected your life. The Rule of Logistics makes sense of its spatial and architectural ramifications by analyzing the stores, distribution centers, databases, and inventory practices of the world&#8217;s largest corporation.    </p>
<p>                    The Rule of Logistics tells the story of Walmart&#8217;s buildings in the context of the corporation&#8217;s entire operation, itself characterized by an obsession with logistics. Beginning with the company&#8217;s founding in 1962, Jesse LeCavalier reveals how logistics-as a branch of knowledge, an area of work, and a collection of processes-takes shape and changes our built environment. Weaving together archival material with original drawings, LeCavalier shows how a diverse array of ideas, people, and things-military theory and chewing gum, Howard Dean and satellite networks, Hudson River School painters and real estate software, to name a few-are all connected through Walmart&#8217;s logistical operations and in turn are transforming how its buildings are conceptualized, located, built, and inhabited.    </p>
<p>                    A major new contribution to architectural history and theory, The Rule of Logistics helps us understand how retailing today is changing our bodies, brains, buildings, and cities and predicts what future forms architecture might take when shaped by systems that exceed its current capacities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rule-of-logistics-walmart-and-the-architecture-of-fulfillment-jesse-lecavalier-abridged/">The Rule of Logistics : Walmart and the Architecture of Fulfillment &#8211; Jesse LeCavalier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to convert website visitors into customers Part science and part art, conversion optimization is designed to turn visitors into customers. Carefully developed testing procedures are necessary to help you fine-tune images, headlines, navigation, colors, buttons, and every other element, creating a website that encourages visitors to take the action you seek. This book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/">You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to convert website visitors into customers Part science and part art, conversion optimization is designed to turn visitors into customers. Carefully developed testing procedures are necessary to help you fine-tune images, headlines, navigation, colors, buttons, and every other element, creating a website that encourages visitors to take the action you seek. This book guides you through creating an optimization strategy that supports your business goals, using appropriate analytics tools, generating quality testing ideas, running online experiments, and making the adjustments that work.<br />
                    * Conversion optimization is part science and part art; this guide provides step-by-step guidance to help you optimize your website for maximum conversion rates * Explains how to analyze data, prioritize experiment opportunities, and choose the right testing methods * Helps you learn what to adjust, how to do it, and how to analyze the results * Features hands-on exercises, case studies, and a full-color insert reinforcing key tactics * Author has used these techniques to assist Fortune 500 clients You Should Test That explains both the &#8220;why&#8221; and the &#8220;how&#8221; of conversion optimization, helping you maximize the value of your website.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/">You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Walton : Made In America &#8211; Sam Walton, Contributions by John Huey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meet a genuine American folk hero cut from the homespun cloth of America&#8217;s heartland: Sam Walton, who parlayed a single dime store in a hardscrabble cotton town into Wal-Mart, the largest retailer in the world. The undisputed merchant king of the late twentieth century, Sam never lost the common touch. Here, finally, inimitable words. Genuinely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/">Sam Walton : Made In America &#8211; Sam Walton, Contributions by John Huey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meet a genuine American folk hero cut from the homespun cloth of America&#8217;s heartland: Sam Walton, who parlayed a single dime store in a hardscrabble cotton town into Wal-Mart, the largest retailer in the world. The undisputed merchant king of the late twentieth century, Sam never lost the common touch. Here, finally, inimitable words. Genuinely modest, but always sure if his ambitions and achievements. Sam shares his thinking in a candid, straight-from-the-shoulder style.     </p>
<p>                    In a story rich with anecdotes and the &#8220;rules of the road&#8221; of both Main Street and Wall Street, Sam Walton chronicles the inspiration, heart, and optimism that propelled him to lasso the American Dream.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/">Sam Walton : Made In America &#8211; Sam Walton, Contributions by John Huey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever. From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business     </p>
<p>                    Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever.    </p>
<p>                    From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the go-to guide to building a solid small-business by establishing a loyal audience before you sell any products or services. In these pages, Joe Pulizzi provides a lower-risk, better way to build a successful business by re-engineering the process that so often leads to failure: You&#8217;ll learn how to develop valuable content, build an audience around that content-and then create a product for that audience. Content Inc. walks you through the entire process, showing how to    </p>
<p>                    Identify the intersection of your expertise and your future customer&#8217;s needs<br />
                    Determine how to &#8220;tilt&#8221; your sweet spot to find a place where little or no competition exists<br />
                    Establish your number-one channel for disseminating content (blog, podcast, YouTube, etc.)<br />
                    Use social-media and SEO to convert one-time visitors into long-term subscribers<br />
                    Grow your business by expanding into multiple delivery channels<br />
                    Monetize your product or service for ultimate business success<br />
                    Understand how to sell your content asset for millions or build the business into a large enterprise    </p>
<p>                    This fully updated edition includes new and enhanced coverage of platforms like TikTok, SnapChat, and Instagram, a new section about the exit strategy for the model, more practical how-tos, and current examples of companies that have successfully implemented these strategies.      </p>
<p>                    Apply the methods laid out for you in Content Inc., and before you know it, you&#8217;ll be running your own profitable, scalable business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s business world, it takes more than a website to stay competitive. The smartest, most successful companies are using radically new membership models, subscription-based formats, and freemium pricing structures to grow their customer base-and explode their market valuation-in the most disruptive shift in business since the Industrial Revolution. This is The Membership Economy. Written [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/">The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s business world, it takes more than a website to stay competitive. The smartest, most successful companies are using radically new membership models, subscription-based formats, and freemium pricing structures to grow their customer base-and explode their market valuation-in the most disruptive shift in business since the Industrial Revolution.    </p>
<p>                    This is The Membership Economy.    </p>
<p>                     Written by an expertconsultant, this groundbreaking book will show you how to turn ordinary customers into members for life. Learn how to:    </p>
<p>                     Turn digital subscriptions into forever sales Build an online community your customers will loveDevelop new loyalty programs that really pay offTransform freemium users into superusers Create a self-generating revenue stream Keep memberships and profits growing for years to come<br />
                    Whether you&#8217;re a small business with limited resources, an established company using a traditional business model, or a hungry start-up who wants a bigger bang for your buck, this comprehensive guide provides a wealth of membership-building options to suit every need.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll learn the best-kept secrets of top industry leaders, from global giants like Am Ex and Weight Watchers to smaller dot-com successes like SurveyMonkey and Pandora. You&#8217;ll find proven strategies for creating membership programs for everything from vacation timeshares and car rentals to video streaming and Software-as-a-Service.    </p>
<p>                     Most importantly, you&#8217;ll discover what works, and what doesn&#8217;t, from some of the key players in the new membership economy. It&#8217;s not about ownership; it&#8217;s about access, options, and freedom.    </p>
<p>                    When you join forces with your customers, membership has its rewards-for you, your company, and your continued success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/">The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walmart : Key Insights and Practical Lessons from the World&#8217;s Largest Retailer &#8211; Bryan Roberts, Natalie Berg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multinationals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Purchasing & Supply Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Walmart provides a detailed assessment of the world&#8217;s largest retailer that forever changed the face of retailing. The book examines Walmart&#8217;s successes, failures, and whether it can stay ahead for the next 50 years. Despite being a source for best practice in procurement, logistics, systems and store format innovation, the retail giant is now facing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/">Walmart : Key Insights and Practical Lessons from the World&#8217;s Largest Retailer &#8211; Bryan Roberts, Natalie Berg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Walmart provides a detailed assessment of the world&#8217;s largest retailer that forever changed the face of retailing. The book examines Walmart&#8217;s successes, failures, and whether it can stay ahead for the next 50 years. Despite being a source for best practice in procurement, logistics, systems and store format innovation, the retail giant is now facing several issues that affect its future development. Starting from its inception in rural Arkansas in 1962, this objective analysis of Walmart&#8217;s history addresses the rapid change of retail, including the rise of e-commerce and multi-channel retailing; Walmart International and its &#8216;everyday low prices&#8217; philosophy; the saturation of the superstore format, and much more.     </p>
<p>                    In a time of rapid change, will the world&#8217;s largest retailer be able to reconfigure? Walmart provides the necessary insights for retailers, advertisers, other business professionals and students to understand how Walmart became a retail giant, the lessons that can be learned, and what is in store for the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/">Walmart : Key Insights and Practical Lessons from the World&#8217;s Largest Retailer &#8211; Bryan Roberts, Natalie Berg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rethinking Prestige Branding : Secrets of the Ueber-Brands &#8211; Wolfgang Schaefer, JP Kuehlwein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rethinking-prestige-branding-secrets-of-the-ueber-brands-wolfgang-schaefer-jp-kuehlwein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rethinking-prestige-branding-secrets-of-the-ueber-brands-wolfgang-schaefer-jp-kuehlwein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What makes someone covet a Kelly bag? Why are Cirque Du Soleil or Grey Goose so successful despite breaking all the conventions of their categories? What does Gucci&#8217;s approach to marketing have in common with Nespresso&#8217;s? And why do some people pay a relative fortune for Renova toilet paper or Aesop detergent even though they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rethinking-prestige-branding-secrets-of-the-ueber-brands-wolfgang-schaefer-jp-kuehlwein-abridged/">Rethinking Prestige Branding : Secrets of the Ueber-Brands &#8211; Wolfgang Schaefer, JP Kuehlwein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What makes someone covet a Kelly bag? Why are Cirque Du Soleil or Grey Goose so successful despite breaking all the conventions of their categories? What does Gucci&#8217;s approach to marketing have in common with Nespresso&#8217;s? And why do some people pay a relative fortune for Renova toilet paper or Aesop detergent even though they hardly ever &#8216;advertise&#8217; and seem to have none of the &#8216;functional performance advantages&#8217; conventional marketers would seek to demonstrate? Prestige brand experts JP Kuehlwein and Wolfgang Schaefer have dedicated themselves to studying what drives the success of prestige brands. Rethinking Prestige Branding collects their insights.    </p>
<p>                    Uncovering the secrets of why and how some brands are created more equal than others, Rethinking Prestige Branding  includes over 100 case studies from Apple and Abercrombie &#038; Fitch to Tate Modern and Tesla. Rather than re-telling brand success stories or re-hashing long-standing marketing principles, it takes readers on a colourful journey behind the scenes of today&#8217;s marketing pros. This book will fascinate marketing professional just as much as those who are simply curious as to how premium brands tick.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rethinking-prestige-branding-secrets-of-the-ueber-brands-wolfgang-schaefer-jp-kuehlwein-abridged/">Rethinking Prestige Branding : Secrets of the Ueber-Brands &#8211; Wolfgang Schaefer, JP Kuehlwein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Rules : How to Create Killer Blogs, Podcasts, Videos, Ebooks, Webinars (and More) That Engage Customers and Ignite Your Business &#8211; Ann Handley, C. C. Chapman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/content-rules-how-to-create-killer-blogs-podcasts-videos-ebooks-webinars-and-more-that-engage-customers-and-ignite-your-business-ann-handley-c-c-chapman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/content-rules-how-to-create-killer-blogs-podcasts-videos-ebooks-webinars-and-more-that-engage-customers-and-ignite-your-business-ann-handley-c-c-chapman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The guide to creating engaging web content and building a loyal following, revised and updated Blogs, YouTube, Facebook, Twitter, Google+, and other platforms are giving everyone a &#8220;voice,&#8221; including organizations and their customers. So how do you create the stories, videos, and blog posts that cultivate fans, arouse passion for your products or services, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-rules-how-to-create-killer-blogs-podcasts-videos-ebooks-webinars-and-more-that-engage-customers-and-ignite-your-business-ann-handley-c-c-chapman-abridged/">Content Rules : How to Create Killer Blogs, Podcasts, Videos, Ebooks, Webinars (and More) That Engage Customers and Ignite Your Business &#8211; Ann Handley, C. C. Chapman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The guide to creating engaging web content and building a loyal following, revised and updated Blogs, YouTube, Facebook, Twitter, Google+, and other platforms are giving everyone a &#8220;voice,&#8221; including organizations and their customers. So how do you create the stories, videos, and blog posts that cultivate fans, arouse passion for your products or services, and ignite your business? Content Rules equips you for online success as a one-stop source on the art and science of developing content that people care about. This coverage is interwoven with case studies of companies successfully spreading their ideas online and using them to establish credibility and build a loyal customer base.<br />
                    * Find an authentic &#8220;voice&#8221; and craft bold content that will resonate with prospects and buyers and encourage them to share it with others * Leverage social media and social tools to get your content and ideas distributed as widely as possible * Understand why you are generating content getting to the meat of your message in practical, commonsense language, and defining the goals of your content strategy * Write in a way that powerfully communicates your service, product, or message across various Web mediums * Boost your online presence and engage with customers and prospects like never before with Content Rules.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-rules-how-to-create-killer-blogs-podcasts-videos-ebooks-webinars-and-more-that-engage-customers-and-ignite-your-business-ann-handley-c-c-chapman-abridged/">Content Rules : How to Create Killer Blogs, Podcasts, Videos, Ebooks, Webinars (and More) That Engage Customers and Ignite Your Business &#8211; Ann Handley, C. C. Chapman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon : How the World&#8217;s Most Relentless Retailer will Continue to Revolutionize Commerce &#8211; Natalie Berg, Miya Knights (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is the secret to Amazon&#8217;s success? What does the ecommerce giant have in store for the future? Explore the disruptive new retail strategies of the world&#8217;s most relentless retailer and gain valuable lessons that can be applied to any business in the ecommerce sector, with original insight from the company as it continues to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/">Amazon : How the World&#8217;s Most Relentless Retailer will Continue to Revolutionize Commerce &#8211; Natalie Berg, Miya Knights (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is the secret to Amazon&#8217;s success? What does the ecommerce giant have in store for the future? Explore the disruptive new retail strategies of the world&#8217;s most relentless retailer and gain valuable lessons that can be applied to any business in the ecommerce sector, with original insight from the company as it continues to revolutionize itself even further.    </p>
<p>                    The retail industry is facing unprecedented challenges. Across all sectors and markets, retailers are shifting their business models and customer engagement strategies to ensure they survive. The rise of online shopping, and its primary player, Amazon, is at the heart of these changes and opportunities.    </p>
<p>                    Amazon&#8217;s relentless dissatisfaction with the status quo is what makes it such an extraordinary retailer. This book explores whether Amazon has what it takes to become a credible grocery retailer, and as it transitions to bricks and mortar retailing, investigates whether Amazon&#8217;s stores can be as compelling as its online offering.    </p>
<p>                    Exploring the ecommerce giant&#8217;s strategies, Amazon offers unique insight into how innovations such voice technology, checkout-free stores and its Prime ecosystem, will fundamentally change the way consumers shop.    </p>
<p>                    Written by industry leading retail analysts who have spent decades providing research-based analysis and opinion on retail strategy and enterprise technology use in retail, Amazon analyzes the impact these initiatives will have on the wider retail sector and the lessons that can be learned from its unprecedented rise to dominance &#8211; as stores of the future become less about transactions and more about experiences.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/">Amazon : How the World&#8217;s Most Relentless Retailer will Continue to Revolutionize Commerce &#8211; Natalie Berg, Miya Knights (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
