<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sociology: Work &amp; Labour Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sociology-work-labour/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sociology-work-labour/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sociology: Work &amp; Labour Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sociology-work-labour/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pensions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface* Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time? Many of us have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface*    </p>
<p>                    Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time?     </p>
<p>                    Many of us have been raised on the traditional notion of a three-stage approach to our working lives: education, followed by work and then retirement.  But this well-established pathway is already beginning to collapse &#8211; life expectancy is rising, final-salary pensions are vanishing, and increasing numbers of people are juggling multiple careers. Whether you are 18, 45 or 60, you will need to do things very differently from previous generations and learn to structure your life in completely new ways.    </p>
<p>                    The 100-Year Life is here to help.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the unique pairing of their experience in psychology and economics, Lynda Gratton and Andrew J. Scott offer a broad-ranging analysis as well as a raft of solutions, showing how to rethink your finances, your education, your career and your relationships and create a fulfilling 100-year life.     </p>
<p>                    * How can you fashion a career and life path that defines you and your values and creates a shifting balance between work and leisure?    </p>
<p>                    * What are the most effective ways of boosting your physical and mental health over a longer and more dynamic lifespan?    </p>
<p>                    * How can you make the most of your intangible assets &#8211; such as family and friends &#8211; as you build a productive, longer life?    </p>
<p>                    * In a multiple-stage life how can you learn to make the transitions that will be so crucial and experiment with new ways of living, working and learning?    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award and featuring a new preface, The 100-Year Life is a wake-up call that describes what to expect and considers the choices and options that you will face. It is also fundamentally a call to action for individuals, politicians, firms and governments and offers the clearest demonstration that a 100-year life can be a wonderful and inspiring one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Work &#8211; Barry Schwartz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Part of the TED series: Why We Work Why do we work? The question seems so simple. But Professor Barry Schwartz proves that the answer is surprising, complex and urgent. We&#8217;ve long been taught that the reason we work is primarily for a paycheck. In fact, we&#8217;ve shaped much of the infrastructure of our society [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/">Why We Work &#8211; Barry Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Part of the TED series: Why We Work    </p>
<p>                    Why do we work? The question seems so simple. But Professor Barry Schwartz proves that the answer is surprising, complex and urgent.     </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve long been taught that the reason we work is primarily for a paycheck. In fact, we&#8217;ve shaped much of the infrastructure of our society to accommodate this belief. Then why are so many people dissatisfied with their work, despite healthy compensation? And why do so many people find immense fulfillment and satisfaction through &#8220;menial&#8221; jobs?     </p>
<p>                    Schwartz reveals exactly how the false idea that the goal for work should be pay came to be, how we came to believe that paying workers more leads to better work, and why this has made our society confused, unhappy and has established a dangerously misguided system.     </p>
<p>                    Ultimately, Schwartz proves that the root of what drives us to good work can rarely be incentivized, and that the cause of bad work is often an attempt to do just that. With great insight and wisdom, Schwartz illuminates the path for readers to take their first steps toward understanding, empowering us all to find great work.     </p>
<p>                    Schwartz is also the author of The Paradox of Choice: Why More Is Less, which has been translated into twenty languages. He can be seen discussing his ideas in his TEDTalks The Paradox of Choiceand Using Our Practical Wisdom.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/">Why We Work &#8211; Barry Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in their working lives.    </p>
<p>                    Overcoming Mobbing is an informative, comprehensive guidebook written for the victims of mobbing and their families who often can&#8217;t make sense of the experience or mobilize resources for recovery. In an engaging, reader-friendly style, the book distinguishes mobbing from bullying in that it takes place within organizational or institutional settings and involves organizational dynamics. Mobbing is not about the occasional negative experience at work; it is ongoing negative acts, both<br />
                    overt and covert, over time, that erode workers&#8217; confidence in themselves and in their workplaces and that no amount of sophistication or maturity can make sense of.  Duffy and Sperry, leading authorities on this special type of aggression, provide effective strategies for recovery from mobbing as well as for<br />
                    prevention, and they demystify the experience through the use of case vignettes. More than a simple self-help book, this volume brings the concept and terminology relating to mobbing into the public vocabulary by virtue of its strong foundation in psychological and organizational research. It offers a detailed presentation of the causes and consequences of mobbing, helps readers avoid falling into the trap of misplacing blame, and holds organizations at the center of responsibility for<br />
                    preventing the abuse. In addition to those who have experienced mobbing themselves, this book is an invaluable resource for workplace managers and human resources personnel who wish to prevent or reverse mobbing within their own professional settings.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unfair Advantage : BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD-WINNER: How You Already Have What It Takes to Succeed &#8211; Ash Ali, Hasan Kubba (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unfair-advantage-business-book-of-the-year-award-winner-how-you-already-have-what-it-takes-to-succeed-ash-ali-hasan-kubba-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unfair-advantage-business-book-of-the-year-award-winner-how-you-already-have-what-it-takes-to-succeed-ash-ali-hasan-kubba-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2021 AND BEST START UP/SCALE UP BOOK AWARD 2021 This ground-breaking book exposes the myths behind startup success, illuminates the real forces at work and shows how they can be harnessed in your favour. The world isn&#8217;t a level playing field. Meritocracy is a myth. And if [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unfair-advantage-business-book-of-the-year-award-winner-how-you-already-have-what-it-takes-to-succeed-ash-ali-hasan-kubba-abridged/">The Unfair Advantage : BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD-WINNER: How You Already Have What It Takes to Succeed &#8211; Ash Ali, Hasan Kubba (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2021 AND BEST START UP/SCALE UP BOOK AWARD 2021    </p>
<p>                    This ground-breaking book exposes the myths behind startup success, illuminates the real forces at work and shows how they can be harnessed in your favour.    </p>
<p>                    The world isn&#8217;t a level playing field. Meritocracy is a myth. And if you look at those at the top, you realise that behind every success story is an Unfair Advantage. But that doesn&#8217;t just mean your parents&#8217; wealth or who you know. An Unfair Advantage is any element that gives you an edge over your competition. And we all have one.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on over two decades of hands-on experience, including as the first Marketing Director of Just Eat (a startup now worth over GBP5 billion), the authors show how to identify your own unfair advantages and apply them to any project. Hard work and grit aren&#8217;t enough, so they explore the importance of money, intelligence, insight, location, education, expertise, status and luck in the journey to success. From Snapchat to Spanx, Oprah to Elon Musk, unfair advantages have shaped the journeys of some of the most successful brands in the world. This book helps you too find the external circumstances and internal strengths to succeed in the world of business and beyond.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unfair-advantage-business-book-of-the-year-award-winner-how-you-already-have-what-it-takes-to-succeed-ash-ali-hasan-kubba-abridged/">The Unfair Advantage : BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD-WINNER: How You Already Have What It Takes to Succeed &#8211; Ash Ali, Hasan Kubba (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dangerously Sleepy : Overworked Americans and the Cult of Manly Wakefulness &#8211; Alan Derickson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Workers in the United States are losing sleep. In the global economy a growing number of employees hold jobs-often more than one at once-with unpredictable hours. Even before the rise of the twenty-four-hour workplace, the relationship between sleep and industry was problematic: sleep is frequently cast as an enemy or a weakness, while constant productivity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/">Dangerously Sleepy : Overworked Americans and the Cult of Manly Wakefulness &#8211; Alan Derickson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Workers in the United States are losing sleep. In the global economy a growing number of employees hold jobs-often more than one at once-with unpredictable hours. Even before the rise of the twenty-four-hour workplace, the relationship between sleep and industry was problematic: sleep is frequently cast as an enemy or a weakness, while constant productivity and flexibility are glorified at the expense of health and safety.    </p>
<p>                    Dangerously Sleepy is the first book to track the longtime association of overwork and sleep deprivation from the nineteenth century to the present. Health and labor historian Alan Derickson charts the cultural and political forces behind the overvaluation-and masculinization-of wakefulness in the United States. Since the nineteenth century, men at all levels of society have toiled around the clock by necessity: steel workers coped with rotating shifts, Pullman porters grappled with ever-changing timetables and unrelenting on-call status, and long-haul truckers dealt with chaotic life on the road. But the dangerous realities of exhaustion were minimized and even glamorized when the entrepreneurial drive of public figures such as Thomas Edison and Donald Trump encouraged American men to deny biological need in the name of success. For workers, resisting sleep became a challenge of masculine strength.    </p>
<p>                    This lucid history of the wakeful work ethic suggests that for millions of American men and women, untenable work schedules have been the main factor leading to sleep loss, newer ailments such as shift work sleep disorder, and related morbidity and mortality. Dangerously Sleepy places these public health problems in historical context.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/">Dangerously Sleepy : Overworked Americans and the Cult of Manly Wakefulness &#8211; Alan Derickson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumerism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about? Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about?     </p>
<p>                    Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to balance economic growth with the human costs of globalisation, Small Is Beautiful puts forward the revolutionary yet viable case for building our economies around the needs of communities, not corporations.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the 100 most influential books published since World War II&#8217; The Times Literary Supplement</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good People, Bad Managers : How Work Culture Corrupts Good Intentions &#8211; Samuel A. Culbert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-people-bad-managers-how-work-culture-corrupts-good-intentions-samuel-a-culbert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-people-bad-managers-how-work-culture-corrupts-good-intentions-samuel-a-culbert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s worse than a bad manager who everybody knows is bad? A bad manager who is well-intentioned and considered to be good. Yet these well-intentioned bad managers make up the bulk of management today. How did that happen? How did so many of today&#8217;s managers end up with a self-preservation mindset that doesn&#8217;t always translate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-people-bad-managers-how-work-culture-corrupts-good-intentions-samuel-a-culbert-abridged/">Good People, Bad Managers : How Work Culture Corrupts Good Intentions &#8211; Samuel A. Culbert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s worse than a bad manager who everybody knows is bad? A bad manager who is well-intentioned and considered to be good. Yet these well-intentioned bad managers make up the bulk of management today. How did that happen? How did so many of today&#8217;s managers end up with a self-preservation mindset that doesn&#8217;t  always translate to a productive and mission-oriented environment? How did so many good people become wedded to a work culture that saps morale, well-being<br />
                    and performance at both the individual and organizational levels?     </p>
<p>                    an the well-intentioned doling it out realize&#8230; and even In Good People, Bad Managers: How Work Culture Corrupts Good Intentions, author Samuel A. Culbert sheds a light on the bad habits that are routinely followed by these well-intended managers. Managers need to understand the causes of their misguided practices. They need to become more aware of the damage they inflict, and the hollowness of the rationales they use to justify what they do. Company leaders, CEOs, and top-tier<br />
                    managers must become aware of how they have gone astray as a first step in implementing the truly beneficial management mentality that their companies, their managers and their employees require to succeed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-people-bad-managers-how-work-culture-corrupts-good-intentions-samuel-a-culbert-abridged/">Good People, Bad Managers : How Work Culture Corrupts Good Intentions &#8211; Samuel A. Culbert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unfinished Business : Women Men Work Family &#8211; Anne-Marie Slaughter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Orwell Prize for Books 2016 Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015 When Anne-Marie Slaughter&#8217;s Atlantic article, &#8220;Why Women Still Can&#8217;t Have it All&#8221; first appeared, it immediately went viral, sparking a firestorm of debate across countries and continents. Within four days, it had become [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/">Unfinished Business : Women Men Work Family &#8211; Anne-Marie Slaughter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Orwell Prize for Books 2016    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015    </p>
<p>                    When Anne-Marie Slaughter&#8217;s Atlantic article, &#8220;Why Women Still Can&#8217;t Have it All&#8221; first appeared, it immediately went viral, sparking a firestorm of debate across countries and continents. Within four days, it had become the most-read article in the history of the magazine. In the following months, Slaughter became a leading voice in the discussion on work-life balance and on women&#8217;s changing role in the workplace.    </p>
<p>                    Now, Slaughter is here with her eagerly anticipated take on the problems we still face, and how we can finally get past them. In her pragmatic, down-to-earth style, Slaughter bursts the bubble on all the &#8220;half-truths&#8221; we tell young women about &#8220;having it all&#8221;, and explains what is really necessary to get true gender equality, both in the workplace and at home. Deeply researched, and filled with all the warm, wise and funny anecdotes that first made her the most trusted and admired voice on the issue, Anne-Marie Slaughter&#8217;s book is sure to change minds, ignite debate and be the topic of conversation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/">Unfinished Business : Women Men Work Family &#8211; Anne-Marie Slaughter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>White Trash : The 400-Year Untold History of Class in America &#8211; Nancy Isenberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/white-trash-the-400-year-untold-history-of-class-in-america-nancy-isenberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/white-trash-the-400-year-untold-history-of-class-in-america-nancy-isenberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller, with a new preface from the author &#8220;This estimable book rides into the summer doldrums like rural electrification. . . . It deals in the truths that matter.&#8221;-Dwight Garner, The New York Times &#8220;This eye-opening investigation into our country&#8217;s entrenched social hierarchy is acutely relevant.&#8221;-O, The Oprah Magazine &#8220;White Trash [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/white-trash-the-400-year-untold-history-of-class-in-america-nancy-isenberg-abridged/">White Trash : The 400-Year Untold History of Class in America &#8211; Nancy Isenberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller, with a new preface from the author    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This estimable book rides into the summer doldrums like rural electrification. . . . It deals in the truths that matter.&#8221;-Dwight Garner, The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This eye-opening investigation into our country&#8217;s entrenched social hierarchy is acutely relevant.&#8221;-O, The Oprah Magazine    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;White Trash will change the way we think about our past and present.&#8221;<br />
                     -T. J. Stiles, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Custer&#8217;s Trials     </p>
<p>                     In her groundbreaking  bestselling history of the class system in America, Nancy Isenberg, co-author of The Problem of Democracy, takes on our comforting myths about equality, uncovering the crucial legacy of the ever-present, always embarrassing-if occasionally entertaining-poor white trash.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;When you turn an election into a three-ring circus, there&#8217;s always a chance that the dancing bear will win,&#8221; says Isenberg of the political climate surrounding Sarah Palin. And we recognize how right she is today. Yet the voters that put Trump in the White House have been a permanent part of our American fabric, argues Isenberg.    </p>
<p>                     The wretched and landless poor have existed from the time of the earliest British colonial settlement to today&#8217;s hillbillies. They were alternately known as &#8220;waste people,&#8221; &#8220;offals,&#8221; &#8220;rubbish,&#8221; &#8220;lazy lubbers,&#8221; and &#8220;crackers.&#8221; By the 1850s, the downtrodden included so-called &#8220;clay eaters&#8221; and &#8220;sandhillers,&#8221; known for prematurely aged children distinguished by their yellowish skin, ragged clothing, and listless minds.    </p>
<p>                     Surveying political rhetoric and policy, popular literature and scientific theories over four hundred years, Isenberg upends assumptions about America&#8217;s supposedly class-free society&#8211;where liberty and hard work were meant to ensure real social mobility. Poor whites were central to the rise of the Republican Party in the early nineteenth century, and the Civil War itself was fought over class issues nearly as much as it was fought over slavery. Reconstruction pitted poor white trash against newly freed slaves, which factored in the rise of eugenics&#8211;a widely popular movement embraced by Theodore Roosevelt that targeted poor whites for sterilization. These poor were at the heart of New Deal reforms and LBJ&#8217;s Great Society; they haunt us in reality TV shows like Here Comes Honey Boo Boo and Duck Dynasty. Marginalized as a class, white trash have always been at or near the center of major political debates over the character of the American identity.    </p>
<p>                     We acknowledge racial injustice as an ugly stain on our nation&#8217;s history. With Isenberg&#8217;s landmark book, we will have to face the truth about the enduring, malevolent nature of class as well.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/white-trash-the-400-year-untold-history-of-class-in-america-nancy-isenberg-abridged/">White Trash : The 400-Year Untold History of Class in America &#8211; Nancy Isenberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
