<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Biology, Life Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/biology-life-sciences/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/biology-life-sciences/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Biology, Life Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/biology-life-sciences/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Third Chimpanzee : The Evolution and Future of the Human Animal &#8211; Jared M Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Wonderful&#8230;.Jared Diamond conducts his fascinating study of our behavior and origins with a naturalist&#8217;s eye and a philosopher&#8217;s cunning.&#8221; &#8211;Diane Ackerman, author of A Natural History of the Senses In this fascinating, provocative, passionate, funny, endlessly entertaining work, renowned Pulitzer Prize-winning author and scientist Jared Diamond, author of Gun, Germs, and Steel, explores how the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/">The Third Chimpanzee : The Evolution and Future of the Human Animal &#8211; Jared M Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Wonderful&#8230;.Jared Diamond conducts his fascinating study of our behavior and origins with a naturalist&#8217;s eye and a philosopher&#8217;s cunning.&#8221; &#8211;Diane Ackerman, author of A Natural History of the Senses    </p>
<p>                    In this fascinating, provocative, passionate, funny, endlessly entertaining work, renowned Pulitzer Prize-winning author and scientist Jared Diamond, author of Gun, Germs, and Steel, explores how the extraordinary human animal, in a remarkably short time, developed the capacity to rule the world . . . and the means to irrevocably destroy it.     </p>
<p>                    We human beings share 98 percent of our genes with chimpanzees. Yet humans are the dominant species on the planet&#8211;having founded civilizations and religions, developed intricate and diverse forms of communication, learned science, built cities, and created breathtaking works of art&#8211;while chimps remain animals concerned primarily with the basic necessities of survival. What is it about that two percent difference in DNA that has created such a divergence between evolutionary cousins?     </p>
<p>                    The Third Chimpanzee is a tour de force, an iconoclastic, compelling, sometimes alarming look at the unique and marvelous creature that is the human animal.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/">The Third Chimpanzee : The Evolution and Future of the Human Animal &#8211; Jared M Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized  the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much more besides. In it, Dawkins extended the gene&#8217;s eye view to argue that the genes that sit within an organism have an<br />
                    influence that reaches out beyond the visible traits in that body &#8211; the phenotype &#8211; to the wider environment, which can include other individuals. So, for instance, the genes of the beaver drive it to gather twigs to produce the substantial physical structure of a dam; and the genes of the cuckoo chick produce effects that<br />
                    manipulate the behaviour of the host bird, making it nurture the intruder as one of its own. This notion of the extended phenotype has proved to be highly influential in the way we understand evolution and the natural world. It represents a key scientific contribution to evolutionary biology, and it continues to play an important role in research in the life sciences.    </p>
<p>                    The Extended Phenotype is a conceptually deep book that forms important reading for biologists and students. But Dawkins&#8217; clear exposition is accessible to all who are prepared to put in a little effort.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons : The History of the Human Brain as Revealed by True Stories of Trauma, Madness, and Recovery &#8211; Sam Kean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the bestseller The Disappearing Spoon reveals the secret inner workings of the brain through strange but true stories. Early studies of the human brain used a simple method: wait for misfortune to strike &#8212; strokes, seizures, infectious diseases, horrendous accidents &#8212; and see how victims coped. In many cases their survival was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/">The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons : The History of the Human Brain as Revealed by True Stories of Trauma, Madness, and Recovery &#8211; Sam Kean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the bestseller The Disappearing Spoon reveals the secret inner workings of the brain through strange but true stories.      </p>
<p>                     Early studies of the human brain used a simple method: wait for misfortune to strike &#8212; strokes, seizures, infectious diseases, horrendous accidents &#8212; and see how victims coped. In many cases their survival was miraculous, if puzzling. Observers were amazed by the transformations that took place when different parts of the brain were destroyed, altering victims&#8217; personalities. Parents suddenly couldn&#8217;t recognize their own children. Pillars of the community became pathological liars. Some people couldn&#8217;t speak but could still sing.     </p>
<p>                     In The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons, Sam Kean travels through time with stories of neurological curiosities: phantom limbs, Siamese twin brains, viruses that eat patients&#8217; memories, blind people who see through their tongues. He weaves these narratives together with prose that makes the pages fly by, to create a story of discovery that reaches back to the 1500s and the high-profile jousting accident that inspired this book&#8217;s title.     </p>
<p>                     With the lucid, masterful explanations and razor-sharp wit his fans have come to expect, Kean explores the brain&#8217;s secret passageways and recounts the forgotten tales of the ordinary people whose struggles, resilience, and deep humanity made neuroscience possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/">The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons : The History of the Human Brain as Revealed by True Stories of Trauma, Madness, and Recovery &#8211; Sam Kean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life. Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211; probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life.     </p>
<p>                    Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of<br />
                    nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211;<br />
                    probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine rock formations and fossil charcoals<br />
                    all tell the same story. High oxygen levels may also explain the global firestorm that contributed to the<br />
                    demise of the dinosaurs after the asteroid impact.    </p>
<p>                    The strange and profound effects that oxygen has had on the evolution of life pose a riddle, which this book<br />
                    sets out to answer. Oxygen is a toxic gas. Divers breathing pure oxygen at depth suffer from convulsions<br />
                    and lung injury. Fruit flies raised at twice normal atmospheric levels of oxygen live half as long as their<br />
                    siblings. Reactive forms of oxygen, known as free radicals, are thought to cause ageing in people. Yet if<br />
                    atmospheric oxygen reached 35 per cent in the Carboniferous, why did it promote exuberant growth,<br />
                    instead of rapid ageing and death?    </p>
<p>                    Oxygen takes the reader on an enthralling journey, as gripping as a thriller, as it unravels the unexpected<br />
                    ways in which oxygen spurred the evolution of life and death. The book explains far more than the size of<br />
                    ancient insects: it shows how oxygen underpins the origin of biological complexity, the birth of photosynthesis, the sudden evolution of animals, the need for two sexes, the accelerated ageing of cloned animals like Dolly the sheep, and the surprisingly long lives of bats and birds.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on this grand evolutionary canvas, Oxygen offers fresh perspectives on our own lives and deaths,<br />
                    explaining modern killer diseases, why we age, and what we can do about it. Advancing revelatory new ideas,<br />
                    following chains of evidence, the book ranges through many disciplines, from environmental sciences to<br />
                    molecular medicine. The result is a captivating vision of contemporary science and a humane synthesis of our<br />
                    place in nature. This remarkable book might just redefine the way we think about the world.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Why do human beings behave as they do? &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    Why do human beings behave as they do?     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm    </p>
<p>                     We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of our nature destined to win out over the other?    </p>
<p>                     Every act of human behaviour has multiple layers of causation, spiralling back seconds, minutes, hours, days, months, years, even centuries, right back to the dawn of time and the origins of our species.     </p>
<p>                     In the epic sweep of history, how does our biology affect the arc of war and peace, justice and persecution? How have our brains evolved alongside our cultures?    </p>
<p>                     This is the exhilarating story of human morality and the science underpinning the biggest question of all: what makes us human?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the best scientist-writers of our time&#8217; Oliver Sacks</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Power, Sex, Suicide : Mitochondria and the meaning of life &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mitochondria are tiny structures located inside our cells that carry out the essential task of producing energy for the cell. They are found in all complex living things, and in that sense, they are fundamental for driving complex life on the planet. But there is much more to them than that. Mitochondria have their own [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/">Power, Sex, Suicide : Mitochondria and the meaning of life &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mitochondria are tiny structures located inside our cells that carry out the essential task of producing energy for the cell. They are found in all complex living things, and in that sense, they are fundamental for driving complex life on the planet. But there is much more to them than that.     </p>
<p>                    Mitochondria have their own DNA, with their own small collection of genes, separate from those in the cell nucleus. It is thought that they were once bacteria living independent lives. Their enslavement within the larger cell was a turning point in the evolution of life, enabling the development of complex organisms and, closely related, the origin of two sexes. Unlike the DNA in the nucleus, mitochondrial DNA is passed down exclusively (or almost exclusively) via the female line. That&#8217;s why it<br />
                    has been used by some researchers to trace human ancestry daughter-to-mother, to &#8216;Mitochondrial Eve&#8217;. Mitochondria give us important information about our evolutionary history. And that&#8217;s not all. Mitochondrial genes mutate much faster than those in the nucleus because of the free radicals produced<br />
                    in their energy-generating role. This high mutation rate lies behind our ageing and certain congenital diseases. The latest research suggests that mitochondria play a key role in degenerative diseases such as cancer, through their involvement in precipitating cell suicide.     </p>
<p>                    Mitochondria, then, are pivotal in power, sex, and suicide. In this fascinating and thought-provoking book, Nick Lane brings together the latest research findings in this exciting field to show how our growing understanding of mitochondria is shedding light on how complex life evolved, why sex arose (why don&#8217;t we just bud?), and why we age and die. This understanding is of fundamental importance, both in understanding how we and all other complex life came to be, but also in order to be able to<br />
                    control our own illnesses, and delay our degeneration and death.     </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/">Power, Sex, Suicide : Mitochondria and the meaning of life &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Daily Telegraph and TLS Book of the Year &#8216;An audacious tour of all that science can teach us&#8217; Edward O. Wilson Specialist scientific fields are developing at incredibly swift speeds, but what can they really tell us about how the universe began and how humans evolved to play such a dominant role on Earth? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/">Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Daily Telegraph and TLS Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An audacious tour of all that science can teach us&#8217; Edward O. Wilson    </p>
<p>                    Specialist scientific fields are developing at incredibly swift speeds, but what can they really tell us about how the universe began and how humans evolved to play such a dominant role on Earth? John Hands&#8217;s extraordinarily ambitious quest brings together our scientific knowledge and evaluates the theories and evidence about the origin and evolution of matter, life, consciousness, and humankind.    </p>
<p>                    Cosmosapiens provides the most comprehensive account yet of current ideas such as cosmic inflation, dark energy, the selfish gene, and neurogenetic determinism. In clear and accessible language, Hands differentiates the firmly established from the speculative and examines the claims of various fields such as string theory to approach a unified theory of everything. In doing so he challenges the orthodox consensus in those branches of cosmology, biology, and neuroscience that have ossified into dogma. His striking analysis reveals underlying patterns of cooperation, complexification, and convergence that lead to the unique emergence in humans of a self-reflective consciousness that enables us to determine our future evolution. This groundbreaking book is destined to become a classic of scientific thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/">Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Obesity Code : the bestselling guide to unlocking the secrets of weight loss &#8211; Dr Jason Fung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-obesity-code-the-bestselling-guide-to-unlocking-the-secrets-of-weight-loss-dr-jason-fung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Obesity: Treatment & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy & Therapeutics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-obesity-code-the-bestselling-guide-to-unlocking-the-secrets-of-weight-loss-dr-jason-fung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are in the midst of an obesity epidemic, but despite being inundated with diet advice we are only getting fatter. We count calories and exercise regularly, yet still the pounds won&#8217;t budge. Why? In this highly readable and provocative book, Dr Jason Fung sets out a groundbreaking new theory: that obesity is caused by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-obesity-code-the-bestselling-guide-to-unlocking-the-secrets-of-weight-loss-dr-jason-fung-abridged/">The Obesity Code : the bestselling guide to unlocking the secrets of weight loss &#8211; Dr Jason Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are in the midst of an obesity epidemic, but despite being inundated with diet advice we are only getting fatter. We count calories and exercise regularly, yet still the pounds won&#8217;t budge. Why?    </p>
<p>                    In this highly readable and provocative book, Dr Jason Fung sets out a groundbreaking new theory: that obesity is caused by our hormones, rather than a lack of self-control.    </p>
<p>                    He reveals that overproduction of insulin in the body is the root cause of obesity and obesity-related illnesses including type 2 diabetes, and offers robust scientific evidence that reversing insulin resistance is the only way to lose weight in the long term.    </p>
<p>                    It turns out that when we eat is just as important as what we eat, so in addition to his five basic steps &#8211; a set of life-long eating habits that will improve your health and control your insulin levels &#8211; Dr Fung explains how to use intermittent fasting to break the cycle of insulin resistance and reach a healthy weight &#8211; for good.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-obesity-code-the-bestselling-guide-to-unlocking-the-secrets-of-weight-loss-dr-jason-fung-abridged/">The Obesity Code : the bestselling guide to unlocking the secrets of weight loss &#8211; Dr Jason Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maturation & Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life. From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life.    </p>
<p>                    From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of his career. He knows that everyone thinks they want to live forever, until they hit middle age and witness the suffering of their parents and even their peers. So how do we solve the paradox of wanting to live to a ripe old age-but enjoy the benefits of youth?    </p>
<p>                    This groundbreaking book holds the answer. Working with thousands of patients, Dr. Gundry has discovered that the &#8220;diseases of aging&#8221; we most fear are not simply a function of age; rather, they are a byproduct of the way we have lived over the decades. In The Longevity Paradox, he maps out a new approach to aging well-one that is based on supporting the health of the &#8220;oldest&#8221; parts of us: the microorganisms that live within our bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Our gut bugs-the bacteria that make up the microbiome-largely determine our health over the years. From diseases like cancer and Alzheimer&#8217;s to common ailments like arthritis to our weight and the appearance of our skin, these bugs are in the driver&#8217;s seat, controlling our quality of life as we age.    </p>
<p>                    The good news is, it&#8217;s never too late to support these microbes and give them what they need to help them-and you-thrive. In The Longevity Paradox, Dr. Gundry outlines a nutrition and lifestyle plan to support gut health and live well for decades to come. A progressive take on the new science of aging, The Longevity Paradox offers an action plan to prevent and reverse disease as well as simple hacks to help anyone look and feel younger and more vital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans. Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests? By studying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans.      </p>
<p>                    Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests?     </p>
<p>                    By studying social behaviors in animals, such as bonding, the herd instinct, the forming of trusting alliances, expressions of consolation, and conflict resolution, Frans de Waal demonstrates that animals-and humans-are preprogrammed to reach out. He has found that chimpanzees care for mates that are wounded by leopards, elephants offer reassuring rumbles to youngsters in distress, and dolphins support sick companions near the water&#8217;s surface to prevent them from drowning. From day one humans have innate sensitivities to faces, bodies, and voices; we&#8217;ve been designed to feel for one another.     </p>
<p>                    De Waal&#8217;s theory runs counter to the assumption that humans are inherently selfish, which can be seen in the fields of politics, law, and finance. But he cites the public&#8217;s outrage at the U.S. government&#8217;s lack of empathy in the wake of Hurricane Katrina as a significant shift in perspective-one that helped Barack Obama become elected and ushered in what perhaps could become an Age of Empathy. Through a better understanding of empathy&#8217;s survival value in evolution, de Waal suggests, we can work together toward a more just society based on a more generous and accurate view of human nature.     </p>
<p>                    Written in layman&#8217;s prose with a wealth of anecdotes, wry humor, and incisive intelligence, The Age of Empathy is essential reading for our embattled times.     </p>
<p>                    An important and timely message about the biological roots of human kindness.&#8211;Desmond Morris, author of The Naked Ape</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Survival of the Prettiest : The Science of Beauty &#8211; Nancy Etcoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmetics, Hair & Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A provocative and thoroughly researched inquiry into what we find beautiful and why, skewering the myth that the pursuit of beauty is a learned behavior. In Survival of the Prettiest, Nancy Etcoff, a faculty member at Harvard Medical School and a practicing psychologist at Massachusetts General Hospital, argues that beauty is neither a cultural construction, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/">Survival of the Prettiest : The Science of Beauty &#8211; Nancy Etcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A provocative and thoroughly researched inquiry into what we find beautiful and why, skewering the myth that the pursuit of beauty is a learned behavior.     </p>
<p>                     In Survival of the Prettiest, Nancy Etcoff, a faculty member at Harvard Medical School and a practicing psychologist at Massachusetts General Hospital, argues that beauty is neither a cultural construction, an invention of the fashion industry, nor a backlash against feminism&#8211;it&#8217;s in our biology.     </p>
<p>                     Beauty, she explains, is an essential and ineradicable part of human nature that is revered and ferociously pursued in nearly every civilization&#8211;and for good reason. Those features to which we are most attracted are often signals of fertility and fecundity. When seen in the context of a Darwinian struggle for survival, our sometimes extreme attempts to attain beauty&#8211;both to become beautiful ourselves and to acquire an attractive partner&#8211;suddenly become much more understandable. Moreover, if we understand how the desire for beauty is innate, then we can begin to work in our own interests, and not just the interests of our genetic tendencies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/">Survival of the Prettiest : The Science of Beauty &#8211; Nancy Etcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Body : A Guide for Occupants &#8211; THE SUNDAY TIMES NO.1 BESTSELLER &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-body-a-guide-for-occupants-the-sunday-times-no-1-bestseller-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-body-a-guide-for-occupants-the-sunday-times-no-1-bestseller-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; SUNDAY TIMES SCIENCE BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019 _______ &#8216;A directory of wonders.&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian &#8216;Jaw-dropping.&#8217; &#8211; The Times &#8216;Classic, wry, gleeful Bryson&#8230;an entertaining and absolutely fact-rammed book.&#8217; &#8211; The Sunday Times &#8216;It is a feat of narrative skill to bake so many facts into an entertaining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-a-guide-for-occupants-the-sunday-times-no-1-bestseller-bill-bryson-abridged/">The Body : A Guide for Occupants &#8211; THE SUNDAY TIMES NO.1 BESTSELLER &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; SUNDAY TIMES SCIENCE BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A directory of wonders.&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jaw-dropping.&#8217; &#8211; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Classic, wry, gleeful Bryson&#8230;an entertaining and absolutely fact-rammed book.&#8217; &#8211; The Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is a feat of narrative skill to bake so many facts into an entertaining and nutritious book.&#8217; &#8211; The Daily Telegraph<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We spend our whole lives in one body and yet most of us have practically no idea how it works and what goes on inside it. The idea of the book is simply to try to understand the extraordinary contraption that is us.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Bill Bryson sets off to explore the human body, how it functions and its remarkable ability to heal itself. Full of extraordinary facts and astonishing stories The Body: A Guide for Occupants is a brilliant, often very funny attempt to understand the miracle of our physical and neurological make up.     </p>
<p>                    A wonderful successor to A Short History of Nearly Everything, this new book is an instant classic. It will  have you marvelling at the form you occupy, and celebrating the genius of your existence, time and time again.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;What I learned is that we are infinitely more complex and wondrous, and often more mysterious, than I had ever suspected. There really is no story more amazing than the story of us.&#8217; Bill Bryson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-a-guide-for-occupants-the-sunday-times-no-1-bestseller-bill-bryson-abridged/">The Body : A Guide for Occupants &#8211; THE SUNDAY TIMES NO.1 BESTSELLER &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8220;A valuable read that will help you understand what it takes to stop COVID-19. &#8230; A super interesting look at the science of immunity.&#8221; -Bill Gates, Gates Notes Summer Reading List The Pulitzer Prize-winning New York Times journalist &#8220;explicates for the lay reader the intricate biology of our immune system&#8221; (Jerome Groopman, MD, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/">Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable read that will help you understand what it takes to stop COVID-19. &#8230; A super interesting look at the science of immunity.&#8221; -Bill Gates, Gates Notes Summer Reading List    </p>
<p>                    The Pulitzer Prize-winning New York Times journalist &#8220;explicates for the lay reader the intricate biology of our immune system&#8221; (Jerome Groopman, MD, New York Review of Books)    </p>
<p>                    From New York Times science journalist Matt Richtel, An Elegant Defense is an acclaimed and definitive exploration of the immune system and the secrets of health. Interweaving cutting-edge science with the intimate stories of four individual patients, this epic, first-of-its-kind book &#8220;give[s] lay readers a means of understanding what&#8217;s known so far about the intricate biology of our immune systems&#8221; (The Week).    </p>
<p>                    The immune system is our body&#8217;s essential defense network, a guardian vigilantly fighting illness, healing wounds, maintaining order and balance, and keeping us alive. It has been honed by evolution over millennia to face an almost infinite array of threats. For all its astonishing complexity, however, the immune system can be easily compromised by fatigue, stress, toxins, advanced age, and poor nutrition-hallmarks of modern life-and even by excessive hygiene. Paradoxically, it is a fragile wonder weapon that can turn on our own bodies with startling results, leading today to epidemic levels of autoimmune disorders.    </p>
<p>                    An Elegant Defense effortlessly guides readers on a scientific detective tale winding from the Black Plague to twentieth-century breakthroughs in vaccination and antibiotics, to today&#8217;s laboratories that are revolutionizing immunology-perhaps the most extraordinary and consequential medical story of our time. Drawing on extensive new interviews with dozens of world-renowned scientists, Richtel has produced a landmark book, equally an investigation into the deepest riddles of survival and a profoundly human tale that is movingly brought to life through the eyes of his four main characters, each of whom illuminates an essential facet of our &#8220;elegant defense.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/">Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mosquito : A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator &#8211; Timothy C. Winegard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Butterflies, Other Insects & Spiders]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**The instant New York Times bestseller** *An international bestseller* &#8220;Hugely impressive, a major work.&#8221;&#8211;NPR A pioneering and groundbreaking work of narrative nonfiction that offers a dramatic new perspective on the history of humankind, showing how through millennia, the mosquito has been the single most powerful force in determining humanity&#8217;s fate. Why was gin and tonic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/">The Mosquito : A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator &#8211; Timothy C. Winegard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**The instant New York Times bestseller**<br />
                    *An international bestseller*     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hugely impressive, a major work.&#8221;&#8211;NPR    </p>
<p>                    A pioneering and groundbreaking work of narrative nonfiction that offers a dramatic new perspective on the history of humankind, showing how through millennia, the mosquito has been the single most powerful force in determining humanity&#8217;s fate.     </p>
<p>                     Why was gin and tonic the cocktail of choice for British colonists in India and Africa? What does Starbucks have to thank for its global domination? What has protected the lives of popes for millennia? Why did Scotland surrender its sovereignty to England? What was George Washington&#8217;s secret weapon during the American Revolution?     </p>
<p>                     The answer to all these questions, and many more, is the mosquito.     </p>
<p>                     Across our planet since the dawn of humankind, this nefarious pest, roughly the size and weight of a grape seed, has been at the frontlines of history as the grim reaper, the harvester of human populations, and the ultimate agent of historical change. As the mosquito transformed the landscapes of civilization, humans were unwittingly required to respond to its piercing impact and universal projection of power.     </p>
<p>                     The mosquito has determined the fates of empires and nations, razed and crippled economies, and decided the outcome of pivotal wars, killing nearly half of humanity along the way. She (only females bite) has dispatched an estimated 52 billion people from a total of 108 billion throughout our relatively brief existence. As the greatest purveyor of extermination we have ever known, she has played a greater role in shaping our human story than any other living thing with which we share our global village.     </p>
<p>                     Imagine for a moment a world without deadly mosquitoes, or any mosquitoes, for that matter? Our history and the world we know, or think we know, would be completely unrecognizable.     </p>
<p>                     Driven by surprising insights and fast-paced storytelling, The Mosquito is the extraordinary untold story of the mosquito&#8217;s reign through human history and her indelible impact on our modern world order.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/">The Mosquito : A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator &#8211; Timothy C. Winegard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Genius of Dogs : Discovering the Unique Intelligence of Man&#8217;s Best Friend &#8211; Brian Hare, Vanessa Woods (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-genius-of-dogs-discovering-the-unique-intelligence-of-mans-best-friend-brian-hare-vanessa-woods-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dog Obedience & Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogs As Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Animals & Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-genius-of-dogs-discovering-the-unique-intelligence-of-mans-best-friend-brian-hare-vanessa-woods-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The international bestseller that reveals the amazing mind of your favourite friend Is your dog purposefully disobeying you? Probably, and usually behind your back. Should you act like &#8216;top dog&#8217; to maintain control? No, you&#8217;re better off displaying your friendliness &#8211; and not just to your dog. Which breed is the cleverest? That&#8217;s the wrong [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-genius-of-dogs-discovering-the-unique-intelligence-of-mans-best-friend-brian-hare-vanessa-woods-abridged/">The Genius of Dogs : Discovering the Unique Intelligence of Man&#8217;s Best Friend &#8211; Brian Hare, Vanessa Woods (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The international bestseller that reveals the amazing mind of your favourite friend    </p>
<p>                    Is your dog purposefully disobeying you? Probably, and usually behind your back. Should you act like &#8216;top dog&#8217; to maintain control? No, you&#8217;re better off displaying your friendliness &#8211; and not just to your dog. Which breed is the cleverest? That&#8217;s the wrong question to ask.    </p>
<p>                    These are just some of the extraordinary insights to be found in The Genius of Dogs &#8211; the seminal book on how dogs evolved their unique intelligence by award-winning scientist Dr Brian Hare. He shares more than two decades of startling discoveries about the mysteries of the dog mind and how you can use his groundbreaking work to build a better relationship with your own dog.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-genius-of-dogs-discovering-the-unique-intelligence-of-mans-best-friend-brian-hare-vanessa-woods-abridged/">The Genius of Dogs : Discovering the Unique Intelligence of Man&#8217;s Best Friend &#8211; Brian Hare, Vanessa Woods (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction and A New York Times Notable Book of 2018. Our understanding of the &#8216;tree of life&#8217;, with powerful implications for human genetics, human health and our own human nature, has recently completely changed. This book is about a new method of telling the story of life on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/">The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction and A New York Times Notable Book of 2018.    </p>
<p>                              Our understanding of the &#8216;tree of life&#8217;, with powerful implications for human genetics, human health and our own human nature, has recently completely changed.    </p>
<p>                              This book is about a new method of telling the story of life on earth &#8211; through molecular phylogenetics. It involves a fairly simple method &#8211; the reading of the deep history of life by looking at the variation in protein molecules found in living organisms. For instance, we now know that roughly eight per cent of the human genome arrived not through traditional inheritance from directly ancestral forms, but sideways by viral infection.    </p>
<p>                              In The Tangled Tree, acclaimed science writer David Quammen chronicles these discoveries through the lives of the researchers who made them &#8211; such as Carl Woese, the most important little-known biologist of the twentieth century; Lynn Margulis, the notorious maverick whose wild ideas about &#8216;mosaic&#8217; creatures proved to be true; and Tsutomu Wantanabe, who discovered that the scourge of antibiotic-resistant bacteria is a direct result of horizontal gene transfer, bringing the deep study of genome histories to bear on a global crisis in public health.    </p>
<p>                              Quammen explains how molecular studies of evolution have brought startling recognitions about the tangled tree of life &#8211; including where we humans fit into it. Thanks to new technologies, we now have the ability to alter even our genetic composition &#8211; through sideways insertions, as nature has long been doing. The Tangled Tree is a brilliant exploration of our transformed understanding of evolution and of life&#8217;s history itself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/">The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nine Pints : A Journey Through the Mysterious, Miraculous World of Blood &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most humans contain between nine and twelve pints of blood. Here Rose George, who probably contains nine pints, tells nine different stories about the liquid that sustains us, discovering what it reveals about who we are. In Nepal, she meets girls challenging the taboos surrounding menstruation; in the Canadian prairies, she visits a controversial plasma [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/">Nine Pints : A Journey Through the Mysterious, Miraculous World of Blood &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most humans contain between nine and twelve pints of blood. Here Rose George, who probably contains nine pints, tells nine different stories about the liquid that sustains us, discovering what it reveals about who we are. In Nepal, she meets girls challenging the taboos surrounding menstruation; in the Canadian prairies, she visits a controversial plasma clinic; in Wales she gets a tour of the UK&#8217;s only leech farm to learn about the vital role the creatures still play in modern surgery; and in a London hospital she accompanies a medical team revolutionising the way we treat trauma.    </p>
<p>                     Nine Pints reveals the richness and wonder of the potent red fluid that courses around our bodies, unseen but miraculous.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/">Nine Pints : A Journey Through the Mysterious, Miraculous World of Blood &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating insight into how human sexuality came to be the way it is now &#8211; Jared Diamond explains why we are different from the animal kingdom. Why are humans one of the few species to have sex in private? Why do humans have sex any day of the month or year, including when the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/">Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating insight into how human sexuality came to be the way it is now &#8211; Jared Diamond explains why we are different from the animal kingdom.    </p>
<p>                    Why are humans one of the few species to have sex in private? Why do humans have sex any day of the month or year, including when the female is pregnant, beyond her reproductive years, or between her fertile cycles? Why are human females one of the few mammals to go through menopause?    </p>
<p>                    Human sexuality seems normal to us but it is bizarre by the standards of other animals. Jared Diamond argues that our strange sex lives were as crucial to our rise to human status as were our large brains. He also describes the battle of the sexes in the human and animal world over parental care, and why sex differences in the genetic value of parental care provide a biological basis for the all-too-familiar different attitudes of men and women towards extramarital sex.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/">Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Red Queen : Sex and the Evolution of Human Nature &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-red-queen-sex-and-the-evolution-of-human-nature-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-red-queen-sex-and-the-evolution-of-human-nature-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A terrific book, witty and lucid, and brimming with provocative conjectures.&#8221; (Wall Street Journal) from the author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller Genome Brilliantly written, The Red Queen compels us to rethink everything from the persistence of sexism to the endurance of romantic love. Referring to Lewis Carroll&#8217;s Red Queen from Through the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-red-queen-sex-and-the-evolution-of-human-nature-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Red Queen : Sex and the Evolution of Human Nature &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A terrific book, witty and lucid, and brimming with provocative conjectures.&#8221; (Wall Street Journal) from the author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller Genome    </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly written, The Red Queen compels us to rethink everything from the persistence of sexism to the endurance of romantic love.    </p>
<p>                    Referring to Lewis Carroll&#8217;s Red Queen from Through the Looking-Glass, a character who has to keep running to stay in the same place, Matt Ridley demonstrates why sex is humanity&#8217;s best strategy for outwitting its constantly mutating internal predators. The Red Queen answers dozens of other riddles of human nature and culture&#8211;including why men propose marriage, the method behind our maddening notions of beauty, and the disquieting fact that a woman is more likely to conceive a child by an adulterous lover than by her husband. The Red Queen offers an extraordinary new way of interpreting the human condition and how it has evolved.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-red-queen-sex-and-the-evolution-of-human-nature-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Red Queen : Sex and the Evolution of Human Nature &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Parasite Rex (with a New Epilogue): Inside the Bizarre World of Nature&#8217;sMost Dangerous Creatures &#8211; Zimmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/parasite-rex-with-a-new-epilogue-inside-the-bizarre-world-of-naturesmost-dangerous-creatures-zimmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insects (entomology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Parasitology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Invertebrates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/parasite-rex-with-a-new-epilogue-inside-the-bizarre-world-of-naturesmost-dangerous-creatures-zimmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For decades parasites were the pariahs of science. Only recently have biologists begun to appreciate that these diverse and complex organisms are the most highly evolved life forms on earth. In this work, Carl Zimmer takes the reader on a tour of the strange and bizzare world that parasites inhabit, and recounts the voyages of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/parasite-rex-with-a-new-epilogue-inside-the-bizarre-world-of-naturesmost-dangerous-creatures-zimmer-abridged/">Parasite Rex (with a New Epilogue): Inside the Bizarre World of Nature&#8217;sMost Dangerous Creatures &#8211; Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For decades parasites were the pariahs of science. Only recently have biologists begun to appreciate that these diverse and complex organisms are the most highly evolved life forms on earth. In this work, Carl Zimmer takes the reader on a tour of the strange and bizzare world that parasites inhabit, and recounts the voyages of these wonders of creation. Parasites can: rewrite DNA; rewire the brain; genetically engineer viruses as weapons; and turn healthy hosts into the living dead. This book follows researchers in parasitology as they attempt to penetrate the mysteries of these omnipotent creatures who control evolution, ecxosystems, and perhaps the future of the human race.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/parasite-rex-with-a-new-epilogue-inside-the-bizarre-world-of-naturesmost-dangerous-creatures-zimmer-abridged/">Parasite Rex (with a New Epilogue): Inside the Bizarre World of Nature&#8217;sMost Dangerous Creatures &#8211; Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dinosaurs & The Prehistoric World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Palaeontology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Times Science Book of the Year. A Sunday Times Bestseller. 66 million years ago the dinosaurs were wiped from the face of the earth. Today, Dr. Steve Brusatte, one of the leading scientists of a new generation of dinosaur hunters, armed with cutting edge technology, is piecing together the complete story of how the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/">The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Times Science Book of the Year.<br />
                    A Sunday Times Bestseller.    </p>
<p>                    66 million years ago the dinosaurs were wiped from the face of the earth. Today, Dr. Steve Brusatte, one of the leading scientists of a new generation of dinosaur hunters, armed with cutting edge technology, is piecing together the complete story of how the dinosaurs ruled the earth for 150 million years.    </p>
<p>                    The world of the dinosaurs has fascinated on book and screen for decades &#8211; from early science fiction classics like The Lost World, to Godzilla terrorizing the streets of Tokyo, and the monsters of Jurassic Park. But what if we got it wrong? In The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs, top dinosaur expert Brusatte, tells the real story of how dinosaurs rose to dominate the planet. Using the fossil clues that have been gathered using state of the art technology, Brusatte follows these magnificent creatures from their beginnings in the Early Triassic period, through the Jurassic period to their final days in the Cretaceous and the legacy that they left behind.    </p>
<p>                    Along the way, Brusatte introduces us to modern day dinosaur hunters and gives an insight into what it&#8217;s like to be a paleontologist. The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs is full of thrilling accounts of some of his personal discoveries, including primitive human-sized tyrannosaurs, monstrous carnivores even larger than T. rex, and feathered raptor dinosaurs preserved in lava from China.     </p>
<p>                    At a time when Homo sapiens has existed for less than 200,000 years and we are already talking about planetary extinction, The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs is a timely reminder of what humans can learn from the magnificent creatures who ruled the earth before us.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling . . . the best book on the subject written for the general reader since the 1980s.&#8217; &#8211;  The Sunday Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/">The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2018 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh presents a profoundly original perspective on what we pass along from generation to generation. Charles Darwin played a crucial part in turning heredity into a scientific question, and yet he failed spectacularly to answer it. The birth of genetics in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/">She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2018 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION    </p>
<p>                    She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh presents a profoundly original perspective on what we pass along from generation to generation. Charles Darwin played a crucial part in turning heredity into a scientific question, and yet he failed spectacularly to answer it. The birth of genetics in the early 1900s seemed to do precisely that. Gradually, people translated their old notions about heredity into a language of genes. As the technology for studying genes became cheaper, millions of people ordered genetic tests to link themselves to missing parents, to distant ancestors, to ethnic identities . . .    </p>
<p>                    But, award-winning science writer Carl Zimmer argues, heredity isn&#8217;t just about genes that pass from parent to child. Heredity continues within our own bodies, as a single cell gives rise to trillions of cells that make up our bodies. We say we inherit genes from our ancestors but we inherit other things that matter as much or more to our lives, from microbes to technologies we use to make life more comfortable. We need a new definition of what heredity is and, through Carl Zimmer&#8217;s lucid exposition and storytelling, this resounding tour de force delivers it.    </p>
<p>                    Weaving together historical and current scientific research, his own experience with his two daughters, and the kind of original reporting expected of one of the world&#8217;s best science journalists, Zimmer ultimately unpacks urgent bioethical quandaries arising from new biomedical technologies, but also long-standing presumptions about who we really are and what we can pass on to future generations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/">She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Reason for Flowers : Their History, Culture, Biology, and How They Change Our Lives &#8211; Stephen Buchmann (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-reason-for-flowers-their-history-culture-biology-and-how-they-change-our-lives-stephen-buchmann-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening: Flowers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening: Plants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees, Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-reason-for-flowers-their-history-culture-biology-and-how-they-change-our-lives-stephen-buchmann-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Fascinating&#8230;Buchmann&#8217;s knowledge and enthusiasm jump off the page.&#8221; -The Wall Street Journal &#8220;An extraordinarily good book.&#8221; -Edward O. Wilson The lively and definitive story of the beauty, sexuality, lore, economics, and ecology of the world &#8216;s flowers, written by a devoted scientist and illustrated with his stunning photographs. Flowers-and the fruits they often become-feed, clothe, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-reason-for-flowers-their-history-culture-biology-and-how-they-change-our-lives-stephen-buchmann-abridged/">The Reason for Flowers : Their History, Culture, Biology, and How They Change Our Lives &#8211; Stephen Buchmann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Fascinating&#8230;Buchmann&#8217;s knowledge and enthusiasm jump off the page.&#8221; -The Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An extraordinarily good book.&#8221; -Edward O. Wilson    </p>
<p>                    The lively and definitive story of the beauty, sexuality, lore, economics, and ecology of the world &#8216;s flowers, written by a devoted scientist and illustrated with his stunning photographs.    </p>
<p>                    Flowers-and the fruits they often become-feed, clothe, and inspire us. Indeed, they have done so for all of human history. Yet although we use flowers to celebrate important occasions, to express love, and to please our senses, we know little about them, their functions in nature, or even how we depend on them.    </p>
<p>                    In a volume that will delight gardeners, naturalists, cooks, artists, or anyone interested in history or culture, pollination ecologist Stephen Buchmann serves as an expert guide through the fascinating world of flowers. He explains how other species relate to flowers in ways crucial to the natural world. Next he takes us on an engaging exploration of the roles flowers play in the production of food, spices, medicines, and perfumes. Flowering plants, Buchmann then shows, have long served as inspirational themes in art and literature. Flowers have in fact so thoroughly seduced us that we now buy some ten million a day, driving breeders to create infinite varieties and unusual blooms. In this cultural and natural investigation of floral history, Stephen Buchmann&#8217;s masterful narrative illuminates just why there is, indeed, a reason for flowers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-reason-for-flowers-their-history-culture-biology-and-how-they-change-our-lives-stephen-buchmann-abridged/">The Reason for Flowers : Their History, Culture, Biology, and How They Change Our Lives &#8211; Stephen Buchmann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Crack in Creation : Gene Editing and the Unthinkable Power to Control Evolution &#8211; Jennifer A Doudna, Samuel H Sternberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BY THE WINNER OF THE 2020 NOBEL PRIZE IN CHEMISTRY Finalist for the Los Angeles Times Book Prize &#8220;A powerful mix of science and ethics . . . This book is required reading for every concerned citizen&#8211;the material it covers should be discussed in schools, colleges, and universities throughout the country.&#8221;&#8211; New York Review of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/">A Crack in Creation : Gene Editing and the Unthinkable Power to Control Evolution &#8211; Jennifer A Doudna, Samuel H Sternberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BY THE WINNER OF THE 2020 NOBEL PRIZE IN CHEMISTRY Finalist for the Los Angeles Times Book Prize     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A powerful mix of science and ethics . . . This book is required reading for every concerned citizen&#8211;the material it covers should be discussed in schools, colleges, and universities throughout the country.&#8221;&#8211; New York Review of Books      </p>
<p>                     Not since the atomic bomb has a technology so alarmed its inventors that they warned the world about its use. That is, until 2015, when biologist Jennifer Doudna called for a worldwide moratorium on the use of the gene-editing tool CRISPR&#8211;a revolutionary new technology that she helped create&#8211;to make heritable changes in human embryos. The cheapest, simplest, most effective way of manipulating DNA ever known, CRISPR may well give us the cure to HIV, genetic diseases, and some cancers. Yet even the tiniest changes to DNA could have myriad, unforeseeable consequences, to say nothing of the ethical and societal repercussions of intentionally mutating embryos to create &#8220;better&#8221; humans. Writing with fellow researcher Sam Sternberg, Doudna&#8211;who has since won the Nobel Prize for her CRISPR research&#8211;shares the thrilling story of her discovery and describes the enormous responsibility that comes with the power to rewrite the code of life.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The future is in our hands as never before, and this book explains the stakes like no other.&#8221; &#8212; George Lucas     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An invaluable account . . . We owe Doudna several times over.&#8221; &#8212; Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/">A Crack in Creation : Gene Editing and the Unthinkable Power to Control Evolution &#8211; Jennifer A Doudna, Samuel H Sternberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Contain Multitudes : The Microbes Within Us and a Grander View of Life &#8211; Ed Yong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE WINNER OF THE 2021 PULITZER PRIZE Your body is teeming with tens of trillions of microbes. It&#8217;s an entire world, a colony full of life. In other words, you contain multitudes. They sculpt our organs, protect us from diseases, guide our behaviour, and bombard us with their genes. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/">I Contain Multitudes : The Microbes Within Us and a Grander View of Life &#8211; Ed Yong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE WINNER OF THE 2021 PULITZER PRIZE    </p>
<p>                     Your body is teeming with tens of trillions of microbes. It&#8217;s an entire world, a colony full of life.    </p>
<p>                     In other words, you contain multitudes.    </p>
<p>                     They sculpt our organs, protect us from diseases, guide our behaviour, and bombard us with their genes. They also hold the key to understanding all life on earth.    </p>
<p>                     In I Contain Multitudes, Ed Yong opens our eyes and invites us to marvel at ourselves and other animals in a new light, less as individuals and more as thriving ecosystems.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll never think about your mind, body or preferences in the same way again.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Super-interesting&#8230; He just keeps imparting one surprising, fascinating insight after the next. I Contain Multitudes is science journalism at its best&#8217; Bill Gates<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2017<br />
                     SHORTLISTED FOR THE ROYAL SOCIETY SCIENCE BOOK PRIZE 2017</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/">I Contain Multitudes : The Microbes Within Us and a Grander View of Life &#8211; Ed Yong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control  chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Blood of Emmett Till &#8211; Timothy B. Tyson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* Longlisted for the National Book Award * Winner of the Robert F. Kennedy Book Award * A New York Times Notable Book * A Washington Post Notable Book * An NPR Best Book of 2017 * A Los Angeles Times Best Book of 2017 * An Atlanta Journal-Constitution Best Southern Book of 2017 * [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/">The Blood of Emmett Till &#8211; Timothy B. Tyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* Longlisted for the National Book Award * Winner of the Robert F. Kennedy Book Award * A New York Times Notable Book * A Washington Post Notable Book * An NPR Best Book of 2017 * A Los Angeles Times Best Book of 2017 * An Atlanta Journal-Constitution Best Southern Book of 2017 *    </p>
<p>                     This extraordinary New York Times bestseller reexamines a pivotal event of the civil rights movement-the 1955 lynching of Emmett Till-&#8220;and demands that we do the one vital thing we aren&#8217;t often enough asked to do with history: learn from it&#8221; (The Atlantic).    </p>
<p>                    In 1955, white men in the Mississippi Delta lynched a fourteen-year-old from Chicago named Emmett Till. His murder was part of a wave of white terrorism in the wake of the 1954 Supreme Court decision that declared public school segregation unconstitutional. Only weeks later, Rosa Parks thought about young Emmett as she refused to move to the back of a city bus in Montgomery, Alabama. Five years later, Black students who called themselves &#8220;the Emmett Till generation&#8221; launched sit-in campaigns that turned the struggle for civil rights into a mass movement. Till&#8217;s lynching became the most notorious hate crime in American history.    </p>
<p>                    But what actually happened to Emmett Till-not the icon of injustice, but the flesh-and-blood boy? Part detective story, part political history, The Blood of Emmett Till &#8220;unfolds like a movie&#8221; (The Atlanta Journal-Constitution), drawing on a wealth of new evidence, including a shocking admission of Till&#8217;s innocence from the woman in whose name he was killed. &#8220;Jolting and powerful&#8221; (The Washington Post), the book &#8220;provides fresh insight into the way race has informed and deformed our democratic institutions&#8221; (Diane McWhorter, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Carry Me Home) and &#8220;calls us to the cause of justice today&#8221; (Rev. Dr. William J. Barber, II, president of the North Carolina NAACP).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/">The Blood of Emmett Till &#8211; Timothy B. Tyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, WithBrendan Buhler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more. In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, WithBrendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more.     </p>
<p>                    In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly within our intestines&#8211;has an astonishing impact on our lives. Your health, mood, sleep patterns, eating preferences&#8211;even your likelihood of getting bitten by mosquitoes&#8211;can be traced in part to the tiny creatures that live on and inside of us.     </p>
<p>                    In Follow Your Gut,  pioneering scientist Rob Knight pairs with award-winning science journalist Brendan Buhler to explain&#8211;with good humor and easy-to-grasp examples&#8211;why these new findings matter to everyone. They lead a detailed tour of the previously unseen world inside our bodies, calling out the diseases and conditions believed to be most directly impacted by them.     </p>
<p>                    With a practical eye toward deeper knowledge and better decisions, they also explore the known effects of antibiotics, probiotics, diet choice and even birth method on our children&#8217;s lifelong health. Ultimately, this pioneering book explains how to learn about your own microbiome and take steps toward understanding and improving your health, using the latest research as a guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, WithBrendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On the Origin of Species : By Means of Natural Selection &#8211; Charles Darwin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-the-origin-of-species-by-means-of-natural-selection-charles-darwin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-the-origin-of-species-by-means-of-natural-selection-charles-darwin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Origin is one of the most important books ever published, and a knowledge of it should be a part of the intellectual equipment of every educated person. . . . The book will endure in future ages so long as a knowledge of science persists among mankind. &#8212; Nature It took Charles Darwin more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-the-origin-of-species-by-means-of-natural-selection-charles-darwin-abridged/">On the Origin of Species : By Means of Natural Selection &#8211; Charles Darwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Origin is one of the most important books ever published, and a knowledge of it should be a part of the intellectual equipment of every educated person. . . . The book will endure in future ages so long as a knowledge of science persists among mankind. &#8212; Nature<br />
                    It took Charles Darwin more than twenty years to publish this book, in part because he realized that it would ignite a firestorm of controversy. On the Origin of Species first appeared in 1859, and it remains a continuing source of conflict to this day. Even among those who reject its ideas, however, the work&#8217;s impact is undeniable. In science, philosophy, and theology, this is a book that changed the world.<br />
                    In addition to its status as the focus of a dramatic turning point in scientific thought, On the Origin of Species stands as a remarkably readable study. Carefully reasoned and well-documented in its arguments, the work offers coherent views of natural selection, adaptation, the struggle for existence, survival of the fittest, and other concepts that form the foundation of modern evolutionary theory. This volume is a reprint of the critically acclaimed first edition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-the-origin-of-species-by-means-of-natural-selection-charles-darwin-abridged/">On the Origin of Species : By Means of Natural Selection &#8211; Charles Darwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals. In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals.     </p>
<p>                    In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind societies. He explores how the tension between identity and anonymity defines how societies develop, function, and fail. In the vein of Guns, Germs, and Steel and Sapiens, The Human Swarm reveals how mankind created sprawling civilizations of unrivalled complexity &#8211; and what it will take to sustain them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cannibalism: a Perfectly Natural History &#8211; Bill Schutt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cannibalism-a-perfectly-natural-history-bill-schutt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cannibalism-a-perfectly-natural-history-bill-schutt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Surprising. Impressive. Cannibalism restores my faith in humanity.&#8221; &#8211;Sy Montgomery, The New York Times Book Review For centuries scientists have written off cannibalism as a bizarre phenomenon with little biological significance. Its presence in nature was dismissed as a desperate response to starvation or other life-threatening circumstances, and few spent time studying it. A taboo [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cannibalism-a-perfectly-natural-history-bill-schutt-abridged/">Cannibalism: a Perfectly Natural History &#8211; Bill Schutt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Surprising. Impressive. Cannibalism restores my faith in humanity.&#8221; &#8211;Sy Montgomery, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                     For centuries scientists have written off cannibalism as a bizarre phenomenon with little biological significance. Its presence in nature was dismissed as a desperate response to starvation or other life-threatening circumstances, and few spent time studying it. A taboo subject in our culture, the behavior was portrayed mostly through horror movies or tabloids sensationalizing the crimes of real-life flesh-eaters. But the true nature of cannibalism&#8211;the role it plays in evolution as well as human history&#8211;is even more intriguing (and more normal) than the misconceptions we&#8217;ve come to accept as fact.    </p>
<p>                     In Cannibalism: A Perfectly Natural History,  zoologist Bill Schutt sets the record straight, debunking common myths and investigating our new understanding of cannibalism&#8217;s role in biology, anthropology, and history in the most fascinating account yet written on this complex topic. Schutt takes readers from Arizona&#8217;s Chiricahua Mountains, where he wades through ponds full of tadpoles devouring their siblings, to the Sierra Nevadas, where he joins researchers who are shedding new light on what happened to the Donner Party&#8211;the most infamous episode of cannibalism in American history. He even meets with an expert on the preparation and consumption of human placenta (and, yes, it goes well with Chianti).    </p>
<p>                     Bringing together the latest cutting-edge science, Schutt answers questions such as why some amphibians consume their mother&#8217;s skin; why certain insects bite the heads off their partners after sex; why, up until the end of the twentieth century, Europeans regularly ate human body parts as medical curatives; and how cannibalism might be linked to the extinction of the Neanderthals. He takes us into the future as well, investigating whether, as climate change causes famine, disease, and overcrowding, we may see more outbreaks of cannibalism in many more species&#8211;including our own.    </p>
<p>                     Cannibalism places a perfectly natural occurrence into a vital new context and invites us to explore why it both enthralls and repels us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cannibalism-a-perfectly-natural-history-bill-schutt-abridged/">Cannibalism: a Perfectly Natural History &#8211; Bill Schutt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A leading figure in immunology takes readers inside the remarkably powerful human immune system. Winner of the CHOICE Outstanding Academic Title of the Choice ACRL The immune system has incredible power to protect us from the ravages of infection. Boosted by vaccines, it can protect us from diseases such as measles. However, the power of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/">Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A leading figure in immunology takes readers inside the remarkably powerful human immune system.    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the CHOICE Outstanding Academic Title of the Choice ACRL    </p>
<p>                    The immune system has incredible power to protect us from the ravages of infection. Boosted by vaccines, it can protect us from diseases such as measles. However, the power of the immune system is a double-edged sword: an overactive immune system can wreak havoc, destroying normal tissue and causing diseases such as type I diabetes, rheumatoid arthritis, and multiple sclerosis. The consequences of an impaired immune system, on the other hand, are all too evident in the agonies of AIDS.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with illustrations, stories from Dr. William E. Paul&#8217;s distinguished career, and fascinating accounts of scientific discovery, Immunity presents the three laws of the human immune system-universality, tolerance, and appropriateness-and explains how the system both protects and harms us. From the tale of how smallpox was overcome and the lessons of the Ebola epidemic to the hope that the immune system can be used to treat or prevent cancer, Dr. Paul argues that we must take advantage of cutting-edge technologies and promising new tools in immunological research.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/">Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
