<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Insurance &amp; Actuarial Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/insurance-actuarial-studies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/insurance-actuarial-studies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Insurance &amp; Actuarial Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/insurance-actuarial-studies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Foolproof : A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8211; Greg Ip (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/foolproof-a-financial-times-book-of-the-year-greg-ip-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insurance & Actuarial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/foolproof-a-financial-times-book-of-the-year-greg-ip-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why anti-lock brakes make us drive faster Why saving money can lead to financial crises How football helmets make the game more dangerous Why letting forest fires burn can be safer than putting them out We have learned a staggering amount about human nature and disaster-yet we are continually unprepared for car crashes, floods, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/foolproof-a-financial-times-book-of-the-year-greg-ip-abridged/">Foolproof : A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8211; Greg Ip (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why anti-lock brakes make us drive faster    </p>
<p>                      Why saving money can lead to financial crises    </p>
<p>                    How football helmets make the game more dangerous    </p>
<p>                    Why letting forest fires burn can be safer than putting them out    </p>
<p>                    We have learned a staggering amount about human nature and disaster-yet we are continually unprepared for car crashes, floods, and financial crises. Partly this is because the very success we&#8217;ve had making life safer enables us to take more extreme, different risks. As our cities, transport systems, and financial markets become more interconnected and complex, so does the potential for disaster.     </p>
<p>                    How do we stay safe? Should we? What if our attempts are exposing us even more to the very risks we are trying to avoid? What if acceptance of danger ultimately makes us more secure and prosperous? Is there such a thing as foolproof?     </p>
<p>                    In this fascinating account of risk-taking and crisis, Greg Ip presents a macro theory of human nature and disaster that explains how we can keep ourselves safe in our increasingly dangerous world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/foolproof-a-financial-times-book-of-the-year-greg-ip-abridged/">Foolproof : A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8211; Greg Ip (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insurance & Actuarial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicolegal Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017 &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene At a moment of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene      </p>
<p>                    At a moment of drastic political upheaval, An American Sickness is a shocking investigation into our dysfunctional healthcare system &#8211; and offers practical solutions to its myriad problems.    </p>
<p>                     In these troubled times, perhaps no institution has unraveled more quickly and more completely than American medicine. In only a few decades, the medical system has been overrun by organizations seeking to exploit for profit the trust that vulnerable and sick Americans place in their healthcare. Our politicians have proven themselves either unwilling or incapable of reining in the increasingly outrageous costs faced by patients, and market-based solutions only seem to funnel larger and larger sums of our money into the hands of corporations. Impossibly high insurance premiums and inexplicably large bills have become facts of life; fatalism has set in. Very quickly Americans have been made to accept paying more for less. How did things get so bad so fast?     </p>
<p>                     Breaking down this monolithic business into the individual industries-the hospitals, doctors, insurance companies, and drug manufacturers-that together constitute our healthcare system, Rosenthal exposes the recent evolution of American medicine as never before. How did healthcare, the caring endeavor, become healthcare, the highly profitable industry? Hospital systems, which are managed by business executives, behave like predatory lenders, hounding patients and seizing their homes. Research charities are in bed with big pharmaceutical companies, which surreptitiously profit from the donations made by working people. Patients receive bills in code, from entrepreneurial doctors they never even saw.     </p>
<p>                     The system is in tatters, but we can fight back. Dr. Elisabeth Rosenthal doesn&#8217;t just explain the symptoms, she diagnoses and treats the disease itself. In clear and practical terms, she spells out exactly how to decode medical doublespeak, avoid the pitfalls of the pharmaceuticals racket, and get the care you and your family deserve. She takes you inside the doctor-patient relationship and to hospital C-suites, explaining step-by-step the workings of a system badly lacking transparency. This is about what we can do, as individual patients, both to navigate the maze that is American healthcare and also to demand far-reaching reform. An American Sickness is the frontline defense against a healthcare system that no longer has our well-being at heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
