<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sagas Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sagas/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sagas/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sagas Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sagas/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Thursday Murder Club : The Record-Breaking Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Richard Osman</title>
		<link>/the-thursday-murder-club-the-record-breaking-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-richard-osman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-thursday-murder-club-the-record-breaking-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-richard-osman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Such a beacon of pleasure&#8217; KATE ATKINSON &#8216;So smart and funny. Deplorably good&#8217; IAN RANKIN &#8216;A gripping read&#8217; SUNDAY TIMES THE FIRST BOOK IN THE #1 BESTSELLING THURSDAY MURDER CLUB SERIES BY TV PRESENTER RICHARD OSMAN __________________________________ In a peaceful retirement village, four unlikely friends meet up once a week to investigate unsolved murders. But [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thursday-murder-club-the-record-breaking-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-richard-osman/">The Thursday Murder Club : The Record-Breaking Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Richard Osman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Such a beacon of pleasure&#8217; KATE ATKINSON<br />
                    &#8216;So smart and funny. Deplorably good&#8217; IAN RANKIN<br />
                    &#8216;A gripping read&#8217; SUNDAY TIMES</p>
<p>                    THE FIRST BOOK IN THE #1 BESTSELLING THURSDAY MURDER CLUB SERIES BY TV PRESENTER RICHARD OSMAN<br />
                    __________________________________</p>
<p>                    In a peaceful retirement village, four unlikely friends meet up once a week to investigate unsolved murders.</p>
<p>                    But when a brutal killing takes place on their very doorstep, the Thursday Murder Club find themselves in the middle of their first live case.</p>
<p>                    Elizabeth, Joyce, Ibrahim and Ron might be pushing eighty but they still have a few tricks up their sleeves.</p>
<p>                    Can our unorthodox but brilliant gang catch the killer before it&#8217;s too late?<br />
                    __________________________________</p>
<p>                    WHAT PEOPLE ARE SAYING ABOUT THE THURSDAY MURDER CLUB</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling, moving, laugh-out-loud funny&#8217; MARK BILLINGHAM</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A great read, I really enjoyed it&#8217; GRAHAM NORTON</p>
<p>                    &#8216;As the bodies pile up, and more is revealed of the lives and loves of Joyce, Ibrahim, Ron and Elizabeth, you can&#8217;t help cheering them on &#8211; and hoping to meet them again soon&#8217; THE TIMES, CRIME BOOK OF THE MONTH</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Mystery fans are going to be enthralled&#8217; HARLAN COBEN</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Pure escapism&#8217; THE GUARDIAN, BEST CRIME AND THRILLERS OF 2020</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the most enjoyable books of the year&#8217; DAILY EXPRESS</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Smart, compassionate, warm, moving and so VERY funny&#8217; MARIAN KEYES</p>
<p>                    &#8216;As gripping as it is funny&#8217; EVENING STANDARD</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Funny, clever and achingly British&#8217; ADAM KAY</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An exciting new talent in crime fiction&#8217; DAILY MAIL</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A warm, wise and witty warning never to underestimate the elderly&#8217; VAL MCDERMID</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Delight after delight from first page to last&#8217; RED MAGAZINE</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I completely fell in love with it&#8217; SHARI LAPENA</p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is properly brilliant. The pages fly and I can&#8217;t stop smiling&#8217; STEVE CAVANAGH</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Charming, clever debut&#8217; STYLIST</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I laughed my arse off&#8217; BELINDA BAUER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A witty and poignant tale&#8217; DAILY TELEGRAPH</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Clever, clever plot&#8217; FIONA BARTON</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An absolutely delightful read&#8217; PRIMA MAGAZINE</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Utterly charming&#8217; SARAH PINBOROUGH</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Funny and original&#8217; THE SUN</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Properly funny and totally charming&#8230; steeped in Agatha Christie joy&#8217; ARAMINTA HALL</p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is one of the most delightful novels of the year&#8217; DAILY MIRROR</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A bundle of joy&#8217; JANE FALLON</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thursday-murder-club-the-record-breaking-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-richard-osman/">The Thursday Murder Club : The Record-Breaking Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Richard Osman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Long Petal of the Sea : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Isabel Allende</title>
		<link>/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spanish Civil War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller &#8216;One of the strongest and most affecting works in Allende&#8217;s long career&#8217; New York Times Book Review &#8216;A defiantly warm and funny novel, by somebody who has earned the right to argue that love and optimism can survive whatever history might throw at us&#8217; Daily Telegraph September 3, 1939, the day [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/">A Long Petal of the Sea : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Isabel Allende</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the strongest and most affecting works in Allende&#8217;s long career&#8217; New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A defiantly warm and funny novel, by somebody who has earned the right to argue that love and optimism can survive whatever history might throw at us&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>                    September 3, 1939, the day of the Spanish exiles&#8217; splendid arrival in Chile, the Second World War broke out in Europe.</p>
<p>                    Victor Dalmau is a young doctor when he is caught up in the Spanish Civil War, a tragedy that leaves his life &#8211; and the fate of his country &#8211; forever changed. Together with his sister-in-law, the pianist Roser, he is forced out of his beloved Barcelona and into exile. </p>
<p>                    When opportunity to seek refuge arises, they board a ship chartered by the poet Pablo Neruda to Chile, the promised &#8216;long petal of sea and wine and snow&#8217;. There, they find themselves enmeshed in a rich web of characters who come together in love and tragedy over the course of four generations, destined to witness the battle between freedom and repression as it plays out across the world.</p>
<p>                    A masterful work of historical fiction that soars from the Spanish Civil War to the rise and fall of Pinochet, A Long Petal of the Sea is Isabel Allende at the height of her powers.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An epic that starts in 1939 and spans decades and continents . . . A masterful work of historical fiction about hope, exile and belonging, and one that sheds light on the way we live now&#8217; Independent.co.uk</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Full of ambition and humanity&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Allende knows that all stories are love stories, and the greatest love stories are told by time&#8217; Colum McCann</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Allende&#8217;s style is impressively Olympian and the payoff is remarkable&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Epic in scope, yet intimate in execution&#8217; i</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/">A Long Petal of the Sea : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Isabel Allende</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</title>
		<link>/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD *************************** Memphis, Tennessee, 1939 Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story </p>
<p>                    OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD</p>
<p>                    THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD</p>
<p>                    ***************************</p>
<p>                    Memphis, Tennessee, 1939</p>
<p>                    Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. But when their father must rush their mother to the hospital one stormy night, Rill is left in charge, until strangers arrive in force. Wrenched from all that is familiar and thrown into a Tennessee Children&#8217;s Home Society orphanage, the Foss children are assured that they will soon be returned to their parents &#8211; but they quickly realize the dark truth&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Aiken, South Carolina, present day</p>
<p>                    Born into wealth and privilege, Avery Stafford seems to have it all: a successful career, a handsome fiance, and a lavish wedding on the horizon. But when Avery returns home to help her father weather a health crisis, a chance encounter leaves her with uncomfortable questions and compels her to take a journey through her family&#8217;s long-hidden history, on a path that will ultimately lead either to devastation or to redemption.</p>
<p>                    *********************</p>
<p>                    Based on one of America&#8217;s most notorious real-life scandals, in which Georgia Tann, director of a Memphis-based adoption organization, kidnapped and sold poor children to wealthy families all over the country, Before We Were Yours is a riveting, wrenching and ultimately uplifting global bestseller. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A tale of enduring power&#8217; Paula McLain</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is impossible not to get swept up in this near-perfect novel&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book of Two Ways : A Novel &#8211; Jodi Picoult</title>
		<link>/the-book-of-two-ways-a-novel-jodi-picoult/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-of-two-ways-a-novel-jodi-picoult/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER • From the author of Small Great Things and A Spark of Light comes a “powerful” (The Washington Post) novel about the choices that alter the course of our lives. NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY MARIE CLAIRE Everything changes in a single moment for Dawn Edelstein. She’s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-two-ways-a-novel-jodi-picoult/">The Book of Two Ways : A Novel &#8211; Jodi Picoult</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER • From the author of Small Great Things and A Spark of Light comes a “powerful” (The Washington Post) novel about the choices that alter the course of our lives. </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY MARIE CLAIRE</p>
<p>                     Everything changes in a single moment for Dawn Edelstein. She’s on a plane when the flight attendant makes an announcement: Prepare for a crash landing. She braces herself as thoughts flash through her mind. The shocking thing is, the thoughts are not of her husband but of a man she last saw fifteen years ago: Wyatt Armstrong.</p>
<p>                      Dawn, miraculously, survives the crash, but so do all the doubts that have suddenly been raised. She has led a good life. Back in Boston, there is her husband, Brian, their beloved daughter, and her work as a death doula, in which she helps ease the transition between life and death for her clients.</p>
<p>                      But somewhere in Egypt is Wyatt Armstrong, who works as an archaeologist unearthing ancient burial sites, a career Dawn once studied for but was forced to abandon when life suddenly intervened. And now, when it seems that fate is offering her second chances, she is not as sure of the choice she once made.</p>
<p>                      After the crash landing, the airline ensures that the survivors are seen by a doctor, then offers transportation to wherever they want to go. The obvious destination is to fly home, but she could take another path: return to the archaeological site she left years before, reconnect with Wyatt and their unresolved history, and maybe even complete her research on The Book of Two Ways—the first known map of the afterlife.</p>
<p>                      As the story unfolds, Dawn’s two possible futures unspool side by side, as do the secrets and doubts long buried with them. Dawn must confront the questions she’s never truly asked: What does a life well lived look like? When we leave this earth, what do we leave behind? Do we make choices . . . or do our choices make us? And who would you be if you hadn’t turned out to be the person you are right now?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-two-ways-a-novel-jodi-picoult/">The Book of Two Ways : A Novel &#8211; Jodi Picoult</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret of the Nagas &#8211; Amish Tripathi</title>
		<link>/the-secret-of-the-nagas-amish-tripathi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-of-the-nagas-amish-tripathi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, He is a God. 4000 years ago, He was just a man. The hunt is on. The sinister Naga warrior has killed his friend Brahaspati and now stalks his wife Sati. Shiva, the Tibetan immigrant who is the prophesied destroyer of evil, will not rest till he finds his demonic adversary. His vengeance and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-of-the-nagas-amish-tripathi/">The Secret of the Nagas &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today, He is a God. 4000 years ago, He was just a man. The hunt is on.</p>
<p>                    The sinister Naga warrior has killed his friend Brahaspati and now stalks his wife Sati. Shiva, the Tibetan immigrant who is the prophesied destroyer of evil, will not rest till he finds his demonic adversary. His vengeance and the path to evil will lead him to the door of the Nagas, the serpent people. Of that he is certain.</p>
<p>                    The evidence of the malevolent rise of evil is everywhere. A kingdom is dying as it is held to ransom for a miracle drug. A crown prince is murdered. The Vasudevs &#8211; Shiva&#8217;s philosopher guides &#8211; betray his unquestioning faith as they take the aid of the dark side. Even the perfect empire, Meluha is riddled with a terrible secret in Maika, the city of births. Unknown to Shiva, a master puppeteer is playing a grand game.</p>
<p>                    In a journey that will take him across the length and breadth of ancient India, Shiva searches for the truth in a land of deadly mysteries &#8211; only to find that nothing is what it seems. Fierce battles will be fought. Surprising alliances will be forged. Unbelievable secrets will be revealed in this second book of the Shiva Trilogy, the sequel to the #1 national bestseller, The Immortals of Meluha.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-of-the-nagas-amish-tripathi/">The Secret of the Nagas &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Oath of The Vayuputras &#8211; Amish Tripathi</title>
		<link>/the-oath-of-the-vayuputras-amish-tripathi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-oath-of-the-vayuputras-amish-tripathi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, Shiva is a god. But four thousand years ago, he was just a man &#8211; until he brought his people to Meluha, a near-perfect empire founded by the great king Lord Ram. There he discovered he was the Neelkanth, a barbarian long prophesied to be Meluha&#8217;s saviour. But in his hour of victory fighting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-oath-of-the-vayuputras-amish-tripathi/">The Oath of The Vayuputras &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today, Shiva is a god. But four thousand years ago, he was just a man &#8211; until he brought his people to Meluha, a near-perfect empire founded by the great king Lord Ram. There he discovered he was the Neelkanth, a barbarian long prophesied to be Meluha&#8217;s saviour.    </p>
<p>                    But in his hour of victory fighting the Chandravanshis &#8211; Meluha&#8217;s enemy &#8211; he discovered they had their own prophecy.    </p>
<p>                    Now he must fight to uncover the treachery within his inner circle, and unmask those who are about to destroy all that he has fought for. Shiva is about to learn that good and evil are two sides of the same coin&#8230;.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-oath-of-the-vayuputras-amish-tripathi/">The Oath of The Vayuputras &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Easy Fortune &#8211; Zachary Webber, Rachel Fulginiti, Kristen Proby</title>
		<link>/easy-fortune-zachary-webber-rachel-fulginiti-kristen-proby/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/easy-fortune-zachary-webber-rachel-fulginiti-kristen-proby/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Boudreaux Series &#8211; Sexy. Intriguing. Easy. Sometimes the past is better left behind you&#8230;. Lena Turner has spent her life as the outsider. Thanks to her extraordinary gifts, she&#8217;s learned to be independent &#8211; especially when it comes to men. She&#8217;s content to live her life in New Orleans as a schoolteacher, dating casually [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/easy-fortune-zachary-webber-rachel-fulginiti-kristen-proby/">Easy Fortune &#8211; Zachary Webber, Rachel Fulginiti, Kristen Proby</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Boudreaux Series &#8211; Sexy. Intriguing. Easy.     </p>
<p>                    Sometimes the past is better left behind you&#8230;.     </p>
<p>                    Lena Turner has spent her life as the outsider. Thanks to her extraordinary gifts, she&#8217;s learned to be independent &#8211; especially when it comes to men. She&#8217;s content to live her life in New Orleans as a schoolteacher, dating casually and dedicated to her small family. Long term is not part of her plan.     </p>
<p>                    Sometimes the past catches up with you&#8230;.     </p>
<p>                    Leaving Lena behind to pursue his career was the most difficult thing Mason Coulter ever did. He told himself that it was for the best, had even convinced himself that he had only Lena&#8217;s best interests in mind. But now, after six long years, he&#8217;s back in New Orleans to settle his late eccentric aunt&#8217;s estate. All he has to do is get in and out of the city without submitting to the need to see Lena. But to Mason&#8217;s dismay, his aunt made other plans.     </p>
<p>                    And sometimes the future and the past collide&#8230;.     </p>
<p>                    Having Mason walk back into her life is something Lena never saw coming. She could refuse to help him, but she&#8217;s never been good at telling Mason no. So she&#8217;ll do what she can to get the estate settled and Mason out of her life for good.     </p>
<p>                    At least that&#8217;s the plan. But Mason has plans of his own&#8230;.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/easy-fortune-zachary-webber-rachel-fulginiti-kristen-proby/">Easy Fortune &#8211; Zachary Webber, Rachel Fulginiti, Kristen Proby</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Easy Magic &#8211; Zachary Webber, Rachel Fulginiti, Kristen Proby</title>
		<link>/easy-magic-zachary-webber-rachel-fulginiti-kristen-proby/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/easy-magic-zachary-webber-rachel-fulginiti-kristen-proby/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Family. Responsibility. Stability. As the co-CEO of Bayou Enterprises and the eldest of the Boudreaux clan, Beau is the epitome of these. Now that his baby sister, Gabby, is happily settled down, Beau has moved into the company loft in the heart of the French Quarter to be closer to his office while his own [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/easy-magic-zachary-webber-rachel-fulginiti-kristen-proby/">Easy Magic &#8211; Zachary Webber, Rachel Fulginiti, Kristen Proby</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Family. Responsibility. Stability. As the co-CEO of Bayou Enterprises and the eldest of the Boudreaux clan, Beau is the epitome of these. Now that his baby sister, Gabby, is happily settled down, Beau has moved into the company loft in the heart of the French Quarter to be closer to his office while his own home is built. He doesn&#8217;t have time for anything but the family he adores and the company that drives him.     </p>
<p>                    If only the bewitching owner of the herb shop downstairs from Beau&#8217;s loft weren&#8217;t so damn tempting.     </p>
<p>                    Mallory Adams is living the life. The good life. The best life for her. After years of hiding who she is and the gifts she&#8217;s been cursed with, Mallory opened her little shop in the French Quarter, offering herbs and lotions for anything from soothing a sunburn to chasing those pesky ghosts New Orleans is known for out of a client&#8217;s home. Some call her eccentric, and some say she&#8217;s simply odd, and that&#8217;s okay with her. She is a bit odd, but in her experience, all of the best people are.     </p>
<p>                    When an old pipe bursts in the loft above her store, flooding her storeroom, Mallory comes face to face with Beau Boudreaux, and she doesn&#8217;t need the clairvoyant abilities that have been passed down through generations to know that she&#8217;ll never be the same. Beau is her exact opposite: serious, straitlaced. He wears suits, for Pete&#8217;s sake, and probably wouldn&#8217;t know the difference between arnica and flaxseed if his life depended on it. But when he touches her, the electricity is through the roof, and she&#8217;s smart enough to know that a chemistry like theirs doesn&#8217;t happen every day.     </p>
<p>                    Can two people so very different possibly find their way to happily ever after?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/easy-magic-zachary-webber-rachel-fulginiti-kristen-proby/">Easy Magic &#8211; Zachary Webber, Rachel Fulginiti, Kristen Proby</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wicked Dirty &#8211; Paula Hoffman, J. Kenner</title>
		<link>/wicked-dirty-paula-hoffman-j-kenner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wicked-dirty-paula-hoffman-j-kenner/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes bad isn&#8217;t good enough&#8230;. On the outside, Lyle Tarpin is a clean-cut Hollywood actor whose star is on the rise. Inside, he&#8217;s battling his own demons, shunning relationships, and finding solace in the arms of a string of anonymous women paid very well for their discretion. But when he&#8217;s photographed in a compromising position [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wicked-dirty-paula-hoffman-j-kenner/">Wicked Dirty &#8211; Paula Hoffman, J. Kenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes bad isn&#8217;t good enough&#8230;.     </p>
<p>                    On the outside, Lyle Tarpin is a clean-cut Hollywood actor whose star is on the rise. Inside, he&#8217;s battling his own demons, shunning relationships, and finding solace in the arms of a string of anonymous women paid very well for their discretion. But when he&#8217;s photographed in a compromising position by an over-eager reporter, the only way to save his career is to say that the woman he was with is his fianc&#8217;e. And now Lyle has to play a very public game with the only woman who&#8217;s ever managed to get under his skin.     </p>
<p>                    Struggling waitress Sugar Laine agrees to spend one night with Lyle &#8211; but only because she&#8217;s desperate to save her family home. She never expects that a night of passion will turn into a pretend engagement&#8230;or that the heat between them will blossom into love.     </p>
<p>                    But sometimes love has a price.     </p>
<p>                    And now the only question is &#8211; can Lyle and Sugar afford to pay it?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wicked-dirty-paula-hoffman-j-kenner/">Wicked Dirty &#8211; Paula Hoffman, J. Kenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Easy Kisses : A Boudreaux Novel &#8211; Kristen Proby</title>
		<link>/easy-kisses-a-boudreaux-novel-kristen-proby/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/easy-kisses-a-boudreaux-novel-kristen-proby/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times Bestselling author Kristen Proby comes a series set in the intriguing New Orleans, Louisiana. A powerful family, the Boudreaux siblings are successful and ready to find love!Simon Danbury, an internationally sought-after motivational speaker, helps women from all walks of life with love, self-esteem, dating and career building skills. Handsome, witty and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/easy-kisses-a-boudreaux-novel-kristen-proby/">Easy Kisses : A Boudreaux Novel &#8211; Kristen Proby</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times Bestselling author Kristen Proby comes a series set in the intriguing New Orleans, Louisiana. A powerful family, the Boudreaux siblings are successful and ready to find love!Simon Danbury, an internationally sought-after motivational speaker, helps women from all walks of life with love, self-esteem, dating and career building skills. Handsome, witty and wealthy, Simon seemingly has everything a man could want. But appearances can be deceiving. While Simon may have the answers for millions of women all over the world, when it comes to his own love life, he&#8217;s a giant, sexy mess. Divorced, and convinced that he&#8217;ll never love again, the very last thing he expects is one Charly Boudreaux. Charly doesn&#8217;t want to be at this seminar in the middle of nowhere, but her sister made her go. She&#8217;s the one who has her life together. Great career, amazing family, nice home, and loyal friends. So what if she doesn&#8217;t have a man? She doesn&#8217;t need one. If she&#8217;s learned anything in her almost thirty years, it&#8217;s that men are more trouble than they&#8217;re worth. And they have a nasty habit of breaking your heart into a million tiny pieces. So, she&#8217;ll sit through all of Simon&#8217;s touchy-feely crap and go home and get on with her life. Except Simon isn&#8217;t really spouting crap, and when he smiles at her, the butterflies are ridiculous. Never mixing business with pleasure, Simon finds Charly to be a bright spot in a universe that&#8217;s been dark for too long. But will he be able to resist her? And why would he want to?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/easy-kisses-a-boudreaux-novel-kristen-proby/">Easy Kisses : A Boudreaux Novel &#8211; Kristen Proby</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Winter of the World : Book Two of the Century Trilogy &#8211; Ken Follett</title>
		<link>/winter-of-the-world-book-two-of-the-century-trilogy-ken-follett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/winter-of-the-world-book-two-of-the-century-trilogy-ken-follett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This book is truly epic. . . . The reader will probably wish there was a thousand more pages.&#8221; -The Huffington Post Picking up where Fall of Giants, the first novel in the extraordinary Century Trilogy, left off, Winter of the World follows its five interrelated families-American, German, Russian, English, and Welsh-through a time of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/winter-of-the-world-book-two-of-the-century-trilogy-ken-follett/">Winter of the World : Book Two of the Century Trilogy &#8211; Ken Follett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This book is truly epic. . . . The reader will probably wish there was a thousand more pages.&#8221; -The Huffington Post    </p>
<p>                    Picking up where Fall of Giants, the first novel in the extraordinary Century Trilogy, left off, Winter of the World follows its five interrelated families-American, German, Russian, English, and Welsh-through a time of enormous social, political, and economic turmoil, beginning with the rise of the Third Reich, through the great dramas of World War II, and into the beginning of the long Cold War.    </p>
<p>                     Carla von Ulrich, born of German and English parents, finds her life engulfed by the Nazi tide until daring to commit a deed of great courage and heartbreak . . . . American brothers Woody and Chuck Dewar, each with a secret, take separate paths to momentous events, one in Washington, the other in the bloody jungles of the Pacific . . . . English student Lloyd Williams discovers in the crucible of the Spanish Civil War that he must fight Communism just as hard as Fascism . . . . Daisy Peshkov, a driven social climber, cares only for popularity and the fast set until war transforms her life, while her cousin Volodya carves out a position in Soviet intelligence that will affect not only this war but also the war to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/winter-of-the-world-book-two-of-the-century-trilogy-ken-follett/">Winter of the World : Book Two of the Century Trilogy &#8211; Ken Follett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Immortals of Meluha &#8211; Amish Tripathi</title>
		<link>/the-immortals-of-meluha-amish-tripathi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-immortals-of-meluha-amish-tripathi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>1900 BC. In what modern Indians mistakenly call the Indus Valley Civilisation. The inhabitants of that period called it the land of Meluha &#8211; a near perfect empire created many centuries earlier by Lord Ram, one of the greatest monarchs that ever lived. This once proud empire and its Suryavanshi rulers face severe perils as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortals-of-meluha-amish-tripathi/">The Immortals of Meluha &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>1900 BC. In what modern Indians mistakenly call the Indus Valley Civilisation. The inhabitants of that period called it the land of Meluha &#8211; a near perfect empire created many centuries earlier by Lord Ram, one of the greatest monarchs that ever lived. This once proud empire and its Suryavanshi rulers face severe perils as its primary river, the revered Saraswati, is slowly drying to extinction. They also face devastating terrorist attacks from the east, the land of the Chandravanshis. To make matters worse, the Chandravanshis appear to have allied with the Nagas, an ostracised and sinister race of deformed humans with astonishing martial skills. The only hope for the Suryavanshis is an ancient legend: &#8216;When evil reaches epic proportions, when all seems lost, when it appears that your enemies have triumphed, a hero will emerge.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Is the rough-hewn Tibetan immigrant Shiva, really that hero? And does he want to be that hero at all? Drawn suddenly to his destiny, by duty as well as by love, will Shiva lead the Suryavanshi vengeance and destroy evil? This is the first book in a trilogy on Shiva, the simple man whose karma re-cast him as our Mahadev, the God of Gods.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortals-of-meluha-amish-tripathi/">The Immortals of Meluha &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conqueror (Conqueror, Book 5) &#8211; Conn Iggulden</title>
		<link>/conqueror-conqueror-book-5-conn-iggulden/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conqueror-conqueror-book-5-conn-iggulden/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The one and only Conn Iggulden takes on the story of the mighty Kublai Khan. An epic tale of a great and heroic mind; his action-packed rule; and how in conquering one-fifth of the world&#8217;s inhabited land, he changed the course of history forever. A scholar who conquered an empire larger than those of Alexander [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conqueror-conqueror-book-5-conn-iggulden/">Conqueror (Conqueror, Book 5) &#8211; Conn Iggulden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The one and only Conn Iggulden takes on the story of the mighty Kublai Khan. An epic tale of a great and heroic mind; his action-packed rule; and how in conquering one-fifth of the world&#8217;s inhabited land, he changed the course of history forever. A scholar who conquered an empire larger than those of Alexander or Caesar. A warrior who would rule a fifth of the world with strength and wisdom. A man who betrayed a brother to protect a nation. From a young scholar to one of history&#8217;s most powerful warriors, Conqueror tells the story of Kublai Khan &#8211; an extraordinary man who should be remembered alongside Julius Caesar, Alexander the Great and Napoleon Bonaparte as one of the greatest conquerors the world has ever known. It should have been a golden age, with an empire to dwarf the lands won by the mighty Genghis Khan. Instead, the vast Mongol nation is slowly losing ground, swallowed whole by their most ancient enemy. A new generation has arisen, yet the long shadow of the Great Khan still hangs over them all &#8230;Kublai dreams of an empire stretching from sea to sea. But to see it built, this scholar must first learn the art of war.<br />
                    He must take his nation&#8217;s warriors to the ends of the known world. And when he is weary, when he is wounded, he must face his own brothers in bloody civil war.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conqueror-conqueror-book-5-conn-iggulden/">Conqueror (Conqueror, Book 5) &#8211; Conn Iggulden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
