<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Political Activism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/political-activism/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/political-activism/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Political Activism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/political-activism/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Make Trouble : Stand Up, Speak Out, and Find the Courage to Lead &#8211; Cecile Richards, With Lauren Peterson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pressure Groups & Lobbying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Cecile Richards, the former president of Planned Parenthood for more than a decade, daughter of the late Ann Richards, featured speaker at the Women&#8217;s March on Washington, and &#8220;the heroine of the resistance&#8221; (Vogue), comes &#8220;an enthralling memoir&#8221; (Booklist, starred review) filled with &#8220;practical advice and inspiration for aspiring leaders everywhere&#8221; (Hillary Rodham Clinton). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/">Make Trouble : Stand Up, Speak Out, and Find the Courage to Lead &#8211; Cecile Richards, With Lauren Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Cecile Richards, the former president of Planned Parenthood for more than a decade, daughter of the late Ann Richards, featured speaker at the Women&#8217;s March on Washington, and &#8220;the heroine of the resistance&#8221; (Vogue), comes &#8220;an enthralling memoir&#8221; (Booklist, starred review) filled with &#8220;practical advice and inspiration for aspiring leaders everywhere&#8221; (Hillary Rodham Clinton).    </p>
<p>                    Cecile Richards has been an activist since she was taken to the principal&#8217;s office in seventh grade for wearing an armband in protest of the Vietnam War. Richards had an extraordinary childhood in ultra-conservative Texas, where her civil rights attorney father and activist mother taught their kids to be troublemakers. She had a front-row seat to observe the rise of women in American politics and watched her mother, Ann, transform from a housewife to an electrifying force in the Democratic party.    </p>
<p>                    As a young woman, Richards worked as a labor organizer alongside women earning minimum wage, and learned that those in power don&#8217;t give it up without a fight. She experienced first-hand the misogyny, sexism, fake news, and the ever-looming threat of violence that constantly confront women who challenge authority.    </p>
<p>                    Now, after years of advocacy, resistance, and progressive leadership, she shares her &#8220;truly inspiring&#8221; (Redbook) story for the first time-from the joy and heartbreak of activism to the challenges of raising kids, having a life, and making change, all the while garnering a reputation as &#8220;the most badass feminist EVER&#8221; (Teen Vogue).    </p>
<p>                    In the &#8220;powerful and infinitely readable&#8221; (Gloria Steinem) Make Trouble, Richards reflects on the people and lessons that have gotten her through good times and bad, and encourages the rest of us to take risks, make mistakes, and make trouble along the way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/">Make Trouble : Stand Up, Speak Out, and Find the Courage to Lead &#8211; Cecile Richards, With Lauren Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blueprint for Revolution : How to Use Rice Pudding, Lego Men, and Other Nonviolent Techniques to Galvanize Communities, Overthrow Dictators, or Simply Change the World &#8211; Srdja Popovic, Matthew Miller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An urgent and accessible handbook for peaceful protesters, activists, and community organizers&#8211;anyone trying to defend their rights, hold their government accountable, or change the world Blueprint for Revolution will teach you how to &#8211; make oppression backfire by playing your opponents&#8217; strongest card against them &#8211; identify the &#8220;almighty pillars of power&#8221; in order to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/">Blueprint for Revolution : How to Use Rice Pudding, Lego Men, and Other Nonviolent Techniques to Galvanize Communities, Overthrow Dictators, or Simply Change the World &#8211; Srdja Popovic, Matthew Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An urgent and accessible handbook for peaceful protesters, activists, and community organizers&#8211;anyone trying to defend their rights, hold their government accountable, or change the world  Blueprint for Revolution will teach you how to<br />
                     &#8211; make oppression backfire by playing your opponents&#8217; strongest card against them<br />
                     &#8211; identify the &#8220;almighty pillars of power&#8221; in order to shift the balance of control<br />
                     &#8211; dream big, but start small: learn how to pick battles you can win<br />
                     &#8211; listen to what people actually care about in order to incorporate their needs into your revolutionary vision<br />
                     &#8211; master the art of compromise to bring together even the most disparate groups<br />
                     &#8211; recognize your allies and view your enemies as potential partners<br />
                     &#8211; use humor to make yourself heard, defuse potentially violent situations, and &#8220;laugh your way to victory&#8221;  Praise for Blueprint for Revolution &#8220;The title is no exaggeration. Otpor&#8217;s methods . . . have been adopted by democracy movements around the world. The Egyptian opposition used them to topple Hosni Mubarak. In Lebanon, the Serbs helped the Cedar Revolution extricate the country from Syrian control. In Maldives, their methods were the key to overthrowing a dictator who had held power for thirty years. In many other countries, people have used what Canvas teaches to accomplish other political goals, such as fighting corruption or protecting the environment.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times &#8220;A clear, well-constructed, and easily applicable set of principles for any David facing any Goliath (sans slingshot, of course) . . . By the end of Blueprint,  the idea that a punch is no match for a punch line feels like anything but a joke.&#8221;&#8211;The Boston Globe &#8220;An entertaining primer on the theory and practice of peaceful protest.&#8221;&#8211;The Guardian  &#8220;With this wonderful book, Srdja Popovic is inspiring ordinary people facing injustice and oppression to use this tool kit to challenge their oppressors and create something much better. When I was growing up, we dreamed that young people could bring down those who misused their power and create a more just and democratic society. For Srdja Popovic, living in Belgrade in 1998, this same dream was potentially a much more dangerous idea. But with an extraordinarily courageous group of students that formed Otpor!, Srdja used imagination, invention, cunning, and lots of humor to create a movement that not only succeeded in toppling the brutal dictator Slobodan Milosevic but has become a blueprint for nonviolent revolution around the world. Srdja rules!&#8221;&#8211;Peter Gabriel  &#8220;Blueprint for Revolution is not only a spirited guide to changing the world but a breakthrough in the annals of advice for those who seek justice and democracy. It asks (and not heavy-handedly): As long as you want to change the world, why not do it joyfully? It&#8217;s not just funny. It&#8217;s seriously funny. No joke.&#8221;&#8211;Todd Gitlin, author of The Sixties and Occupy Nation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/">Blueprint for Revolution : How to Use Rice Pudding, Lego Men, and Other Nonviolent Techniques to Galvanize Communities, Overthrow Dictators, or Simply Change the World &#8211; Srdja Popovic, Matthew Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Excellent Daughters : The Secret Lives of Young Women Who Are Transforming the Arab World &#8211; Katherine Zoepf (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For more than a decade, Katherine Zoepf has lived in or traveled throughout the Arab world, reporting on the lives of women, whose role in the region has never been more in flux. Only a generation ago, female adolescence as we know it in the West did not exist in the Middle East. There were [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/">Excellent Daughters : The Secret Lives of Young Women Who Are Transforming the Arab World &#8211; Katherine Zoepf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For more than a decade, Katherine Zoepf has lived in or traveled throughout the Arab world, reporting on the lives of women, whose role in the region has never been more in flux. Only a generation ago, female adolescence as we know it in the West did not exist in the Middle East. There were only children and married women. Today, young Arab women outnumber men in universities, and a few are beginning to face down religious and social tradition in order to live independently, to delay marriage, and to pursue professional goals. Hundreds of thousands of devout girls and women are attending Qur&#8217;anic schools&#8211;and using the training to argue for greater rights and freedoms from an Islamic perspective. And, in 2011, young women helped to lead antigovernment protests in the Arab Spring. But their voices have not been heard. Their stories have not been told. In Syria, before its civil war, she documents a complex society in the midst of soul searching about its place in the world and about the role of women. In Lebanon, she documents a country that on the surface is freer than other Arab nations but whose women must balance extreme standards of self-presentation with Islamic codes of virtue. In Abu Dhabi, Zoepf reports on a generation of Arab women who&#8217;ve found freedom in work outside the home. In Saudi Arabia she chronicles driving protests and women entering the retail industry for the first time. In the aftermath of Tahrir Square, she examines the crucial role of women in Egypt&#8217;s popular uprising. Deeply informed, heartfelt, and urgent, Excellent Daughters brings us a new understanding of the changing Arab societies&#8211;from 9/11 to Tahrir Square to the rise of ISIS&#8211;and gives voice to the remarkable women at the forefront of this change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/">Excellent Daughters : The Secret Lives of Young Women Who Are Transforming the Arab World &#8211; Katherine Zoepf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Writing My Wrongs : Life, Death, and the Redemption in an American Prison &#8211; Shaka Senghor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An &#8220;extraordinary, unforgettable&#8221; (Michelle Alexander, author of The New Jim Crow) memoir of redemption and second chances amidst America&#8217;s mass incarceration epidemic, from a member of Oprah&#8217;s SuperSoul 100 Shaka Senghor was raised in a middle-class neighborhood on Detroit&#8217;s east side during the height of the 1980s crack epidemic. An [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/">Writing My Wrongs : Life, Death, and the Redemption in an American Prison &#8211; Shaka Senghor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An &#8220;extraordinary, unforgettable&#8221; (Michelle Alexander, author of The New Jim Crow) memoir of redemption and second chances amidst America&#8217;s mass incarceration epidemic, from a member of Oprah&#8217;s SuperSoul 100     </p>
<p>                    Shaka Senghor was raised in a middle-class neighborhood on Detroit&#8217;s east side during the height of the 1980s crack epidemic. An honor roll student and a natural leader, he dreamed of becoming a doctor&#8211;but at age eleven, his parents&#8217; marriage began to unravel, and beatings from his mother worsened, which sent him on a downward spiral. He ran away from home, turned to drug dealing to survive, and ended up in prison for murder at the age of nineteen, full of anger and despair.     </p>
<p>                    Writing My Wrongs is the story of what came next. During his nineteen-year incarceration, seven of which were spent in solitary confinement, Senghor discovered literature, meditation, self-examination, and the kindness of others&#8211;tools he used to confront the demons of his past, forgive the people who hurt him, and begin atoning for the wrongs he had committed. Upon his release at age thirty-eight, Senghor became an activist and mentor to young men and women facing circumstances like his. His work in the community and the courage to share his story led him to fellowships at the MIT Media Lab and the Kellogg Foundation and invitations to speak at events like TED and the Aspen Ideas Festival.     </p>
<p>                    In equal turns, Writing My Wrongs is a page-turning portrait of life in the shadow of poverty, violence, and fear; an unforgettable story of redemption; and a compelling witness to our country&#8217;s need for rethinking its approach to crime, prison, and the men and women sent there.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/">Writing My Wrongs : Life, Death, and the Redemption in an American Prison &#8211; Shaka Senghor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Than Enough : Claiming Space for Who You Are (No Matter What They Say) &#8211; Elaine Welteroth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WINNER OF THE 2020 NAACP IMAGE AWARD FOR OUTSTANDING LITERARY WORK &#8211; BIOGRAPHY/AUTOBIOGRAPHY In this part-manifesto, part-memoir, the revolutionary editor who infused social consciousness into the pages of Teen Vogue explores what it means to come into your own &#8211; on your own terms. Elaine Welteroth has climbed the ranks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/">More Than Enough : Claiming Space for Who You Are (No Matter What They Say) &#8211; Elaine Welteroth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    WINNER OF THE 2020 NAACP IMAGE AWARD FOR OUTSTANDING LITERARY WORK &#8211; BIOGRAPHY/AUTOBIOGRAPHY    </p>
<p>                    In this part-manifesto, part-memoir, the revolutionary editor who infused social consciousness into the pages of Teen Vogue explores what it means to come into your own &#8211; on your own terms.    </p>
<p>                    Elaine Welteroth has climbed the ranks of media and fashion,  shattering ceilings along the way. In this riveting and timely memoir,  the groundbreaking editor unpacks lessons on race, identity, and  success through her own journey, from navigating her way as the  unstoppable child of a unlikely interracial marriage in small-town  California to finding herself on the frontlines of a modern movement for  the next generation of change makers.     </p>
<p>                    Welteroth moves beyond  the headlines and highlight reels to share the profound lessons and  struggles of being a barrier-breaker across so many intersections. As a  young boss and the only black woman in the room, she&#8217;s had enough of the  world telling her &#8211; and all women &#8211; they&#8217;re not enough. As she learns to  rely on herself by looking both inward and upward, we&#8217;re ultimately  reminded that we&#8217;re more than enough.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/">More Than Enough : Claiming Space for Who You Are (No Matter What They Say) &#8211; Elaine Welteroth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good and Mad : The Revolutionary Power of Women&#8217;s Anger &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-and-mad-the-revolutionary-power-of-womens-anger-rebecca-traister-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-and-mad-the-revolutionary-power-of-womens-anger-rebecca-traister-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>***NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER*** ***BEST BOOKS OF 2018 SELECTION BY*** * WASHINGTON POST * People * NPR * ESQUIRE * ELLE * WIRED * REFINERY 29 * &#8220;In a year when issues of gender and sexuality dominated the national conversation, no one shaped that exchange more than Rebecca Traister. Her wise and provocative columns helped [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-and-mad-the-revolutionary-power-of-womens-anger-rebecca-traister-abridged/">Good and Mad : The Revolutionary Power of Women&#8217;s Anger &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>***NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER***    </p>
<p>                    ***BEST BOOKS OF 2018 SELECTION BY***<br />
                     * WASHINGTON POST  * People * NPR * ESQUIRE * ELLE * WIRED * REFINERY 29 *    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In a year when issues of gender and sexuality dominated the national conversation, no one shaped that exchange more than Rebecca Traister. Her wise and provocative columns helped make sense of a cultural transformation.&#8221;-National Magazine Award Citation, 2018    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The most brilliant voice on feminism in this country.&#8221;-Anne Lamott, author of Bird by Bird    </p>
<p>                    From Rebecca Traister, the New York Times bestselling author of All the Single Ladies comes a vital, incisive exploration into the transformative power of female anger and its ability to transcend into a political movement.     </p>
<p>                    In the year 2018, it seems as if women&#8217;s anger has suddenly erupted into the public conversation. But long before Pantsuit Nation, before the Women&#8217;s March, and before the #MeToo movement, women&#8217;s anger was not only politically catalytic-but politically problematic. The story of female fury and its cultural significance demonstrates the long history of bitter resentment that has enshrouded women&#8217;s slow rise to political power in America, as well as the ways that anger is received when it comes from women as opposed to when it comes from men.    </p>
<p>                     With eloquence and fervor, Rebecca tracks the history of female anger as political fuel-from suffragettes marching on the White House to office workers vacating their buildings after Clarence Thomas was confirmed to the Supreme Court. Here Traister explores women&#8217;s anger at both men and other women; anger between ideological allies and foes; the varied ways anger is perceived based on its owner; as well as the history of caricaturing and delegitimizing female anger; and the way women&#8217;s collective fury has become transformative political fuel-as is most certainly occurring today. She deconstructs society&#8217;s (and the media&#8217;s) condemnation of female emotion (notably, rage) and the impact of their resulting repercussions.    </p>
<p>                     Highlighting a double standard perpetuated against women by all sexes, and its disastrous, stultifying effect, Traister&#8217;s latest is timely and crucial. It offers a glimpse into the galvanizing force of women&#8217;s collective anger, which, when harnessed, can change history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-and-mad-the-revolutionary-power-of-womens-anger-rebecca-traister-abridged/">Good and Mad : The Revolutionary Power of Women&#8217;s Anger &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The voice of reason in a world that won&#8217;t shut up. The Sunday Times Bestseller Winner of the Parliamentary Book Awards Every day, James O&#8217;Brien listens to people blaming hard-working immigrants for stealing their jobs while scrounging benefits, and pointing their fingers at the EU and feminists for destroying Britain. But what makes James&#8217;s daily [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/">How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The voice of reason in a world that won&#8217;t shut up.    </p>
<p>                    The Sunday Times Bestseller<br />
                    Winner of the Parliamentary Book Awards    </p>
<p>                    Every day, James O&#8217;Brien listens to people blaming hard-working immigrants for stealing their jobs while scrounging benefits, and pointing their fingers at the EU and feminists for destroying Britain. But what makes James&#8217;s daily LBC show such essential listening &#8211; and has made James a standout social media star &#8211; is the incisive way he punctures their assumptions and dismantles their arguments live on air, every single morning.    </p>
<p>                    In the bestselling How To Be Right, James provides a hilarious and invigorating guide to talking to people with unchallenged opinions. With chapters on every lightning-rod issue, James shows how people have been fooled into thinking the way they do, and in each case outlines the key questions to ask to reveal fallacies, inconsistencies and double standards.    </p>
<p>                    If you ever get cornered by ardent Brexiteers, Daily Mail disciples or corporate cronies, this book is your conversation survival guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/">How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drought & Water Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An inspiring personal story of redemption, second chances, and the transformative power within us all, from the founder and CEO of the nonprofit charity: water. At 28 years old, Scott Harrison had it all. A top nightclub promoter in New York City, his life was an endless cycle of drugs, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/">Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An inspiring personal story of redemption, second chances, and the transformative power within us all, from the founder and CEO of the nonprofit charity: water.    </p>
<p>                    At 28 years old, Scott Harrison had it all. A top nightclub promoter in New York City, his life was an endless cycle of drugs, booze, models&#8211;repeat. But 10 years in, desperately unhappy and morally bankrupt, he asked himself, What would the exact opposite of my life look like? Walking away from everything, Harrison spent the next 16 months on a hospital ship in West Africa and discovered his true calling. In 2006, with no money and less than no experience, Harrison founded charity: water. Today, his organization has raised over $400 million to bring clean drinking water to more than 10 million people around the globe.     </p>
<p>                    In Thirst, Harrison recounts the twists and turns that built charity: water into one of the most trusted and admired nonprofits in the world. Renowned for its 100% donation model, bold storytelling, imaginative branding, and radical commitment to transparency, charity: water has disrupted how social entrepreneurs work while inspiring millions of people to join its mission of bringing clean water to everyone on the planet within our lifetime.     </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of such bestselling books as Shoe Dog and Mountains Beyond Mountains, Thirst is a riveting account of how to build a better charity, a better business, a better life&#8211;and a gritty tale that proves it&#8217;s never too late to make a change.     </p>
<p>                    100% of the author&#8217;s net proceeds from Thirst will go to fund charity: water projects around the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/">Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Is Not Enough : Defeating the New Shock Politics &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-is-not-enough-defeating-the-new-shock-politics-naomi-klein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-is-not-enough-defeating-the-new-shock-politics-naomi-klein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**The New York Times and Sunday Times Bestseller** &#8216;An ordinary person&#8217;s guide to hope. Read this book&#8217; Arundhati Roy &#8216;As accessible as it is brilliant&#8217; Owen Jones &#8216;A genuine page turner&#8217; Michelle Alexander Naomi Klein &#8211; award-winning journalist, bestselling author of No Logo, The Shock Doctrine and This Changes Everything, scourge of brand bullies and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-is-not-enough-defeating-the-new-shock-politics-naomi-klein-abridged/">No Is Not Enough : Defeating the New Shock Politics &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**The New York Times and Sunday Times Bestseller**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An ordinary person&#8217;s guide to hope. Read this book&#8217; Arundhati Roy<br />
                    &#8216;As accessible as it is brilliant&#8217; Owen Jones<br />
                    &#8216;A genuine page turner&#8217; Michelle Alexander    </p>
<p>                    Naomi Klein &#8211; award-winning journalist, bestselling author of No Logo, The Shock Doctrine and This Changes Everything, scourge of brand bullies and corporate liars &#8211; gives us the toolkit we need to survive our surreal, shocking age.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This  is a look at how we arrived at this surreal political moment, how to  keep it from getting a lot worse, and how, if we keep our heads, we can  flip the script.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    Remember when love was supposed to  Trump hate? Remember when the oil companies and bankers seemed to be  running scared? What the hell happened? And what can we do about it?  Naomi Klein shows us how we got here, and how we can make things better.      </p>
<p>                    No Is Not Enough reveals, among other things, that the  disorientation we&#8217;re feeling is deliberate. That around the world, shock  political tactics are being used to generate crisis after crisis,  designed to force through policies that will destroy people, the  environment, the economy and our security. That extremism isn&#8217;t a freak  event &#8211; it&#8217;s a toxic cocktail of our times.     </p>
<p>                    From how to trash  the Trump megabrand to the art of reclaiming the populist argument,  Naomi Klein shows all of us how we can break the spell and win the world  we need. Don&#8217;t let them get away with it.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Who better than Naomi to make sense of this madness, and help us find a way out? A top-of-the-stack must read&#8217; Michael Stipe    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Naomi  Klein&#8217;s new book incites us brilliantly to interweave our No with a  programmatic Yes. A manual for emancipation&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Magnificent &#8230; a courageous coruscating counterspell&#8217; Junot Diaz</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-is-not-enough-defeating-the-new-shock-politics-naomi-klein-abridged/">No Is Not Enough : Defeating the New Shock Politics &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER* &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran Imagine a world where&#8230; * Your phone is too big for your hand * Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body * [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    Imagine a world where&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    *        Your phone is too big for your hand<br />
                    *        Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body<br />
                    *        In a car accident you are 47% more likely to be injured.    </p>
<p>                    If any of that sounds familiar, chances are you&#8217;re a woman.    </p>
<p>                    From government policy and medical research, to technology, workplaces, and the media. Invisible Women reveals how in a world built for and by men we are systematically ignoring half of the population, often with disastrous consequences. Caroline Criado Perez brings together for the first time an impressive range of case studies, stories and new research from across the world that illustrate the hidden ways in which women are forgotten, and the profound impact this has on us all.    </p>
<p>                    Discover the shocking gender bias that affects our everyday lives.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book that changes the way you see the world&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Revelatory, frightening, hopeful&#8217; Jeanette Winterson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
