<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Advice On Parenting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/advice-on-parenting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/advice-on-parenting/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Advice On Parenting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/advice-on-parenting/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Becoming : The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Michelle Obama</title>
		<link>/becoming-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-michelle-obama/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/becoming-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-michelle-obama/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An intimate, powerful, and inspiring memoir; 15 million copies sold worldwide THE NO. 1 BESTSELLER BRITISH BOOK AWARDS, NON-FICTION BOOK OF THE YEAR THE SUNDAY TIMES, MEMOIR OF THE YEAR BOOKS OF THE YEAR: THE TIMES, OBSERVER, GUARDIAN, EVENING STANDARD Now in paperback featuring a new introduction by Michelle Obama, a letter from the author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-michelle-obama/">Becoming : The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Michelle Obama</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An intimate, powerful, and inspiring memoir; 15 million copies sold worldwide</p>
<p>                    THE NO. 1 BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    BRITISH BOOK AWARDS, NON-FICTION BOOK OF THE YEAR</p>
<p>                    THE SUNDAY TIMES, MEMOIR OF THE YEAR</p>
<p>                    BOOKS OF THE YEAR: THE TIMES, OBSERVER, GUARDIAN, EVENING STANDARD</p>
<p>                    Now in paperback featuring a new introduction by Michelle Obama, a letter from the author to her younger self, and a book club guide with 20 discussion questions and a 5-question Q&#038;A, the intimate, powerful, and inspiring memoir by the former First Lady of the United States</p>
<p>                    In her memoir, a work of deep reflection and mesmerizing storytelling, Michelle Obama invites readers into her world, chronicling the experiences that have shaped her &#8212; from her childhood on the South Side of Chicago to her years as an executive balancing the demands of motherhood and work, to her time spent at the world&#8217;s most famous address. With unerring honesty and lively wit, she describes her triumphs and her disappointments, both public and private, telling her full story as she has lived it &#8212; in her own words and on her own terms.</p>
<p>                    Warm, wise, and revelatory, Becoming is the deeply personal reckoning of a woman of soul and substance who has steadily defied expectations &#8212; and whose story inspires us to do the same.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-michelle-obama/">Becoming : The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Michelle Obama</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The UltraMind Solution : The Simple Way to Defeat Depression, Overcome Anxiety, and Sharpen Your Mind &#8211; Mark Hyman</title>
		<link>/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Ultramind Solutionspeaks directly to the massive generation of boomers who, for the first time, are encountering diminishing memory and focus, among other affects of life on earth and the human brain. Like all of Dr. Hyman&#8217;s work, this latest instalment in the &#8220;Ultra&#8221; series teaches the reader how to use the body to heal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/">The UltraMind Solution : The Simple Way to Defeat Depression, Overcome Anxiety, and Sharpen Your Mind &#8211; Mark Hyman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ultramind Solutionspeaks directly to the massive generation of boomers who, for the first time, are encountering diminishing memory and focus, among other affects of life on earth and the human brain. Like all of Dr. Hyman&#8217;s work, this latest instalment in the &#8220;Ultra&#8221; series teaches the reader how to use the body to heal the body, this time making lifestyle changes that will foster brain function, including memory, mood, and attention span as well as battle everything from brain fatigue to depression.     </p>
<p>                    Like all of Dr. Hyman&#8217;s books, Ultramindincludes the 7 Keys to Brain Health and a simple 6 week program that will cleanse, heal and strengthen the brain. Each section has a quiz for the reader to access the affect of each particular key on their brain function, provides a list of diagnostic tests for clinical treatments as well as a how to implement healing solutions from changes in nutrition to supplements, hormones, detoxification, and fighting brain &#8220;allergies.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    The Ultramind Solutionincludes a brain workout and recipes for &#8220;brain&#8221; foods that stimulate performance.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/">The UltraMind Solution : The Simple Way to Defeat Depression, Overcome Anxiety, and Sharpen Your Mind &#8211; Mark Hyman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Racing in the Rain &#8211; Garth Stein</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogs As Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major motion picture, this heart-warming and inspirational tale follows Enzo, a loyal family dog, tells the story of his human family, how they nearly fell apart, and what he did to bring them back together. Enzo knows he is different from other dogs: he thinks and feels in nearly human ways. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/">The Art of Racing in the Rain &#8211; Garth Stein</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major motion picture, this heart-warming and inspirational tale follows Enzo, a loyal family dog, tells the story of his human family, how they nearly fell apart, and what he did to bring them back together.    </p>
<p>                              Enzo knows he is different from other dogs: he thinks and feels in nearly human ways. He has educated himself by watching extensive television, and by listening very closely to the words of his master, Denny Swift, an up-and-coming race car driver. Through Denny, Enzo realizes that racing is a metaphor: that by applying the techniques a driver would apply on the race track, one can successfully navigate the ordeals and travails one encounters in life.    </p>
<p>                              Enzo relates the story of his human family, sharing their tragedies and triumphs. In the end, despite what he sees as his own limitations as a dog, Enzo comes through heroically to preserve the Swift family.    </p>
<p>                              The Art of Racing in the Rain is a testament to a man&#8217;s life, given by his dog. But it is also a testament to the dog, himself. Though Enzo cannot speak, he understands everything that happens around him as he bears witness to his master&#8217;s problems. His enforced muteness only refines his listening ability, and allows him to understand many of life&#8217;s nuances that are lost on most humans. With humour, sharp observation, and a courageous heart, Enzo guides the reader to the bittersweet yet ultimately satisfying conclusion: there are no limitations to what we can achieve, if we truly know where we want to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/">The Art of Racing in the Rain &#8211; Garth Stein</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>If I Have to Tell You One More Time&#8230; : The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids to Listen without Nagging, Reminding or Yelling &#8211; Amy McCready</title>
		<link>/if-i-have-to-tell-you-one-more-time-the-revolutionary-program-that-gets-your-kids-to-listen-without-nagging-reminding-or-yelling-amy-mccready/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/if-i-have-to-tell-you-one-more-time-the-revolutionary-program-that-gets-your-kids-to-listen-without-nagging-reminding-or-yelling-amy-mccready/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids To Listen Without Nagging, Reminding, or Yelling Why does it feel sometimes as if our children have special powers that enable them to tune us out completely? You ask your child to do her homework, get ready for school or bedtime. You think she heard you but . [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/if-i-have-to-tell-you-one-more-time-the-revolutionary-program-that-gets-your-kids-to-listen-without-nagging-reminding-or-yelling-amy-mccready/">If I Have to Tell You One More Time&#8230; : The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids to Listen without Nagging, Reminding or Yelling &#8211; Amy McCready</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids To Listen Without Nagging, Reminding, or Yelling     </p>
<p>                    Why does it feel sometimes as if our children have special powers that enable them to tune us out completely? You ask your child to do her homework, get ready for school or bedtime. You think she heard you but . . . no response. You&#8217;ve tried everything&#8211;time-outs, nagging, counting to three&#8211;and nothing seems to work. In this invaluable book, Amy McCready, founder of the popular online parenting course Positive Parenting Solutions, presents a nag-and-scream-free program for compassionately yet effectively, correcting your children&#8217;s bad behavior.    </p>
<p>                    McCready draws on Adlerian psychology and Positive Discipline, which focuses on the central idea that every human being has a basic need to feel connected and empowered&#8211;children being no exception to the rule. According to McCready, when this need isn&#8217;t met in positive ways, kids resort to negative methods. In this book she provides parents with a virtual toolbox of strategies they can use to give their children the attention and power they crave&#8211;and do away with the misbehaving that adults dread.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/if-i-have-to-tell-you-one-more-time-the-revolutionary-program-that-gets-your-kids-to-listen-without-nagging-reminding-or-yelling-amy-mccready/">If I Have to Tell You One More Time&#8230; : The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids to Listen without Nagging, Reminding or Yelling &#8211; Amy McCready</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In a time in which the ways we communicate and connect are constantly changing, and not always for the better, Sherry Turkle provides a much needed voice of caution and reason to help explain what the f*** is going on.&#8221; &#8211;Aziz Ansari, author of Modern Romance Renowned media scholar Sherry Turkle investigates how a flight [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In a time in which the ways we communicate and connect are constantly changing, and not always for the better, Sherry Turkle provides a much needed voice of caution and reason to help explain what the f*** is going on.&#8221; &#8211;Aziz Ansari,  author of Modern Romance     </p>
<p>                    Renowned media scholar Sherry Turkle investigates how a flight from conversation undermines our relationships, creativity, and productivity&#8211;and why reclaiming face-to-face conversation can help us regain lost ground.    </p>
<p>                    We live in a technological universe in which we are always communicating. And yet we have sacrificed conversation for mere connection.     </p>
<p>                     Preeminent author and researcher Sherry Turkle has been studying digital culture for over thirty years. Long an enthusiast for its possibilities, here she investigates a troubling consequence: at work, at home, in politics, and in love, we find ways around conversation, tempted by the possibilities of a text or an email in which we don&#8217;t have to look, listen, or reveal ourselves.     </p>
<p>                     We develop a taste for what mere connection offers. The dinner table falls silent as children compete with phones for their parents&#8217; attention. Friends learn strategies to keep conversations going when only a few people are looking up from their phones. At work, we retreat to our screens although it is conversation at the water cooler that increases not only productivity but commitment to work. Online, we only want to share opinions that our followers will agree with &#8211; a politics that shies away from the real conflicts and solutions of the public square.     </p>
<p>                     The case for conversation begins with the necessary conversations of solitude and self-reflection. They are endangered: these days, always connected, we see loneliness as a problem that technology should solve. Afraid of being alone, we rely on other people to give us a sense of ourselves, and our capacity for empathy and relationship suffers. We see the costs of the flight from conversation everywhere: conversation is the cornerstone for democracy and in business it is good for the bottom line. In the private sphere, it builds empathy, friendship, love, learning, and productivity.     </p>
<p>                     But there is good news: we are resilient. Conversation cures.     </p>
<p>                     Based on five years of research and interviews in homes, schools, and the workplace, Turkle argues that we have come to a better understanding of where our technology can and cannot take us and that the time is right to reclaim conversation. The most human&#8211;and humanizing&#8211;thing that we do.     </p>
<p>                     The virtues of person-to-person conversation are timeless, and our most basic technology, talk, responds to our modern challenges. We have everything we need to start, we have each other.     </p>
<p>                    Turkle&#8217;s latest book, The Empathy Diaries (3/2/21) is available now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A witty, compelling guide to raising open-minded and morally grounded kids in these crazy times, with an approach that&#8217;s rooted in science, psychology, and faith &#8220;Groundbreaking, profound, frank and friendly.&#8221;&#8211;Wendy Mogel, PhD, author of The Blessing of a Skinned Knee NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY LIBRARY JOURNAL When Rev. Molly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/">Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A witty, compelling guide to raising open-minded and morally grounded kids in these crazy times, with an approach that&#8217;s rooted in science, psychology, and faith     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Groundbreaking, profound, frank and friendly.&#8221;&#8211;Wendy Mogel, PhD, author of The Blessing of a Skinned Knee     </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY LIBRARY JOURNAL     </p>
<p>                    When Rev. Molly Baskette and Dr. Ellen O&#8217;Donnell first met, they were both new mothers seeking parenting wisdom. They read a lot of books on the topic, but none of them contained practical suggestions that would help their families psychologically and spiritually while maintaining their progressive values: How do we teach the art of forgiving and serving others? How do we raise kids who are tolerant, curious, and honorable? And what about the sex talk?     </p>
<p>                    Taking matters into their own hands, Baskette and O&#8217;Donnell began creating actionable steps addressing these questions and more. This book is the fruit of their many conversations begun long ago during the daycare carpool, from angsty moments to hallelujahs.     </p>
<p>                    In Bless This Mess, readers will gain constructive tools as they learn how to talk to their children about social justice, money, God, ethics, bullying, disabilities, sexuality, and their bodies. Parents will also glean insights on how to serve others with joy, give generously and gratefully, and&#8211;perhaps most important&#8211;learn how to stop being so afraid all the damn time, even while raising kids in an increasingly chaotic and often scary world. With real-life examples, relatable personal stories, and strategies tailored to the toddler, preteen, or teenager, Bless This Mess guides parents of children at all stages of their development.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/">Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let It Go : Downsizing Your Way to a Richer, Happier Life &#8211; Peter Walsh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/let-it-go-downsizing-your-way-to-a-richer-happier-life-peter-walsh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-it-go-downsizing-your-way-to-a-richer-happier-life-peter-walsh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A unique approach to decluttering for anyone in the process of downsizing, from Australia&#8217;s organising expert. Whether you&#8217;re selling your family home, blending households, or cleaning out your ageing parents&#8217; home, sorting through a lifetime&#8217;s worth of accumulated possessions can be a daunting and stressful experience. When decluttering guru Peter Walsh went through the process [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-it-go-downsizing-your-way-to-a-richer-happier-life-peter-walsh-abridged/">Let It Go : Downsizing Your Way to a Richer, Happier Life &#8211; Peter Walsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A unique approach to decluttering for anyone in the process of downsizing, from Australia&#8217;s organising expert.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re selling your family home, blending households, or cleaning out your ageing parents&#8217; home, sorting through a lifetime&#8217;s worth of accumulated possessions can be a daunting and stressful experience. When decluttering guru Peter Walsh went through the process of downsizing his childhood home and dividing his late parents&#8217; possessions among his family, he realised that making these decisions about mementos and heirlooms creates strong emotions and can be an overwhelming chore.     </p>
<p>                    In Let It Go, Walsh helps you turn downsizing into a rejuvenating life change. He offers useful tips and practical takeaways, including how to understand the emotional challenges that accompany downsizing, establishing a hierarchy of mementos and collectibles, calculating the amount of stuff you can bring into your new life, and creating strategies for dividing heirlooms among family members without drama. Change your mindset around possessions and feel freer and happier than you ever thought possible when you learn to Let It Go.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-it-go-downsizing-your-way-to-a-richer-happier-life-peter-walsh-abridged/">Let It Go : Downsizing Your Way to a Richer, Happier Life &#8211; Peter Walsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee and Po Bronson and Ashley Merryman&#8217;s Nurture Shock, New York Times &#8220;Your Money&#8221; columnist Ron Lieber delivers a taboo-shattering manifesto that explains how talking openly to children about money can help parents raise modest, patient, grounded young adults who are financially wise beyond [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/">The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee and Po Bronson and Ashley Merryman&#8217;s Nurture Shock, New York Times &#8220;Your Money&#8221; columnist Ron Lieber delivers a taboo-shattering manifesto that explains how talking openly to children about money can help parents raise modest, patient, grounded young adults who are financially wise beyond their years.  For Ron Lieber, a personal finance columnist and father, good parenting means talking about money with our kids. Children are hyper-aware of money, and they have scores of questions about its nuances. But when parents shy away from the topic, they lose a tremendous opportunity-not just to model the basic financial behaviors that are increasingly important for young adults but also to imprint lessons about what the family truly values.  Written in a warm, accessible voice, grounded in real-world experience and stories from families with a range of incomes, The Opposite of Spoiled is both a practical guidebook and a values-based philosophy.<br />
                    The foundation of the book is a detailed blueprint for the best ways to handle the basics: the tooth fairy, allowance, chores, charity, saving, birthdays, holidays, cell phones, checking accounts, clothing, cars, part-time jobs, and college tuition. It identifies a set of traits and virtues that embody the opposite of spoiled, and shares how to embrace the topic of money to help parents raise kids who are more generous and less materialistic.  But The Opposite of Spoiled is also a promise to our kids that we will make them better with money than we are. It is for all of the parents who know that honest conversations about money with their curious children can help them become more patient and prudent, but who don&#8217;t know how and when to start.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/">The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raising Cain : Protecting the Emotional Life of Boys &#8211; Dan Kindlon, Michael Thompson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Raising Cain, Dan Kindlon, Ph.D., and Michael Thompson, Ph.D., two of the country&#8217;s leading child psychologists, share what they have learned in more than thirty-five years of combined experience working with boys and their families. They reveal a nation of boys who are hurting&#8211;sad, afraid, angry, and silent. Kindlon and Thompson set out to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/">Raising Cain : Protecting the Emotional Life of Boys &#8211; Dan Kindlon, Michael Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Raising Cain, Dan Kindlon, Ph.D., and Michael Thompson, Ph.D., two of the country&#8217;s leading child psychologists, share what they have learned in more than thirty-five years of combined experience working with boys and their families. They reveal a nation of boys who are hurting&#8211;sad, afraid, angry, and silent. Kindlon and Thompson set out to answer this basic, crucial question: What do boys need that they&#8217;re not getting? They illuminate the forces that threaten our boys, teaching them to believe that &#8220;cool&#8221; equals macho strength and stoicism. Cutting through outdated theories of &#8220;mother blame,&#8221; &#8220;boy biology,&#8221; and &#8220;testosterone,&#8221; the authors shed light on the destructive emotional training our boys receive&#8211;the emotional miseducation of boys. Kindlon and Thompson make a compelling case that emotional literacy is the most valuable gift we can offer our sons, urging parents to recognize the price boys pay when we hold them to an impossible standard of manhood. They identify the social and emotional challenges that boys encounter in school and show how parents can help boys cultivate emotional awareness and empathy&#8211;giving them the vital connections and support they need to navigate the social pressures of youth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/">Raising Cain : Protecting the Emotional Life of Boys &#8211; Dan Kindlon, Michael Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Whole-Brain Child : 12 Revolutionary Strategies to Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-whole-brain-child-12-revolutionary-strategies-to-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-whole-brain-child-12-revolutionary-strategies-to-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; More than 1 million copies in print! &#8211; The authors of No-Drama Discipline and The Yes Brain explain the new science of how a child&#8217;s brain is wired and how it matures in this pioneering, practical book. &#8220;Simple, smart, and effective solutions to your child&#8217;s struggles.&#8221;&#8211;Harvey Karp, M.D. In this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-whole-brain-child-12-revolutionary-strategies-to-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/">The Whole-Brain Child : 12 Revolutionary Strategies to Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; More than 1 million copies in print! &#8211; The authors of No-Drama Discipline and The Yes Brain explain the new science of how a child&#8217;s brain is wired and how it matures in this pioneering, practical book.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Simple, smart, and effective solutions to your child&#8217;s struggles.&#8221;&#8211;Harvey Karp, M.D.     </p>
<p>                     In this pioneering, practical book, Daniel J. Siegel, neuropsychiatrist and author of the bestselling Mindsight, and parenting expert Tina Payne Bryson offer a revolutionary approach to child rearing with twelve key strategies that foster healthy brain development, leading to calmer, happier children. The authors explain&#8211;and make accessible&#8211;the new science of how a child&#8217;s brain is wired and how it matures. The &#8220;upstairs brain,&#8221; which makes decisions and balances emotions, is under construction until the mid-twenties. And especially in young children, the right brain and its emotions tend to rule over the logic of the left brain. No wonder kids throw tantrums, fight, or sulk in silence. By applying these discoveries to everyday parenting, you can turn any outburst, argument, or fear into a chance to integrate your child&#8217;s brain and foster vital growth.     </p>
<p>                     Complete with age-appropriate strategies for dealing with day-to-day struggles and illustrations that will help you explain these concepts to your child, The Whole-Brain Child shows you how to cultivate healthy emotional and intellectual development so that your children can lead balanced, meaningful, and connected lives.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;[A] useful child-rearing resource for the entire family . . . The authors include a fair amount of brain science, but they present it for both adult and child audiences.&#8221;&#8211;Kirkus Reviews    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Strategies for getting a youngster to chill out [with] compassion.&#8221;&#8211;The Washington Post    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This erudite, tender, and funny book is filled with fresh ideas based on the latest neuroscience research. I urge all parents who want kind, happy, and emotionally healthy kids to read The Whole-Brain Child. This is my new baby gift.&#8221;&#8211;Mary Pipher, Ph.D., author of Reviving Ophelia and The Shelter of Each Other     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Gives parents and teachers ideas to get all parts of a healthy child&#8217;s brain working together.&#8221;&#8211;Parent to Parent</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-whole-brain-child-12-revolutionary-strategies-to-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/">The Whole-Brain Child : 12 Revolutionary Strategies to Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moms Mean Business : A Guide to Creating a Successful Company and Happy Life as a Mom Entrepreneur &#8211; Lara Galloway, Erin Baebler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/moms-mean-business-a-guide-to-creating-a-successful-company-and-happy-life-as-a-mom-entrepreneur-lara-galloway-erin-baebler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/moms-mean-business-a-guide-to-creating-a-successful-company-and-happy-life-as-a-mom-entrepreneur-lara-galloway-erin-baebler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are 9 million women-owned businesses in the United States; they account for $1.3 trillion in revenue. American women are starting businesses at a rate twice that of men. Most of these women are also moms. What does it take to be successful as both a mom and as an entrepreneur? Moms Mean Business gives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moms-mean-business-a-guide-to-creating-a-successful-company-and-happy-life-as-a-mom-entrepreneur-lara-galloway-erin-baebler-abridged/">Moms Mean Business : A Guide to Creating a Successful Company and Happy Life as a Mom Entrepreneur &#8211; Lara Galloway, Erin Baebler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are 9 million women-owned businesses in the United States; they account for $1.3 trillion in revenue. American women are starting businesses at a rate twice that of men. Most of these women are also moms.     </p>
<p>                    What does it take to be successful as both a mom and as an entrepreneur? Moms Mean Business gives existing and potential mom business owners the encouragement, advice, and healthy dose of how-to they need.     </p>
<p>                    In this helpful guide, you will create a customized strategy that includes:<br />
                    A personal definition of success in both life and business&#8211;and the way to achieve it<br />
                    The tools needed to manage time and productivity when your priorities as a mom and business owner conflict<br />
                    A mom-friendly business plan to get you focused<br />
                    An approach to self-care that allows you to handle all that&#8217;s thrown your way<br />
                    Tips, checklists, and guidance to quickly solve the problems mom entrepreneurs encounter     </p>
<p>                    Behind-the-scenes stories and advice from well-known mom entrepreneurs make Moms Mean Business fun to read and full of that all-important me, too! factor. It is inspiring, motivating, and, above all, practical.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moms-mean-business-a-guide-to-creating-a-successful-company-and-happy-life-as-a-mom-entrepreneur-lara-galloway-erin-baebler-abridged/">Moms Mean Business : A Guide to Creating a Successful Company and Happy Life as a Mom Entrepreneur &#8211; Lara Galloway, Erin Baebler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness. As the focus of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness.    </p>
<p>                    As the focus of the family has turned to the glow of the screen&#8211;children constantly texting their friends or going online to do homework; parents working online around the clock&#8211;everyday life is undergoing a massive transformation. Easy access to the Internet and social media has erased the boundaries that protect children from damaging exposure to excessive marketing and the unsavory aspects of adult culture. Parents often feel they are losing a meaningful connection with their children. Children are feeling lonely and alienated. The digital world is here to stay, but what are families losing with technology&#8217;s gain?    </p>
<p>                    As renowned clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair explains, families are in crisis as they face this issue, and even more so than they realize. Not only do chronic tech distractions have deep and lasting effects but children also desperately need parents to provide what tech cannot: close, significant interactions with the adults in their lives. Drawing on real-life stories from her clinical work with children and parents and her consulting work with educators and experts across the country, Steiner-Adair offers insights and advice that can help parents achieve greater understanding, authority, and confidence as they engage with the tech revolution unfolding in their living rooms.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raising a Secure Child : How Circle of Security Parenting Can Help You Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Attachment, Emotional Resilience, and Freedom to Explore &#8211; Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, Bert Powell, Christine M. Benton, Daniel J. Siegel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raising-a-secure-child-how-circle-of-security-parenting-can-help-you-nurture-your-childs-attachment-emotional-resilience-and-freedom-to-explore-kent-hoffman-glen-cooper-bert-powell-christine/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Counselling & Advice Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raising-a-secure-child-how-circle-of-security-parenting-can-help-you-nurture-your-childs-attachment-emotional-resilience-and-freedom-to-explore-kent-hoffman-glen-cooper-bert-powell-christine/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s parents are constantly pressured to be perfect. But in striving to do everything right, we risk missing what children really need for lifelong emotional security. Now the simple, powerful &#8220;Circle of Security&#8221; parenting strategies that Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, and Bert Powell have taught thousands of families are available in self-help form for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-a-secure-child-how-circle-of-security-parenting-can-help-you-nurture-your-childs-attachment-emotional-resilience-and-freedom-to-explore-kent-hoffman-glen-cooper-bert-powell-christine/">Raising a Secure Child : How Circle of Security Parenting Can Help You Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Attachment, Emotional Resilience, and Freedom to Explore &#8211; Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, Bert Powell, Christine M. Benton, Daniel J. Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s parents are constantly pressured to be perfect. But in striving to do everything right, we risk missing what children really need for lifelong emotional security. Now the simple, powerful &#8220;Circle of Security&#8221; parenting strategies that Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, and Bert Powell have taught thousands of families are available in self-help form for the first time.    </p>
<p>                     You will learn:<br />
                     *How to balance nurturing and protectiveness with promoting your child&#8217;s independence.<br />
                     *What emotional needs a toddler or older child may be expressing through difficult behavior.<br />
                     *How your own upbringing affects your parenting style&#8211;and what you can do about it.    </p>
<p>                     Filled with vivid stories and unique practical tools, this book puts the keys to healthy attachment within everyone&#8217;s reach&#8211;self-understanding, flexibility, and the willingness to make and learn from mistakes. Self-assessment checklists can be downloaded and printed for ease of use.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-a-secure-child-how-circle-of-security-parenting-can-help-you-nurture-your-childs-attachment-emotional-resilience-and-freedom-to-explore-kent-hoffman-glen-cooper-bert-powell-christine/">Raising a Secure Child : How Circle of Security Parenting Can Help You Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Attachment, Emotional Resilience, and Freedom to Explore &#8211; Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, Bert Powell, Christine M. Benton, Daniel J. Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brain Rules for Baby (Updated and Expanded): How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five : How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five &#8211; John Medina (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brain-rules-for-baby-updated-and-expanded-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-john-medina-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brain-rules-for-baby-updated-and-expanded-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-john-medina-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s the single most important thing you can do during pregnancy? What does watching TV do to a child&#8217;s brain? What&#8217;s the best way to handle temper tantrums? Scientists know. In his New York Times bestseller Brain Rules, Dr. John Medina showed us how our brains really work&#8211;and why we ought to redesign our workplaces [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-rules-for-baby-updated-and-expanded-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-john-medina-abridged/">Brain Rules for Baby (Updated and Expanded): How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five : How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five &#8211; John Medina (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s the single most important thing you can do during pregnancy? What does watching TV do to a child&#8217;s brain? What&#8217;s the best way to handle temper tantrums? Scientists know. In his New York Times bestseller Brain Rules, Dr. John Medina showed us how our brains really work&#8211;and why we ought to redesign our workplaces and schools. Now, in Brain Rules for Baby, he shares what the latest science says about how to raise smart and happy children from zero to five. This book is destined to revolutionize parenting. Just one of the surprises: The best way to get your children into the college of their choice? Teach them impulse control. Brain Rules for Baby bridges the gap between what scientists know and what parents practice. Through fascinating and funny stories, Medina, a developmental molecular biologist and dad, unravels how a child&#8217;s brain develops &#8212; and what you can do to optimize it. You will view your children&#8211;and how to raise them&#8211;in a whole new light. You&#8217;ll learn: Where nature ends and nurture begins Why men should do more household chores What you do when emotions run hot affects how your baby turns out, because babies need to feel safe above all TV is harmful for children under 2 Your child&#8217;s ability to relate to others predicts her future math performance Smart and happy are inseparable. Pursuing your child&#8217;s intellectual success at the expense of his happiness achieves neither Praising effort is better than praising intelligence The best predictor of academic performance is not IQ. It&#8217;s self-control What you do right now&#8211;before pregnancy, during pregnancy, and through the first five years&#8211;will affect your children for the rest of their lives. Brain Rules for Baby is an indispensable guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-rules-for-baby-updated-and-expanded-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-john-medina-abridged/">Brain Rules for Baby (Updated and Expanded): How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five : How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five &#8211; John Medina (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Strength Switch : how the new science of strength-based parenting helps your child and your teen flourish &#8211; Lea Waters (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your child&#8217;s potential by helping them build their strengths. As a strengths-based scientist for more than 20 years, Dr Lea Waters has witnessed first-hand how focusing on our children&#8217;s strengths, rather than correcting their weaknesses, can help build resilience and optimism, and offer protection from depression and anxiety. In this game-changing book, she argues [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/">The Strength Switch : how the new science of strength-based parenting helps your child and your teen flourish &#8211; Lea Waters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your child&#8217;s potential by helping them build their strengths.    </p>
<p>                    As a strengths-based scientist for more than 20 years, Dr Lea Waters has witnessed first-hand how focusing on our children&#8217;s strengths, rather than correcting their weaknesses, can help build resilience and optimism, and offer protection from depression and anxiety.     </p>
<p>                    In this game-changing book, she argues that by throwing the &#8216;strength switch&#8217; parents can encourage creativity, develop their children&#8217;s self-esteem and energy, and enhance achievement &#8211; and she offers easy-to-follow steps to teach parents how.    </p>
<p>                    With specific tips for interacting with your kids and your teens, The Strength Switch offers all the tools parents need to discover talents in their children, use positive emotions as a resource, build strong brains, and deal with problem behaviours and difficult emotions. This essential book will show parents how a small shift can yield enormous results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/">The Strength Switch : how the new science of strength-based parenting helps your child and your teen flourish &#8211; Lea Waters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Screamfree Parenting : The Revolutionary Approach to Raising your Kids by Keeping your Cool &#8211; Hal Edward Runkel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Parents are facing the toughest challenge of their lives. They want to create a loving family environment filled with mutual respect and cooperation&#8230; but they find instead that human nature and the influence of our culture combine to produce an atmosphere of anxiety, exhaustion, and far too much screaming. Perhaps you can relate! Whether you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/">Screamfree Parenting : The Revolutionary Approach to Raising your Kids by Keeping your Cool &#8211; Hal Edward Runkel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Parents are facing the toughest challenge of their lives. They want to create a loving family environment filled with mutual respect and cooperation&#8230; but they find instead that human nature and the influence of our culture combine to produce an atmosphere of anxiety, exhaustion, and far too much screaming. Perhaps you can relate!     </p>
<p>                    Whether you scream at your children or not, you no doubt feel anxious about them and their choices. You worry how they&#8217;ll turn out. Unfortunately for parents, many of the techniques some experts present only seem to make matters worse. Hal Edward Runkel has discovered why: Parents are spending far too much time orbiting their lives around their children. They need to return the focus to themselves. They need to grow up and calm down.     </p>
<p>                    ScreamFree Parenting is about taming your reactive responses to your deep anxiety. Rather than learning new techniques, you&#8217;ll discover the liberating principles, based on scriptural truths, that are inspiring parents just like you to revolutionize their family life. Principles that will enable you to remain cool, calm, and connected with your children, no matter what.     </p>
<p>                    Learn how to parent less out of your deepest fears and more out of the highest principles in ScreamFree Parenting.     </p>
<p>                    Special edition distributed through Christian booksellers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/">Screamfree Parenting : The Revolutionary Approach to Raising your Kids by Keeping your Cool &#8211; Hal Edward Runkel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UnSelfie : Why Empathetic Kids Succeed in Our All-About-Me World &#8211; Michele Borba (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unselfie-why-empathetic-kids-succeed-in-our-all-about-me-world-michele-borba-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unselfie-why-empathetic-kids-succeed-in-our-all-about-me-world-michele-borba-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Teens today are forty percent less empathetic than they were thirty years ago. Why is a lack of empathy-which goes hand-in-hand with the self-absorption epidemic Dr. Michele Borba calls the Selfie Syndrome-so dangerous? First, it hurts kids&#8217; academic performance and leads to bullying behaviours. Also, it correlates with more cheating and less resilience. And once [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unselfie-why-empathetic-kids-succeed-in-our-all-about-me-world-michele-borba-abridged/">UnSelfie : Why Empathetic Kids Succeed in Our All-About-Me World &#8211; Michele Borba (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Teens today are forty percent less empathetic than they were thirty years ago. Why is a lack of empathy-which goes hand-in-hand with the self-absorption epidemic Dr. Michele Borba calls the Selfie Syndrome-so dangerous? First, it hurts kids&#8217; academic performance and leads to bullying behaviours. Also, it correlates with more cheating and less resilience. And once children grow up, a lack of empathy hampers their ability to collaborate, innovate and problem-solve-all must-have skills for the global economy.<br />
                         In UnSelfie Dr. Borba pinpoints the forces causing the empathy crisis and shares a revolutionary, researched-based, nine-step plan for reversing it. Empathy is a trait that can be taught and nurtured. Dr. Borba offers a framework for parenting that yields the results we all want: successful, happy kids who also are kind, moral, courageous, and resilient. UnSelfie is a blueprint for parents and educators who want to kids shift their focus from I, me, and mine&#8230;to we, us, and ours.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unselfie-why-empathetic-kids-succeed-in-our-all-about-me-world-michele-borba-abridged/">UnSelfie : Why Empathetic Kids Succeed in Our All-About-Me World &#8211; Michele Borba (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simplicity Parenting : Using the Extraordinary Power of Less to Raise Calmer, Happier, and More Secure Kids &#8211; Kim John Payne, Lisa M. Ross (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s busier, faster society is waging an undeclared war on childhood. With too much stuff, too many choices, and too little time, children can become anxious, have trouble with friends and school, or even be diagnosed with behavioral problems. Now internationally renowned family consultant Kim John Payne helps parents reclaim for their children the space [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/">Simplicity Parenting : Using the Extraordinary Power of Less to Raise Calmer, Happier, and More Secure Kids &#8211; Kim John Payne, Lisa M. Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s busier, faster society is waging an undeclared war on childhood. With too much stuff, too many choices, and too little time, children can become anxious, have trouble with friends and school, or even be diagnosed with behavioral problems. Now internationally renowned family consultant Kim John Payne helps parents reclaim for their children the space and freedom that all kids need for their attention to deepen and their individuality to flourish. Simplicity Parenting offers inspiration, ideas, and a blueprint for change:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Streamline your home environment. Reduce the amount of toys, books, and clutter&#8211;as well as the lights, sounds, and general sensory overload.<br />
                    &#8211; Establish rhythms and rituals. Discover ways to ease daily tensions, create battle-free mealtimes and bedtimes, and tell if your child is overwhelmed.<br />
                    &#8211; Schedule a break in the schedule. Establish intervals of calm and connection in your child&#8217;s daily torrent of constant doing.<br />
                    &#8211; Scale back on media and parental involvement. Manage your children&#8217;s &#8220;screen time&#8221; to limit the endless deluge of information and stimulation.     </p>
<p>                    A manifesto for protecting the grace of childhood, Simplicity Parenting is an eloquent guide to bringing new rhythms to bear on the lifelong art of raising children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/">Simplicity Parenting : Using the Extraordinary Power of Less to Raise Calmer, Happier, and More Secure Kids &#8211; Kim John Payne, Lisa M. Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fifth Trimester : The Working Mom&#8217;s Guide to Style, Sanity, and Success After Baby &#8211; Lauren Smith Brody (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fifth-trimester-the-working-moms-guide-to-style-sanity-and-success-after-baby-lauren-smith-brody-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fifth-trimester-the-working-moms-guide-to-style-sanity-and-success-after-baby-lauren-smith-brody-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Packed with honest, funny, and comforting advice&#8211;&#8220;a book you MUST read if you are returning to work after the birth of a child&#8230;. I loved it and you will too.&#8221; &#8211;New York Times bestselling author Lois P. Frankel, Ph.D. The first three trimesters (and the fourth&#8211;those blurry newborn days) are for the baby, but the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fifth-trimester-the-working-moms-guide-to-style-sanity-and-success-after-baby-lauren-smith-brody-abridged/">The Fifth Trimester : The Working Mom&#8217;s Guide to Style, Sanity, and Success After Baby &#8211; Lauren Smith Brody (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Packed with honest, funny, and comforting advice&#8211;&#8220;a book you MUST read if you are returning to work after the birth of a child&#8230;. I loved it and you will too.&#8221; &#8211;New York Times bestselling author Lois P. Frankel, Ph.D.      </p>
<p>                    The first three trimesters (and the fourth&#8211;those blurry newborn days) are for the baby, but the Fifth Trimester is when the working mom is born. A funny, tells-it-like-it-is guide for new mothers coping with the demands of returning to the real world after giving birth, The Fifth Trimester contains advice from 800 moms, including:     </p>
<p>                     -The boss-approved way to ask for flextime (and more money!)<br />
                    -How to know if it&#8217;s more than &#8220;just the baby blues&#8221;<br />
                    -How to pump breastmilk on an airplane (or, if you must, in a bathroom)<br />
                    -What military science knows about working through sleep deprivation<br />
                    -Your new sixty-second get-out-of-the-house beauty routine<br />
                    -How to turn your commute into a mini-therapy session<br />
                    -Your daycare tour or nanny interview, totally decoded</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fifth-trimester-the-working-moms-guide-to-style-sanity-and-success-after-baby-lauren-smith-brody-abridged/">The Fifth Trimester : The Working Mom&#8217;s Guide to Style, Sanity, and Success After Baby &#8211; Lauren Smith Brody (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The founder and director of the Thirty Million Words Initiative, Professor Dana Suskind, explains why the most important&#8211;and astoundingly simple&#8211;thing you can do for your child&#8217;s future success in life is to to talk to them. What nurtures the brain to optimum intelligence and stability? It is a secret hiding in plain sight: the most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/">Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The founder and director of the Thirty Million Words Initiative, Professor Dana Suskind, explains why the most important&#8211;and astoundingly simple&#8211;thing you can do for your child&#8217;s future success in life is to to talk to them.     </p>
<p>                    What nurtures the brain to optimum intelligence and stability?     </p>
<p>                    It is a secret hiding in plain sight: the most important thing we can do for our children is to have conversations with them. The way you talk with your growing child literally builds his or her brain. Parent talk can drastically improve school readiness and lifelong learning in everything from math to art. Indeed, parent-child talk is a fundamental, critical factor in building grit, self-control, leadership skills, and generosity. It is crucial to making the most in life of the luck you have with your genes.     </p>
<p>                    This landmark account of a new scientific perspective describes what works and what doesn&#8217;t (baby talk is fine; relentless correction isn&#8217;t). Discover how to create the best language environments for children by following the simple structure of the Three Ts: Tune In; Talk More; Take Turns. Dr. Suskind and her colleagues around the country have worked with thousands of families; now their insights and successful, measured approaches are available to all.     </p>
<p>                    This is the first book to reveal how and why the first step in nurturing successful lives is talking to children in ways that build their brains. Your family&#8211;and our nation&#8211;need to know.     </p>
<p>                    *Nominated for the Books for a Better Life Award*</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/">Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Freelance Mum : A Flexible Career Guide for Better Work-Life Balance &#8211; Annie Ridout (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-freelance-mum-a-flexible-career-guide-for-better-work-life-balance-annie-ridout-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-freelance-mum-a-flexible-career-guide-for-better-work-life-balance-annie-ridout-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More time with your kids, making the money you know you&#8217;re worth and a better work/life balance. No wonder more women than ever are choosing to be become freelance mums. In the last decade, 70% more mums have chosen to go freelance. Annie Ridout was one of them. And in her enlightening new book, she [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-freelance-mum-a-flexible-career-guide-for-better-work-life-balance-annie-ridout-abridged/">The Freelance Mum : A Flexible Career Guide for Better Work-Life Balance &#8211; Annie Ridout (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More time with your kids, making the money you know you&#8217;re worth and a better work/life balance. No wonder more women than ever are choosing to be become freelance mums.     </p>
<p>                              In the last decade, 70% more mums have chosen to go freelance. Annie Ridout was one of them. And in her enlightening new book, she shares the tips and tricks that helped her build a better working life around her family.     </p>
<p>                    From choosing a career and launching a website, to getting your name out there and perfecting your brand, to the nitty gritty of childcare options and daily routines, The Freelance Mum is a comprehensive guide to setting out on your own path.    </p>
<p>                    Using her own experience, alongside advice from other mums that make it work, including Arianna Huffington, Scummy Mummies, Carrie-Anne Roberts, Robyn Wilder, Zoe de Pass, Cherry Healey, Sali Hughes and Anna Jones, Annie will show that with hard work and determination, any mother can thrive as a freelancer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-freelance-mum-a-flexible-career-guide-for-better-work-life-balance-annie-ridout-abridged/">The Freelance Mum : A Flexible Career Guide for Better Work-Life Balance &#8211; Annie Ridout (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniquely Human : A Different Way of Seeing Autism &#8211; PH D Barry M Prizant, WithThomas Fields-Meyer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/uniquely-human-a-different-way-of-seeing-autism-ph-d-barry-m-prizant-with-thomas-fields-meyer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paediatric Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/uniquely-human-a-different-way-of-seeing-autism-ph-d-barry-m-prizant-with-thomas-fields-meyer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Autism Society of America&#8217;s Dr. Temple Grandin Award for the Outstanding Literary Work in Autism A groundbreaking book on autism, by one of the world&#8217;s leading experts, who portrays autism as a unique way of being human&#8211;this is &#8220;required reading&#8230;.Breathtakingly simple and profoundly positive&#8221; (Chicago Tribune). Autism therapy typically focuses on ridding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uniquely-human-a-different-way-of-seeing-autism-ph-d-barry-m-prizant-with-thomas-fields-meyer-abridged/">Uniquely Human : A Different Way of Seeing Autism &#8211; PH D Barry M Prizant, WithThomas Fields-Meyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Autism Society of America&#8217;s Dr. Temple Grandin Award for the Outstanding Literary Work in Autism     </p>
<p>                     A groundbreaking book on autism, by one of the world&#8217;s leading experts, who portrays autism as a unique way of being human&#8211;this is &#8220;required reading&#8230;.Breathtakingly simple and profoundly positive&#8221; (Chicago Tribune).     </p>
<p>                    Autism therapy typically focuses on ridding individuals of &#8220;autistic&#8221; symptoms such as difficulties interacting socially, problems in communicating, sensory challenges, and repetitive behavior patterns. Now Dr. Barry M. Prizant offers a new and compelling paradigm: the most successful approaches to autism don&#8217;t aim at fixing a person by eliminating symptoms, but rather seeking to understand the individual&#8217;s experience and what underlies the behavior.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A must-read for anyone touched by autism&#8230; Dr. Prizant&#8217;s Uniquely Human is a crucial step in promoting better understanding and a more humane approach&#8221; (Associated Press). Instead of classifying &#8220;autistic&#8221; behaviors as signs of pathology, Dr. Prizant sees them as part of a range of strategies to cope with a world that feels chaotic and overwhelming. Rather than curb these behaviors, it&#8217;s better to enhance abilities, build on strengths, and offer supports that will lead to more desirable behavior and a better quality of life.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A remarkable approach to autism&#8230;.A truly impactful, necessary book&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review), Uniquely Human offers inspiration and practical advice drawn from Dr. Prizant&#8217;s four-decade career. It conveys a deep respect for people with autism and their own unique qualities. Filled with humanity and wisdom, Uniquely Human &#8220;should reassure parents and caregivers of kids with autism and any other disability that their kids are not broken, but, indeed, special&#8221; (Booklist, starred review).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uniquely-human-a-different-way-of-seeing-autism-ph-d-barry-m-prizant-with-thomas-fields-meyer-abridged/">Uniquely Human : A Different Way of Seeing Autism &#8211; PH D Barry M Prizant, WithThomas Fields-Meyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Raise Successful People: Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient : Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient &#8211; Esther Wojcicki (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-raise-successful-people-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-esth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secondary Schools]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-raise-successful-people-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-esth/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Godmother of Silicon Valley, legendary teacher, and mother of a Super Family shares her tried-and-tested methods for raising happy, healthy, successful children using Trust, Respect, Independence, Collaboration, and Kindness: TRICK. Esther Wojcicki&#8211;&#8220;Woj&#8221; to her many friends and admirers&#8211;is famous for three things: teaching a high school class that has changed the lives of thousands [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-successful-people-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-esth/">How to Raise Successful People: Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient : Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient &#8211; Esther Wojcicki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Godmother of Silicon Valley, legendary teacher, and mother of a Super Family shares her tried-and-tested methods for raising happy, healthy, successful children using Trust, Respect, Independence, Collaboration, and Kindness: TRICK.    </p>
<p>                    Esther Wojcicki&#8211;&#8220;Woj&#8221; to her many friends and admirers&#8211;is famous for three things: teaching a high school class that has changed the lives of thousands of kids, inspiring Silicon Valley legends like Steve Jobs, and raising three daughters who have each become famously successful. What do these three accomplishments have in common? They&#8217;re the result of TRICK, Woj&#8217;s secret to raising successful people: Trust, Respect, Independence, Collaboration, and Kindness.     </p>
<p>                    Simple lessons, but the results are radical. Wojcicki&#8217;s methods are the opposite of helicopter parenting. As we face an epidemic of parental anxiety, Woj is here to say: relax. Talk to infants as if they are adults. Allow teenagers to pick projects that relate to the real world and their own passions, and let them figure out how to complete them. Above all, let your child lead. How to Raise Successful People offers essential lessons for raising, educating, and managing people to their highest potential. Change your parenting, change the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-successful-people-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-esth/">How to Raise Successful People: Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient : Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient &#8211; Esther Wojcicki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weird Parenting Wins : Bathtub Dining, Family Screams, and Other Hacks from the Parenting Trenches &#8211; Hillary Frank (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unconventional&#8211;yet effective&#8211;parenting strategies, carefully curated by the creator of the popular podcast The Longest Shortest Time Some of the best parenting advice that Hillary Frank ever received did not come from parenting experts, but from friends and podcast listeners who acted on a whim, often in moments of desperation. These weird parenting wins were born [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/">Weird Parenting Wins : Bathtub Dining, Family Screams, and Other Hacks from the Parenting Trenches &#8211; Hillary Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unconventional&#8211;yet effective&#8211;parenting strategies, carefully curated by the creator of the popular podcast The Longest Shortest Time     </p>
<p>                    Some of the best parenting advice that Hillary Frank ever received did not come from parenting experts, but from friends and podcast listeners who acted on a whim, often in moments of desperation. These weird parenting wins were born of moments when the expert advice wasn&#8217;t working, and instead of freaking out, these parents had a stroke of genius. For example, there&#8217;s the dad who pig-snorted in his baby&#8217;s ear to get her to stop crying, and the mom who made a flat daddy out of cardboard and sat it at the dinner table when her kids were missing their deployed military father.<br />
                     Every parent and kid is unique, and as we get to know our kids, we can figure out what makes them tick. Because this is an ongoing process, Weird Parenting Wins covers children of all ages, ranging in topics from The Art of Getting Your Kid to Act Like a Person (on hygiene, potty training, and manners) to The Art of Getting Your Kid to Tell You Things (because eventually, they&#8217;re going to be tight-lipped). You may find that someone else&#8217;s weird parenting win works for you, or you might be inspired to try something new the next time you&#8217;re stuck in a parenting rut. Or maybe you&#8217;ll just get a good laugh out of the mom who got her kid to try beets because&#8230;it might turn her poop pink.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/">Weird Parenting Wins : Bathtub Dining, Family Screams, and Other Hacks from the Parenting Trenches &#8211; Hillary Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A personal and powerful essay from Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie, the bestselling author of Americanah and Half of a Yellow Sun. &#8216;I would like to ask that we begin to dream about and plan for a different world. A fairer world. A world of happier men and happier women who are truer to themselves. And this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A personal and powerful essay from Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie, the bestselling author of Americanah and Half of a Yellow Sun.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;I would like to ask that we begin to dream about and plan for a different world. A fairer world. A world of happier men and happier women who are truer to themselves. And this is how to start: we must raise our daughters differently. We must also raise our sons differently&#8230;&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              What does &#8220;feminism&#8221; mean today?    </p>
<p>                              In this personal, eloquently argued essay &#8211; adapted from her much-admired Tedx talk of the same name &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie offers readers a unique definition of feminism for the twenty-first century, one rooted in inclusion and awareness. Drawing extensively on her own experiences and her deep understanding of the often masked realities of sexual politics, here is one remarkable author&#8217;s exploration of what it means to be a woman now &#8211; an of-the-moment rallying cry for why we should all be feminists.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiest Baby on the Block; Fully Revised and Updated Second Edition : The New Way to Calm Crying and Help Your Newborn Baby Sleep Longer &#8211; Harvey Karp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Never again will you have to stand by helplessly while your little baby cries and cries. There is a way to calm most crying babies . . . usually in minutes! Thousands of parents, from regular moms and dads to Hollywood superstars, have come to baby expert Dr. Harvey Karp to learn his remarkable techniques [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/">The Happiest Baby on the Block; Fully Revised and Updated Second Edition : The New Way to Calm Crying and Help Your Newborn Baby Sleep Longer &#8211; Harvey Karp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Never again will you have to stand by helplessly while your little baby cries and cries. There is a way to calm most crying babies . . . usually in minutes!      </p>
<p>                     Thousands of parents, from regular moms and dads to Hollywood superstars, have come to baby expert Dr. Harvey Karp to learn his remarkable techniques for soothing babies and increasing sleep. Now his landmark book&#8211;fully revised and updated with the latest insights into infant sleep, bedsharing, breastfeeding, swaddling, and SIDS risk&#8211;can teach you too! Dr. Karp&#8217;s highly successful method is based on four revolutionary concepts:     </p>
<p>                     1. The Fourth Trimester: Why babies still yearn for a womblike atmosphere . . . even after birth<br />
                     2. The Calming Reflex: An &#8220;off switch&#8221; all babies are born with<br />
                     3. The 5 S&#8217;s: Five easy steps to turn on your baby&#8217;s amazing calming reflex<br />
                     4. The Cuddle Cure:  How to combine the 5 S&#8217;s to calm even colicky babies     </p>
<p>                     With Dr. Karp&#8217;s sensible advice, parents and grandparents, nurses and nannies, will be able to transform even the fussiest infant into the happiest baby on the block!     </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Happiest Baby on the Block     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Dr. Karp&#8217;s book is fascinating and will guide new parents for years to come.&#8221;&#8211;Julius Richmond, M.D., Harvard Medical School, former Surgeon General of the United States     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Happiest Baby on the Block is fun and convincing. I highly recommend it.&#8221;&#8211;Elisabeth Bing, co-founder of Lamaze International     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Will fascinate anyone who wants to know how babies experience the world, and wants to answer their cries lovingly and effectively.&#8221;&#8211;The San Diego Union-Tribune</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/">The Happiest Baby on the Block; Fully Revised and Updated Second Edition : The New Way to Calm Crying and Help Your Newborn Baby Sleep Longer &#8211; Harvey Karp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER From the UK&#8217;s favourite therapist, as seen on Channel 4&#8217;s Grayson&#8217;s Art Club. &#8216;A wonderful book&#8217; Richard Osman &#8216;So clear and true &#8230; Helpful for all relationships in life&#8217; Nigella Lawson &#8216;A fascinating read on the emotional baggage we all carry&#8217; Elizabeth Day ______________________________________________________________________________________ How can we have better relationships? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/">The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    From the UK&#8217;s favourite therapist, as seen on Channel 4&#8217;s Grayson&#8217;s Art Club.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wonderful book&#8217; Richard Osman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;So clear and true &#8230; Helpful for all relationships in life&#8217; Nigella Lawson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fascinating read on the emotional baggage we all carry&#8217; Elizabeth Day<br />
                    ______________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    How can we have better relationships?    </p>
<p>                    In this Sunday Times bestseller, leading psychotherapist Philippa Perry reveals the vital do&#8217;s and don&#8217;ts of relationships. This is a book for us all. Whether you are interested in understanding how your upbringing has shaped you, looking to handle your child&#8217;s feelings or wishing to support your partner, you will find indispensable information and realistic tips in these pages. Philippa Perry&#8217;s sane, sage and judgement-free advice is an essential resource on how to have the best possible relationships with the people who matter to you most.<br />
                    _____________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It gave me hope as a new parent&#8217; Babita Sharma    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This has genuinely had such a positive impact on my life and my relationship with my daughter&#8217; Josh Widdicombe    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;She writes with an inquisitive elegance rarely found in parenting guides &#8230; it is forgiving and persuasive&#8217;   Hadley Freeman, the Guardian      </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Philippa Perry is one of the wisest, most sane and secure people I&#8217;ve ever met&#8217; Decca Aitkenhead, Sunday Times Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/">The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Importance Of Being Little : What Preschoolers Really Need from Grownups &#8211; Erika Christakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pre-school & Kindergarten]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Christakis . . . expertly weaves academic research, personal experience and anecdotal evidence into her book . . . a bracing and convincing case that early education has reached a point of crisis . . . her book is a rare thing: a serious work of research that also happens to be well-written and personal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/">The Importance Of Being Little : What Preschoolers Really Need from Grownups &#8211; Erika Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Christakis . . . expertly weaves academic research, personal experience and anecdotal evidence into her book . . . a bracing and convincing case that early education has reached a point of crisis . . . her book is a rare thing: a serious work of research that also happens to be well-written and personal . . . engaging and important.&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;Washington Post     </p>
<p>                    What kids need from grown-ups (but aren&#8217;t getting)&#8230;an impassioned plea for educators and parents to put down the worksheets and flash cards, ditch the tired craft projects (yes, you, Thanksgiving Handprint Turkey) and exotic vocabulary lessons, and double-down on one, simple word: play.<br />
                    &#8211;NPR     </p>
<p>                    The New York Times bestseller that provides a bold challenge to the conventional wisdom about early childhood, with a pragmatic program to encourage parents and teachers to rethink how and where young children learn best by taking the child&#8217;s eye view of the learning environment     </p>
<p>                     To a four-year-old watching bulldozers at a construction site or chasing butterflies in flight, the world is awash with promise. Little children come into the world hardwired to learn in virtually any setting and about any matter. Yet in today&#8217;s preschool and kindergarten classrooms, learning has been reduced to scripted lessons and suspect metrics that too often undervalue a child&#8217;s intelligence while overtaxing the child&#8217;s growing brain. These mismatched expectations wreak havoc on the family: parents fear that if they choose the &#8220;wrong&#8221; program, their child won&#8217;t get into the &#8220;right&#8221; college. But Yale early childhood expert Erika Christakis says our fears are wildly misplaced. Our anxiety about preparing and safeguarding our children&#8217;s future seems to have reached a fever pitch at a time when, ironically, science gives us more certainty than ever before that young children are exceptionally strong thinkers.<br />
                     In her pathbreaking book, Christakis explains what it&#8217;s like to be a young child in America today, in a world designed by and for adults, where we have confused schooling with learning. She offers real-life solutions to real-life issues, with nuance and direction that takes us far beyond the usual prescriptions for fewer tests, more play. She looks at children&#8217;s use of language, their artistic expressions, the way their imaginations grow, and how they build deep emotional bonds to stretch the boundaries of their small worlds. Rather than clutter their worlds with more and more stuff, sometimes the wisest course for us is to learn how to get out of their way.<br />
                     Christakis&#8217;s message is energizing and reassuring: young children are inherently powerful, and they (and their parents) will flourish when we learn new ways of restoring the vital early learning environment to one that is best suited to the littlest learners. This bold and pragmatic challenge to the conventional wisdom peels back the mystery of childhood, revealing a place that&#8217;s rich with possibility.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/">The Importance Of Being Little : What Preschoolers Really Need from Grownups &#8211; Erika Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sacred Cows : The Truth About Divorce and Marriage &#8211; M.D. Danielle Teller, Astro Teller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sacred-cows-the-truth-about-divorce-and-marriage-m-d-danielle-teller-astro-teller-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Separation & Divorce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sacred-cows-the-truth-about-divorce-and-marriage-m-d-danielle-teller-astro-teller-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Astro Teller currently oversees Google[x] and Danielle Teller is a physician specializing in the fields of intensive care and lung medicine. Together, they bring a fresh and startling perspective on marriage and divorce in SACRED COWS. Drs. Astro and Danielle Teller know better than most that finding the right partner in life doesn&#8217;t always happen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sacred-cows-the-truth-about-divorce-and-marriage-m-d-danielle-teller-astro-teller-abridged/">Sacred Cows : The Truth About Divorce and Marriage &#8211; M.D. Danielle Teller, Astro Teller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Astro Teller currently oversees Google[x] and Danielle Teller is a physician specializing in the fields of intensive care and lung medicine. Together, they bring a fresh and startling perspective on marriage and divorce in SACRED COWS.    </p>
<p>                     Drs. Astro and Danielle Teller know better than most that finding the right partner in life doesn&#8217;t always happen the first time around. Through their own divorces they learned how widely held cultural assumptions and misinformation that nobody thinks to question-what they refer to as &#8220;sacred cows&#8221;-create unnecessary heartache for people who are already suffering through a terrible time.    </p>
<p>                     Do you think, for example, that the divorce rate in the United States is rising? Or that children are harmed by divorce? Most people do, but it turns out that neither of these notions is supported by the data. Combining the rigor that has established them as leaders in their respective fields along with a dose of good-natured humor, the Tellers ask readers to take a fresh look at seven common sacred cows: the Holy Cow, the Expert Cow, the Selfish Cow, the Defective Cow, the Innocent Victim Cow, the One True Cow, and the Other Cow. This is not a book that is &#8220;for&#8221; marriage or &#8220;for&#8221; divorce, but &#8220;for&#8221; the freedom to decide how to live most honestly and happily either as part of a couple or a single person.    </p>
<p>                     In the same way that Esther Perel&#8217;s bestselling MATING IN CAPTIVITY gave couples a fresh perspective on their married life, so SACRED COWS invites readers to question assumptions and conventional wisdom. It offers a smart, insightful, and sympathetic view for those in a marital crisis, marriage counsellors, or anyone looking to gain a fresh perspective on one of our most cherished and misunderstood institutions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sacred-cows-the-truth-about-divorce-and-marriage-m-d-danielle-teller-astro-teller-abridged/">Sacred Cows : The Truth About Divorce and Marriage &#8211; M.D. Danielle Teller, Astro Teller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cribsheet : A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting, from Birth to Preschool &#8211; Emily Oster (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Emily Oster is the non-judgemental girlfriend holding our hand and guiding us through pregnancy and motherhood. She has done the work to get us the hard facts in a soft, understandable way&#8217; Amy Schumer Parenting is full of decisions, nearly all of which can be agonized over. There is an abundance of often-conflicting advice hurled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/">Cribsheet : A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting, from Birth to Preschool &#8211; Emily Oster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Emily Oster is the non-judgemental girlfriend holding our hand and guiding us through pregnancy and motherhood. She has done the work to get us the hard facts in a soft, understandable way&#8217; Amy Schumer    </p>
<p>                    Parenting is full of decisions, nearly all of which can be agonized over. There is an abundance of often-conflicting advice hurled at you from doctors, family, friends, and strangers on the internet. But the benefits of these choices can be overstated, and the trade-offs can be profound. How do you make your own best decision?     </p>
<p>                     Armed with the data, Oster finds that the conventional wisdom doesn&#8217;t always hold up. She debunks myths and offers non-judgemental ways to consider our options in light of the facts. Cribsheet is a thinking parent&#8217;s guide that empowers us to make better, less fraught decisions &#8211; and stay sane in the years before preschool.    </p>
<p>                    *Now you can navigate the primary school years with Emily Oster too, in her new book The Family Firm, out now*</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/">Cribsheet : A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting, from Birth to Preschool &#8211; Emily Oster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting To 50/50 : How Working Parents Can Have It All &#8211; Sharon Meers, Joanna Strober (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-to-50-50-how-working-parents-can-have-it-all-sharon-meers-joanna-strober-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-to-50-50-how-working-parents-can-have-it-all-sharon-meers-joanna-strober-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the ForeWord Reviews 2013 IndieFab Awards Silver medal in the category of Family &#038; Relationships Winner of the Independent Publisher Book Awards 2014 Gold medal in the category of Parenting Sharon Meers and Joanna Strober are professionals wives and mothers. They understand the challenges and rewards of two-career households. They also know that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-to-50-50-how-working-parents-can-have-it-all-sharon-meers-joanna-strober-abridged/">Getting To 50/50 : How Working Parents Can Have It All &#8211; Sharon Meers, Joanna Strober (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the ForeWord Reviews 2013 IndieFab Awards Silver medal in the category of Family &#038; Relationships     </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Independent Publisher Book Awards 2014 Gold medal in the category of Parenting     </p>
<p>                    Sharon Meers and Joanna Strober are professionals wives and mothers. They understand the challenges and rewards of two-career households. They also know that families thrive not in spite of working mothers but because of them. You can have a great career a great marriage and be a great mother. The key is tapping into your best resource and most powerful ally&#8211;the man you married.     </p>
<p>                    After interviewing hundreds of parents and employers surveying more than a thousand working mothers and combing through the latest government and social science research the authors have discovered that kids husbands and wives all reap huge benefits when couples commit to share equally as breadwinners and caregivers. Mothers work without guilt fathers bond with their kids and children blossom with the attention of two involved parents.     </p>
<p>                    From baby boot camp for new dads to exactly what to say when negotiating a leave with the boss this savvy book offers fresh ideas to today&#8217;s families offering encouragement hope and confidence to any woman who has ever questioned her choices regarding work and family.     </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Independent Publisher Award Gold Medal in Parenting</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-to-50-50-how-working-parents-can-have-it-all-sharon-meers-joanna-strober-abridged/">Getting To 50/50 : How Working Parents Can Have It All &#8211; Sharon Meers, Joanna Strober (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chika Jeune was born three days before the devastating earthquake that decimated Haiti in 2010. She spent her infancy in extreme poverty, and when her mother died giving birth to a baby brother, Chika was brought to the Have Faith Haiti Orphanage that Mitch and his wife, Janine operate. Chika&#8217;s arrival made a quick impression. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/">Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chika Jeune was born three days before the devastating earthquake that decimated Haiti in 2010. She spent her infancy in extreme poverty, and when her mother died giving birth to a baby brother, Chika was brought to the Have Faith Haiti Orphanage that Mitch and his wife, Janine operate.    </p>
<p>                    Chika&#8217;s arrival made a quick impression. Brave and self-assured, even as a three-year-old, she delighted the other kids and teachers. But at age five, Chika was suddenly diagnosed with a terminal disease that no doctor in Haiti could help with.    </p>
<p>                    Mitch and Janine took Chika to America, hoping that treatment there would enable her to go back home.  Instead, Chika became a permanent part of their lives, as they embarked on a two-year, around-the-world journey to find a cure. As Chika&#8217;s boundless optimism and humour taught Mitch the joys of caring for a child, he learnt that a relationship built on love, no matter what blows it takes, can never be lost.    </p>
<p>                    This is Mitch Albom at his most poignant, powerful and personal. Chika is a celebration of a girl, her adoptive guardians, and the incredible bond they formed &#8211; a devastatingly beautiful portrait of what it means to be a family, regardless of how it is made.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/">Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Untangled : Guiding Teenage Girls Through the Seven Transitions into Adulthood &#8211; Lisa Damour (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leading clinical psychologist Lisa Damour identifies the seven key phases marking the journey from girlhood to womanhood, and offers practical advice for those raising teenage girls. We expect an enormous amount from our teenage girls in a world where they are bombarded with messages about how they should look, behave, succeed. Yet we also speak [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/">Untangled : Guiding Teenage Girls Through the Seven Transitions into Adulthood &#8211; Lisa Damour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading clinical psychologist Lisa Damour identifies the seven key phases marking the journey from girlhood to womanhood, and offers practical advice for those raising teenage girls.    </p>
<p>                    We expect an enormous amount from our teenage girls in a world where they are bombarded with messages about how they should look, behave, succeed. Yet we also speak as though adolescence is a nightmare rollercoaster ride for both parent and child, to be endured rather than enjoyed.     </p>
<p>                    In Untangled, world authority and clinical psychologist Lisa Damour provides an accessible, detailed, comprehensive guide to parenting teenage girls. She believes there is a predictable blueprint for how girls grow; seven easily recognisable &#8216;strands&#8217; of transition from childhood through adolescence and on to adulthood. Girls naturally develop at different rates, typically on more than one front, and the transition will be unique to every girl.     </p>
<p>                    Each chapter describes a phase, such as &#8216;contending with adult authority&#8217; and &#8216;entering the romantic world&#8217;, with hints and tips for parents and daughters, and a &#8216;when to worry&#8217; section. Damour writes sympathetically and clearly, providing a practical and helpful guide for any parent, and for teenage girls too.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/">Untangled : Guiding Teenage Girls Through the Seven Transitions into Adulthood &#8211; Lisa Damour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend. A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend.<br />
                              A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. Dear Ijeawele is Adichie&#8217;s letter of response.    </p>
<p>                              Here are fifteen invaluable suggestions-compelling, direct, wryly funny, and perceptive-for how to empower a daughter to become a strong, independent woman. From encouraging her to choose a helicopter, and not only a doll, as a toy if she so desires; having open conversations with her about clothes, makeup, and sexuality; debunking the myth that women are somehow biologically arranged to be in the kitchen making dinner, and that men can &#8220;allow&#8221; women to have full careers, Dear Ijeawele goes right to the heart of sexual politics in the twenty-first century. It will start a new and urgently needed conversation about what it really means to be a woman today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s Going on in There? : How the Brain and Mind Develop in the First Five Years of Life &#8211; Lise Eliot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As a research neuroscientist, Lise Eliot has made the study of the human brain her life&#8217;s work. But it wasn&#8217;t until she was pregnant with her first child that she became intrigued with the study of brain development. She wanted to know precisely how the baby&#8217;s brain is formed, and when and how each sense, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/">What&#8217;s Going on in There? : How the Brain and Mind Develop in the First Five Years of Life &#8211; Lise Eliot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As a research neuroscientist, Lise Eliot has made the study of the human brain her life&#8217;s work. But it wasn&#8217;t until she was pregnant with her first child that she became intrigued with the study of brain development. She wanted to know precisely how the baby&#8217;s brain is formed, and when and how each sense, skill, and cognitive ability is developed. And just as important, she was interested in finding out how her role as a nurturer can affect this complex process. How much of her baby&#8217;s development is genetically ordained&#8211;and how much is determined by environment? Is there anything parents can do to make their babies&#8217; brains work better&#8211;to help them become smarter, happier people? Drawing upon the exploding research in this field as well as the stories of real children, What&#8217;s Going On in There? is a lively and thought-provoking book that charts the brain&#8217;s development from conception through the critical first five years. In examining the many factors that play crucial roles in that process, What&#8217;s Going On in There? explores the evolution of the senses, motor skills, social and emotional behaviors, and mental functions such as attention, language, memory, reasoning, and intelligence. This remarkable book also discusses:     </p>
<p>                     how a baby&#8217;s brain is &#8220;assembled&#8221; from scratch<br />
                    the critical prenatal factors that shapebrain development<br />
                    how the birthing process itself affects the brain<br />
                    which forms of stimulation are most effective at promoting cognitive development<br />
                    how boys&#8217; and girls&#8217; brains develop differently<br />
                    how nutrition, stress, and other physical and social factors can permanently affect a child&#8217;s brain     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly blending cutting-edge science with a mother&#8217;s wisdom and insight, What&#8217;s Going On in There? is an invaluable contribution to the nature versus nurture debate. Children&#8217;s development is determined both by the genes they are born with and the richness of their early environment. This timely and important book shows parents the innumerable ways in which they can actually help their children grow better brains.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/">What&#8217;s Going on in There? : How the Brain and Mind Develop in the First Five Years of Life &#8211; Lise Eliot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother &#8211; Amy Chua (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/battle-hymn-of-the-tiger-mother-amy-chua-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/battle-hymn-of-the-tiger-mother-amy-chua-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated with a new postscript by Amy Chua and a letter from her eldest daughter, Sophia Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother is a story about a mother, two daughters, and two dogs. It was supposed to be a story of how Chinese parents are better at raising kids than Western ones. But instead, it&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/battle-hymn-of-the-tiger-mother-amy-chua-abridged/">Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother &#8211; Amy Chua (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated with a new postscript by Amy Chua and a letter from her eldest daughter, Sophia    </p>
<p>                    Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother is a story about a mother, two daughters, and two dogs. It was supposed to be a story of how Chinese parents are better at raising kids than Western ones. But instead, it&#8217;s about a bitter clash of cultures, a fleeting taste of glory, and how you can be humbled by a thirteen-year-old.    </p>
<p>                    Witty, entertaining and provocative, this is a unique and important book that will transform your perspective of parenting forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/battle-hymn-of-the-tiger-mother-amy-chua-abridged/">Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother &#8211; Amy Chua (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Raise an Adult &#8211; Julie Lythcott-Haims (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-raise-an-adult-julie-lythcott-haims-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-raise-an-adult-julie-lythcott-haims-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Across a decade as Stanford University&#8217;s dean of freshmen, Julie Lythcott-Haims noticed a startling rise in parental involvement in students&#8217; lives. Every year, more parents were exerting control over students&#8217; academic work, extracurricular, and career choices, taking matters into their own hands rather than risk their child&#8217;s failure or disappointment. Meanwhile, Lythcott-Haims encountered increasing numbers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-an-adult-julie-lythcott-haims-abridged/">How to Raise an Adult &#8211; Julie Lythcott-Haims (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Across a decade as Stanford University&#8217;s dean of freshmen, Julie Lythcott-Haims noticed a startling rise in parental involvement in students&#8217; lives. Every year, more parents were exerting control over students&#8217; academic work, extracurricular, and career choices, taking matters into their own hands rather than risk their child&#8217;s failure or disappointment. Meanwhile, Lythcott-Haims encountered increasing numbers of students who, as a result of hyper attentive parenting, lacked a strong sense of self and were poorly equipped to handle the demands of adult life. In How to Raise an Adult, Lythcott-Haims draws on research, on conversations with admissions officers, educators, and employers, and on her own insights as a mother and as a student clean to highlight the ways in which over parenting harms children and their stressed-out parents, and our society at large. While empathising with the parental hopes and, especially, fears that lead to over helping, Lythcott-Haims offers practical alternative strategies that underline the importance of allowing children to make their own mistakes and develop the resilience, resourcefulness, and inner determination necessary for success.<br />
                    Relevant to parents of toddlers as well as of twenty something&#8217;s and of special value to parents of teens &#8211; this book is a rallying cry for those who wish to ensure that the next generation can take charge of their own lives with competence and confidence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-an-adult-julie-lythcott-haims-abridged/">How to Raise an Adult &#8211; Julie Lythcott-Haims (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maid : A Barack Obama Summer Reading Pick and now a major Netflix series! &#8211; Stephanie Land (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/maid-a-barack-obama-summer-reading-pick-and-now-a-major-netflix-series-stephanie-land-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/maid-a-barack-obama-summer-reading-pick-and-now-a-major-netflix-series-stephanie-land-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NOW A NETFLIX SERIES STARRING MARGARET QUALLEY &#038; ANDY MACDOWELL. BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S SUMMER READING PICK, 2019. BBC RADIO 4 BOOK OF THE WEEK. Educated meets Nickel and Dimed in Stephanie Land&#8217;s memoir about working as a maid. A beautiful and gritty exploration of poverty in the western world. Includes a foreword by international bestelling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maid-a-barack-obama-summer-reading-pick-and-now-a-major-netflix-series-stephanie-land-abridged/">Maid : A Barack Obama Summer Reading Pick and now a major Netflix series! &#8211; Stephanie Land (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NOW A NETFLIX SERIES STARRING MARGARET QUALLEY &#038; ANDY MACDOWELL.<br />
                    BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S SUMMER READING PICK, 2019.<br />
                    BBC RADIO 4 BOOK OF THE WEEK.    </p>
<p>                    Educated meets Nickel and Dimed  in Stephanie Land&#8217;s memoir about working as a maid. A beautiful and  gritty exploration of poverty in the western world. Includes a foreword  by international bestelling author Barbara Ehrenreich.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My daughter learned to walk in a homeless shelter.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    As  a struggling single mum, determined to keep a roof over her daughter&#8217;s  head, Stephanie Land worked for years as a maid, working long hours in  order to provide for her small family. In Maid, she reveals the dark truth of what it takes to survive and thrive in today&#8217;s inequitable society.    </p>
<p>                      As she worked hard to climb her way out of poverty as a single parent,  scrubbing the toilets of the wealthy, navigating domestic labour jobs as  a cleaner whilst also juggling higher education, assisted housing, and a  tangled web of government assistance, Stephanie wrote. She wrote the  true stories that weren&#8217;t being told. The stories of the overworked and  underpaid.    </p>
<p>                     Written in honest, heart-rending prose and with great insight, Maid  explores the underbelly of the upper-middle classes and the reality of  what it&#8217;s like to be in service to them. &#8216;I&#8217;d become a nameless ghost,&#8217;  Stephanie writes. With this book, she gives voice to the &#8216;servant&#8217;  worker, those who fight daily to scramble and scrape by for their own  lives and the lives of their children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maid-a-barack-obama-summer-reading-pick-and-now-a-major-netflix-series-stephanie-land-abridged/">Maid : A Barack Obama Summer Reading Pick and now a major Netflix series! &#8211; Stephanie Land (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-alcoholic Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217; &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217;  &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller      </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice O&#8217;Keeffe, Guardian     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Truthful, modern and real&#8217; &#8211; Stylist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Brave, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober came to me at a time when I much needed it&#8230; The book became my best friend, and got me through, and took me on a journey.&#8217; &#8211; Sadie Frost     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Particularly lovely, because it&#8217;s not a deep and dark dive into someone&#8217;s terrible addiction. It&#8217;s a celebration of everything that she has gained from not drinking&#8217; &#8211; Laura Donnelly     </p>
<p>                    Ever sworn off alcohol for a month and found yourself drinking by the 7th? Think there&#8217;s &#8216;no point&#8217; in just one drink? Welcome! There are millions of us. 64% of Brits want to drink less.    </p>
<p>                    Catherine Gray was stuck in a hellish whirligig of Drink, Make horrible decisions, Hangover, Repeat. She had her fair share of &#8216;drunk tank&#8217; jail cells and topless-in-a-hot-tub misadventures.    </p>
<p>                    But this book goes beyond the binges and blackouts to deep-dive into uncharted territory: What happens after you quit drinking? This gripping, heart-breaking and witty book takes us down the rabbit-hole of an alternative reality. A life with zero hangovers, through sober weddings, sex, Christmases and breakups.     </p>
<p>                    In The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober, Catherine Gray shines a light on society&#8217;s drink-pushing and talks to top neuroscientists and psychologists about why we drink, delving into the science behind what it does to our brains and bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Much more than a tale from the netherworld of addicted drinking, this book is about the escape, and why a sober life can be more intoxicating than you ever imagined. Whether you&#8217;re a hopelessly devoted drinker, merely sober-curious, or you&#8217;ve already ditched the drink, you will love this book.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Haunting, admirable and enlightening&#8217; &#8211; The Pool     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A riveting, raw, yet humorous memoir with actionable advice. A truly unique blend of storytelling and science that holds a universe of hope.&#8217; &#8211; Annie Grace, author of This Naked Mind     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Like listening to your best friend teach you to be sober. Lighthearted but serious, it&#8217;s packed with ideas, tools, tips and, most importantly, reasons for living a sober life. This book is excellent.&#8217;- Eric Zimmer, host of podcast The One You Feed     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s fizzy writing succeeds in making this potentially boring-as-hell subject both engaging and highly seductive&#8217; &#8211; The Bookseller     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray is an exceptional writer. Her exquisitely crafted thoughts on the joys of being sober are not only deeply honest and pragmatic, but she manages to infuse tons of humor. This is a delightful, informative, and compelling read for all those who are sober or seeking sobriety.&#8217; &#8211; Sasha Tozzi, Huffington Post columnist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine&#8217;s writing style and voice captivate me. She has a way of translating her story into an experience I don&#8217;t want to end. I want to drink every drop she produces.&#8217; &#8211; Holly Whitaker, founder of Hip Sobriety School and co-presenter of Home podcast     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book is great. A balanced, informative and entertaining melange of memoir, sociology and psychology. I identified very strongly with huge sections of it.&#8217; &#8211; Jon Stewart, guitarist of Sleeper and Leaving AA, Staying Sober blogger >    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Sober is too often equated with &#8220;sombre&#8221; in our culture. Gray&#8217;s book turns that idea on its head. Her experience of sobriety is joyful and life-affirming. A must-read for anyone who has a nagging suspicion that alcohol may be taking away more than it&#8217;s giving.&#8217; &#8211; Hilda Burke, psychotherapist and couples counsellor     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray really captures the FUN we can have in sobriety. This book challenges the status quo; sobriet sounds as liberating as taking a trip to the jungle. Fun and inspirational. What an important book for our time! A joy to read.&#8217; &#8211; Samantha Moyo, founder of Morning Gloryville     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;No other author writes about sober living with as much warmth or emotional range as Catherine Gray. Her deep insight into the subtle psychologies of drinking, and of life, means that everything she writes is both utterly relatable and stretches our minds. Hers is a rare wisdom.&#8217; &#8211; Dr Richard Piper, CEO, Alcohol Change UK</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 3 MILLION COPIES SOLD Do you ever suspect that everyone else has life figured out and you don&#8217;t have a clue? If so, Rachel Hollis has something to tell you: that&#8217;s a lie. If you have ever said any of these things to yourself . . . Something [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/">Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 3 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    Do you ever suspect that everyone else has life figured out and you don&#8217;t have a clue? If so, Rachel Hollis has something to tell you: that&#8217;s a lie.    </p>
<p>                    If you have ever said any of these things to yourself . . .    </p>
<p>                    Something else will make me happy.<br />
                    I&#8217;m not a good mom.<br />
                    I will never get past this.<br />
                    I am defined by my weight.<br />
                    I should be further along by now.    </p>
<p>                    . . . then you could benefit from the unflinching faith and rock-hard tenacity Rachel Hollis has in store for you. In this challenging but conversational book, Rachel exposes the twenty lies and misconceptions that too often hold us back from living joyfully and productively, lies we&#8217;ve told ourselves so often we don&#8217;t even hear them anymore.    </p>
<p>                    Rachel is real and talks about real issues. More than that, she reveals the specific practical strategies that helped her move past them. In the process, she encourages, entertains, and even kicks a little butt, all to convince you to do whatever it takes to get real and become the joyous, confident woman you were meant to be. Because you really can live with passion and hustle &#8211; and give yourself grace without giving up.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/">Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave, Not Perfect : Fear Less, Fail More and Live Bolder &#8211; Reshma Saujani (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brave-not-perfect-fear-less-fail-more-and-live-bolder-reshma-saujani-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-not-perfect-fear-less-fail-more-and-live-bolder-reshma-saujani-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The new Lean In, from the multi-award-winning Founder and CEO of national non-profit Girls Who Code and New York Times bestselling author Reshma Saujani. &#8216;We are raising our boys to be brave, but our girls to be perfect. And this is holding us back.&#8217; Imagine if you lived without the fear of failure, without the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-not-perfect-fear-less-fail-more-and-live-bolder-reshma-saujani-abridged/">Brave, Not Perfect : Fear Less, Fail More and Live Bolder &#8211; Reshma Saujani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The new Lean In, from the multi-award-winning Founder and CEO of national non-profit Girls Who Code and New York Times bestselling author Reshma Saujani.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;We are raising our boys to be brave, but our girls to be perfect. And this is holding us back.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              Imagine if you lived without the fear of failure, without the fear of not measuring up. If you no longer felt the need to stifle your thoughts and swallow what you really want to say in order to please and appease others. If you could stop berating yourself mercilessly for human mistakes, let go of the guilt and the strangling pressure to be perfect, and just breathe. What if, in every decision you faced, you made the brave choice or took the bolder path. Would you be happier? Would you impact the world in the ways you dream you can?    </p>
<p>                                I believe the answer to both is yes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-not-perfect-fear-less-fail-more-and-live-bolder-reshma-saujani-abridged/">Brave, Not Perfect : Fear Less, Fail More and Live Bolder &#8211; Reshma Saujani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FULLY REVISED &#038; UPDATED, WITH A NEW EPILOGUE &#8220;Delightful.&#8221;-The Economist There&#8217;s Santa Claus, Shakespeare, Mickey Mouse, the Bible, and then there&#8217;s Star Wars. Nothing quite compares to sitting down with a young child and hearing the sound of John Williams&#8217;s score as those beloved golden letters fill the screen. In this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/">The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    FULLY REVISED &#038; UPDATED, WITH A NEW EPILOGUE    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Delightful.&#8221;-The Economist    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s Santa Claus, Shakespeare, Mickey Mouse, the Bible, and then there&#8217;s Star Wars. Nothing quite compares to sitting down with a young child and hearing the sound of John Williams&#8217;s score as those beloved golden letters fill the screen. In this fun, erudite, and often moving book, Cass R. Sunstein explores the lessons of Star Wars as they relate to childhood, fathers, the Dark Side, rebellion, and redemption. As it turns out, Star Wars also has a lot to teach us about constitutional law, economics, and political uprisings.    </p>
<p>                              In rich detail, Sunstein tells the story of the films&#8217; wildly unanticipated success and explores why some things succeed while others fail. Ultimately, Sunstein argues, Star Wars is about freedom of choice and our never-ending ability to make the right decision when the chips are down. Written with buoyant prose and considerable heart, The World According to Star Wars shines a bright new light on the most beloved story of our time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/">The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rich Dad Poor Dad : What the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money That the Poor and Middle Class Do Not! &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-that-the-poor-and-middle-class-do-not-robert-t-kiyosaki-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-that-the-poor-and-middle-class-do-not-robert-t-kiyosaki-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s been nearly 25 years since Robert Kiyosaki&#8217;s Rich Dad Poor Dad first made waves in the Personal Finance arena. It has since become the #1 Personal Finance book of all time&#8230; translated into dozens of languages and sold around the world. Rich Dad Poor Dad is Robert&#8217;s story of growing up with two dads [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-that-the-poor-and-middle-class-do-not-robert-t-kiyosaki-abridged/">Rich Dad Poor Dad : What the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money That the Poor and Middle Class Do Not! &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s been nearly 25 years since Robert Kiyosaki&#8217;s Rich Dad Poor Dad first made waves in the Personal Finance arena.<br />
                    It has since become the #1 Personal Finance book of all time&#8230; translated into dozens of languages and sold around the world.    </p>
<p>                    Rich Dad Poor Dad is Robert&#8217;s story of growing up with two dads   his real father and the father of his best friend, his rich dad   and the ways in which both men shaped his thoughts about money and investing. The book explodes the myth that you need to earn a high income to be rich and explains the difference between working for money and having your money work for you.    </p>
<p>                    20 Years&#8230; 20/20 Hindsight    </p>
<p>                    In the 20th Anniversary Edition of this classic, Robert offers an update on what we&#8217;ve seen over the past 20 years related to money, investing, and the global economy. Sidebars throughout the book will take readers &#8220;fast forward&#8221;   from 1997 to today   as Robert assesses how the principles taught by his rich dad have stood the test of time.    </p>
<p>                    In many ways, the messages of Rich Dad Poor Dad, messages that were criticized and challenged two decades ago, are more meaningful, relevant and important today than they were 20 years ago.    </p>
<p>                    As always, readers can expect that Robert will be candid, insightful&#8230; and continue to rock more than a few boats in his retrospective.    </p>
<p>                    Will there be a few surprises? Count on it.    </p>
<p>                    Rich Dad Poor Dad&#8230;    </p>
<p>                      Explodes the myth that you need to earn a high income to become rich<br />
                      Challenges the belief that your house is an asset<br />
                      Shows parents why they can&#8217;t rely on the school system to teach their kids<br />
                      about money<br />
                      Defines once and for all an asset and a liability<br />
                      Teaches you what to teach your kids about money for their future financial<br />
                      success</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-that-the-poor-and-middle-class-do-not-robert-t-kiyosaki-abridged/">Rich Dad Poor Dad : What the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money That the Poor and Middle Class Do Not! &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Talk so Kids Will Listen and Listen so Kids Will Talk &#8211; Adele Faber, Elaine Mazlish (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-and-listen-so-kids-will-talk-adele-faber-elaine-mazlish-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-and-listen-so-kids-will-talk-adele-faber-elaine-mazlish-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this international bestseller, discover the number one practical guide to family life. Parenting experts Adele Faber and Elaine Mazlish provide effective step by step techniques to help you improve and enrich your relationships with your children. Learn how to: * Break a pattern of arguments * Cope with your child&#8217;s negative feelings * Engage [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-and-listen-so-kids-will-talk-adele-faber-elaine-mazlish-abridged/">How to Talk so Kids Will Listen and Listen so Kids Will Talk &#8211; Adele Faber, Elaine Mazlish (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this international bestseller, discover the number one practical guide to family life.    </p>
<p>                    Parenting experts Adele Faber and Elaine Mazlish provide effective step by step techniques to help you improve and enrich your relationships with your children.     </p>
<p>                    Learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    * Break a pattern of arguments<br />
                    * Cope with your child&#8217;s negative feelings<br />
                    * Engage your child&#8217;s co-operation<br />
                    * Set clear limits and still maintain goodwill<br />
                    * Express your anger without being hurtful<br />
                    * Resolve family conflicts peacefully</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-and-listen-so-kids-will-talk-adele-faber-elaine-mazlish-abridged/">How to Talk so Kids Will Listen and Listen so Kids Will Talk &#8211; Adele Faber, Elaine Mazlish (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Becoming Attached : First Relationships &#8211; Robert Karen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/becoming-attached-first-relationships-robert-karen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/becoming-attached-first-relationships-robert-karen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The struggle to understand the infant-parent bond ranks as one of the great quests of modern psychology, one that touches us deeply because it holds so many clues to how we become who we are. How are our personalities formed? How do our early struggles with our parents reappear in the way we relate to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-attached-first-relationships-robert-karen-abridged/">Becoming Attached : First Relationships &#8211; Robert Karen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The struggle to understand the infant-parent bond ranks as one of the great quests of modern psychology, one that touches us deeply because it holds so many clues to how we become who we are. How are our personalities formed? How do our early struggles with our parents reappear in the way we relate to others as adults? Why do we repeat with our own children&#8211;seemingly against our will&#8211;the very behaviors we most disliked about our parents? In Becoming Attached, psychologist and noted journalist Robert Karen offers fresh insight into some of the most fundamental and fascinating questions of emotional life.<br />
                     Karen begins by tracing the history of attachment theory through the controversial work of John Bowlby, a British psychoanalyst, and Mary Ainsworth, an American developmental psychologist, who together launched a revolution in child psychology. Karen tells about their personal and professional struggles, their groundbreaking discoveries, and the recent flowering of attachment theory research in universities all over the world, making it one of the century&#8217;s most enduring ideas in developmental psychology.<br />
                     In a world of working parents and makeshift day care, the need to assess the impact of parenting styles and the bond between child and caregiver is more urgent than ever. Karen addresses such issues as: What do children need to feel that the world is a positive place and that they have value? Is day care harmful for children under one year? What experiences in infancy will enable a person to develop healthy relationships as an adult?, and he demonstrates how different approaches to mothering are associated with specific infant behaviors, such as clinginess, avoidance, or secure exploration. He shows how these patterns become ingrained and how they reveal themselves at age two, in the preschool years, in middle childhood, and in adulthood. And, with thought-provoking insights, he gives us a new understanding of how negative patterns and insecure attachment can be changed and resolved throughout a person&#8217;s life.<br />
                     The infant is in many ways a great mystery to us. Every one of us has been one; many of us have lived with or raised them. Becoming Attached is not just a voyage of discovery in child emotional development and its pertinence to adult life but a voyage of personal discovery as well, for it is impossible to read this book without reflecting on one&#8217;s own life as a child, a parent, and an intimate partner in love or marriage.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-attached-first-relationships-robert-karen-abridged/">Becoming Attached : First Relationships &#8211; Robert Karen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boys &#038; Sex : Young Men on Hook-ups, Love, Porn, Consent and Navigating the New Masculinity &#8211; Peggy Orenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/boys-sex-young-men-on-hook-ups-love-porn-consent-and-navigating-the-new-masculinity-peggy-orenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boys-sex-young-men-on-hook-ups-love-porn-consent-and-navigating-the-new-masculinity-peggy-orenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller &#8216;Blows your mind on every page&#8217; Caitlin Moran &#8216;Should be mandatory reading for anyone who cares about the next generation&#8217; Lori Gottlieb, New York Times bestselling author of Maybe You Should Talk to Someone Peggy Orenstein broke ground with her bestselling Girls &#038; Sex, exploring young women&#8217;s right to pleasure [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boys-sex-young-men-on-hook-ups-love-porn-consent-and-navigating-the-new-masculinity-peggy-orenstein-abridged/">Boys &#038; Sex : Young Men on Hook-ups, Love, Porn, Consent and Navigating the New Masculinity &#8211; Peggy Orenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Blows your mind on every page&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Should be mandatory reading for anyone who cares about the next generation&#8217; Lori Gottlieb, New York Times bestselling author of Maybe You Should Talk to Someone    </p>
<p>                    Peggy Orenstein broke ground with her bestselling Girls &#038; Sex, exploring young women&#8217;s right to pleasure and agency in sexual encounters. Now she turns her focus to boys with an examination of how young men are navigating sexual culture in these changing times &#8211; and what we need to do to help them.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on comprehensive interviews with young  men, psychologists and experts in the field, Boys &#038; Sex dissects &#8216;locker room talk&#8217;; pornography as the new sex education; the role of empathy; boys&#8217; understanding of hookup culture and consent; and their experience as both perpetrators and victims of sexual assault.    </p>
<p>                    By presenting young men&#8217;s experience in all its complexity, Orenstein unravels the hidden truths, hard lessons and important realities of young male sexuality in today&#8217;s world. The result is a provocative and paradigm-shifting work that offers a much-needed vision of how boys can truly move forward as better men.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boys-sex-young-men-on-hook-ups-love-porn-consent-and-navigating-the-new-masculinity-peggy-orenstein-abridged/">Boys &#038; Sex : Young Men on Hook-ups, Love, Porn, Consent and Navigating the New Masculinity &#8211; Peggy Orenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motorcycles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed as one of the most exciting books in the history of American letters, this modern epic became an instant bestseller upon publication in 1974, transforming a generation and continuing to inspire millions. A narration of a summer motorcycle trip undertaken by a father and his son, the book becomes a personal and philosophical odyssey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/">Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed as one of the most exciting books in the history of American letters, this modern epic became an instant bestseller upon publication in 1974, transforming a generation and continuing to inspire millions. A narration of a summer motorcycle trip undertaken by a father and his son, the book becomes a personal and philosophical odyssey into fundamental questions of how to live. Resonant with the confusions of existence, Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance is a touching and transcendent book of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/">Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Minimalist Parenting : Enjoy Modern Family Life More by Doing Less &#8211; Christine K. Koh, Asha Dornfest (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/minimalist-parenting-enjoy-modern-family-life-more-by-doing-less-christine-k-koh-asha-dornfest-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/minimalist-parenting-enjoy-modern-family-life-more-by-doing-less-christine-k-koh-asha-dornfest-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re in the midst of a parenting climate that feeds on more. More expert advice, more gear, more fear about competition and safety, and more choices to make about education, nutrition, even entertainment. The result? Overwhelmed, confused parents and overscheduled, overparented kids. In MINIMALIST PARENTING, Christine Koh and Asha Dornfest offer a fresh approach to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/minimalist-parenting-enjoy-modern-family-life-more-by-doing-less-christine-k-koh-asha-dornfest-abridged/">Minimalist Parenting : Enjoy Modern Family Life More by Doing Less &#8211; Christine K. Koh, Asha Dornfest (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re in the midst of a parenting climate that feeds on more. More expert advice, more gear, more fear about competition and safety, and more choices to make about education, nutrition, even entertainment. The result? Overwhelmed, confused parents and overscheduled, overparented kids.    </p>
<p>                    In MINIMALIST PARENTING, Christine Koh and Asha Dornfest offer a fresh approach to navigating all of this conflicting background &#8220;noise.&#8221;  They show how to tune into your family&#8217;s unique values and priorities and confidently identify the activities, stuff, information, and people that truly merit space in your life.    </p>
<p>                    The book begins by showing the value of a minimalist approach, backed by the authors&#8217; personal experience practicing it. It then leads parents through practical strategies for managing time, decluttering the home space, simplifying mealtimes, streamlining recreation, and prioritizing self-care. Filled with parents&#8217; personal stories, readers will come away with a unique plan for a simpler life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/minimalist-parenting-enjoy-modern-family-life-more-by-doing-less-christine-k-koh-asha-dornfest-abridged/">Minimalist Parenting : Enjoy Modern Family Life More by Doing Less &#8211; Christine K. Koh, Asha Dornfest (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No-Drama Discipline : The Whole-Brain Way to Calm the Chaos and Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-drama-discipline-the-whole-brain-way-to-calm-the-chaos-and-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-drama-discipline-the-whole-brain-way-to-calm-the-chaos-and-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The pioneering experts behind The Whole-Brain Child and The Yes Brain tackle the ultimate parenting challenge: discipline. &#8220;A lot of fascinating insights . . . an eye-opener worth reading.&#8221;&#8211;Parents Highlighting the fascinating link between a child&#8217;s neurological development and the way a parent reacts to misbehavior, No-Drama Discipline provides an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-drama-discipline-the-whole-brain-way-to-calm-the-chaos-and-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/">No-Drama Discipline : The Whole-Brain Way to Calm the Chaos and Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The pioneering experts behind The Whole-Brain Child and The Yes Brain tackle the ultimate parenting challenge: discipline.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A lot of fascinating insights . . . an eye-opener worth reading.&#8221;&#8211;Parents     </p>
<p>                    Highlighting the fascinating link between a child&#8217;s neurological development and the way a parent reacts to misbehavior, No-Drama Discipline provides an effective, compassionate road map for dealing with tantrums, tensions, and tears&#8211;without causing a scene.     </p>
<p>                    Defining the true meaning of the &#8220;d&#8221; word (to instruct, not to shout or reprimand), the authors explain how to reach your child, redirect emotions, and turn a meltdown into an opportunity for growth. By doing so, the cycle of negative behavior (and punishment) is essentially brought to a halt, as problem solving becomes a win/win situation. Inside this sanity-saving guide you&#8217;ll discover     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; strategies that help parents identify their own discipline philosophy&#8211;and master the best methods to communicate the lessons they are trying to impart<br />
                     &#8211; facts on child brain development&#8211;and what kind of discipline is most appropriate and constructive at all ages and stages<br />
                     &#8211; the way to calmly and lovingly connect with a child&#8211;no matter how extreme the behavior&#8211;while still setting clear and consistent limits<br />
                     &#8211; tips for navigating your child through a tantrum to achieve insight, empathy, and repair<br />
                     &#8211; twenty discipline mistakes even the best parents make&#8211;and how to stay focused on the principles of whole-brain parenting and discipline techniques     </p>
<p>                     Complete with candid stories and playful illustrations that bring the authors&#8217; suggestions to life, No-Drama Discipline shows you how to work with your child&#8217;s developing mind, peacefully resolve conflicts, and inspire happiness and strengthen resilience in everyone in the family.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for No-Drama Discipline     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;With lucid, engaging prose accompanied by cartoon illustrations, Siegel and Bryson help parents teach and communicate more effectively.&#8221;&#8211;Publishers Weekly     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Wow! This book grabbed me from the very first page and did not let go.&#8221;&#8211;Lawrence J. Cohen, Ph.D., author of The Opposite of Worry</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-drama-discipline-the-whole-brain-way-to-calm-the-chaos-and-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/">No-Drama Discipline : The Whole-Brain Way to Calm the Chaos and Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ungifted : Intelligence Redefined &#8211; Scott Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Ungifted , cognitive psychologist Scott Barry Kaufman,who was relegated to special education as a child,offers a new way of looking at intelligence. He explores the latest research in genetics, neuroscience, and psychology to challenge the conventional wisdom about the childhood predictors of adult success, arguing for a more holistic approach to intelligence that takes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/">Ungifted : Intelligence Redefined &#8211; Scott Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In  Ungifted , cognitive psychologist Scott Barry Kaufman,who was relegated to special education as a child,offers a new way of looking at intelligence. He explores the latest research in genetics, neuroscience, and psychology to challenge the conventional wisdom about the childhood predictors of adult success, arguing for a more holistic approach to intelligence that takes into account each individual&#8217;s abilities, engagement, and personal goals. Combining original research and a singular compassion,  Ungifted  increases our appreciation for all different kinds of minds and ways of achieving both personally meaningful and publicly recognized forms of success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/">Ungifted : Intelligence Redefined &#8211; Scott Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happy Kids Handbook : How to Raise Joyful Children in a Stressful World &#8211; Katie Hurley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With all the parenting information out there and the constant pressure to be the &#8220;perfect&#8221; parent, it seems as if many parents have lost track of one very important piece of the parenting puzzle: raising happy kids. Parenting today has gotten far too complicated. It&#8217;s never been the easiest job in the world, but with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/">The Happy Kids Handbook : How to Raise Joyful Children in a Stressful World &#8211; Katie Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With all the parenting information out there and the constant pressure to be the &#8220;perfect&#8221; parent, it seems as if many parents have lost track of one very important piece of the parenting puzzle: raising happy kids.     </p>
<p>                     Parenting today has gotten far too complicated. It&#8217;s never been the easiest job in the world, but with all the &#8220;parenting advice&#8221; parents are met with at every corner, it&#8217;s hard not to become bewildered. It seems that in the past it was a good deal simpler. You made sure there was dinner on the table and the kids got to school on time and no one set anything on fire, and you called it a success. But today everybody has a different method for dealing with the madness&#8211;attachment parenting, free-range parenting, mindful parenting. And who is to say one is more right or better than another? How do you choose?     </p>
<p>                     The truth is that whatever drumbeat you march to, all parents would agree that we just want our kids to be happy. It seems like a no-brainer, right? But in the face of all the many parenting theories out there, happiness feels like it has become incidental. That&#8217;s where The Happy Kid Handbook by child and adolescent psychotherapist and parenting expert Katie Hurley comes in. She shows parents how happiness is the key to raising confident, capable children. It&#8217;s not about giving in every time your child wants something so they won&#8217;t feel bad when you say no, or making sure that they&#8217;re taking that art class, and the ballet class, and the soccer class (to help with their creativity and their coordination and all that excess energy). Happiness is about parenting the individual, because not every child is the same, and not every child will respond to parenting the same way. By exploring the differences among introverts, extroverts, and everything in between, this definitive guide to parenting offers parents the specific strategies they need to meet their child exactly where he or she needs to be met from a social-emotional perspective. A back-to-basics guide to parenting, The Happy Kid Handbook is a must-have for any parent hoping to be the best parent they can be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/">The Happy Kids Handbook : How to Raise Joyful Children in a Stressful World &#8211; Katie Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Geography & Topography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel With Children / Family Holidays]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>By the beloved and wildly popular host of the PBS Kids show Dinosaur Train, here is the book every parent needs: a rousing call to connect our kids to the natural world, filled with tips and advice. The average North American child now spends about seven hours a day staring at screens and mere minutes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/">How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By the beloved and wildly popular host of the PBS Kids show Dinosaur Train, here is the book every parent needs: a rousing call to connect our kids to the natural world, filled with tips and advice.    </p>
<p>                    The average North American child now spends about seven hours a day staring at screens and mere minutes engaged in unstructured play outdoors. Yet recent research indicates that experiences in nature are essential for healthy growth.     </p>
<p>                    Regular exposure to nature can help relieve stress, depression, and attention deficits. It can reduce bullying, combat obesity, and boost academic scores. Most critical of all, abundant time in natural settings seems to yield long-term benefits in kids&#8217; cognitive, emotional, and social development.     </p>
<p>                    How to Raise a Wild Child is a timely and engaging antidote, offering teachers, parents, and other caregivers the necessary tools to engender a meaningful, lasting connection between children and the natural world.     </p>
<p>                    Distilling the latest research in multiple disciplines, Sampson reveals how adults can help kids fall in love with nature&#8211;enlisting technology as an ally, taking advantage of urban nature, and instilling a sense of place along the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In a time when the connection between humans and the rest of nature is most vulnerable, Scott offers parents and teachers a book of encouragement and knowledge, and to children, the priceless gift of wonder.&#8221;&#8211;Richard Louv, author of Last Child in the Woods and The Nature Principle</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/">How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nanaville : Adventures in Grandparenting &#8211; Anna Quindlen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nanaville-adventures-in-grandparenting-anna-quindlen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nanaville-adventures-in-grandparenting-anna-quindlen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The perfect gift for new parents and grandparents this Mother&#8217;s Day: a bighearted book of wisdom, wit, and insight, celebrating the love and joy of being a grandmother, from the Pulitzer Prize-winning columnist and #1 bestselling author &#8220;This tender book should be required reading for grandparents everywhere.&#8221;&#8211;Booklist (starred review) &#8220;I [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nanaville-adventures-in-grandparenting-anna-quindlen-abridged/">Nanaville : Adventures in Grandparenting &#8211; Anna Quindlen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The perfect gift for new parents and grandparents this Mother&#8217;s Day: a bighearted book of wisdom, wit, and insight, celebrating the love and joy of being a grandmother, from the Pulitzer Prize-winning columnist and #1 bestselling author     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This tender book should be required reading for grandparents everywhere.&#8221;&#8211;Booklist (starred review)     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I am changing his diaper, he is kicking and complaining, his exhausted father has gone to the kitchen for a glass of water, his exhausted mother is prone on the couch. He weighs little more than a large sack of flour and yet he has laid waste to the living room: swaddles on the chair, a nursing pillow on the sofa, a car seat, a stroller. No one cares about order, he is our order, we revolve around him. And as I try to get in the creases of his thighs with a wipe, I look at his, let&#8217;s be honest, largely formless face and unfocused eyes and fall in love with him. Look at him and think, well, that&#8217;s taken care of, I will do anything for you as long as we both shall live, world without end, amen.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     Before blogs even existed, Anna Quindlen became a go-to writer on the joys and challenges of family, motherhood, and modern life, in her nationally syndicated column. Now she&#8217;s taking the next step and going full nana in the pages of this lively, beautiful, and moving book about being a grandmother. Quindlen offers thoughtful and telling observations about her new role, no longer mother and decision-maker but secondary character and support to the parents of her grandson. She writes, &#8220;Where I once led, I have to learn to follow.&#8221; Eventually a close friend provides words to live by: &#8220;Did they ask you?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     Candid, funny, frank, and illuminating, Quindlen&#8217;s singular voice has never been sharper or warmer. With the same insights she brought to motherhood in Living Out Loud and to growing older in Lots of Candles, Plenty of Cake, this new nana uses her own experiences to illuminate those of many others.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Nanaville     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Witty and thoughtful . . . Nanaville serves up enough vivid anecdotes and fresh insights&#8211;about childhood, about parenthood, about grandparenthood and about life&#8211;to make for a gratifying read.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Classic, bittersweet Quindlen . . . [Her] wonder at seeing her eldest child grow into his new role is lovely and moving. . . . The best parts of Nanaville are the charming vignettes of Quindlen&#8217;s solo time with her grandson.&#8221;&#8211;NPR</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nanaville-adventures-in-grandparenting-anna-quindlen-abridged/">Nanaville : Adventures in Grandparenting &#8211; Anna Quindlen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gift of Failure : How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed &#8211; Jessica Lahey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gift-of-failure-how-the-best-parents-learn-to-let-go-so-their-children-can-succeed-jessica-lahey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gift-of-failure-how-the-best-parents-learn-to-let-go-so-their-children-can-succeed-jessica-lahey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8220;Gripping&#8230;how can teachers snatch back their critical role and give children the necessary space to fail? They could start by making parents read Lahey.&#8221; &#8212; New York Times Book Review In the tradition of Paul Tough&#8217;s How Children Succeed and Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee, this groundbreaking manifesto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gift-of-failure-how-the-best-parents-learn-to-let-go-so-their-children-can-succeed-jessica-lahey-abridged/">The Gift of Failure : How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed &#8211; Jessica Lahey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Gripping&#8230;how can teachers snatch back their critical role and give children the necessary space to fail? They could start by making parents read Lahey.&#8221; &#8212; New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of Paul Tough&#8217;s How Children Succeed and Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee, this groundbreaking manifesto focuses on the critical school years when parents must learn to allow their children to experience the disappointment and frustration that occur from life&#8217;s inevitable problems so that they can grow up to be successful, resilient, and self-reliant adults.    </p>
<p>                    Modern parenting is defined by an unprecedented level of overprotectiveness: parents who rush to school at the whim of a phone call to deliver forgotten assignments, who challenge teachers on report card disappointments, mastermind children&#8217;s friendships, and interfere on the playing field. As teacher and writer Jessica Lahey explains, even though these parents see themselves as being highly responsive to their children&#8217;s well being, they aren&#8217;t giving them the chance to experience failure&#8211;or the opportunity to learn to solve their own problems.    </p>
<p>                    Overparenting has the potential to ruin a child&#8217;s confidence and undermine their education, Lahey reminds us. Teachers don&#8217;t just teach reading, writing, and arithmetic. They teach responsibility, organization, manners, restraint, and foresight&#8211;important life skills children carry with them long after they leave the classroom.    </p>
<p>                    Providing a path toward solutions, Lahey lays out a blueprint with targeted advice for handling homework, report cards, social dynamics, and sports. Most importantly, she sets forth a plan to help parents learn to step back and embrace their children&#8217;s failures. Hard-hitting yet warm and wise, The Gift of Failure is essential reading for parents, educators, and psychologists nationwide who want to help children succeed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gift-of-failure-how-the-best-parents-learn-to-let-go-so-their-children-can-succeed-jessica-lahey-abridged/">The Gift of Failure : How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed &#8211; Jessica Lahey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
