<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Middle Eastern History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/middle-eastern-history/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/middle-eastern-history/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Middle Eastern History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/middle-eastern-history/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Heretic : Why Islam Needs a Reformation Now &#8211; Ayaan Hirsi Ali (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/heretic-why-islam-needs-a-reformation-now-ayaan-hirsi-ali-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/heretic-why-islam-needs-a-reformation-now-ayaan-hirsi-ali-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Continuing her journey from a deeply religious Islamic upbringing to a post at Harvard, the brilliant, charismatic and controversial New York Times and Globe and Mail #1 bestselling author of Infidel and Nomad makes a powerful plea for a Muslim Reformation as the only way to end the horrors of terrorism, sectarian warfare and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heretic-why-islam-needs-a-reformation-now-ayaan-hirsi-ali-abridged/">Heretic : Why Islam Needs a Reformation Now &#8211; Ayaan Hirsi Ali (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Continuing her journey from a deeply religious Islamic upbringing to a post at Harvard, the brilliant, charismatic and controversial New York Times and Globe and Mail #1 bestselling author of Infidel and Nomad makes a powerful plea for a Muslim Reformation as the only way to end the horrors of terrorism, sectarian warfare and the repression of women and minorities.  Today, she argues, the world&#8217;s 1.6 billion Muslims can be divided into a minority of extremists, a majority of observant but peaceable Muslims and a few dissidents who risk their lives by questioning their own religion. But there is only one Islam and, as Hirsi Ali shows, there is no denying that some of its key teachings-not least the duty to wage holy war-are incompatible with the values of a free society. For centuries it has seemed as if Islam is immune to change. But Hirsi Ali has come to believe that a Muslim Reformation-a revision of Islamic doctrine aimed at reconciling the religion with modernity-is now at hand, and may even have begun. The Arab Spring may now seem like a political failure.<br />
                    But its challenge to traditional authority revealed a new readiness-not least by Muslim women-to think freely and to speak out.  Courageously challenging the jihadists, she identifies five key amendments to Islamic doctrine that Muslims have to make to bring their religion out of the seventh century and into the twenty-first. And she calls on the Western world to end its appeasement of the Islamists. &#8220;Islam is not a religion of peace,&#8221; she writes. It is the Muslim reformers who need our backing, not the opponents of free speech.  Interweaving her own experiences, historical analogies and powerful examples from contemporary Muslim societies and cultures, Heretic is not a call to arms, but a passionate plea for peaceful change and a new era of global toleration. In the wake of the Charlie Hebdo murders, with jihadists killing thousands from Nigeria to Syria to Pakistan, this book offers an answer to what is fast becoming the world&#8217;s number one problem.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heretic-why-islam-needs-a-reformation-now-ayaan-hirsi-ali-abridged/">Heretic : Why Islam Needs a Reformation Now &#8211; Ayaan Hirsi Ali (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historiography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Liberation & Independence, Post-colonialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton In this highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our  understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton    </p>
<p>                    In this  highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of  Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a  powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for writers, philosophers  and colonial administrators to deal with the &#8216;otherness&#8217; of eastern  culture, customs and beliefs. He traces this view through the writings  of Homer, Nerval and Flaubert, Disraeli and Kipling, whose imaginative  depictions have greatly contributed to the West&#8217;s romantic and exotic  picture of the Orient. Drawing on his own experiences as an Arab  Palestinian living in the West, Said examines how these ideas can be a  reflection of European imperialism and racism.<br />
                    &#8216;Beautifully patterned and passionately argued&#8217;<br />
                    New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Very exciting &#8230; his case is not merely persuasive, but conclusive&#8217;<br />
                    John Leonard, New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Headscarves and Hymens : Why the Middle East Needs a Sexual Revolution &#8211; Mona Eltahawy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shocking, heartfelt and well-researched&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;A ground-shaping book that defines the edge of so many vital contemporary debates. Hers is a voice simultaneously behind and beyond the veil&#8217; Colum McCann &#8216;A fascinating, can&#8217;t-look-away, whistle-stop tour of the Middle East&#8217; Daily Telegraph &#8216;Brave and impassioned . . . A shocking book, and one that will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/">Headscarves and Hymens : Why the Middle East Needs a Sexual Revolution &#8211; Mona Eltahawy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shocking, heartfelt and well-researched&#8217; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A ground-shaping book that defines the edge of so many vital contemporary debates. Hers is a voice simultaneously behind and beyond the veil&#8217; Colum McCann    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fascinating, can&#8217;t-look-away, whistle-stop tour of the Middle East&#8217; Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brave and impassioned . . . A shocking book, and one that will make anyone who has seen veiling as a cultural issue think very hard about what is really going on&#8217; Mail on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    Headscarves and Hymens explodes the myth that we should stand back and watch while women are disempowered and abused in the name of religion.    </p>
<p>                     In this laceratingly honest account, Eltahawy takes aim both at attitudes in the Middle East and at the western liberals who mistake misogyny for cultural difference. Her argument is clear: unless political revolution in the Arab world is accompanied by social and sexual revolution, no progress will be made.    </p>
<p>                    Headscarves and Hymens is the book the world has been crying out for: a powerful, fearless account of what it really means to be a woman in the Muslim world.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A fascinating, can&#8217;t-look-away, whistle-stop tour of the Middle East&#8217; Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brave and impassioned . . . A shocking book, and one that will make anyone who has seen veiling as a cultural issue think very hard about what is really going on&#8217; Mail on Sunday</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/">Headscarves and Hymens : Why the Middle East Needs a Sexual Revolution &#8211; Mona Eltahawy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Destiny Disrupted : A History of the World Through Islamic Eyes &#8211; Tamim Ansary (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/destiny-disrupted-a-history-of-the-world-through-islamic-eyes-tamim-ansary-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/destiny-disrupted-a-history-of-the-world-through-islamic-eyes-tamim-ansary-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We in the west share a common narrative of world history. But our story largely omits a whole civilization whose citizens shared an entirely different narrative for a thousand years. In Destiny Disrupted , Tamim Ansary tells the rich story of world history as the Islamic world saw it, from the time of Mohammed to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/destiny-disrupted-a-history-of-the-world-through-islamic-eyes-tamim-ansary-abridged/">Destiny Disrupted : A History of the World Through Islamic Eyes &#8211; Tamim Ansary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We in the west share a common narrative of world history. But our story largely omits a whole civilization whose citizens shared an entirely different narrative for a thousand years. In  Destiny Disrupted , Tamim Ansary tells the rich story of world history as the Islamic world saw it, from the time of Mohammed to the fall of the Ottoman Empire and beyond. He clarifies why our civilizations grew up oblivious to each other, what happened when they intersected, and how the Islamic world was affected by its slow recognition that Europe,a place it long perceived as primitive and disorganized,had somehow hijacked destiny.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/destiny-disrupted-a-history-of-the-world-through-islamic-eyes-tamim-ansary-abridged/">Destiny Disrupted : A History of the World Through Islamic Eyes &#8211; Tamim Ansary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Peace to End All Peace, 20th Anniversary Edition : The Fall of the Ottoman Empire and the Creation of the Modern Middle East &#8211; David Fromkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-peace-to-end-all-peace-20th-anniversary-edition-the-fall-of-the-ottoman-empire-and-the-creation-of-the-modern-middle-east-david-fromkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-peace-to-end-all-peace-20th-anniversary-edition-the-fall-of-the-ottoman-empire-and-the-creation-of-the-modern-middle-east-david-fromkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Published with a new afterword from the author&#8211;the classic, bestselling account of how the modern Middle East was created The Middle East has long been a region of rival religions, ideologies, nationalisms, and ambitions. All of these conflicts&#8211;including the hostilities between Arabs and Israelis, and the violent challenges posed by Iraq&#8217;s competing sects&#8211;are rooted in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-peace-to-end-all-peace-20th-anniversary-edition-the-fall-of-the-ottoman-empire-and-the-creation-of-the-modern-middle-east-david-fromkin-abridged/">A Peace to End All Peace, 20th Anniversary Edition : The Fall of the Ottoman Empire and the Creation of the Modern Middle East &#8211; David Fromkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Published with a new afterword from the author&#8211;the classic, bestselling account of how the modern Middle East was created     </p>
<p>                    The Middle East has long been a region of rival religions, ideologies, nationalisms, and ambitions. All of these conflicts&#8211;including the hostilities between Arabs and Israelis, and the violent challenges posed by Iraq&#8217;s competing sects&#8211;are rooted in the region&#8217;s political inheritance: the arrangements, unities, and divisions imposed by the Allies after the First World War.     </p>
<p>                    In A Peace to End All Peace, David Fromkin reveals how and why the Allies drew lines on an empty map that remade the geography and politics of the Middle East. Focusing on the formative years of 1914 to 1922, when all seemed possible, he delivers in this sweeping and magisterial book the definitive account of this defining time, showing how the choices narrowed and the Middle East began along a road that led to the conflicts and confusion that continue to this day.     </p>
<p>                    A new afterword from Fromkin, written for this edition of the book, includes his invaluable, updated assessment of this region of the world today, and on what this history has to teach us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-peace-to-end-all-peace-20th-anniversary-edition-the-fall-of-the-ottoman-empire-and-the-creation-of-the-modern-middle-east-david-fromkin-abridged/">A Peace to End All Peace, 20th Anniversary Edition : The Fall of the Ottoman Empire and the Creation of the Modern Middle East &#8211; David Fromkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Saudi Arabia : Its People, Past, Religion, Fault Lines&#8211;and Future &#8211; Karen Elliott House (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-saudi-arabia-its-people-past-religion-fault-lines-and-future-karen-elliott-house-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-saudi-arabia-its-people-past-religion-fault-lines-and-future-karen-elliott-house-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With over thirty years of experience writing about Saudi Arabia, Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter and former publisher of The Wall Street Journal Karen Elliott House has an unprecedented knowledge of life inside this shrouded kingdom. Through anecdotes, observation, analysis, and extensive interviews, she navigates the maze in which Saudi citizens find themselves trapped and reveals the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-saudi-arabia-its-people-past-religion-fault-lines-and-future-karen-elliott-house-abridged/">On Saudi Arabia : Its People, Past, Religion, Fault Lines&#8211;and Future &#8211; Karen Elliott House (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With over thirty years of experience writing about Saudi Arabia, Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter and former publisher of The Wall Street Journal Karen Elliott House has an unprecedented knowledge of life inside this shrouded kingdom. Through anecdotes, observation, analysis, and extensive interviews, she navigates the maze in which Saudi citizens find themselves trapped and reveals the sometimes contradictory nature of the nation that is simultaneously a final bulwark against revolution in the Middle East and a wellspring of Islamic terrorists.     </p>
<p>                     Saudi Arabia finds itself threatened by fissures and forces on all sides, and On Saudi Arabia explores in depth what this portends for the country&#8217;s future&#8211;and our own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-saudi-arabia-its-people-past-religion-fault-lines-and-future-karen-elliott-house-abridged/">On Saudi Arabia : Its People, Past, Religion, Fault Lines&#8211;and Future &#8211; Karen Elliott House (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Isis: Inside The Army Of Terror : Updated Edition &#8211; Michael Weiß, Hassan Hassan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/isis-inside-the-army-of-terror-updated-edition-michael-weis-hassan-hassan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/isis-inside-the-army-of-terror-updated-edition-michael-weis-hassan-hassan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fully Revised &#038; Updated Edition of the New York Times Bestselling and Highly Praised Book on ISIS With newly added material and breaking news including: &#8211;Interview with a former ISIS spymaster &#8211;Why ISIS is targeting Europe and the US &#8211;What Russia wants in Syria &#8211;Revelations on the brutal ideology of ISIS With brutal attacks in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/isis-inside-the-army-of-terror-updated-edition-michael-weis-hassan-hassan-abridged/">Isis: Inside The Army Of Terror : Updated Edition &#8211; Michael Weiß, Hassan Hassan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fully Revised &#038; Updated Edition of the New York Times Bestselling and Highly Praised Book on ISIS  With newly added material and breaking news including:<br />
                     &#8211;Interview with a former ISIS spymaster<br />
                     &#8211;Why ISIS is targeting Europe and the US<br />
                     &#8211;What Russia wants in Syria<br />
                     &#8211;Revelations on the brutal ideology of ISIS With brutal attacks in last year across the globe&#8211;Brussels, Paris, Beirut, Egypt, Turkey&#8211;the Islamic State of Iraq and Syria (ISIS) has proved itself the greatest terrorist threat in the world today. They have conquered massive territories in Syria and Iraq in a bid to create a new Muslim caliphate under the strict dictates of Sharia law.  In this fully revised and updated edition of ISIS: Inside the Army of Terror, American journalist Michael Weiss and Syrian analyst Hassan Hassan explain how these violent extremists evolved from a nearly defeated Iraqi insurgent group into a jihadi army of international volunteers who, with slickly produced murder videos, are spreading violence and mayhem across the globe. Beginning with the early days of Abu Musab al-Zarqawi, the founder of ISIS&#8217;s first incarnation, Weiss and Hassan explain who the key players are&#8211;from their leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi to the former Saddam Baathists in their ranks&#8211;where they come from, how they have attracted both local and global support, and how they operate&#8211;from their social media strategy to their illicit oil revenues. As money and matériel continue to flow into the region to combat the ISIS&#8217;s spreading terror, other forces&#8211;Assad&#8217;s regime, Russian planes, Iranian Quds Forces, and other Shiite militias&#8211;are gaining power and using the fight against ISIS as a means to leverage their agenda in the region.  Political and military maneuvering by the United States, Iraq, Iran, Syria, and Russia have fueled ISIS&#8217;s explosive expansion. In five new chapters, the authors delve further into the inner workings of the Army of Terror and what it is like to live under their ever-tightening rule. With invaluable and exclusive insider information, the authors explore the Islamic State&#8217;s enigmatic recruitment and training methods, the impact of their military successes and failures, and how they structure and empower home-grown cells worldwide to carry out their terror. Drawing on original interviews with former US military officials and current ISIS fighters&#8211;and brand-new interviews with a former ISIS spy, as well as Kurdish and Yazidi survivors of the ISIS&#8217;s assault on northern Iraq&#8211;the authors reveal the internecine struggles within the movement itself, as well as ISIS&#8217;s bloody hatred of Shiite Muslims, which is generating another sectarian war in the region. A new generation of terror has dawned in the world and to understand how to stop it, we must understand who they are.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/isis-inside-the-army-of-terror-updated-edition-michael-weis-hassan-hassan-abridged/">Isis: Inside The Army Of Terror : Updated Edition &#8211; Michael Weiß, Hassan Hassan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let There Be Water : Israel&#8217;s Solution for a Water-Starved World &#8211; Siegel, Seth M. (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drought & Water Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hydrology & The Hydrosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Irrigation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Supply & Treatment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With hardly a day without a water-crisis story somewhere, Let There Be Water offers prescriptions on how countries, cities, and businesses can avoid the worst of it. With sixty percent of the country in a desert and despite a rapidly growing population, Israel has been jumping ahead of the water-innovation curve for decades. Beyond securing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/">Let There Be Water : Israel&#8217;s Solution for a Water-Starved World &#8211; Siegel, Seth M. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With hardly a day without a water-crisis story somewhere, Let There Be Water offers prescriptions on how countries, cities, and businesses can avoid the worst of it. With sixty percent of the country in a desert and despite a rapidly growing population, Israel has been jumping ahead of the water-innovation curve for decades. Beyond securing its own water supply, Israel has also created a high-export industry in water technology, a timely example of how countries can build their economies while making the world better. Built on meticulous research and hundreds of interviews with both world leaders and experts in the field, Let There Be Water tells the inspiring story of how this all came to be. The author is now widely considered to be one of the nation&#8217;s go-to authorities on water and has in the last year alone, spoken to more than 160 different organisations, civic groups, and universities all across the country.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/">Let There Be Water : Israel&#8217;s Solution for a Water-Starved World &#8211; Siegel, Seth M. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Muqaddimah : An Introduction to History &#8211; Abridged Edition &#8211; Ibn Ibn Khaldun, Translated by Franz Rosenthal, Introduction by Bruce B. Lawrence, Edited by N. J. Dawood (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-muqaddimah-an-introduction-to-history-abridged-edition-ibn-ibn-khaldun-translated-by-franz-rosenthal-introduction-by-bruce-b-lawrence-edited-by-n-j-dawood-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Theory & Methods]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic & Arabic Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-muqaddimah-an-introduction-to-history-abridged-edition-ibn-ibn-khaldun-translated-by-franz-rosenthal-introduction-by-bruce-b-lawrence-edited-by-n-j-dawood-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Muqaddimah, often translated as &#8220;Introduction&#8221; or &#8220;Prolegomenon,&#8221; is the most important Islamic history of the premodern world. Written by the great fourteenth-century Arab scholar Ibn Khaldun (d. 1406), this monumental work established the foundations of several fields of knowledge, including the philosophy of history, sociology, ethnography, and economics. The first complete English translation, by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-muqaddimah-an-introduction-to-history-abridged-edition-ibn-ibn-khaldun-translated-by-franz-rosenthal-introduction-by-bruce-b-lawrence-edited-by-n-j-dawood-abridged/">The Muqaddimah : An Introduction to History &#8211; Abridged Edition &#8211; Ibn Ibn Khaldun, Translated by Franz Rosenthal, Introduction by Bruce B. Lawrence, Edited by N. J. Dawood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Muqaddimah, often translated as &#8220;Introduction&#8221; or &#8220;Prolegomenon,&#8221; is the most important Islamic history of the premodern world. Written by the great fourteenth-century Arab scholar Ibn Khaldun (d. 1406), this monumental work established the foundations of several fields of knowledge, including the philosophy of history, sociology, ethnography, and economics. The first complete English translation, by the eminent Islamicist and interpreter of Arabic literature Franz Rosenthal, was published in three volumes in 1958 as part of the Bollingen Series and received immediate acclaim in the United States and abroad. A one-volume abridged version of Rosenthal&#8217;s masterful translation first appeared in 1969. This Princeton Classics edition of the abridged version includes Rosenthal&#8217;s original introduction as well as a contemporary introduction by Bruce B. Lawrence. This volume makes available a seminal work of Islam and medieval and ancient history to twenty-first century audiences.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-muqaddimah-an-introduction-to-history-abridged-edition-ibn-ibn-khaldun-translated-by-franz-rosenthal-introduction-by-bruce-b-lawrence-edited-by-n-j-dawood-abridged/">The Muqaddimah : An Introduction to History &#8211; Abridged Edition &#8211; Ibn Ibn Khaldun, Translated by Franz Rosenthal, Introduction by Bruce B. Lawrence, Edited by N. J. Dawood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revolutionary Iran : A History of the Islamic Republic Second Edition &#8211; Michael Axworthy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/revolutionary-iran-a-history-of-the-islamic-republic-second-edition-michael-axworthy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Postwar 20th Century History, From C 1945 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions, Uprisings, Rebellions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/revolutionary-iran-a-history-of-the-islamic-republic-second-edition-michael-axworthy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FULLY UPDATED SECOND EDITION &#8216;If you were to read only one book on present-day Iran you could not do better than this&#8217; Ervand Abrahamian, Times Higher Education For some 40 years the Islamic Republic has resisted widespread condemnation, sanctions, and sustained attacks by Iraq in an eight-year war. Many policy-makers today share a weary wish [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revolutionary-iran-a-history-of-the-islamic-republic-second-edition-michael-axworthy-abridged/">Revolutionary Iran : A History of the Islamic Republic Second Edition &#8211; Michael Axworthy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FULLY UPDATED SECOND EDITION    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you were to read only one book on present-day Iran you could not do better than this&#8217; Ervand Abrahamian, Times Higher Education    </p>
<p>                    For some 40 years the Islamic Republic has resisted widespread  condemnation, sanctions, and sustained attacks by Iraq in an eight-year  war. Many policy-makers today share a weary wish that Iran would somehow  just disappear as a problem. But with Iran&#8217;s continuing commitment to a  nuclear programme and its reputation as a trouble-maker in Syria,  Afghanistan, Lebanon and elsewhere, this is unlikely any time soon. An  unending stream of assertions about the revolution&#8217;s finally running  down continue to be defied by events, and Iran&#8217;s institutions are still  formidable.    </p>
<p>                    This is the definitive history of this subject, from one of the world&#8217;s principal experts.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revolutionary-iran-a-history-of-the-islamic-republic-second-edition-michael-axworthy-abridged/">Revolutionary Iran : A History of the Islamic Republic Second Edition &#8211; Michael Axworthy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seventh Million : The Israelis and the Holocaust &#8211; Tom Segev, Translated by Professor Haim Watzman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holocaust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Seventh Million is the first book to show the decisive impact of the Holocaust on the identity, ideology, and politics of Israel. Drawing on diaries, interviews, and thousands of declassified documents, Segev reconsiders the major struggles and personalities of Israel&#8217;s past, including Ben-Gurion, Begin, and Nahum Goldmann, and argues that the nation&#8217;s legacy has, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/">The Seventh Million : The Israelis and the Holocaust &#8211; Tom Segev, Translated by Professor Haim Watzman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Seventh Million is the first book to show the decisive impact of the Holocaust on the identity, ideology, and politics of Israel. Drawing on diaries, interviews, and thousands of declassified documents, Segev reconsiders the major struggles and personalities of Israel&#8217;s past, including Ben-Gurion, Begin, and Nahum Goldmann, and argues that the nation&#8217;s legacy has, at critical moments&#8211;the Exodus affair, the Eichmann trial, the case of John Demjanjuk&#8211;have been molded and manipulated in accordance with the ideological requirements of the state. The Seventh Million uncovers a vast and complex story and reveals how the bitter events of decades past continue to shape the experiences not just of individuals but of a nation. Translated by Haim Watzman.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/">The Seventh Million : The Israelis and the Holocaust &#8211; Tom Segev, Translated by Professor Haim Watzman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The First Muslim : The Story of Muhammad &#8211; Lesley Hazleton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-first-muslim-the-story-of-muhammad-lesley-hazleton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-first-muslim-the-story-of-muhammad-lesley-hazleton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The extraordinary life of the man who founded Islam, and the world he inhabited&#8211;and remade. Lesley Hazleton&#8217;s new book, Agnostic: A Spirited Manifesto, is out now from Riverhead Books. Muhammad&#8217;s was a life of almost unparalleled historical importance; yet for all the iconic power of his name, the intensely dramatic story of the prophet of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-muslim-the-story-of-muhammad-lesley-hazleton-abridged/">The First Muslim : The Story of Muhammad &#8211; Lesley Hazleton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The extraordinary life of the man who founded Islam, and the world he inhabited&#8211;and remade.     </p>
<p>                    Lesley Hazleton&#8217;s new book, Agnostic: A Spirited Manifesto, is out now from Riverhead Books.     </p>
<p>                     Muhammad&#8217;s was a life of almost unparalleled historical importance; yet for all the iconic power of his name, the intensely dramatic story of the prophet of Islam is not well known. In The First Muslim, Lesley Hazleton brings him vibrantly to life. Drawing on early eyewitness sources and on history, politics, religion, and psychology, she renders him as a man in full, in all his complexity and vitality.     </p>
<p>                     Hazleton&#8217;s account follows the arc of Muhammad&#8217;s rise from powerlessness to power, from anonymity to renown, from insignificance to lasting significance. How did a child shunted to the margins end up revolutionizing his world? How did a merchant come to challenge the established order with a new vision of social justice? How did the pariah hounded out of Mecca turn exile into a new and victorious beginning? How did the outsider become the ultimate insider?     </p>
<p>                     Impeccably researched and thrillingly readable, Hazleton&#8217;s narrative creates vivid insight into a man navigating between idealism and pragmatism, faith and politics, nonviolence and violence, rejection and acclaim. The First Muslim illuminates not only an immensely significant figure but his lastingly relevant legacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-muslim-the-story-of-muhammad-lesley-hazleton-abridged/">The First Muslim : The Story of Muhammad &#8211; Lesley Hazleton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Exegesis & Hermeneutics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Earliest Times To Present Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This rich and magisterial work traces Palestine&#8217;s millennia-old heritage, uncovering cultures and societies of astounding depth and complexity that stretch back to the very beginnings of recorded history. Starting with the earliest references in Egyptian and Assyrian texts, Nur Masalha explores how Palestine and its Palestinian identity have evolved over thousands of years, from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/">Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This rich and magisterial work traces Palestine&#8217;s millennia-old heritage, uncovering cultures and societies of astounding depth and complexity that stretch back to the very beginnings of recorded history.    </p>
<p>                    Starting with the earliest references in Egyptian and Assyrian texts, Nur Masalha explores how Palestine and its Palestinian identity have evolved over thousands of years, from the Bronze Age to the present day. Drawing on a rich body of sources and the latest archaeological evidence, Masalha shows how Palestine&#8217;s multicultural past has been distorted and mythologised by Biblical lore and the Israel-Palestinian conflict.    </p>
<p>                    In the process, Masalha reveals that the concept of Palestine, contrary to accepted belief, is not a modern invention or one constructed in opposition to Israel, but rooted firmly in ancient past. Palestine represents the authoritative account of the country&#8217;s history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/">Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jerusalem : The Biography &#8211; Simon Sebag Montefiore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/jerusalem-the-biography-simon-sebag-montefiore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Earliest Times To Present Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/jerusalem-the-biography-simon-sebag-montefiore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new, updated, revised edition of JERUSALEM: THE BIOGRAPHY, the wider history of the Middle East through the lens of the Holy City, covering from pre-history to 2020, from King David to Donald Trump. The story of Jerusalem is the story of the world. Jerusalem is the universal city, the capital of two peoples, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jerusalem-the-biography-simon-sebag-montefiore-abridged/">Jerusalem : The Biography &#8211; Simon Sebag Montefiore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new, updated, revised edition of JERUSALEM: THE BIOGRAPHY, the wider history of the Middle East through the lens of the Holy City, covering from pre-history to 2020, from King David to Donald Trump.     </p>
<p>                    The story of Jerusalem is the story of the world.    </p>
<p>                    Jerusalem is the universal city, the capital of two peoples, the shrine of three faiths; it is the site of Judgement Day and the battlefield of today&#8217;s clash of civilisations. How did this small, remote town become the Holy City, the &#8216;centre of the world&#8217; and now the key to peace in the Middle East? Drawing on new archives and a lifetime&#8217;s study, Montefiore reveals this ever-changing city through the wars, love affairs and revelations of the kings, empresses, prophets, poets, saints, conquerors and whores who created, destroyed, chronicled and believed in Jerusalem.    </p>
<p>                    A classic of modern literature, this is not only the epic story of 3,000 years of faith, slaughter, fanaticism and co-existence, but also a freshly-updated history of the entire Middle East, from King David to the twenty-first century, from the birth of Judaism, Christianity and Islam to the Israel-Palestine conflict and the wars of today. This is how Jerusalem became Jerusalem &#8211; the only city that exists twice &#8211; in heaven and on earth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jerusalem-the-biography-simon-sebag-montefiore-abridged/">Jerusalem : The Biography &#8211; Simon Sebag Montefiore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lawrence in Arabia : War, Deceit, Imperial Folly and the Making of the Modern Middle East &#8211; Scott Anderson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Battles & Campaigns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 1 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Arab Revolt against the Turks in World War One was, in the words of T.E. Lawrence, &#8216;a sideshow of a sideshow&#8217;. Amidst the slaughter in European trenches, the Western combatants paid scant attention to the Middle Eastern theatre. As a result, the conflict was shaped to a remarkable degree by a small handful of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/">Lawrence in Arabia : War, Deceit, Imperial Folly and the Making of the Modern Middle East &#8211; Scott Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Arab Revolt against the Turks in World War One was, in the words of T.E. Lawrence, &#8216;a sideshow of a sideshow&#8217;. Amidst the slaughter in European trenches, the Western combatants paid scant attention to the Middle Eastern theatre. As a result, the conflict was shaped to a remarkable degree by a small handful of adventurers and low-level officers far removed from the corridors of power.   At the centre of it all was Lawrence. In early 1914 he was an archaeologist excavating ruins in the sands of Syria; by 1917 he was battling both the enemy and his own government to bring about the vision he had for the Arab people. Operating in the Middle East at the same time, but to wildly different ends, were three other important players: a German attache, an American oilman and a committed Zionist. The intertwined paths of these four young men &#8211; the schemes they put in place, the battles they fought, the betrayals they endured and committed &#8211; mirror the grandeur, intrigue and tragedy of the war in the desert.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/">Lawrence in Arabia : War, Deceit, Imperial Folly and the Making of the Modern Middle East &#8211; Scott Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
