<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Prose: Non-fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/prose-non-fiction/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/prose-non-fiction/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Prose: Non-fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/prose-non-fiction/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hillbilly Elegy : A Memoir of a Family and Culture in Crisis &#8211; J. D. Vance</title>
		<link>/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Mobility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER Coming November 2020 as a major motion picture from Netflix starring Amy Adams and Glenn Close &#8216;The political book of the year&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;A frank, unsentimental, harrowing memoir &#8230; A superb book&#8217; New York Post &#8216;I bought this to try to better understand Trump&#8217;s appeal &#8230; but the memoir is so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/">Hillbilly Elegy : A Memoir of a Family and Culture in Crisis &#8211; J. D. Vance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER<br />
Coming November 2020 as a major motion picture from Netflix starring Amy Adams and Glenn Close</p>
<p>&#8216;The political book of the year&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>&#8216;A frank, unsentimental, harrowing memoir &#8230; A superb book&#8217; New York Post</p>
<p>&#8216;I bought this to try to better understand Trump&#8217;s appeal &#8230; but the memoir is so much more than that. A gripping, unputdownable page-turner&#8217; India Knight, Evening Standard</p>
<p>J. D. Vance grew up in the hills of Kentucky. His family and friends were the people most of the world calls rednecks, hillbillies or white trash.</p>
<p>In this deeply moving memoir, Vance tells the story of his family&#8217;s demons and of America &#8216; s problem with generational neglect. How his mother struggled against, but never fully escaped, the legacies of abuse, alcoholism, poverty and trauma. How his grandparents, &#8216;dirt poor and in love&#8217;, gave everything for their children to chase the American dream. How Vance beat the odds to graduate from Yale Law School. And how America came to abandon and then condescend to its white working classes, until they reached breaking point.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/">Hillbilly Elegy : A Memoir of a Family and Culture in Crisis &#8211; J. D. Vance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley</title>
		<link>/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine). The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine).    </p>
<p>                    The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, as a young man Garrard Conley was terrified and conflicted about his sexuality. When Garrard was a nineteen-year-old college student, he was outed to his parents, and was forced to make a life-changing decision: either agree to attend a church-supported conversion therapy program that promised to cure him of homosexuality; or risk losing family, friends, and the God he had prayed to every day of his life. Through an institutionalized Twelve-Step Program heavy on Bible study, he was supposed to emerge heterosexual, ex-gay, cleansed of impure urges and stronger in his faith in God for his brush with sin. Instead, even when faced with a harrowing and brutal journey, Garrard found the strength and understanding to break out in search of his true self and forgiveness.     </p>
<p>                    By confronting his buried past and the burden of a life lived in shadow, Garrard traces the complex relationships among family, faith, and community. At times heart-breaking, at times triumphant, Boy Erased is a testament to love that survives despite all odds.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore</title>
		<link>/inside-out-demi-moore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inside-out-demi-moore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year. Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir. For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                                A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year.</p>
<p>                                Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir.</p>
<p>                              For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore has never been far from the spotlight &#8211; or the headlines.</p>
<p>                              Even as Demi was becoming the highest paid actress in Hollywood, however, she was always outrunning her past, just one step ahead of the doubts and insecurities that defined her childhood. Throughout her rise to fame and during some of the most pivotal moments of her life, Demi battled addiction, body image issues, and childhood trauma that would follow her for years &#8211; all while juggling a skyrocketing career and at times negative public perception.  As her success grew, Demi found herself questioning if she belonged in Hollywood, if she was a good mother, a good actress &#8211; and, always, if she was simply good enough.</p>
<p>                              As much as her story is about adversity, it is also about tremendous resilience. In this deeply candid and reflective memoir, Demi pulls back the curtain and opens up about her career and personal life &#8211; laying bare her tumultuous relationship with her mother, her marriages, her struggles balancing stardom with raising a family, and her journey toward open heartedness. Inside Outis a story of survival, success, and surrender &#8211; a wrenchingly honest portrayal of one woman&#8217;s at once ordinary and iconic life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</title>
		<link>/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is Me &#8211; the joyously funny, honest and moving story of the most enduringly successful singer/songwriter of all time.<br />
                    ______________</p>
<p>                    Christened Reginald Dwight, he was a shy boy with Buddy Holly glasses who grew up in the London suburb of Pinner and dreamed of becoming a pop star.  By the age of twenty-three, he was performing his first gig in America, facing an astonished audience in his bright yellow dungarees, a star-spangled T-shirt and boots with wings. Elton John had arrived and the music world would never be the same again.</p>
<p>                    His life has been full of drama, from the early rejection of his work with songwriting partner Bernie Taupin to spinning out of control as a chart-topping superstar; from half-heartedly trying to drown himself in his LA swimming pool to disco-dancing with the Queen; from friendships with John Lennon, Freddie Mercury and George Michael to setting up his AIDS Foundation. All the while, Elton was hiding a drug addiction that would grip him for over a decade.</p>
<p>                    In Me Elton also writes powerfully about getting clean and changing his life, about finding love with David Furnish and becoming a father.   In a voice that is warm, humble and open, this is Elton on his music and his relationships, his passions and his mistakes.  This is a story that will stay with you, by a living legend.<br />
                    ______________</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Self-deprecating, funny . . . You cannot help but enjoy his company throughout, temper tantrums and all&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Racy, pacy and crammed with scurrilous anecdotes &#8211; what more could you ask from the rocket man&#8217; Guardian (Book of the Week)</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Chatty, gossipy, amusing and at times brutally candid&#8217; Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Confidence Game : The Psychology of the Con and Why We Fall for It Every Time &#8211; Maria Konnikova</title>
		<link>/the-confidence-game-the-psychology-of-the-con-and-why-we-fall-for-it-every-time-maria-konnikova/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Or Forensic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-confidence-game-the-psychology-of-the-con-and-why-we-fall-for-it-every-time-maria-konnikova/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The con artist: from Bernie Madoff to Clark Rockefeller to Lance Armstrong. How do they get away with it? And what keeps us falling for them, over and over again? In The Confidence Game, Maria Konnikova investigates the psychological principles that underlie each stage of the swindle, from the put-up all the way to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-confidence-game-the-psychology-of-the-con-and-why-we-fall-for-it-every-time-maria-konnikova/">The Confidence Game : The Psychology of the Con and Why We Fall for It Every Time &#8211; Maria Konnikova</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The con artist: from Bernie Madoff to Clark Rockefeller to Lance Armstrong. How do they get away with it? And what keeps us falling for them, over and over again? In The Confidence Game, Maria Konnikova investigates the psychological principles that underlie each stage of the swindle, from the put-up all the way to the fix, and how we can train ourselves to spot a story that isn&#8217;t all it seems.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-confidence-game-the-psychology-of-the-con-and-why-we-fall-for-it-every-time-maria-konnikova/">The Confidence Game : The Psychology of the Con and Why We Fall for It Every Time &#8211; Maria Konnikova</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger</title>
		<link>/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019 _____________________________ The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES<br />
                    THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                    _____________________________</p>
<p>                    The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in the world and inspire the people who bring the magic to life. </p>
<p>                    Robert Iger became CEO of The Walt Disney Company in 2005, during a difficult time. Morale had deteriorated, competition was intense, and technology was changing faster than at any time in the company&#8217;s history. His vision came down to three clear ideas: Recommit to the concept that quality matters, embrace technology instead of fighting it, and think bigger-think global-and turn Disney into a stronger brand in international markets. </p>
<p>                    Fourteen years later, Disney is the largest, most respected media company in the world, counting Pixar, Marvel, Lucasfilm and 21st Century Fox among its properties. Its value is nearly five times what it was when Iger took over, and he is recognized as one of the most innovative and successful CEOs of our era.</p>
<p>                    In The Ride of a Lifetime, Robert Iger shares the lessons he&#8217;s learned while running Disney and leading its 200,000 employees, and he explores the principles that are necessary for true leadership, including:</p>
<p>                     Optimism. Even in the face of difficulty, an optimistic leader will find the path toward the best possible outcome and focus on that, rather than give in to pessimism and blaming.<br />
                     Courage. Leaders have to be willing to take risks and place big bets. Fear of failure destroys creativity.<br />
                     Decisiveness. All decisions, no matter how difficult, can be made on a timely basis. Indecisiveness is both wasteful and destructive to morale.<br />
                     Fairness. Treat people decently, with empathy, and be accessible to them. </p>
<p>                    This book is about the relentless curiosity that has driven Iger for forty-five years, since the day he started as the lowliest studio grunt at ABC. It&#8217;s also about thoughtfulness and respect, and a decency-over-dollars approach that has become the bedrock of every project and partnership Iger pursues, from a deep friendship with Steve Jobs in his final years to an abiding love of the Star Wars mythology.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;The ideas in this book strike me as universal&#8221; Iger writes. &#8220;Not just to the aspiring CEOs of the world, but to anyone wanting to feel less fearful, more confidently themselves, as they navigate their professional and even personal lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Becoming : The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Michelle Obama</title>
		<link>/becoming-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-michelle-obama/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/becoming-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-michelle-obama/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An intimate, powerful, and inspiring memoir; 15 million copies sold worldwide THE NO. 1 BESTSELLER BRITISH BOOK AWARDS, NON-FICTION BOOK OF THE YEAR THE SUNDAY TIMES, MEMOIR OF THE YEAR BOOKS OF THE YEAR: THE TIMES, OBSERVER, GUARDIAN, EVENING STANDARD Now in paperback featuring a new introduction by Michelle Obama, a letter from the author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-michelle-obama/">Becoming : The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Michelle Obama</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An intimate, powerful, and inspiring memoir; 15 million copies sold worldwide</p>
<p>                    THE NO. 1 BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    BRITISH BOOK AWARDS, NON-FICTION BOOK OF THE YEAR</p>
<p>                    THE SUNDAY TIMES, MEMOIR OF THE YEAR</p>
<p>                    BOOKS OF THE YEAR: THE TIMES, OBSERVER, GUARDIAN, EVENING STANDARD</p>
<p>                    Now in paperback featuring a new introduction by Michelle Obama, a letter from the author to her younger self, and a book club guide with 20 discussion questions and a 5-question Q&#038;A, the intimate, powerful, and inspiring memoir by the former First Lady of the United States</p>
<p>                    In her memoir, a work of deep reflection and mesmerizing storytelling, Michelle Obama invites readers into her world, chronicling the experiences that have shaped her &#8212; from her childhood on the South Side of Chicago to her years as an executive balancing the demands of motherhood and work, to her time spent at the world&#8217;s most famous address. With unerring honesty and lively wit, she describes her triumphs and her disappointments, both public and private, telling her full story as she has lived it &#8212; in her own words and on her own terms.</p>
<p>                    Warm, wise, and revelatory, Becoming is the deeply personal reckoning of a woman of soul and substance who has steadily defied expectations &#8212; and whose story inspires us to do the same.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-michelle-obama/">Becoming : The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Michelle Obama</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow</title>
		<link>/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost. In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost.</p>
<p>                    In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was a predator, protected by fear, wealth, and a conspiracy of silence. As Farrow drew closer to the truth, shadowy operatives, from high-priced lawyers to elite war-hardened spies, mounted a secret campaign of intimidation, threatening his career, following his every move and weaponizing an account of abuse in his own family. </p>
<p>                    All the while, Farrow and his producer faced a degree of resistance that could not be explained &#8211; until now. And a trail of clues revealed corruption and cover-ups from Hollywood, to Washington, and beyond. </p>
<p>                    This is the untold story of the exotic tactics of surveillance and intimidation deployed by wealthy and connected men to threaten journalists, evade accountability and silence victims of abuse &#8211; and it&#8217;s the story of the women who risked everything to expose the truth and spark a global movement.</p>
<p>                    Both a spy thriller and a meticulous work of investigative journalism, Catch and Kill breaks devastating new stories about the rampant abuse of power &#8211; and sheds far-reaching light on investigations that shook the culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wild Embers : Poems of rebellion, fire and beauty &#8211; Nikita Gill</title>
		<link>/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry By Individual Poets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A stunning collection of poetry on feminism, trauma, survival and empowerment. You cannot burn away What has always been aflame WILD EMBERS explores the fire that lies within every soul, weaving words around ideas of feeling at home in your own skin, allowing yourself to heal and learning to embrace your uniqueness with love from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/">Wild Embers : Poems of rebellion, fire and beauty &#8211; Nikita Gill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A stunning collection of poetry on feminism, trauma, survival and empowerment.    </p>
<p>                    You cannot burn away<br />
                    What has always been aflame    </p>
<p>                    WILD EMBERS explores the fire that lies within every soul, weaving words around ideas of feeling at home in your own skin, allowing yourself to heal and learning to embrace your uniqueness with love from the universe.     </p>
<p>                    Featuring rewritten fairytale heroines, goddess wisdom and poetry that burns with revolution, this collection is an explosion of femininity, empowerment and personal growth.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/">Wild Embers : Poems of rebellion, fire and beauty &#8211; Nikita Gill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden</title>
		<link>/permanent-record-edward-snowden/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy & Data Protection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/permanent-record-edward-snowden/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down. In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down.</p>
<p>                    In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden shocked the world when he broke with the American intelligence establishment and revealed that the United States government was secretly pursuing the means to collect every single phone call, text message, and email. The result would be an unprecedented system of mass surveillance with the ability to pry into the private lives of every person on earth. Six years later, Snowden reveals for the very first time how he helped to build this system and why he was moved to expose it.</p>
<p>                    Spanning the bucolic Beltway suburbs of his childhood and the clandestine CIA and NSA postings of his adulthood, Permanent Record is the extraordinary account of a bright young man who grew up online &#8211; a man who became a spy, a whistleblower, and, in exile, the Internet&#8217;s conscience. Written with wit, grace, passion, and an unflinching candor, Permanent Record is a crucial memoir of our digital age and destined to be a classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Myself : A Journey &#8211; Alicia Keys</title>
		<link>/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In her intimate memoir, More Myself, Alicia Keys shares her quest for truth: about herself, her past, and her shift from sacrificing her spirit to celebrating her worth. One of the most celebrated musicians of our time, Alicia Keys has enraptured the nation with her heartfelt lyrics, extraordinary vocal range, and soul-stirring piano compositions. Yet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/">More Myself : A Journey &#8211; Alicia Keys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In her intimate memoir, More Myself, Alicia Keys shares her quest for truth: about herself, her past, and her shift from sacrificing her spirit to celebrating her worth.</p>
<p>                    One of the most celebrated musicians of our time, Alicia Keys has enraptured the nation with her heartfelt lyrics, extraordinary vocal range, and soul-stirring piano compositions. Yet away from the spotlight, Alicia has grappled with private heartache over the challenging and complex relationship with her father, the people-pleasing nature that characterized her early career, the loss of privacy surrounding her romantic relationships, and the oppressive expectations of female perfection.</p>
<p>                    Since her rise to fame, Alicia&#8217;s public persona has belied a deep personal truth: she has spent years not fully recognizing or honoring her own worth. After withholding parts of herself for so long, she is at last exploring the questions that live at the heart of her story: Who am I, really? And once I discover that truth, how can I become brave enough to embrace it?</p>
<p>                    More Myself is part autobiography, part narrative documentary. Alicia&#8217;s journey is revealed not only through her own candid recounting, but also through vivid recollections from those who have walked alongside her. The result is a 360-degree perspective on Alicia&#8217;s path: from her girlhood in Hell&#8217;s Kitchen and Harlem, to the process of self-discovery she&#8217;s still navigating.</p>
<p>                    With the raw honesty that epitomizes Alicia&#8217;s artistry, More Myself is at once a riveting account and a clarion call to readers: to define themselves in a world that rarely encourages a true and unique identity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/">More Myself : A Journey &#8211; Alicia Keys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</title>
		<link>/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER** In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER**</p>
<p>                    In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay</p>
<p>                    How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake news or the threat of terrorism? What should we teach our children? </p>
<p>                    Yuval Noah Harari takes us on a thrilling journey through today&#8217;s most urgent issues. The golden thread running through his exhilarating new book is the challenge of maintaining our collective and individual focus in the face of constant and disorienting change.</p>
<p>                    Are we still capable of understanding the world we have created?</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating&#8230; compelling&#8230; [Harari] has teed up a crucial global conversation about how to take on the problems of the 21st century&#8217; Bill Gates, New York Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Truly mind-expanding&#8230; Ultra-topical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Princess Diarist &#8211; Carrie Fisher</title>
		<link>/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Carrie Fisher discovered the journals she kept during the filming of the first Star Wars movie, she was astonished to see what they had preserved &#8211; plaintive love poems, unbridled musings with youthful naivete, and a vulnerability that she barely recognized. Now her fame as an author, actress, and pop-culture icon is indisputable, but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/">The Princess Diarist &#8211; Carrie Fisher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Carrie Fisher discovered the journals she kept during the filming of the first Star Wars movie, she was astonished to see what they had preserved &#8211; plaintive love poems, unbridled musings with youthful naivete, and a vulnerability that she barely recognized. Now her fame as an author, actress, and pop-culture icon is indisputable, but in 1977, Carrie Fisher was just a teenager with an all-consuming crush on her co-star, Harrison Ford.<br />
                     With these excerpts from her handwritten notebooks, The Princess Diarist is Fisher&#8217;s intimate and revealing recollection of what happened on one of the most famous film sets of all time &#8211; and what developed behind the scenes.  Fisher also ponders the joys and insanity of celebrity, and the absurdity of a life spawned by Hollywood royalty, only to be surpassed by her own outer-space royalty. Laugh-out-loud hilarious and endlessly quotable, The Princess Diarist brims with the candour and introspection of a diary while offering shrewd insight into the type of stardom that few will ever experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/">The Princess Diarist &#8211; Carrie Fisher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Melania and Me : The Rise and Fall of My Friendship with the First Lady &#8211; Stephanie Winston Wolkoff</title>
		<link>/melania-and-me-the-rise-and-fall-of-my-friendship-with-the-first-lady-stephanie-winston-wolkoff/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/melania-and-me-the-rise-and-fall-of-my-friendship-with-the-first-lady-stephanie-winston-wolkoff/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What Melania wants, Melania gets. The former director of special events at Vogue and producer of nine legendary Met Galas, Stephanie Winston Wolkoff met Melania Knauss in 2003 and had a front row seat to the transformation of Donald Trump&#8217;s then girlfriend from a rough-cut gem to a precious diamond. As their friendship deepened over [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/melania-and-me-the-rise-and-fall-of-my-friendship-with-the-first-lady-stephanie-winston-wolkoff/">Melania and Me : The Rise and Fall of My Friendship with the First Lady &#8211; Stephanie Winston Wolkoff</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What Melania wants, Melania gets.</p>
<p>                     The former director of special events at Vogue and producer of nine legendary Met Galas, Stephanie Winston Wolkoff met Melania Knauss in 2003 and had a front row seat to the transformation of Donald Trump&#8217;s then girlfriend from a rough-cut gem to a precious diamond. As their friendship deepened over lunches at Manhattan hot spots, black-tie parties and giggle sessions in the penthouse at Trump Tower, Wolkoff watched the newest Mrs Trump raise her son, Barron, and manage her highly scrutinised marriage.</p>
<p>                     After Trump won the 2016 election, Wolkoff was recruited to help produce the 58th Presidential Inaugu ration and to become the First Lady&#8217;s trusted advisor. Melania put Wolkoff in charge of hiring her staff, organising her events, helping her write speeches and creating her debut initiatives. Then it all fell apart when she was made the scapegoat for inauguration finance irregularities. Melania could have defended her innocent friend and confidant, but she stood by her man. The betrayal nearly destroyed Wolkoff.</p>
<p>                     In this candid and emotional memoir, Stephanie Winston Wolkoff takes you into Trump Tower and the White House to tell the funny, thrilling and heartbreaking story of her intimate friendship with one of the most famous women in the world, a woman few people truly understand. How did Melania react to the Access Hollywood tape and her husband&#8217;s affair with Stormy Daniels? Does she get along well with Ivanka? Why did she wear that jacket with &#8216;I really don&#8217;t care, do u?&#8217; printed on the back? Is Melania happy being First Lady? And what really happened with the inauguration&#8217;s funding of $107 million? Wolkoff has some ideas&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/melania-and-me-the-rise-and-fall-of-my-friendship-with-the-first-lady-stephanie-winston-wolkoff/">Melania and Me : The Rise and Fall of My Friendship with the First Lady &#8211; Stephanie Winston Wolkoff</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Danse Macabre &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/danse-macabre-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: C 1800 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/danse-macabre-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It was not long after Halloween when Stephen King received a telephone call from his editor. &#8216;Why don&#8217;t you do a book about the entire horror phenomenon as you see it? Books, movies, radio, TV, the whole thing.&#8217; The result is this unique combination of fantasy and autobiography, of classic horror writing honed to an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/danse-macabre-stephen-king/">Danse Macabre &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It was not long after Halloween when Stephen King received a telephone call from his editor. &#8216;Why don&#8217;t you do a book about the entire horror phenomenon as you see it? Books, movies, radio, TV, the whole thing.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    The result is this unique combination of fantasy and autobiography, of classic horror writing honed to an unforgettable edge by the bestselling master of the genre.    </p>
<p>                    DANSE MACABRE ranges across the whole spectrum of horror in popular culture from the seminal classics of Dracula and Frankenstein. It is a charming and fascinating book, replete with pertinent anecdote and observation, in which Stephen King describes his ideas on how horror works on many levels and how he brings it to bear on his own inimitable novels.    </p>
<p>                    There is a reason why Stephen King is one of the bestselling writers in the world, ever. Described in the Guardian as an author who &#8216;knows how to engage the deepest sympathies of his readers&#8217;, Stephen King writes books that draw you in and are impossible to put down.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/danse-macabre-stephen-king/">Danse Macabre &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Furiously Happy &#8211; Jenny Lawson</title>
		<link>/furiously-happy-jenny-lawson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/furiously-happy-jenny-lawson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For fans of David Sedaris, Tina Fey and Caitlin Moran comes Furiously Happy from Jenny Lawson, author of the #1 New York Times bestseller Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened. In Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened, Jenny Lawson regaled readers with uproarious stories of her bizarre childhood. In Furiously Happy she explores her lifelong battle with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/furiously-happy-jenny-lawson/">Furiously Happy &#8211; Jenny Lawson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For fans of David Sedaris, Tina Fey and Caitlin Moran comes Furiously Happy from Jenny Lawson, author of the #1 New York Times bestseller Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened.    </p>
<p>                    In Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened, Jenny Lawson regaled readers with uproarious stories of her bizarre childhood. In Furiously Happy she explores her lifelong battle with mental illness. A hysterical, ridiculous book about crippling depression and anxiety? That sounds like a terrible idea. And terrible ideas are what Jenny does best.    </p>
<p>                    As Jenny says: &#8216;You can&#8217;t experience pain without also experiencing the baffling and ridiculous moments of being fiercely, unapologetically, intensely and (above all) furiously happy.&#8217;  It&#8217;s a philosophy that has &#8211; quite literally &#8211; saved her life.    </p>
<p>                    Jenny&#8217;s first book, Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened, was ostensibly about family, but deep down it was about celebrating your own weirdness. Furiously Happy is a book about mental illness, but under the surface it&#8217;s about embracing joy in fantastic and outrageous ways.  And who doesn&#8217;t need a bit more of that?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/furiously-happy-jenny-lawson/">Furiously Happy &#8211; Jenny Lawson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cold War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*The No.1 Sunday Times Bestseller* *A BBC Between the Covers book club pick* *Shortlisted for the 2018 Baillie Gifford Prize* &#8216;THE BEST TRUE SPY STORY I HAVE EVER READ&#8217; JOHN LE CARRE An exciting Cold War story about a KGB double agent, by one of Britain&#8217;s greatest historians and the ultimate gift for anyone who [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/">The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*The No.1 Sunday Times Bestseller*<br />
                    *A BBC Between the Covers book club pick*<br />
                    *Shortlisted for the 2018 Baillie Gifford Prize*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;THE BEST TRUE SPY STORY I HAVE EVER READ&#8217; JOHN LE CARRE        </p>
<p>                    An exciting Cold War story about a KGB double agent, by one of Britain&#8217;s greatest historians and the ultimate gift for anyone who loves a good spy thriller!    </p>
<p>                    On a warm July evening in 1985, a middle-aged man stood on the pavement of a busy avenue in the heart of Moscow, holding a plastic carrier bag. In his grey suit and tie, he looked like any other Soviet citizen. The bag alone was mildly conspicuous, printed with the red logo of Safeway, the British supermarket.    </p>
<p>                    The man was a spy. A senior KGB officer, for more than a decade he had supplied his British spymasters with a stream of priceless secrets from deep within the Soviet intelligence machine. No spy had done more to damage the KGB. The Safeway bag was a signal: to activate his escape plan to be smuggled out of Soviet Russia. So began one of the boldest and most extraordinary episodes in the history of spying. Ben Macintyre reveals a tale of espionage, betrayal and raw courage that changed the course of the Cold War forever&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    BEN MACINTYRE&#8217;S NEXT BOOK AGENT SONYA IS AVAILABLE TO BUY NOW</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/">The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unstoppable : My Life So Far &#8211; Maria Sharapova (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fiercely honest, fearless, darkly funny autobiography of global tennis star Maria Sharapova In the middle of the night, a father and his daughter step off a Greyhound bus in Florida and head straight to the Nick Bollettieri Tennis Academy. They ring the bell, though no one is expecting them and they don&#8217;t speak English. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/">Unstoppable : My Life So Far &#8211; Maria Sharapova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fiercely honest, fearless, darkly funny autobiography of global tennis star Maria Sharapova    </p>
<p>                    In the middle of the night, a father and his daughter step off a Greyhound bus in Florida and head straight to the Nick Bollettieri Tennis Academy. They ring the bell, though no one is expecting them and they don&#8217;t speak English. They have arrived from Russia with just seven hundred dollars and the conviction that this six-year-old girl will be the world&#8217;s next great tennis star. They are right.    </p>
<p>                    This is Maria Sharapova&#8217;s gripping and fearless autobiography, telling her story from her roots in the small Siberian town her parents fled to after the Chernobyl disaster, through her arrival in the US with nothing and her phenomenal rise to success &#8211; winning Wimbledon aged just seventeen &#8211; to the disasters that threatened her career and her fight back.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling memoir&#8217; David Shaftel, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An illuminating account &#8230; This is the bildungsroman of a controversial champion, a portrait of the athlete as an uncommonly driven young woman&#8217; Julia Felsenthal, Vogue</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/">Unstoppable : My Life So Far &#8211; Maria Sharapova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Confidence Game : The Psychology of the Con and Why We Fall for It Every Time &#8211; Maria Konnikova (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-confidence-game-the-psychology-of-the-con-and-why-we-fall-for-it-every-time-maria-konnikova-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Or Forensic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-confidence-game-the-psychology-of-the-con-and-why-we-fall-for-it-every-time-maria-konnikova-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The con artist: from Bernie Madoff to Clark Rockefeller to Lance Armstrong. How do they get away with it? And what keeps us falling for them, over and over again? In The Confidence Game, Maria Konnikova investigates the psychological principles that underlie each stage of the swindle, from the put-up all the way to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-confidence-game-the-psychology-of-the-con-and-why-we-fall-for-it-every-time-maria-konnikova-abridged/">The Confidence Game : The Psychology of the Con and Why We Fall for It Every Time &#8211; Maria Konnikova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The con artist: from Bernie Madoff to Clark Rockefeller to Lance Armstrong. How do they get away with it? And what keeps us falling for them, over and over again? In The Confidence Game, Maria Konnikova investigates the psychological principles that underlie each stage of the swindle, from the put-up all the way to the fix, and how we can train ourselves to spot a story that isn&#8217;t all it seems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-confidence-game-the-psychology-of-the-con-and-why-we-fall-for-it-every-time-maria-konnikova-abridged/">The Confidence Game : The Psychology of the Con and Why We Fall for It Every Time &#8211; Maria Konnikova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brit(ish) : On Race, Identity and Belonging &#8211; Afua Hirsch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/british-on-race-identity-and-belonging-afua-hirsch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[British & Irish History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Migration, Immigration & Emigration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/british-on-race-identity-and-belonging-afua-hirsch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Afua Hirsch &#8211; co-presenter of Samuel L. Jackson&#8217;s major BBC TV series Enslaved &#8211; the Sunday Times bestseller that reveals the uncomfortable truth about race and identity in Britain today. You&#8217;re British. Your parents are British. Your partner, your children and most of your friends are British. So why do people keep asking where [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/british-on-race-identity-and-belonging-afua-hirsch-abridged/">Brit(ish) : On Race, Identity and Belonging &#8211; Afua Hirsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Afua Hirsch &#8211; co-presenter of Samuel L. Jackson&#8217;s major BBC TV series Enslaved &#8211; the Sunday Times bestseller that reveals the uncomfortable truth about race and identity in Britain today.    </p>
<p>                    You&#8217;re British.    </p>
<p>                    Your parents are British.    </p>
<p>                    Your partner, your children and most of your friends are British.    </p>
<p>                    So why do people keep asking where you&#8217;re from?    </p>
<p>                    We are a nation in denial about our imperial past and the racism that plagues our present. Brit(ish) is Afua Hirsch&#8217;s personal and provocative exploration of how this came to be &#8211; and an urgent call for change.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book for our divided and dangerous times&#8217;<br />
                    David Olusoga</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/british-on-race-identity-and-belonging-afua-hirsch-abridged/">Brit(ish) : On Race, Identity and Belonging &#8211; Afua Hirsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this book, they will know that you know.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times and New York Times bestseller. A true-life thriller by one of Putin&#8217;s Most Wanted.    </p>
<p>                    In November 2009, the young lawyer Sergei Magnitsky was beaten to death by eight police officers in a freezing cell in a Moscow prison. His crime? Testifying against Russian officials who were involved in a conspiracy to steal $230 million of taxes.    </p>
<p>                    Red Notice is a searing expose of the whitewash of this imprisonment and murder. The killing hasn&#8217;t been investigated. It hasn&#8217;t been punished. Bill Browder is still campaigning for justice for his late lawyer and friend. This is his explosive journey from the heady world of finance in New York and London in the 1990s, through battles with ruthless oligarchs in turbulent post-Soviet Union Moscow, to the shadowy heart of the Kremlin.    </p>
<p>                    With fraud, bribery, corruption and torture exposed at every turn, Red Notice is a shocking political roller-coaster.<br />
                    __________________    </p>
<p>                    Reads like a classic thriller, with an everyman hero alone and in danger in a hostile foreign city &#8230; but it&#8217;s all true, and it&#8217;s a story that needs to be told.&#8217; Lee Child    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A shocking true-life thriller.&#8217; Tom Stoppard    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A riveting account&#8230; it is a powerful story and Browder tells it skilfully.&#8217; The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chasing Hillary : On the Trail of the First Woman President Who Wasn&#8217;T &#8211; Amy Chozick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chasing-hillary-on-the-trail-of-the-first-woman-president-who-wasnt-amy-chozick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chasing-hillary-on-the-trail-of-the-first-woman-president-who-wasnt-amy-chozick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hillary Clinton dominated Amy Chozick&#8217;s life for more than a decade. Here, she tells the inside story of Clinton&#8217;s pursuit of the US presidency in a campaign book like no other. &#8216;A breathtaking, page-turning masterpiece&#8217; Mary Karr A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER Amy Chozick&#8217;s assignments, covering Clinton&#8217;s imploding 2008 campaign and then her front-row seat [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chasing-hillary-on-the-trail-of-the-first-woman-president-who-wasnt-amy-chozick-abridged/">Chasing Hillary : On the Trail of the First Woman President Who Wasn&#8217;T &#8211; Amy Chozick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hillary Clinton dominated Amy Chozick&#8217;s life for more than a decade. Here, she tells the inside story of Clinton&#8217;s pursuit of the US presidency in a campaign book like no other.    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;A breathtaking, page-turning masterpiece&#8217; Mary Karr<br />
                              A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                              Amy Chozick&#8217;s assignments, covering Clinton&#8217;s imploding 2008 campaign and then her front-row seat to the 2016 election on &#8216;The Hillary Beat,&#8217; set off a years-long journey in which the formative years of Chozick&#8217;s life became, both personally and professionally, intrinsically intertwined with Clinton&#8217;s presidential ambitions. As Clinton tried, and twice failed, to shatter &#8216;that highest, hardest glass ceiling,&#8217; Chozick was trying, with various fits and starts, to scale the highest echelons of American journalism.    </p>
<p>                              In this rollicking, hilarious narrative, Chozick takes us through the high- and low-lights of the most noxious and dramatic presidential election in history. Chozick&#8217;s candour and clear-eyed perspective &#8211; from her seat on the Hillary bus and reporting from inside the campaign&#8217;s headquarters to her run-ins with Donald J. Trump &#8211; provide fresh intrigue and insights into the story we think we all know.    </p>
<p>                              But Chasing Hillary is also the unusually personal and moving memoir of how Chozick came to understand Clinton not as a political animal, but as a complete, complex person, full of contradictions and forged in the crucible of many earlier battles. In the process, Chozick develops an intimate understanding of what drives Clinton, how she accomplished what no woman had before, and why she ultimately failed.    </p>
<p>                              The results also make Chozick question everything she&#8217;d worked so hard for in the first place. Political journalism had failed. The elite world Chozick had tried for years to fit in with had been rebuffed. The less qualified, bombastic man had triumphed (as they always seem to do), and Clinton had retreated to the woods, finally showing the real person Chozick had spent years hoping to see. Illuminating, poignant, laugh-out-loud funny, Chasing Hillary is a campaign book unlike any other that reads like a fast-moving political novel.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chasing-hillary-on-the-trail-of-the-first-woman-president-who-wasnt-amy-chozick-abridged/">Chasing Hillary : On the Trail of the First Woman President Who Wasn&#8217;T &#8211; Amy Chozick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Education Of Brett Kavanaugh &#8211; Robin Pogrebin, Kate Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A remarkable work of slowed-down journalism&#8230;They are doing their jobs as journalists and writing the first draft of history. &#8211;Jill Filipovic, The Washington Post &#8230;Generous but also damning. &#8211;Hanna Rosin, The New York Times From two New York Times reporters, a deeper look at the formative years of Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh and his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/">The Education Of Brett Kavanaugh &#8211; Robin Pogrebin, Kate Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A remarkable work of slowed-down journalism&#8230;They are doing their jobs as journalists and writing the first draft of history. &#8211;Jill Filipovic, The Washington Post &#8230;Generous but also damning. &#8211;Hanna Rosin, The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    From two New York Times reporters, a deeper look at the formative years of Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh and his confirmation. In September 2018, the F.B.I. was given only a week to investigate allegations of sexual misconduct against Brett Kavanaugh, President Trump&#8217;s Supreme Court nominee. But even as Kavanaugh was sworn in to his lifetime position, many questions remained unanswered, leaving millions of Americans unsettled. During the Senate confirmation hearings that preceded the bureau&#8217;s brief probe, New York Times reporters Robin Pogrebin and Kate Kelly broke critical stories about Kavanaugh&#8217;s past, including the Renate Alumni yearbook story. They were inundated with tips from former classmates, friends, and associates that couldn&#8217;t be fully investigated before the confirmation process closed. Now, their book fills in the blanks and explores the essential question: Who is Brett Kavanaugh? The Education of Brett Kavanaugh paints a picture of the prep-school and Ivy-League worlds that formed our newest Supreme Court Justice. By offering commentary from key players from his confirmation process who haven&#8217;t yet spoken publicly and pursuing lines of inquiry that were left hanging, it will be essential reading for anyone who wants to understand our political system and Kavanaugh&#8217;s unexpectedly emblematic role in it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/">The Education Of Brett Kavanaugh &#8211; Robin Pogrebin, Kate Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uncanny Valley : Seduction and Disillusionment in San Francisco&#8217;s Startup Scene &#8211; Anna Wiener (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Joan Didion at a startup&#8217; Rebecca Solnit &#8216;Impossibly pleasurable&#8217; Jia Tolentino &#8216;This is essential reading&#8217; Stylist At twenty-five years old, Anna Wiener was beginning to tire of her assistant job in New York publishing. There was no room to grow, and the voyeuristic thrill of answering someone else&#8217;s phone had worn thin. Within a year [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/">Uncanny Valley : Seduction and Disillusionment in San Francisco&#8217;s Startup Scene &#8211; Anna Wiener (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joan Didion at a startup&#8217; Rebecca Solnit    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Impossibly pleasurable&#8217; Jia Tolentino    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;This is essential reading&#8217; Stylist    </p>
<p>                              At twenty-five years old, Anna Wiener was beginning to tire of her assistant job in New York publishing. There was no room to grow, and the voyeuristic thrill of answering someone else&#8217;s phone had worn thin.    </p>
<p>                              Within a year she had moved to Silicon Valley to take up a job at a data analytics startup in San Francisco. Leaving her business casual skirts and shirts in the wardrobe, she began working in company-branded T-shirts. She had a healthy income for the first time in her life. She felt like part of the future.    </p>
<p>                              But a tide was beginning to turn. People were speaking of tech startups as surveillance companies. Out of sixty employees, only eight of her colleagues were women. Casual sexism was rife. Sexual harassment cases were proliferating. And soon, like everyone else, she was addicted to the internet, refreshing the news, refreshing social media, scrolling and scrolling and scrolling. Slowly, she began to realise that her blind faith in ambitious, arrogant young men from America&#8217;s soft suburbs wasn&#8217;t just her own personal pathology. It had become a global affliction.    </p>
<p>                              Uncanny Valley is a coming of age story set against the backdrop of our generation&#8217;s very own gold rush. It&#8217;s a story about the tension between old and new, between art and tech, between the quest for money and the quest for meaning &#8211; about how our world is changing forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/">Uncanny Valley : Seduction and Disillusionment in San Francisco&#8217;s Startup Scene &#8211; Anna Wiener (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ali: A Life : Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year 2017 &#8211; Jonathan Eig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ali-a-life-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2017-jonathan-eig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Boxing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ali-a-life-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2017-jonathan-eig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE WILLIAM HILL SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR PRIZE. SHORTLISTED FOR THE JAMES TAIT BLACK BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR. THE BRITISH SPORTS BOOK AWARDS SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR. WINNER OF THE PEN/ESPN AWARD FOR LITERARY SPORTS WRITING. THE TIMES SPORTS BOOK AWARDS BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR. The most comprehensive and definitive biography [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ali-a-life-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2017-jonathan-eig-abridged/">Ali: A Life : Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year 2017 &#8211; Jonathan Eig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE WILLIAM HILL SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR PRIZE.<br />
                     SHORTLISTED FOR THE JAMES TAIT BLACK BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR.<br />
                     THE BRITISH SPORTS BOOK AWARDS SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR.<br />
                     WINNER OF THE PEN/ESPN AWARD FOR LITERARY SPORTS WRITING.<br />
                     THE TIMES SPORTS BOOK AWARDS BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR.    </p>
<p>                     The most comprehensive and definitive biography of Muhammad Ali that has ever been published, based on more than 500 interviews with those who knew him best, with many dramatic new discoveries about his life and career.     </p>
<p>                     When the frail, trembling figure of Muhammad Ali lit the Olympic flame in Atlanta in 1996, a TV audience of up to 3 billion people was once again gripped by the story of the world&#8217;s most famous sporting icon. The man who had once been reviled for his refusal to fight for his country and for his fast-talking denunciation of his opponents was now almost universally adored, the true cost of his astonishing boxing career clear to see.    </p>
<p>                     In Jonathan Eig&#8217;s ground-breaking biography, backed up with much detailed new research specially commissioned for this book, we get a stunning portrait of one of the most significant personalities of the second half of the twentieth century. We are not only taken inside the ring for some of the most famous bouts in boxing history, we also learn about his personal life, his finances, his faith and the moments when the first signs of his physical decline began to show. Ali was a symbol of freedom and courage, a hero to many, but this is also a very personal story of a warrior who vanquished every opponent but was finally brought down by his own stubborn refusal to quit.    </p>
<p>                     An epic tale of a fighter who became the world&#8217;s most famous pacifist, Ali: A Life does full justice to an extraordinary man.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Ali: A Life is the business &#8211; 640 pages of patient scholarship and intelligent reassessment written in crackly prose&#8217; Giles Smith, The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;[A] richly researched, sympathetic yet unsparing portrait &#8230; Ali: A Life is an epic of a biography&#8217; Joyce Carol Oates, New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ali-a-life-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2017-jonathan-eig-abridged/">Ali: A Life : Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year 2017 &#8211; Jonathan Eig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Notorious RBG : The Life and Times of Ruth Bader Ginsburg &#8211; Irin Carmon, Shana Knizhnik (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/notorious-rbg-the-life-and-times-of-ruth-bader-ginsburg-irin-carmon-shana-knizhnik-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/notorious-rbg-the-life-and-times-of-ruth-bader-ginsburg-irin-carmon-shana-knizhnik-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8220;The authors make this unassuming, most studious woman come pulsing to life&#8230;Notorious RBG may be a playful project, but it asks to be read seriously&#8230;That I responded so personally to it is a testimony to [its] storytelling and panache.&#8221;- Jennifer Senior, New York Times Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg never [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notorious-rbg-the-life-and-times-of-ruth-bader-ginsburg-irin-carmon-shana-knizhnik-abridged/">Notorious RBG : The Life and Times of Ruth Bader Ginsburg &#8211; Irin Carmon, Shana Knizhnik (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER  &#8220;The authors make this unassuming, most studious woman come pulsing to life&#8230;Notorious RBG may be a playful project, but it asks to be read seriously&#8230;That I responded so personally to it is a testimony to [its] storytelling and panache.&#8221;- Jennifer Senior, New York Times  Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg never asked for fame-she has only tried to make the world a little better and a little freer.  But nearly a half-century into her career, something funny happened to the octogenarian: she won the internet. Across America, people who weren&#8217;t even born when Ginsburg first made her name as a feminist pioneer are tattooing themselves with her face, setting her famously searing dissents to music, and making viral videos in tribute.  Notorious RBG, inspired by the Tumblr that amused the Justice herself and brought to you by its founder and an award-winning feminist journalist, is more than just a love letter. It draws on intimate access to Ginsburg&#8217;s family members, close friends, colleagues, and clerks, as well an interview with the Justice herself.<br />
                    An original hybrid of reported narrative, annotated dissents, rare archival photos and documents, and illustrations, the book tells a never-before-told story of an unusual and transformative woman who transcends generational divides. As the country struggles with the unfinished business of gender equality and civil rights, Ginsburg stands as a testament to how far we can come with a little chutzpah.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notorious-rbg-the-life-and-times-of-ruth-bader-ginsburg-irin-carmon-shana-knizhnik-abridged/">Notorious RBG : The Life and Times of Ruth Bader Ginsburg &#8211; Irin Carmon, Shana Knizhnik (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AN ECONOMIST BOOK OF THE YEAR A NEW STATESMAN BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8216;This book is about a whole new way of studying the mind &#8230; Endlessly fascinating&#8217; Steven Pinker &#8216;A whirlwind tour of the modern human psyche&#8217; Economist Everybody lies, to friends, lovers, doctors, pollsters &#8211; and to themselves. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/">Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    AN ECONOMIST BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    A NEW STATESMAN BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is about a whole new way of studying the mind &#8230; Endlessly fascinating&#8217; Steven Pinker    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A whirlwind tour of the modern human psyche&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                    Everybody lies, to friends, lovers, doctors, pollsters &#8211; and to themselves. In Internet searches, however, people confess the truth.    </p>
<p>                    Insightful, funny and always surprising, Everybody Lies explores how this huge collection of data, unprecedented in human history, could just be the most important ever collected. It offers astonishing insights into the human psyche, revealing the biases deeply embedded within us, the questions we&#8217;re afraid to ask that might be essential to our well-being, and the information we can use to change our culture for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/">Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twas The Nightshift Before Christmas : Festive hospital diaries from the author of multi-million-copy hit This is Going to Hurt &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/twas-the-nightshift-before-christmas-festive-hospital-diaries-from-the-author-of-multi-million-copy-hit-this-is-going-to-hurt-adam-kay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diaries, Letters & Journals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/twas-the-nightshift-before-christmas-festive-hospital-diaries-from-the-author-of-multi-million-copy-hit-this-is-going-to-hurt-adam-kay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The number one Sunday Times bestseller &#8211; with a new, fantastically festive front cover! Twas the Nightshift Before Christmas is a short gift book of festive diaries from the author of multi-million-copy bestseller This is Going to Hurt. Christmas is coming, the goose is getting fat . . . but 1.4 million NHS staff are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/twas-the-nightshift-before-christmas-festive-hospital-diaries-from-the-author-of-multi-million-copy-hit-this-is-going-to-hurt-adam-kay-abridged/">Twas The Nightshift Before Christmas : Festive hospital diaries from the author of multi-million-copy hit This is Going to Hurt &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The number one Sunday Times bestseller &#8211; with a new, fantastically festive front cover! Twas the Nightshift Before Christmas is a short gift book of festive diaries from the author of multi-million-copy bestseller This is Going to Hurt.    </p>
<p>                    Christmas is coming, the goose is getting fat . . . but 1.4 million NHS staff are heading off to work. In this perfect present for anyone who has ever set foot in a hospital, Adam Kay delves back into his diaries for a hilarious, horrifying and sometimes heartbreaking peek behind the blue curtain at Christmastime.    </p>
<p>                    This is a love letter to all those who spend their festive season on the front line, removing babies and baubles from the various places they get stuck, at the most wonderful time of the year.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The perfect surgical stocking-filler&#8217; &#8211; The Times    </p>
<p>                    Two different covers of Twas the Nightshift Before Christmas have been printed: one has a special festive design, and the other is our original hardback design. You will either receive the festive design or the original (as shown here) in your order. Specific covers cannot be requested.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/twas-the-nightshift-before-christmas-festive-hospital-diaries-from-the-author-of-multi-million-copy-hit-this-is-going-to-hurt-adam-kay-abridged/">Twas The Nightshift Before Christmas : Festive hospital diaries from the author of multi-million-copy hit This is Going to Hurt &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year. Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir. For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year.    </p>
<p>                                Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir.    </p>
<p>                              For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore has never been far from the spotlight &#8211; or the headlines.    </p>
<p>                              Even as Demi was becoming the highest paid actress in Hollywood, however, she was always outrunning her past, just one step ahead of the doubts and insecurities that defined her childhood. Throughout her rise to fame and during some of the most pivotal moments of her life, Demi battled addiction, body image issues, and childhood trauma that would follow her for years &#8211; all while juggling a skyrocketing career and at times negative public perception.  As her success grew, Demi found herself questioning if she belonged in Hollywood, if she was a good mother, a good actress &#8211; and, always, if she was simply good enough.    </p>
<p>                              As much as her story is about adversity, it is also about tremendous resilience. In this deeply candid and reflective memoir, Demi pulls back the curtain and opens up about her career and personal life &#8211; laying bare her tumultuous relationship with her mother, her marriages, her struggles balancing stardom with raising a family, and her journey toward open heartedness. Inside Outis a story of survival, success, and surrender &#8211; a wrenchingly honest portrayal of one woman&#8217;s at once ordinary and iconic life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth &#8211; Chris Hadfield (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-astronauts-guide-to-life-on-earth-chris-hadfield-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aerospace & Aviation Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronautics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Astronomy & Space]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-astronauts-guide-to-life-on-earth-chris-hadfield-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Back on the earth after three spaceflights, Chris Hadfield&#8217;s captivating memoir An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth reveals extraordinary stories from his life as an astronaut, and shows how to make the impossible a reality. Colonel Chris Hadfield has spent decades training as an astronaut and has logged nearly 4,000 hours in space. During [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-astronauts-guide-to-life-on-earth-chris-hadfield-abridged/">An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth &#8211; Chris Hadfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Back on the earth after three spaceflights, Chris Hadfield&#8217;s captivating memoir An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth reveals extraordinary stories from his life as an astronaut, and shows how to make the impossible a reality.    </p>
<p>                    Colonel Chris Hadfield has spent decades training as an astronaut and has logged nearly 4,000 hours in space. During this time he has broken into a Space Station with a Swiss army knife, disposed of a live snake while piloting a plane, been temporarily blinded while clinging to the exterior of an orbiting spacecraft, and become a YouTube sensation with his performance of David Bowie&#8217;s &#8216;Space Oddity&#8217; in space. The secret to Chris Hadfield&#8217;s success &#8211; and survival &#8211; is an unconventional philosophy he learned at NASA: prepare for the worst &#8211; and enjoy every moment of it.    </p>
<p>                    In his book, An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth, Chris Hadfield takes readers deep into his years of training and space exploration to show how to make the impossible possible. Through eye-opening, entertaining stories filled with the adrenaline of launch, the mesmerizing wonder of spacewalks and the measured, calm responses mandated by crises, he explains how conventional wisdom can get in the way of achievement &#8211; and happiness. His own extraordinary education in space has taught him some counter-intuitive lessons: don&#8217;t visualize success, do care what others think, and always sweat the small stuff.    </p>
<p>                    You might never be able to build a robot, pilot a spacecraft, make a music video or perform basic surgery in zero gravity like Colonel Hadfield. But his vivid and refreshing insights in this book will teach you how to think like an astronaut, and will change, completely, the way you view life on Earth &#8211; especially your own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-astronauts-guide-to-life-on-earth-chris-hadfield-abridged/">An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth &#8211; Chris Hadfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Do Women Want? : Adventures in the Science of Female Desire &#8211; Daniel Bergner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-do-women-want-adventures-in-the-science-of-female-desire-daniel-bergner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sexual Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-do-women-want-adventures-in-the-science-of-female-desire-daniel-bergner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this headline-making book, Daniel Bergner turns everything we thought we knew about women&#8217;s desire on its head. Drawing on extensive research and interviews with renowned behavioural scientists, sexologists, psychologists and everyday women, Daniel Bergner asks: &#8211; Do women really crave intimacy and emotional connection? &#8211; Are women more disposed to sex with strangers or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-do-women-want-adventures-in-the-science-of-female-desire-daniel-bergner-abridged/">What Do Women Want? : Adventures in the Science of Female Desire &#8211; Daniel Bergner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this headline-making book, Daniel Bergner turns everything we thought we knew about women&#8217;s desire on its head. Drawing on extensive research and interviews with renowned behavioural scientists, sexologists, psychologists and everyday women, Daniel Bergner asks:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Do women really crave intimacy and emotional connection?      </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Are women more disposed to sex with strangers or multiple partners than either science or society have ever let on?      </p>
<p>                    &#8211; And is &#8216;the fairer sex&#8217; actually more sexually aggressive and anarchic than men?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-do-women-want-adventures-in-the-science-of-female-desire-daniel-bergner-abridged/">What Do Women Want? : Adventures in the Science of Female Desire &#8211; Daniel Bergner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Restart : The Last Chance for the Indian Economy &#8211; Mihir S Sharma (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/restart-the-last-chance-for-the-indian-economy-mihir-s-sharma-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/restart-the-last-chance-for-the-indian-economy-mihir-s-sharma-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/restart-the-last-chance-for-the-indian-economy-mihir-s-sharma-abridged/">Restart : The Last Chance for the Indian Economy &#8211; Mihir S Sharma (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/restart-the-last-chance-for-the-indian-economy-mihir-s-sharma-abridged/">Restart : The Last Chance for the Indian Economy &#8211; Mihir S Sharma (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States. &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times    </p>
<p>                    The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about social justice. As she rose to prominence as a political leader, her experiences would become her guiding light as she grappled with an array of complex issues and learned to bring a voice to the voiceless.    </p>
<p>                    Now, in The Truths We Hold, Harris reckons with the big challenges we face together. Drawing on the hard-won wisdom and insight from her own career and the work of those who have most inspired her, she communicates a vision of shared struggle, shared purpose, and shared values as we confront the great work of our day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Personal integrity shines through every page&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Furious Hours : Murder, Fraud and the Last Trial of Harper Lee &#8211; Casey Cep (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/furious-hours-murder-fraud-and-the-last-trial-of-harper-lee-casey-cep-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/furious-hours-murder-fraud-and-the-last-trial-of-harper-lee-casey-cep-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A BARACK OBAMA BOOK OF THE YEAR WINNER OF THE 2020 CRIME WRITERS&#8217; ASSOCIATION ALCS GOLD DAGGER FOR NON-FICTION SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2019 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION A SUNDAY TIMES, ECONOMIST AND SPECTATOR BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8216;A triumph on every level. One of the losses to literature is that Harper Lee never found [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/furious-hours-murder-fraud-and-the-last-trial-of-harper-lee-casey-cep-abridged/">Furious Hours : Murder, Fraud and the Last Trial of Harper Lee &#8211; Casey Cep (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A BARACK OBAMA BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    WINNER OF THE 2020 CRIME WRITERS&#8217; ASSOCIATION ALCS GOLD DAGGER FOR NON-FICTION<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2019 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION<br />
                    A SUNDAY TIMES, ECONOMIST AND SPECTATOR BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A triumph on every level. One of the losses to literature is that Harper Lee never found a way to tell a gothic true-crime story she&#8217;d spent years researching. Casey Cep has excavated this mesmerizing story and tells it with grace and insight and a fierce fidelity to the truth.&#8217;<br />
                    DAVID GRANN, author of Killers of the Flower Moon<br />
                    _____________________________<br />
                    The stunning story of an Alabama serial killer and the true-crime book that Harper Lee worked on obsessively in the years after To Kill a Mockingbird    </p>
<p>                    Reverend Willie Maxwell was a rural preacher accused of murdering five of his family members for insurance money in the 1970s. With the help of a savvy lawyer, he escaped justice for years until a relative shot him dead at the funeral of his last victim. Despite hundreds of witnesses, Maxwell&#8217;s murderer was acquitted &#8211; thanks to the same attorney who had previously defended the Reverend.    </p>
<p>                    As Alabama is consumed by these gripping events, it&#8217;s not long until news of the case reaches Alabama&#8217;s &#8211; and America&#8217;s &#8211; most famous writer. Intrigued by the story, Harper Lee makes a journey back to her home state to witness the Reverend&#8217;s killer face trial. Harper had the idea of writing her own In Cold Blood, the true-crime classic she had helped her friend Truman Capote research. Lee spent a year in town reporting on the Maxwell case and many more years trying to finish the book she called The Reverend.    </p>
<p>                    Now Casey Cep brings this story to life, from the shocking murders to the courtroom drama to the racial politics of the Deep South. At the same time, she offers a deeply moving portrait of one of the country&#8217;s most beloved writers and her struggle with fame, success, and the mystery of artistic creativity.    </p>
<p>                    This is the story Harper Lee wanted to write. This is the story of why she couldn&#8217;t.<br />
                    _____________________________<br />
                    &#8216;Fascinating &#8230; Cep has spliced together a Southern-gothic tale  of multiple murder and the unhappy story of Lee&#8217;s literary career, to produce a tale that is engrossing in its detail and deeply poignant&#8230; [Cep] spends the first third of Furious Hours following the jaw-dropping trail of murders &#8230; Engrossing &#8230; Cep writes about all this with great skill, sensitivity and attention to detail.&#8217;<br />
                    SUNDAY TIMES    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s been a long time since I picked up a book so impossible to put down. Furious Hours made me forget dinner, ignore incoming calls, and stay up reading into the small hours. It&#8217;s a work of literary and legal detection as gripping as a thriller. But it&#8217;s also a meditation on motive and mystery, the curious workings of history, hope, and ambition, justice, and the darkest matters of life and death. Casey Cep&#8217;s investigation into an infamous Southern murder trial and Harper Lee&#8217;s quest to write about it is a beautiful, sobering, and sometimes chilling triumph.&#8217;<br />
                    HELEN MACDONALD, author of H is for Hawk    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This story is just too good &#8230; Furious Hours builds and builds until it collides with the writer who saw the power of Maxwell&#8217;s story, but for some reason was unable to harness it. It lays bare the inner life of a woman who had a world-class gift for hiding &#8230; [this] book makes a magical leap, and it goes from being a superbly written true-crime story to the sort of story that even Lee would have been proud to write.&#8217;<br />
                    MICHAEL LEWIS, author of Moneyball and The Big Short</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/furious-hours-murder-fraud-and-the-last-trial-of-harper-lee-casey-cep-abridged/">Furious Hours : Murder, Fraud and the Last Trial of Harper Lee &#8211; Casey Cep (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding My Virginity : The New Autobiography &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>PAPERBACK EDITION FULLY UPDATED WITH TWO NEW CHAPTERS After creating 12 different billion-dollar businesses and breaking dozens of world records, wouldn&#8217;t you think you&#8217;d done it all? Not Sir Richard Branson. Having brought the Virgin brand to all corners of the globe, he&#8217;s now reaching out to the stars as he prepares to launch commercial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/">Finding My Virginity : The New Autobiography &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PAPERBACK EDITION FULLY UPDATED WITH TWO NEW CHAPTERS    </p>
<p>                    After creating 12 different billion-dollar businesses and breaking dozens of world records, wouldn&#8217;t you think you&#8217;d done it all?    </p>
<p>                    Not Sir Richard Branson. Having brought the Virgin brand to all corners of the globe, he&#8217;s now reaching out to the stars as he prepares to launch commercial space travel with Virgin Galactic.    </p>
<p>                    In this non-stop memoir, Richard takes you inside his whirlwind life: from reinventing his companies in the midst of the financial crisis and devastating personal losses, to tackling the planet&#8217;s biggest challenges, to the joys of becoming a &#8216;grand-dude&#8217; at 64.Discover the irrepressible spirit, ingenious vision and relentless drive that has made Richard the ultimate entrepreneur.    </p>
<p>                    The iconoclastic Virgin founder is still changing the world. Next comes outer space.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/">Finding My Virginity : The New Autobiography &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Know My Name : The Survivor of the Stanford Sexual Assault Case Tells Her Story &#8211; Chanel Miller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/know-my-name-the-survivor-of-the-stanford-sexual-assault-case-tells-her-story-chanel-miller-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/know-my-name-the-survivor-of-the-stanford-sexual-assault-case-tells-her-story-chanel-miller-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING MEMOIR &#8216;Incredibly moving and haunting&#8217; Roxane Gay &#8216;I read this book cover to cover and it stunned me&#8217; Jia Tolentino &#8216;Powerful, honest and necessary&#8217; Marian Keyes &#8216;To girls everywhere, I am with you. On nights when you feel alone, I am with you. When people doubt you or dismiss you, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/know-my-name-the-survivor-of-the-stanford-sexual-assault-case-tells-her-story-chanel-miller-abridged/">Know My Name : The Survivor of the Stanford Sexual Assault Case Tells Her Story &#8211; Chanel Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING MEMOIR     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Incredibly moving and haunting&#8217; Roxane Gay<br />
                    &#8216;I read this book cover to cover and it stunned me&#8217; Jia Tolentino<br />
                    &#8216;Powerful, honest and necessary&#8217; Marian Keyes    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;To girls everywhere, I am with you. On nights when you feel alone, I am with you. When people doubt you or dismiss you, I am with you. I fought every day for you. So never stop fighting, I believe you.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Chanel Miller&#8217;s story changed our world forever. In 2016 Brock Turner was sentenced to just six months in jail after he was caught sexually assaulting her on Stanford&#8217;s campus. His light sentencing, and Chanel&#8217;s victim impact statement, which was read by eleven million people in four days, sparked international outrage and action.    </p>
<p>                    Know My Name is an intimate, profoundly moving memoir that exposes a patriarchal culture biased to protect perpetrators, a criminal justice system designed to fail the most vulnerable, and ultimately shines with the courage required to move through suffering and live a full and beautiful life. Entwining pain, resilience, and humour, this breath-taking memoir will stand as a modern classic.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I could not put this phenomenal book down&#8217; Glennon Doyle, bestselling author of UNTAMED    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;To read Know My Name inspires hope&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A searing, beautiful book&#8217; Sunday Times      </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Know My Name marks the debut of a gifted young writer. Miller&#8217;s words are purpose. They are maps. And she is a treasure who has prevailed&#8217; New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/know-my-name-the-survivor-of-the-stanford-sexual-assault-case-tells-her-story-chanel-miller-abridged/">Know My Name : The Survivor of the Stanford Sexual Assault Case Tells Her Story &#8211; Chanel Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Are Displaced : My Journey and Stories from Refugee Girls Around the World &#8211; From Nobel Peace Prize Winner Malala Yousafzai &#8211; Malala Yousafzai (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-are-displaced-my-journey-and-stories-from-refugee-girls-around-the-world-from-nobel-peace-prize-winner-malala-yousafzai-malala-yousafzai-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Migration, Immigration & Emigration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Refugees & Political Asylum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-are-displaced-my-journey-and-stories-from-refugee-girls-around-the-world-from-nobel-peace-prize-winner-malala-yousafzai-malala-yousafzai-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful and emotional New York Times bestseller, Nobel Peace Prize winner and activist Malala Yousafzai shares various stories of displacement, including her own. Part memoir, part communal storytelling, We Are Displaced introduces readers to some of the incredible girls Malala has met on her many journeys and lets each tell her story &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-displaced-my-journey-and-stories-from-refugee-girls-around-the-world-from-nobel-peace-prize-winner-malala-yousafzai-malala-yousafzai-abridged/">We Are Displaced : My Journey and Stories from Refugee Girls Around the World &#8211; From Nobel Peace Prize Winner Malala Yousafzai &#8211; Malala Yousafzai (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful and emotional New York Times bestseller, Nobel Peace Prize winner and activist Malala Yousafzai shares various stories of displacement, including her own. Part memoir, part communal storytelling, We Are Displaced introduces readers to some of the incredible girls Malala has met on her many journeys and lets each tell her story &#8211; girls who have lost their community, relatives and often the only world they&#8217;ve ever known, but have not lost hope.    </p>
<p>                    Longing for home and fear of an uncertain future binds all of these young women, but each is unique. In a time of immigration crises, war and border conflicts, We Are Displaced is an important reminder that every single one of the 79.5 million currently displaced is a person &#8211; often a young person &#8211; with dreams for a better, safer world.    </p>
<p>                    Includes a new Afterword by the author</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-displaced-my-journey-and-stories-from-refugee-girls-around-the-world-from-nobel-peace-prize-winner-malala-yousafzai-malala-yousafzai-abridged/">We Are Displaced : My Journey and Stories from Refugee Girls Around the World &#8211; From Nobel Peace Prize Winner Malala Yousafzai &#8211; Malala Yousafzai (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine). The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine).    </p>
<p>                    The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, as a young man Garrard Conley was terrified and conflicted about his sexuality. When Garrard was a nineteen-year-old college student, he was outed to his parents, and was forced to make a life-changing decision: either agree to attend a church-supported conversion therapy program that promised to cure him of homosexuality; or risk losing family, friends, and the God he had prayed to every day of his life. Through an institutionalized Twelve-Step Program heavy on Bible study, he was supposed to emerge heterosexual, ex-gay, cleansed of impure urges and stronger in his faith in God for his brush with sin. Instead, even when faced with a harrowing and brutal journey, Garrard found the strength and understanding to break out in search of his true self and forgiveness.     </p>
<p>                    By confronting his buried past and the burden of a life lived in shadow, Garrard traces the complex relationships among family, faith, and community. At times heart-breaking, at times triumphant, Boy Erased is a testament to love that survives despite all odds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost. In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost.    </p>
<p>                    In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was a predator, protected by fear, wealth, and a conspiracy of silence. As Farrow drew closer to the truth, shadowy operatives, from high-priced lawyers to elite war-hardened spies, mounted a secret campaign of intimidation, threatening his career, following his every move and weaponizing an account of abuse in his own family.     </p>
<p>                    All the while, Farrow and his producer faced a degree of resistance that could not be explained &#8211; until now. And a trail of clues revealed corruption and cover-ups from Hollywood, to Washington, and beyond.     </p>
<p>                    This is the untold story of the exotic tactics of surveillance and intimidation deployed by wealthy and connected men to threaten journalists, evade accountability and silence victims of abuse &#8211; and it&#8217;s the story of the women who risked everything to expose the truth and spark a global movement.    </p>
<p>                    Both a spy thriller and a meticulous work of investigative journalism, Catch and Kill breaks devastating new stories about the rampant abuse of power &#8211; and sheds far-reaching light on investigations that shook the culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maid : A Barack Obama Summer Reading Pick and now a major Netflix series! &#8211; Stephanie Land (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/maid-a-barack-obama-summer-reading-pick-and-now-a-major-netflix-series-stephanie-land-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/maid-a-barack-obama-summer-reading-pick-and-now-a-major-netflix-series-stephanie-land-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NOW A NETFLIX SERIES STARRING MARGARET QUALLEY &#038; ANDY MACDOWELL. BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S SUMMER READING PICK, 2019. BBC RADIO 4 BOOK OF THE WEEK. Educated meets Nickel and Dimed in Stephanie Land&#8217;s memoir about working as a maid. A beautiful and gritty exploration of poverty in the western world. Includes a foreword by international bestelling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maid-a-barack-obama-summer-reading-pick-and-now-a-major-netflix-series-stephanie-land-abridged/">Maid : A Barack Obama Summer Reading Pick and now a major Netflix series! &#8211; Stephanie Land (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NOW A NETFLIX SERIES STARRING MARGARET QUALLEY &#038; ANDY MACDOWELL.<br />
                    BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S SUMMER READING PICK, 2019.<br />
                    BBC RADIO 4 BOOK OF THE WEEK.    </p>
<p>                    Educated meets Nickel and Dimed  in Stephanie Land&#8217;s memoir about working as a maid. A beautiful and  gritty exploration of poverty in the western world. Includes a foreword  by international bestelling author Barbara Ehrenreich.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My daughter learned to walk in a homeless shelter.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    As  a struggling single mum, determined to keep a roof over her daughter&#8217;s  head, Stephanie Land worked for years as a maid, working long hours in  order to provide for her small family. In Maid, she reveals the dark truth of what it takes to survive and thrive in today&#8217;s inequitable society.    </p>
<p>                      As she worked hard to climb her way out of poverty as a single parent,  scrubbing the toilets of the wealthy, navigating domestic labour jobs as  a cleaner whilst also juggling higher education, assisted housing, and a  tangled web of government assistance, Stephanie wrote. She wrote the  true stories that weren&#8217;t being told. The stories of the overworked and  underpaid.    </p>
<p>                     Written in honest, heart-rending prose and with great insight, Maid  explores the underbelly of the upper-middle classes and the reality of  what it&#8217;s like to be in service to them. &#8216;I&#8217;d become a nameless ghost,&#8217;  Stephanie writes. With this book, she gives voice to the &#8216;servant&#8217;  worker, those who fight daily to scramble and scrape by for their own  lives and the lives of their children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maid-a-barack-obama-summer-reading-pick-and-now-a-major-netflix-series-stephanie-land-abridged/">Maid : A Barack Obama Summer Reading Pick and now a major Netflix series! &#8211; Stephanie Land (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lost Connections : Why You&#8217;re Depressed and How to Find Hope &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Care Of The Mentally Ill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* Pre-order Johann Hari&#8217;s new book Stolen Focus now! * THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8216;A book that could actually make us happy&#8217; SIMON AMSTELL &#8216;This amazing book will change your life&#8217; ELTON JOHN &#8216;One of the most important texts of recent years&#8217; BRITISH JOURNAL OF GENERAL PRACTICE &#8216;Brilliant, stimulating, radical&#8217; MATT HAIG &#8216;The more people read [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/">Lost Connections : Why You&#8217;re Depressed and How to Find Hope &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* Pre-order Johann Hari&#8217;s new book Stolen Focus now! *    </p>
<p>                    THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book that could actually make us happy&#8217; SIMON AMSTELL<br />
                    &#8216;This amazing book will change your life&#8217; ELTON JOHN<br />
                    &#8216;One of the most important texts of recent years&#8217; BRITISH JOURNAL OF GENERAL PRACTICE<br />
                     &#8216;Brilliant, stimulating, radical&#8217; MATT HAIG<br />
                    &#8216;The more people read this book, the better off the world will be&#8217; NAOMI KLEIN<br />
                     &#8216;Wonderful&#8217; HILLARY CLINTON<br />
                    &#8216;Eye-opening&#8217; GUARDIAN<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant for anyone wanting a better understanding of mental health&#8217; ZOE BALL<br />
                     &#8216;A game-changer&#8217; DAVINA MCCALL<br />
                     &#8216;Extraordinary&#8217; DR MAX PEMBERTON<br />
                    &#8216;Beautiful&#8217; RUSSELL BRAND    </p>
<p>                    Depression and anxiety are now at epidemic levels. Why? Across the world, scientists have uncovered evidence for nine different causes. Some are in our biology, but most are in the way we are living today.    </p>
<p>                     Lost Connections offers a radical new way of thinking about this crisis. It shows that once we understand the real causes, we can begin to turn to pioneering new solutions &#8211; ones that offer real hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/">Lost Connections : Why You&#8217;re Depressed and How to Find Hope &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy & Data Protection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down. In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down.    </p>
<p>                    In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden shocked the world when he broke with the American intelligence establishment and revealed that the United States government was secretly pursuing the means to collect every single phone call, text message, and email. The result would be an unprecedented system of mass surveillance with the ability to pry into the private lives of every person on earth. Six years later, Snowden reveals for the very first time how he helped to build this system and why he was moved to expose it.    </p>
<p>                    Spanning the bucolic Beltway suburbs of his childhood and the clandestine CIA and NSA postings of his adulthood, Permanent Record is the extraordinary account of a bright young man who grew up online &#8211; a man who became a spy, a whistleblower, and, in exile, the Internet&#8217;s conscience. Written with wit, grace, passion, and an unflinching candor, Permanent Record is a crucial memoir of our digital age and destined to be a classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians, Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is Me &#8211; the joyously funny, honest and moving story of the most enduringly successful singer/songwriter of all time.<br />
                    ______________    </p>
<p>                    Christened Reginald Dwight, he was a shy boy with Buddy Holly glasses who grew up in the London suburb of Pinner and dreamed of becoming a pop star.  By the age of twenty-three, he was performing his first gig in America, facing an astonished audience in his bright yellow dungarees, a star-spangled T-shirt and boots with wings. Elton John had arrived and the music world would never be the same again.    </p>
<p>                    His life has been full of drama, from the early rejection of his work with songwriting partner Bernie Taupin to spinning out of control as a chart-topping superstar; from half-heartedly trying to drown himself in his LA swimming pool to disco-dancing with the Queen; from friendships with John Lennon, Freddie Mercury and George Michael to setting up his AIDS Foundation. All the while, Elton was hiding a drug addiction that would grip him for over a decade.    </p>
<p>                    In Me Elton also writes powerfully about getting clean and changing his life, about finding love with David Furnish and becoming a father.   In a voice that is warm, humble and open, this is Elton on his music and his relationships, his passions and his mistakes.  This is a story that will stay with you, by a living legend.<br />
                    ______________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Self-deprecating, funny . . . You cannot help but enjoy his company throughout, temper tantrums and all&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Racy, pacy and crammed with scurrilous anecdotes &#8211; what more could you ask from the rocket man&#8217; Guardian (Book of the Week)    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Chatty, gossipy, amusing and at times brutally candid&#8217; Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019 _____________________________ The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES<br />
                    THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                    _____________________________    </p>
<p>                    The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in the world and inspire the people who bring the magic to life.     </p>
<p>                    Robert Iger became CEO of The Walt Disney Company in 2005, during a difficult time. Morale had deteriorated, competition was intense, and technology was changing faster than at any time in the company&#8217;s history. His vision came down to three clear ideas: Recommit to the concept that quality matters, embrace technology instead of fighting it, and think bigger-think global-and turn Disney into a stronger brand in international markets.     </p>
<p>                    Fourteen years later, Disney is the largest, most respected media company in the world, counting Pixar, Marvel, Lucasfilm and 21st Century Fox among its properties. Its value is nearly five times what it was when Iger took over, and he is recognized as one of the most innovative and successful CEOs of our era.    </p>
<p>                    In The Ride of a Lifetime, Robert Iger shares the lessons he&#8217;s learned while running Disney and leading its 200,000 employees, and he explores the principles that are necessary for true leadership, including:    </p>
<p>                     Optimism. Even in the face of difficulty, an optimistic leader will find the path toward the best possible outcome and focus on that, rather than give in to pessimism and blaming.<br />
                     Courage. Leaders have to be willing to take risks and place big bets. Fear of failure destroys creativity.<br />
                     Decisiveness. All decisions, no matter how difficult, can be made on a timely basis. Indecisiveness is both wasteful and destructive to morale.<br />
                     Fairness. Treat people decently, with empathy, and be accessible to them.     </p>
<p>                    This book is about the relentless curiosity that has driven Iger for forty-five years, since the day he started as the lowliest studio grunt at ABC. It&#8217;s also about thoughtfulness and respect, and a decency-over-dollars approach that has become the bedrock of every project and partnership Iger pursues, from a deep friendship with Steve Jobs in his final years to an abiding love of the Star Wars mythology.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The ideas in this book strike me as universal&#8221; Iger writes. &#8220;Not just to the aspiring CEOs of the world, but to anyone wanting to feel less fearful, more confidently themselves, as they navigate their professional and even personal lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING * &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING *     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly written haymaker&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly three years of reporting, hundreds of hours of interviews and more than two hundred sources, including some of the most senior members of the administration, friends and first-hand witnesses who have never spoken before, Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig take us inside some of the most controversial moments of Trump&#8217;s presidency. They peer deeply into Trump&#8217;s White House &#8211; at the aides pressured to lie to the public, the lawyers scrambling to clear up norm-breaking disasters, and the staffers whose careers have been reduced to ashes &#8211; to paint an unparalleled group portrait of an administration driven by self-preservation and paranoia.     </p>
<p>                    Rucker and Leonnig reveal Trump at his most unvarnished, showing the unhinged decision-making and incompetence that has floored officials and stunned foreign leaders. They portray unscripted calls with Vladimir Putin, steak dinners with Kim Jong-un, and calls with Theresa May so hostile that they left her aides shaken. They also take a hard look at Robert Mueller, Trump&#8217;s greatest antagonist to date, and how his investigation slowly unravelled an administration whose universal value is loyalty &#8211; not to country, but to the president himself.    </p>
<p>                    Grippingly told, A Very Stable Genius is a behind-the-scenes account of Trump&#8217;s vainglorious pursuit of power in his first term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hard Choices : A Memoir &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>HILLARY RODHAM CLINTON&#8217;S INSIDE ACCOUNT OF THE CRISES, CHOICES AND CHALLENGES SHE FACED DURING HER FOUR YEARS AS AMERICA&#8217;S 67THSECRETARY OF STATE, AND HOW THOSE EXPERIENCES DRIVE HER VIEW OF THE FUTURE, INCLUDING A NEW EPILOGUE. &#8216;All of us face hard choices in our lives,&#8217; Hillary Rodham Clinton writes at the start of this personal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">Hard Choices : A Memoir &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HILLARY RODHAM CLINTON&#8217;S INSIDE ACCOUNT OF THE CRISES, CHOICES AND CHALLENGES SHE FACED DURING HER FOUR YEARS AS AMERICA&#8217;S 67THSECRETARY OF STATE, AND HOW THOSE EXPERIENCES DRIVE HER VIEW OF THE FUTURE, INCLUDING A NEW EPILOGUE.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;All of us face hard choices in our lives,&#8217; Hillary Rodham Clinton writes at the start of this personal chronicle of years at the centre of world events. &#8216;Life is about making such choices. Our choices and how we handle them shape the people we become.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                     In the aftermath of her 2008 presidential run, she expected to return to representing New York in the Unites States Senate. To her surprise, her formal rival for the Democratic Party nomination, newly elected President Barack Obama, asked her to serve in his administration as Secretary of State. This memoir is the story of the four extraordinary and historic years that followed, and the hard choices that she and her colleagues confronted.     </p>
<p>                     Secretary Clinton and President Obama had to decide how to repair fractured alliances, wind down two wars and address a global financial crisis. They faced a rising competitor in China, growing threats from Iran and North Korea, and revolutions across the Middle East. Along the way, they grappled with some of the toughest dilemmas of US foreign policy, especially the decision to send Americans into harm&#8217;s way, from Afghanistan to Libya to the hunt for Osama bin Laden.     </p>
<p>                    By the end of her tenure, Secretary Clinton had visited 112 countries, travelled nearly one million miles and gained a truly global perspective on many of the major trends reshaping the landscape of the twenty-first century, from economic inequality to climate change to revolutions in energy, communications and health. Drawing on conversations with numerous leaders and experts, Secretary Clinton offers her views on what it will take for the United States to compete and thrive in an interdependent world. She makes a passionate case for human rights and the full participation in society of girls, youth and LGBT people. An astute eyewitness to decades of social change, she distinguishes the trendlines from the headlines and describes the progress occurring throughout the world, day after day.     </p>
<p>                     Secretary Clinton&#8217;s descriptions of diplomatic conversations at the highest levels offer readers a masterclass in international relations, as does her analysis of how we can best use &#8216;smart power&#8217; to deliver security and prosperity in a rapidly changing world &#8211; one in which America remains the indispensable nation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">Hard Choices : A Memoir &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life. Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life.    </p>
<p>                     Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a movie star. By the age of 21, he was living in Los Angeles and had been crowned Mr Universe. Within five years, he had learned English and become the greatest bodybuilder in the world. Within ten years, he had earned his college degree and was a millionaire from his business enterprises in real estate, landscaping and bodybuilding. He was also the winner of a Golden Globe Award for his debut as a dramatic actor in Stay Hungry.    </p>
<p>                     But that was only the beginning. The Terminator spawned numerous sequels and made him one of Hollywood&#8217;s biggest stars, as he had a series of hit films including Predator, Total Recall, True Lies and Twins. He married Maria Shriver, becoming part of the Kennedy clan, while going on to become the Republican governor of California, where he led the state through a budget crisis, natural disasters and political turmoil.     </p>
<p>                    It is the greatest immigrant success story of our time. His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. Until now, he has never told the full story of his life, in his own voice. Here is Arnold, with total recall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Notes on a Nervous Planet &#8211; Matt Haig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Order THE COMFORT BOOK. Available now! THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The world is messing with our minds. What if there was something we could do about it? Looking at sleep, news, social media, addiction, work and play, Matt Haig invites us to feel calmer, happier and to question the habits of the digital [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/">Notes on a Nervous Planet &#8211; Matt Haig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Order THE COMFORT BOOK. Available now!    </p>
<p>                    THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The world is messing with our minds. What if there was something we could do about it?    </p>
<p>                    Looking at sleep, news, social media, addiction, work and play, Matt Haig invites us to feel calmer, happier and to question the habits of the digital age. This book might even change the way you spend your precious time on earth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/">Notes on a Nervous Planet &#8211; Matt Haig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
