<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Islamic Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/islamic-studies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/islamic-studies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Islamic Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/islamic-studies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</title>
		<link>/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Worship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Koran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Slavery & Abolition Of Slavery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when authorities you venerate condone something you know is wrong? Every major religion and philosophy once condoned or approved of slavery, but in modern times nothing is seen as more evil. Americans confront this crisis of authority when they erect statues of Founding Fathers who slept with their slaves. And Muslims faced it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/">Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when authorities you venerate condone something you know is wrong?</p>
<p>                    Every major religion and philosophy once condoned or approved of slavery, but in modern times nothing is seen as more evil. Americans confront this crisis of authority when they erect statues of Founding Fathers who slept with their slaves. And Muslims faced it when ISIS revived sex slavery, justifying it with verses from the Quran and the practice of Muhammad.</p>
<p>                    Exploring the moral and ultimately theological problem of slavery, Jonathan A.C. Brown traces how the Christian, Jewish and Islamic traditions have tried to reconcile modern moral certainties with the infallibility of God&#8217;s message. He lays out how Islam viewed slavery in theory, and the reality of how it was practiced across Islamic civilization. Finally, Brown carefully examines arguments put forward by Muslims for the abolition of slavery.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/">Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sex and the Citadel : Intimate Life in a Changing Arab World &#8211; Shereen El Feki (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Kirkus Reviews Best Book of the Year As the &#8220;Arab Spring&#8221; and its aftermath sweep streets and squares, parliaments and presidential palaces of the Middle East, Shereen El Feki&#8211;an award-winning Canadian-Egyptian journalist&#8211;has been looking at unrest a little closer to home: in the sexual lives of Arab men and women. The result is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/">Sex and the Citadel : Intimate Life in a Changing Arab World &#8211; Shereen El Feki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Kirkus Reviews Best Book of the Year     </p>
<p>                    As the &#8220;Arab Spring&#8221; and its aftermath sweep streets and squares, parliaments and presidential palaces of the Middle East, Shereen El Feki&#8211;an award-winning Canadian-Egyptian journalist&#8211;has been looking at unrest a little closer to home: in the sexual lives of Arab men and women. The result is an informative, insightful, and engaging account of this sensitive and still largely secret aspect of Arab society.     </p>
<p>                     Sexual attitudes and behaviors are shaped by politics and economics, religion and tradition, gender and generations&#8211;not only a reflection of the conditions that led to the uprisings, but also a measure of hard-won reforms in the years to come. Highly personal, rich with original research and remarkable stories, Sex and the Citadel gives us unprecedented and timely insight into a part of the world that is changing before our eyes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/">Sex and the Citadel : Intimate Life in a Changing Arab World &#8211; Shereen El Feki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Headscarves and Hymens : Why the Middle East Needs a Sexual Revolution &#8211; Mona Eltahawy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shocking, heartfelt and well-researched&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;A ground-shaping book that defines the edge of so many vital contemporary debates. Hers is a voice simultaneously behind and beyond the veil&#8217; Colum McCann &#8216;A fascinating, can&#8217;t-look-away, whistle-stop tour of the Middle East&#8217; Daily Telegraph &#8216;Brave and impassioned . . . A shocking book, and one that will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/">Headscarves and Hymens : Why the Middle East Needs a Sexual Revolution &#8211; Mona Eltahawy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shocking, heartfelt and well-researched&#8217; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A ground-shaping book that defines the edge of so many vital contemporary debates. Hers is a voice simultaneously behind and beyond the veil&#8217; Colum McCann    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fascinating, can&#8217;t-look-away, whistle-stop tour of the Middle East&#8217; Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brave and impassioned . . . A shocking book, and one that will make anyone who has seen veiling as a cultural issue think very hard about what is really going on&#8217; Mail on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    Headscarves and Hymens explodes the myth that we should stand back and watch while women are disempowered and abused in the name of religion.    </p>
<p>                     In this laceratingly honest account, Eltahawy takes aim both at attitudes in the Middle East and at the western liberals who mistake misogyny for cultural difference. Her argument is clear: unless political revolution in the Arab world is accompanied by social and sexual revolution, no progress will be made.    </p>
<p>                    Headscarves and Hymens is the book the world has been crying out for: a powerful, fearless account of what it really means to be a woman in the Muslim world.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A fascinating, can&#8217;t-look-away, whistle-stop tour of the Middle East&#8217; Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brave and impassioned . . . A shocking book, and one that will make anyone who has seen veiling as a cultural issue think very hard about what is really going on&#8217; Mail on Sunday</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/">Headscarves and Hymens : Why the Middle East Needs a Sexual Revolution &#8211; Mona Eltahawy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Destiny Disrupted : A History of the World Through Islamic Eyes &#8211; Tamim Ansary (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/destiny-disrupted-a-history-of-the-world-through-islamic-eyes-tamim-ansary-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/destiny-disrupted-a-history-of-the-world-through-islamic-eyes-tamim-ansary-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We in the west share a common narrative of world history. But our story largely omits a whole civilization whose citizens shared an entirely different narrative for a thousand years. In Destiny Disrupted , Tamim Ansary tells the rich story of world history as the Islamic world saw it, from the time of Mohammed to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/destiny-disrupted-a-history-of-the-world-through-islamic-eyes-tamim-ansary-abridged/">Destiny Disrupted : A History of the World Through Islamic Eyes &#8211; Tamim Ansary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We in the west share a common narrative of world history. But our story largely omits a whole civilization whose citizens shared an entirely different narrative for a thousand years. In  Destiny Disrupted , Tamim Ansary tells the rich story of world history as the Islamic world saw it, from the time of Mohammed to the fall of the Ottoman Empire and beyond. He clarifies why our civilizations grew up oblivious to each other, what happened when they intersected, and how the Islamic world was affected by its slow recognition that Europe,a place it long perceived as primitive and disorganized,had somehow hijacked destiny.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/destiny-disrupted-a-history-of-the-world-through-islamic-eyes-tamim-ansary-abridged/">Destiny Disrupted : A History of the World Through Islamic Eyes &#8211; Tamim Ansary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Excellent Daughters : The Secret Lives of Young Women Who Are Transforming the Arab World &#8211; Katherine Zoepf (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For more than a decade, Katherine Zoepf has lived in or traveled throughout the Arab world, reporting on the lives of women, whose role in the region has never been more in flux. Only a generation ago, female adolescence as we know it in the West did not exist in the Middle East. There were [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/">Excellent Daughters : The Secret Lives of Young Women Who Are Transforming the Arab World &#8211; Katherine Zoepf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For more than a decade, Katherine Zoepf has lived in or traveled throughout the Arab world, reporting on the lives of women, whose role in the region has never been more in flux. Only a generation ago, female adolescence as we know it in the West did not exist in the Middle East. There were only children and married women. Today, young Arab women outnumber men in universities, and a few are beginning to face down religious and social tradition in order to live independently, to delay marriage, and to pursue professional goals. Hundreds of thousands of devout girls and women are attending Qur&#8217;anic schools&#8211;and using the training to argue for greater rights and freedoms from an Islamic perspective. And, in 2011, young women helped to lead antigovernment protests in the Arab Spring. But their voices have not been heard. Their stories have not been told. In Syria, before its civil war, she documents a complex society in the midst of soul searching about its place in the world and about the role of women. In Lebanon, she documents a country that on the surface is freer than other Arab nations but whose women must balance extreme standards of self-presentation with Islamic codes of virtue. In Abu Dhabi, Zoepf reports on a generation of Arab women who&#8217;ve found freedom in work outside the home. In Saudi Arabia she chronicles driving protests and women entering the retail industry for the first time. In the aftermath of Tahrir Square, she examines the crucial role of women in Egypt&#8217;s popular uprising. Deeply informed, heartfelt, and urgent, Excellent Daughters brings us a new understanding of the changing Arab societies&#8211;from 9/11 to Tahrir Square to the rise of ISIS&#8211;and gives voice to the remarkable women at the forefront of this change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/">Excellent Daughters : The Secret Lives of Young Women Who Are Transforming the Arab World &#8211; Katherine Zoepf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Flags : The Rise of ISIS &#8211; Joby Warrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Fundamentalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**WINNER of the PULITZER PRIZE for NON-FICTION 2016** In a thrilling dramatic narrative, Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter Joby Warrick traces how the strain of militant Islam behind ISIS first arose in a remote Jordanian prison and spread to become the world&#8217;s greatest threat. When the government of Jordan granted amnesty to a group of political prisoners [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/">Black Flags : The Rise of ISIS &#8211; Joby Warrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**WINNER of the PULITZER PRIZE for NON-FICTION 2016**    </p>
<p>                    In a thrilling dramatic narrative, Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter  Joby Warrick traces how the strain of militant Islam behind ISIS first  arose in a remote Jordanian prison and spread to become the world&#8217;s greatest threat.    </p>
<p>                                   When the government of Jordan granted amnesty to a group of political prisoners in 1999, it little realized that among them was Abu Musab al-Zarqawi, a terrorist mastermind and soon the architect of an Islamist movement bent on dominating the Middle East. In Black Flags, an unprecedented character-driven account of the rise of ISIS, Joby Warrick shows how the zeal of this one man and the strategic mistakes of Western governments led to the banner of ISIS being raised over huge swathes of Syria and Iraq.    </p>
<p>                     Zarqawi began by directing terror attacks from a base in northern Iraq, but it was the allied invasion in 2003 that catapulted him to the head of a vast insurgency. By falsely identifying him as the link between Saddam Hussein and Osama bin Laden, Western officials inadvertently spurred like-minded radicals to rally to his cause. Their wave of brutal beheadings and suicide bombings persisted until American and Jordanian intelligence discovered clues that led to a lethal airstrike on Zarqawi&#8217;s hideout in 2006.    </p>
<p>                     His movement, however, endured. First calling themselves al-Qaeda in Iraq, then Islamic State of Iraq and Syria, or ISIS, his followers sought refuge in unstable, ungoverned pockets on the Iraq-Syria border. When the Syrian civil war broke out in 2011, and the rest of the world largely stood by, ISIS seized its chance to pursue Zarqawi&#8217;s dream of an ultra-conservative Islamic caliphate.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on unique high-level access to global intelligence sources, Warrick weaves gripping, moment-by-moment operational details with the perspectives of diplomats and spies, generals and heads of state, many of whom foresaw a menace worse than al Qaeda and tried desperately to stop it. Black Flags is a brilliant and definitive history that reveals the long arc of today&#8217;s most dangerous extremist threat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/">Black Flags : The Rise of ISIS &#8211; Joby Warrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Muqaddimah : An Introduction to History &#8211; Abridged Edition &#8211; Ibn Ibn Khaldun, Translated by Franz Rosenthal, Introduction by Bruce B. Lawrence, Edited by N. J. Dawood (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-muqaddimah-an-introduction-to-history-abridged-edition-ibn-ibn-khaldun-translated-by-franz-rosenthal-introduction-by-bruce-b-lawrence-edited-by-n-j-dawood-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Theory & Methods]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic & Arabic Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-muqaddimah-an-introduction-to-history-abridged-edition-ibn-ibn-khaldun-translated-by-franz-rosenthal-introduction-by-bruce-b-lawrence-edited-by-n-j-dawood-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Muqaddimah, often translated as &#8220;Introduction&#8221; or &#8220;Prolegomenon,&#8221; is the most important Islamic history of the premodern world. Written by the great fourteenth-century Arab scholar Ibn Khaldun (d. 1406), this monumental work established the foundations of several fields of knowledge, including the philosophy of history, sociology, ethnography, and economics. The first complete English translation, by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-muqaddimah-an-introduction-to-history-abridged-edition-ibn-ibn-khaldun-translated-by-franz-rosenthal-introduction-by-bruce-b-lawrence-edited-by-n-j-dawood-abridged/">The Muqaddimah : An Introduction to History &#8211; Abridged Edition &#8211; Ibn Ibn Khaldun, Translated by Franz Rosenthal, Introduction by Bruce B. Lawrence, Edited by N. J. Dawood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Muqaddimah, often translated as &#8220;Introduction&#8221; or &#8220;Prolegomenon,&#8221; is the most important Islamic history of the premodern world. Written by the great fourteenth-century Arab scholar Ibn Khaldun (d. 1406), this monumental work established the foundations of several fields of knowledge, including the philosophy of history, sociology, ethnography, and economics. The first complete English translation, by the eminent Islamicist and interpreter of Arabic literature Franz Rosenthal, was published in three volumes in 1958 as part of the Bollingen Series and received immediate acclaim in the United States and abroad. A one-volume abridged version of Rosenthal&#8217;s masterful translation first appeared in 1969. This Princeton Classics edition of the abridged version includes Rosenthal&#8217;s original introduction as well as a contemporary introduction by Bruce B. Lawrence. This volume makes available a seminal work of Islam and medieval and ancient history to twenty-first century audiences.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-muqaddimah-an-introduction-to-history-abridged-edition-ibn-ibn-khaldun-translated-by-franz-rosenthal-introduction-by-bruce-b-lawrence-edited-by-n-j-dawood-abridged/">The Muqaddimah : An Introduction to History &#8211; Abridged Edition &#8211; Ibn Ibn Khaldun, Translated by Franz Rosenthal, Introduction by Bruce B. Lawrence, Edited by N. J. Dawood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Islam &#8211; Karen Armstrong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/islam-karen-armstrong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/islam-karen-armstrong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the world&#8217;s foremost commentators on religious affairs on the history (and destiny) of the world&#8217;s most misunderstood religion. In the public mind, Islam is a religion of extremes: it is the world&#8217;s fastest growing faith; more than three-quarters of the world&#8217;s refugees are Islamic; it has produced government by authoritarian monarchies in Saudi [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/islam-karen-armstrong-abridged/">Islam &#8211; Karen Armstrong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the world&#8217;s foremost commentators on religious affairs on the history (and destiny) of the world&#8217;s most misunderstood religion.    </p>
<p>                    In the public mind, Islam is a religion of extremes: it is the world&#8217;s fastest growing faith; more than three-quarters of the world&#8217;s refugees are Islamic; it has produced government by authoritarian monarchies in Saudi Arabia and ultra-republicans in Iran. Whether we are reading about civil war in Algeria or Afghanistan, the struggle for the soul of Turkey, or political turmoil in Pakistan or Malaysia, the Islamic context permeates all these situations.    </p>
<p>                    Karen Armstrong&#8217;s elegant and concise book traces how Islam grew from the other religions of the book, Judaism and Christianity; introduces us to the character of Muhammed; and demonstrates that for much of its history, the religion has been a force for enlightenment that promoted liberties for women and allowed the arts and sciences to flourish.    </p>
<p>                    ISLAM shows how this progressive legacy is today often set aside as the faith struggles to come to terms with the economic and political weakness of most of its believers and with the forces of modernity itself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/islam-karen-armstrong-abridged/">Islam &#8211; Karen Armstrong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
