<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Teaching Of A Specific Subject Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/teaching-of-a-specific-subject/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/teaching-of-a-specific-subject/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Teaching Of A Specific Subject Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/teaching-of-a-specific-subject/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Innumeracy : Mathematical Illiteracy and Its Consequences &#8211; John Allen Paulos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Citizenship & Social Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of A Specific Subject]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Readers of Innumeracy will be rewarded with scores of astonishing facts, a fistful of powerful ideas, and, most important, a clearer, more quantitative way of looking at their world. Why do even well-educated people understand so little about mathematics? And what are the costs of our innumeracy? John Allen Paulos, in his celebrated bestseller first [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/">Innumeracy : Mathematical Illiteracy and Its Consequences &#8211; John Allen Paulos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Readers of Innumeracy will be rewarded with scores of astonishing facts, a fistful of powerful ideas, and, most important, a clearer, more quantitative way of looking at their world.     </p>
<p>                    Why do even well-educated people understand so little about mathematics? And what are the costs of our innumeracy? John Allen Paulos, in his celebrated bestseller first published in 1988, argues that our inability to deal rationally with very large numbers and the probabilities associated with them results in misinformed governmental policies, confused personal decisions, and an increased susceptibility to pseudoscience of all kinds. Innumeracy lets us know what we&#8217;re missing, and how we can do something about it.     </p>
<p>                    Sprinkling his discussion of numbers and probabilities with quirky stories and anecdotes, Paulos ranges freely over many aspects of modern life, from contested elections to sports stats, from stock scams and newspaper psychics to diet and medical claims, sex discrimination, insurance, lotteries, and drug testing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/">Innumeracy : Mathematical Illiteracy and Its Consequences &#8211; John Allen Paulos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Call of the Wild and Free : Reclaiming the Wonder in Your Child&#8217;s Education, A New Way to Homeschool &#8211; Ainsley Arment (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-call-of-the-wild-and-free-reclaiming-the-wonder-in-your-childs-education-a-new-way-to-homeschool-ainsley-arment-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Learning, Home Learning, Distance Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary & Middle Schools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of A Specific Subject]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-call-of-the-wild-and-free-reclaiming-the-wonder-in-your-childs-education-a-new-way-to-homeschool-ainsley-arment-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Allow your children to experience the adventure, freedom, and wonder of childhood with this practical guide that provides all the information, inspiration, and advice you need for creating a modern, quality homeschool education. Inspired by the spirit of Henry David Thoreau-&#8220;All good things are wild and free&#8221;-mother of five Ainsley Arment founded Wild + Free. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-call-of-the-wild-and-free-reclaiming-the-wonder-in-your-childs-education-a-new-way-to-homeschool-ainsley-arment-abridged/">The Call of the Wild and Free : Reclaiming the Wonder in Your Child&#8217;s Education, A New Way to Homeschool &#8211; Ainsley Arment (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Allow your children to experience the adventure, freedom, and wonder of childhood with this practical guide that provides all the information, inspiration, and advice you need for creating a modern, quality homeschool education.    </p>
<p>                    Inspired by the spirit of Henry David Thoreau-&#8220;All good things are wild and free&#8221;-mother of five Ainsley Arment founded Wild + Free. This growing online community of mothers and families want their children to receive a quality education at home by challenging their intellectual abilities and nurturing their sense of curiosity, joy and awe-the essence of a positive childhood.     </p>
<p>                    The homeschool approach of past generations is gone-including the stigma of socially awkward kids, conservative clothes, and a classroom setting replicated in the home. The Wild + Free movement is focused on a love of nature, reading great books, pursuing interests and hobbies, making the entire world a classroom, and prolonging the wonder of childhood, an appealing philosophy that is unpacked in the pages of this book    </p>
<p>                    The Call of the Wild and Free offers advice, information, and positive encouragement for parents considering homeschooling, those currently in the trenches looking for inspiration, as well as parents, educators, and caregivers who want supplementary resources to enhance their kids&#8217; traditional educations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-call-of-the-wild-and-free-reclaiming-the-wonder-in-your-childs-education-a-new-way-to-homeschool-ainsley-arment-abridged/">The Call of the Wild and Free : Reclaiming the Wonder in Your Child&#8217;s Education, A New Way to Homeschool &#8211; Ainsley Arment (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ten Days to Faster Reading &#8211; Abby Marks-Beale (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of A Specific Subject]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jump-Start Your Reading Skills! Speed reading used to require months of training. Now you can rev up your reading in just a few minutes a day. With quizzes to determine your present reading level and exercises to introduce new skills quickly, 10 Days to Faster Reading will improve your reading comprehension and speed as it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/">Ten Days to Faster Reading &#8211; Abby Marks-Beale (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jump-Start Your Reading Skills! Speed reading used to require months of training. Now you can rev up your reading in just a few minutes a day. With quizzes to determine your present reading level and exercises to introduce new skills quickly, 10 Days to Faster Reading will improve your reading comprehension and speed as it shows you how to:     </p>
<p>                     Break the Bad Habits That Slow You Down<br />
                     Develop Your Powers of Concentration<br />
                     Cut Your Reading Time in Half<br />
                     Use Proven, Specially Designed Reading Techniques<br />
                     Boost the Power of Your Peripheral Vision     </p>
<p>                     Learn How to Scan and Skim a Written Report &#8230;And All in 10 Days!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/">Ten Days to Faster Reading &#8211; Abby Marks-Beale (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
