<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Historical &amp; Comparative Linguistics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/historical-comparative-linguistics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/historical-comparative-linguistics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Historical &amp; Comparative Linguistics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/historical-comparative-linguistics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>My Grammar and I (Or Should That Be &#8216;Me&#8217;?) : Old-School Ways to Sharpen Your English &#8211; Caroline Taggart</title>
		<link>/my-grammar-and-i-or-should-that-be-me-old-school-ways-to-sharpen-your-english-caroline-taggart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-grammar-and-i-or-should-that-be-me-old-school-ways-to-sharpen-your-english-caroline-taggart/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Will do for grammar what Eats Shoots and Leaves did for punctuation&#8217; &#8211; The Times _______________________ A runaway hit and Sunday Times bestseller in 2008, My Grammar and I has continued to grow in popularity, becoming the go-to guide for grammar. My Grammar and I offers amusing examples of awful grammar, while steering you in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-grammar-and-i-or-should-that-be-me-old-school-ways-to-sharpen-your-english-caroline-taggart/">My Grammar and I (Or Should That Be &#8216;Me&#8217;?) : Old-School Ways to Sharpen Your English &#8211; Caroline Taggart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will do for grammar what Eats Shoots and Leaves did for punctuation&#8217; &#8211; The Times<br />
                    _______________________    </p>
<p>                    A runaway hit and Sunday Times bestseller in 2008, My Grammar and I has continued to grow in popularity, becoming the go-to guide for grammar.    </p>
<p>                    My Grammar and I offers amusing examples of awful grammar, while steering you in the direction of grammatical greatness. Taking you on a tour of the English language through the minefield of rules and conditions that can catch you out, from dangling modifiers to split infinitives, it highlights the common pitfalls that every English language user faces on a day to day basis.    </p>
<p>                    Refreshing everything you should have learnt at school and more, My Grammar and I is informative yet entertaining: a must-have reference guide for any English language enthusiast.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-grammar-and-i-or-should-that-be-me-old-school-ways-to-sharpen-your-english-caroline-taggart/">My Grammar and I (Or Should That Be &#8216;Me&#8217;?) : Old-School Ways to Sharpen Your English &#8211; Caroline Taggart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Horse, the Wheel, and Language : How Bronze-Age Riders from the Eurasian Steppes Shaped the Modern World &#8211; David W. Anthony</title>
		<link>/the-horse-the-wheel-and-language-how-bronze-age-riders-from-the-eurasian-steppes-shaped-the-modern-world-david-w-anthony/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prehistoric Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-horse-the-wheel-and-language-how-bronze-age-riders-from-the-eurasian-steppes-shaped-the-modern-world-david-w-anthony/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Roughly half the world&#8217;s population speaks languages derived from a shared linguistic source known as Proto-Indo-European. But who were the early speakers of this ancient mother tongue, and how did they manage to spread it around the globe? Until now their identity has remained a tantalizing mystery to linguists, archaeologists, and even Nazis seeking the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-horse-the-wheel-and-language-how-bronze-age-riders-from-the-eurasian-steppes-shaped-the-modern-world-david-w-anthony/">The Horse, the Wheel, and Language : How Bronze-Age Riders from the Eurasian Steppes Shaped the Modern World &#8211; David W. Anthony</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Roughly half the world&#8217;s population speaks languages derived from a shared linguistic source known as Proto-Indo-European. But who were the early speakers of this ancient mother tongue, and how did they manage to spread it around the globe? Until now their identity has remained a tantalizing mystery to linguists, archaeologists, and even Nazis seeking the roots of the Aryan race. The Horse, the Wheel, and Language lifts the veil that has long shrouded these original Indo-European speakers, and reveals how their domestication of horses and use of the wheel spread language and transformed civilization. Linking prehistoric archaeological remains with the development of language, David Anthony identifies the prehistoric peoples of central Eurasia&#8217;s steppe grasslands as the original speakers of Proto-Indo-European, and shows how their innovative use of the ox wagon, horseback riding, and the warrior&#8217;s chariot turned the Eurasian steppes into a thriving transcontinental corridor of communication, commerce, and cultural exchange.<br />
                    He explains how they spread their traditions and gave rise to important advances in copper mining, warfare, and patron-client political institutions, thereby ushering in an era of vibrant social change. Anthony also describes his fascinating discovery of how the wear from bits on ancient horse teeth reveals the origins of horseback riding. The Horse, the Wheel, and Language solves a puzzle that has vexed scholars for two centuries&#8211;the source of the Indo-European languages and English&#8211;and recovers a magnificent and influential civilization from the past.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-horse-the-wheel-and-language-how-bronze-age-riders-from-the-eurasian-steppes-shaped-the-modern-world-david-w-anthony/">The Horse, the Wheel, and Language : How Bronze-Age Riders from the Eurasian Steppes Shaped the Modern World &#8211; David W. Anthony</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Words on the Move : Why English Won&#8217;t &#8211; And Can&#8217;t &#8211; Sit Still (Like, Literally) &#8211; Professor of Linguistics John McWhorter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/words-on-the-move-why-english-wont-and-cant-sit-still-like-literally-professor-of-linguistics-john-mcwhorter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar & Vocabulary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/words-on-the-move-why-english-wont-and-cant-sit-still-like-literally-professor-of-linguistics-john-mcwhorter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Language is always changing, but the way English is spoken today rubs many of us the wrong way. Whether it&#8217;s the use of literally to mean &#8220;figuratively,&#8221; or the way young people use LOL or business jargon like What&#8217;s the ask?&#8211;it often seems as if the language is deteriorating before our eyes. But the truth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/words-on-the-move-why-english-wont-and-cant-sit-still-like-literally-professor-of-linguistics-john-mcwhorter-abridged/">Words on the Move : Why English Won&#8217;t &#8211; And Can&#8217;t &#8211; Sit Still (Like, Literally) &#8211; Professor of Linguistics John McWhorter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Language is always changing, but the way English is spoken today rubs many of us the wrong way. Whether it&#8217;s the use of literally to mean &#8220;figuratively,&#8221; or the way young people use LOL or business jargon like What&#8217;s the ask?&#8211;it often seems as if the language is deteriorating before our eyes.     </p>
<p>                    But the truth is different and a lot less scary. Drawing examples from everyday life and employing a generous helping of humor, John McWhorter shows that these shifts are common to all languages, and that we should embrace these changes, not condemn them.     </p>
<p>                    He opens our eyes to the surprising backstories to words and expressions we use every day. Did you know that silly once meant &#8220;blessed&#8221;? Or that ought was the original past tense of owe? Or that the suffix -ly in adverbs is actually a remnant of the word like?     </p>
<p>                    In Words on the Move, McWhorter encourages us to marvel at the dynamism and resilience of the English language, and his book offers a delightful journey where we see that words are ever on the move and our lives are all the richer for it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/words-on-the-move-why-english-wont-and-cant-sit-still-like-literally-professor-of-linguistics-john-mcwhorter-abridged/">Words on the Move : Why English Won&#8217;t &#8211; And Can&#8217;t &#8211; Sit Still (Like, Literally) &#8211; Professor of Linguistics John McWhorter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. But swearing is also a uniquely well-suited lens through which to look at history, offering a fascinating record of what people care about on the<br />
                    deepest levels of a culture-what&#8217;s divine, what&#8217;s terrifying, and what&#8217;s taboo.     </p>
<p>                    Holy Sh*t tells the story of two kinds of swearing-obscenities and oaths-from ancient Rome and the Bible to today. With humor and insight, Melissa Mohr takes readers on a journey to discover how &#8220;swearing&#8221; has come to include both testifying with your hand on the Bible and calling someone a *#$&#038;!* when they cut you off on the highway. She explores obscenities in ancient Rome-which were remarkably similar to our own-and unearths the history of religious oaths in the Middle Ages,<br />
                    when swearing (or not swearing) an oath was often a matter of life and death. Holy Sh*t also explains the advancement of civility and corresponding censorship of language in the 18th century, considers the rise of racial slurs after World War II, examines the physiological effects of swearing (increased heart<br />
                    rate and greater pain tolerance), and answers a question that preoccupies the FCC, the US Senate, and anyone who has recently overheard little kids at a playground: are we swearing more now than people did in the past?     </p>
<p>                    A gem of lexicography and cultural history, Holy Sh*t is a serious exploration of obscenity-and it also just might expand your repertoire of words to choose from the next time you shut your finger in the car door.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
