<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Advertising &amp; Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/advertising-society/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/advertising-society/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Advertising &amp; Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/advertising-society/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Post-Truth Business : How to Rebuild Brand Authenticity in a Distrusting World &#8211; Sean Pillot de Chenecey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FINALIST &#8211; Business Book Awards 2019 &#8211; Embracing Change Category Brands are built on trust, but in a post-truth world they&#8217;re faced with a serious challenge: so much of modern life is defined by mistrust. A shattering of the vital trust connection between brands and consumers, together with the evaporation of authenticity as a core [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/">The Post-Truth Business : How to Rebuild Brand Authenticity in a Distrusting World &#8211; Sean Pillot de Chenecey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FINALIST &#8211; Business Book Awards 2019 &#8211; Embracing Change Category    </p>
<p>                    Brands are built on trust, but in a post-truth world they&#8217;re faced with a serious challenge: so much of modern life is defined by mistrust. A shattering of the vital trust connection between brands and consumers, together with the evaporation of authenticity as a core brand pillar, is causing enormous problems for businesses on a global scale. If a brand isn&#8217;t seen as trustworthy, then when choice is available it will be rejected in favour of one that is.    </p>
<p>                    The Post-Truth Business provides a way forward for any organization wishing to rebuild brand authenticity in a distrustful world. It explains the interconnected problems facing businesses, with important topics including:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; The impact of fake news, disinformation and the weaponizing of lies<br />
                    &#8211; The safeguarding of privacy, alongside privacy as a tradable asset<br />
                    &#8211; Why and how brands must create communication with meaning<br />
                    &#8211; The dangers of inauthentic cultural marketing activities<br />
                    &#8211; Examples of conscious capitalism and brand activism<br />
                    &#8211; Lessons in authenticity from artisans and innovators<br />
                    &#8211; National branding and reputation capital<br />
                    &#8211; Leveraging the power of &#8216;brand trust&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    The Post-Truth Business shows how to strengthen consumer engagement by closing the &#8216;brand credibility gap&#8217;. It&#8217;s packed with examples of inspiring people, brands and international campaigns from the fashion, beauty, outdoor, motor, drinks, finance, media, technology, entertainment and health sectors. Each of them demonstrates a dynamic and positive way forward.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/">The Post-Truth Business : How to Rebuild Brand Authenticity in a Distrusting World &#8211; Sean Pillot de Chenecey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zucked : Waking Up to the Facebook Catastrophe &#8211; Roger McNamee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zucked-waking-up-to-the-facebook-catastrophe-roger-mcnamee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zucked-waking-up-to-the-facebook-catastrophe-roger-mcnamee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is the dramatic story of how a noted tech venture capitalist, an early mentor to Mark Zuckerberg and investor in his company, woke up to the serious damage Facebook was doing to our society and set out to try to stop it. If you had told Roger McNamee three years ago that he would [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zucked-waking-up-to-the-facebook-catastrophe-roger-mcnamee-abridged/">Zucked : Waking Up to the Facebook Catastrophe &#8211; Roger McNamee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the dramatic story of how a noted tech venture capitalist, an early mentor to Mark Zuckerberg and investor in his company, woke up to the serious damage Facebook was doing to our society and set out to try to stop it.    </p>
<p>                              If you had told Roger McNamee three years ago that he would soon be devoting himself to stopping Facebook from destroying democracy, he would have howled with laughter. He had mentored many tech leaders in his illustrious career as an investor, but few things had made him prouder, or been better for his fund&#8217;s bottom line, than his early service to Mark Zuckerberg. Still a large shareholder in Facebook, he had every good reason to stay on the bright side. Until he simply couldn&#8217;t.     </p>
<p>                              Zucked is McNamee&#8217;s intimate reckoning with the catastrophic failure of the head of one of the world&#8217;s most powerful companies to face up to the damage he is doing. It&#8217;s a story that begins with a series of rude awakenings. First there is the author&#8217;s dawning realization that the platform is being manipulated by some very bad actors. Then there is the even more unsettling realization that Zuckerberg and Sheryl Sandberg are unable or unwilling to share his concerns, polite as they may be to his face.     </p>
<p>                              And then comes Brexit and the election of Donald Trump, and the emergence of one horrific piece of news after another about the malign ends to which the Facebook platform has been put. To McNamee&#8217;s shock, Facebook&#8217;s leaders still duck and dissemble, viewing the matter as a public relations problem. Now thoroughly alienated, McNamee digs into the issue, and fortuitously meets up with some fellow travellers who share his concerns, and help him sharpen its focus. Soon he and a dream team of Silicon Valley technologists are charging into the fray, to raise consciousness about the existential threat of Facebook, and the persuasion architecture of the attention economy more broadly &#8211; to our public health and to our political order.     </p>
<p>                              Zucked is both an enthralling personal narrative and a masterful explication of the forces that have conspired to place us all on the horns of this dilemma. This is the story of a company and its leadership, but it&#8217;s also a larger tale of a business sector unmoored from normal constraints, at a moment of political and cultural crisis, the worst possible time to be given new tools for summoning the darker angels of our nature and whipping them into a frenzy. This is a wise, hard-hitting, and urgently necessary account that crystallizes the issue definitively for the rest of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zucked-waking-up-to-the-facebook-catastrophe-roger-mcnamee-abridged/">Zucked : Waking Up to the Facebook Catastrophe &#8211; Roger McNamee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
