<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Social Forecasting, Future Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/social-forecasting-future-studies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/social-forecasting-future-studies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Social Forecasting, Future Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/social-forecasting-future-studies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Inevitable : Understanding the 12 Technological Forces That Will Shape Our Future &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A quintessential work of technological futurism.&#8221; &#8211; James Surowiecki, strategy + business, &#8220;Best Business Books 2017 &#8211; Innovation&#8221; From one of our leading technology thinkers and writers, a guide through the twelve technological imperatives that will shape the next thirty years and transform our lives Much of what will happen in the next thirty years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/">The Inevitable : Understanding the 12 Technological Forces That Will Shape Our Future &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A quintessential work of technological futurism.&#8221; &#8211; James Surowiecki, strategy + business, &#8220;Best Business Books 2017 &#8211; Innovation&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    From one of our leading technology thinkers and writers, a guide through the twelve technological imperatives that will shape the next thirty years and transform our lives     </p>
<p>                    Much of what will happen in the next thirty years is inevitable, driven by technological trends that are already in motion. In this fascinating, provocative new book, Kevin Kelly provides an optimistic road map for the future, showing how the coming changes in our lives&#8211;from virtual reality in the home to an on-demand economy to artificial intelligence embedded in everything we manufacture&#8211;can be understood as the result of a few long-term, accelerating forces. Kelly both describes these deep trends&#8211;interacting, cognifying, flowing, screening, accessing, sharing, filtering, remixing, tracking, and questioning&#8211;and demonstrates how they overlap and are codependent on one another. These larger forces will completely revolutionize the way we buy, work, learn, and communicate with each other. By understanding and embracing them, says Kelly, it will be easier for us to remain on top of the coming wave of changes and to arrange our day-to-day relationships with technology in ways that bring forth maximum benefits. Kelly&#8217;s bright, hopeful book will be indispensable to anyone who seeks guidance on where their business, industry, or life is heading&#8211;what to invent, where to work, in what to invest, how to better reach customers, and what to begin to put into place&#8211;as this new world emerges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/">The Inevitable : Understanding the 12 Technological Forces That Will Shape Our Future &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Future Crimes : Inside The Digital Underground and the Battle For Our Connected World &#8211; Marc Goodman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER * * Future-proof yourself and your business by reading this book * Technological advances have benefited our world in immeasurable ways, but there is an ominous flipside. Criminals are often the earliest, and most innovative, adopters of technology and modern times have led to modern crimes. Today&#8217;s criminals are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/">Future Crimes : Inside The Digital Underground and the Battle For Our Connected World &#8211; Marc Goodman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER *    </p>
<p>                    * Future-proof yourself and your business by reading this book *     </p>
<p>                    Technological advances have benefited our world in immeasurable ways, but there is an ominous flipside. Criminals are often the earliest, and most innovative, adopters of technology and modern times have led to modern crimes. Today&#8217;s criminals are stealing identities, draining online bank-accounts and wiping out computer servers.  It&#8217;s disturbingly easy to activate baby cam monitors to spy on families, pacemakers can be hacked to deliver a lethal jolt, and thieves are analyzing your social media in order to determine the best time for a home invasion.    </p>
<p>                    Meanwhile, 3D printers produce AK-47s, terrorists can download the recipe for the Ebola virus, and drug cartels are building drones. This is just the beginning of the tsunami of technological threats coming our way.  In Future Crimes, Marc Goodman rips open his database of hundreds of real cases to give us front-row access to these impending perils. Reading like a sci-fi thriller, but based in startling fact, Goodman raises tough questions about the expanding role of technology in our lives. Future Crimes is a call to action for better security measures worldwide, but most importantly, will empower readers to protect themselves against these looming technological threats &#8211; before it&#8217;s too late.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/">Future Crimes : Inside The Digital Underground and the Battle For Our Connected World &#8211; Marc Goodman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Could Be Our Future : A Manifesto for a More Generous World &#8211; Yancey Strickler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-could-be-our-future-a-manifesto-for-a-more-generous-world-yancey-strickler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-could-be-our-future-a-manifesto-for-a-more-generous-world-yancey-strickler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Break free from a wealth-obsessed world Western society is trapped by three assumptions: 1) the point of life is to maximize your self-interest and wealth, 2) we&#8217;re individuals trapped in an adversarial world, and 3) that this path is inevitable. These ideas separate us, keep us powerless, and limit our imagination for the future. We [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-could-be-our-future-a-manifesto-for-a-more-generous-world-yancey-strickler-abridged/">This Could Be Our Future : A Manifesto for a More Generous World &#8211; Yancey Strickler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Break free from a wealth-obsessed world    </p>
<p>                    Western society is trapped by three assumptions: 1) the point of life is to maximize your self-interest and wealth, 2) we&#8217;re individuals trapped in an adversarial world, and 3) that this path is inevitable.    </p>
<p>                    These ideas separate us, keep us powerless, and limit our imagination for the future. We see them as the truth, but they are just a point of view that previous generations accepted as inevitable. It&#8217;s time we replace them with something new.    </p>
<p>                    In this bold, powerful book, Yancey Strickler &#8211; co-founder of Kickstarter &#8211; lays out an inspiring vision for a new world we have the power to create and how we can change course. While the pursuit of wealth has produced innovation and prosperity, it&#8217;s also produced dire consequences: environmental collapse, corruption, exploitation, and unhappiness around the world. We don&#8217;t have to get rid of money entirely, though: we can co-opt the tools we have used toward better measurement of what matters, technology, and specificity of goals&#8211;and refocus them to build a more generous, fair, and future-prepared society. By re-calibrating our definition of value, a world of scarcity can blossom into a world of abundance.    </p>
<p>                    Hopeful but firmly grounded, full of concrete examples and bursting with creativity, This Could Be Our Future brilliantly dissects the world we live in and shows us a road map to the world we are capable of making.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-could-be-our-future-a-manifesto-for-a-more-generous-world-yancey-strickler-abridged/">This Could Be Our Future : A Manifesto for a More Generous World &#8211; Yancey Strickler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enchanted Objects : Innovation, Design, and the Future of Technology &#8211; David Rose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of Who Owns the Future, an MIT Media Lab scientist imagines how everyday objects can intuit our needs, improve our lives, and form &#8220;an ethereal interconnection of gadgets and human desires that&#8230;will pervade our lives in the very near future&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). We are now standing at the precipice of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/">Enchanted Objects : Innovation, Design, and the Future of Technology &#8211; David Rose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of Who Owns the Future, an MIT Media Lab scientist imagines how everyday objects can intuit our needs, improve our lives, and form &#8220;an ethereal interconnection of gadgets and human desires that&#8230;will pervade our lives in the very near future&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).     </p>
<p>                    We are now standing at the precipice of the next transformative development, a world in which technology becomes more human. Soon, connected technology will be embedded in hundreds of everyday objects we already use: our cars, wallets, watches, umbrellas, even our trash cans. These objects will respond to our needs, come to know us, and even learn to think ahead on our behalf. David Rose calls these devices&#8211;which are just beginning to creep into the marketplace&#8211;Enchanted Objects.     </p>
<p>                     In Rose&#8217;s vision of the future, technology atomizes, combining itself with the objects that make up the very fabric of daily living. Such innovations will be woven into the background of our environment, enhancing human relationships, channeling desires for omniscience, long life, and creative expression. The enchanted objects of fairy tales and science fiction will enter real life.     </p>
<p>                     Groundbreaking, timely, and provocative, Enchanted Objects is a &#8220;delightful&#8221; (The New York Times) blueprint for a better future, where efficient solutions come hand in hand with technology that delights our senses. It is essential reading for designers, technologists, entrepreneurs, business leaders, and anyone who wishes to take a glimpse into the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/">Enchanted Objects : Innovation, Design, and the Future of Technology &#8211; David Rose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WASHINGTON POST BESTSELLER Winner of the getAbstract 17th International Book Award &#8220;The Seventh Sense is a concept every businessman, diplomat, or student should aspire to master&#8211;a powerful idea, backed by stories and figures that will be impossible to forget.&#8221; &#8212; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs and Leonardo da Vinci Endless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/">The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    WASHINGTON POST BESTSELLER Winner of the getAbstract 17th International Book Award &#8220;The Seventh Sense is a concept every businessman, diplomat, or student should aspire to master&#8211;a powerful idea, backed by stories and figures that will be impossible to forget.&#8221; &#8212; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs and Leonardo da Vinci Endless terror. Refugee waves. An unfixable global economy. Surprising election results. New billion-dollar fortunes. Miracle medical advances. What if they were all connected? What if you could understand why?  The Seventh Sense is the story of what all of today&#8217;s successful figures see and feel: the forces that are invisible to most of us but explain everything from explosive technological change to uneasy political ripples. The secret to power now is understanding our new age of networks. Not merely the Internet, but also webs of trade, finance, and even DNA. Based on his years of advising generals, CEOs, and politicians, Ramo takes us into the opaque heart of our world&#8217;s rapidly connected systems and teaches us what the losers are not yet seeing&#8211;and what the victors of this age already know.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/">The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where Will Man Take Us? : The bold story of the man technology is creating &#8211; Atul Jalan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/where-will-man-take-us-the-bold-story-of-the-man-technology-is-creating-atul-jalan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/where-will-man-take-us-the-bold-story-of-the-man-technology-is-creating-atul-jalan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first person who will live to be 150 years old has already been born. The screen that we peer into will soon be within us. We could soon be taking happiness pills before breakfast. The perfect partner might need to be charged before bed. This is a new world we are walking into. And [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/where-will-man-take-us-the-bold-story-of-the-man-technology-is-creating-atul-jalan-abridged/">Where Will Man Take Us? : The bold story of the man technology is creating &#8211; Atul Jalan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first person who will live to be 150 years old has already been born.<br />
                    The screen that we peer into will soon be within us.<br />
                    We could soon be taking happiness pills before breakfast.<br />
                    The perfect partner might need to be charged before bed.    </p>
<p>                    This is a new world we are walking into. And the man who began this journey won&#8217;t be the man who ends this journey. Where Will Man Take Us? explores the changes technology is bringing about in us-as a society and as a species. What will the next generation turn into, what will it be like, how will the new Adam and Eve live and love?<br />
                    In this book, Atul Jalan tackles nanotechnology, artificial intelligence, quantum computing and genetics, seamlessly weaving the future of technology with the changing dynamics of human love, morality and ethics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/where-will-man-take-us-the-bold-story-of-the-man-technology-is-creating-atul-jalan-abridged/">Where Will Man Take Us? : The bold story of the man technology is creating &#8211; Atul Jalan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Book of the Year for The Economist and the Observer Our world seems to be collapsing. The daily news cycle reports the deterioration: divisive politics across the Western world, racism, poverty, war, inequality, hunger. While politicians, journalists and activists from all sides talk about the damage done, Johan Norberg offers an illuminating and heartening [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/">Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Book of the Year for The Economist and the Observer    </p>
<p>                    Our world seems to be collapsing. The daily news cycle reports the deterioration: divisive politics across the Western world, racism, poverty, war, inequality, hunger. While politicians, journalists and activists from all sides talk about the damage done, Johan Norberg offers an illuminating and heartening analysis of just how far we have come in tackling the greatest problems facing humanity. In the face of fear-mongering, darkness and division, the facts are unequivocal: the golden age is now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/">Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder and CEO, Whole Foods Market).     </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Age, Byron Reese makes the case that technology has reshaped humanity just three times in history: 100,000 years ago, we harnessed fire, which led to language; 10,000 years ago, we developed agriculture, which led to cities and warfare; 5,000 years ago, we invented the wheel and writing, which lead to the nation state.    </p>
<p>                    We are now on the doorstep of a fourth change brought about by two technologies: AI and robotics. &#8220;Timely, highly informative, and certainly optimistic&#8221; (Booklist), The Fourth Age provides an essential background on how we got to this point, and how-rather than what-we should think about the topics we&#8217;ll soon all be facing: machine consciousness, automation, changes in employment, creative computers, radical life extension, artificial life, AI ethics, the future of warfare, superintelligence, and the implications of extreme prosperity.    </p>
<p>                    By asking questions like &#8220;Are you a machine?&#8221; and &#8220;Could a computer feel anything?&#8221;, Reese leads you through a discussion along the cutting edge in robotics and AI, and provides a framework by which we can all understand, discuss, and act on the issues of the Fourth Age and how they&#8217;ll transform humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Technologies & Applied Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).     </p>
<p>                    Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot be closed. But it is closing-fast.     </p>
<p>                    InAbundance, space entrepreneur turned innovation pioneer Peter H. Diamandis and award-winning science writer Steven Kotler document how progress in artificial intelligence, robotics, digital manufacturing synthetic biology, and other exponentially growing technologies will enable us to make greater gains in the next two decades than we have in the previous 200 years. We will soon have the ability to meet and exceed the basic needs of every person on the planet. Abundance for all is within our grasp.     </p>
<p>                    Breaking down human needs by category-water, food, energy, healthcare, education, freedom-Diamandis and Kotler introduce us to innovators and industry captains making tremendous strides in each area. &#8220;Not only isAbundancea riveting page-turner&#8230;but it&#8217;s a book that gives us a future worth fighting for. And even more than that, it shows us our place in that fight&#8221; (The Christian Science Monitor).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable. We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable.    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the time of Columbus, Copernicus, Gutenberg and others, redrew all maps of the world, liberated information and shifted Western civilization from the medieval to the early modern era. Such change came at a price: social division, political extremism, economic shocks, pandemics and other unintended consequences of human endeavour.    </p>
<p>                    Now is our second Renaissance. In the face of terrorism, Brexit, refugee crises and the global impact of a Trump presidency, we can flourish-if we heed the urgent lessons of history. Age of Discovery, revised and updated for this paperback edition, shows us how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene<br />
                    Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the future of our species for fans of Homo Deus and The Gene.<br />
                    After 3.8 billion years humankind is about to start evolving by new rules&#8230;<br />
                    From leading geopolitical expert and technology futurist Jamie Metzl comes a groundbreaking exploration of the many ways genetic-engineering is shaking the core foundations of our lives-sex, war, love, and death.<br />
                    At the dawn of the genetics revolution, our DNA is becoming as readable, writable, and hackable as our information technology. But as humanity starts retooling our own genetic code, the choices we make today will be the difference between realizing breathtaking advances in human well-being and descending into a dangerous and potentially deadly genetic arms race.<br />
                    Enter the laboratories where scientists are turning science fiction into reality. Look towards a future where our deepest beliefs, morals, religions, and politics are challenged like never before and the very essence of what it means to be human is at play. When we can engineer our future children, massively extend our lifespans, build life from scratch, and recreate the plant and animal world, should we?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An indispensable guide.&#8217; Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn &#8216;Tech&#8217;s most valuable teacher.&#8217; Forbes Silicon Valley&#8217;s leading intellectual and the founder of O&#8217;Reilly Media explores the upside and the potential downsides of our future &#8211; what he calls the &#8216;next economy&#8217;. Tim O&#8217;Reilly&#8217;s genius is to identify and explain emerging technologies with world shaking potential &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/">WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An indispensable guide.&#8217; Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tech&#8217;s most valuable teacher.&#8217; Forbes    </p>
<p>                    Silicon Valley&#8217;s leading intellectual and the founder of O&#8217;Reilly Media explores the upside and the potential downsides of our future &#8211; what he calls the &#8216;next economy&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    Tim O&#8217;Reilly&#8217;s genius is to identify and explain emerging technologies with world shaking potential &#8211; the World Wide Web, Open Source Software, Web 2.0, Open Government data, the Maker Movement, Big Data. &#8216;The man who can really can make a whole industry happen,&#8217; according to Executive Chairman of Google Eric Schmidt, O&#8217;Reilly has most recently focused on the future of work &#8211; AI, algorithms, and new approaches to business organisation that will shape our lives. He has brought together an unlikely coalition of technologists, business leaders, labour advocates, and policy makers to wrestle with these issues. In WTF? he shares the evolution of his intellectual development, applying his approach to a number of challenging issues we will face as citizens, employees, business leaders, and a nation.    </p>
<p>                    What is the future when an increasing number of jobs can be performed by intelligent machines instead of people, or only done by people in partnership with those machines? What happens to our consumer based societies &#8211; to workers and to the companies that depend on their purchasing power? Is income inequality and unemployment an inevitable consequence of technological advancement, or are there paths to a better future? What will happen to business when technology-enabled networks and marketplaces are better at deploying talent than traditional companies? What&#8217;s the future of education when on-demand learning outperforms traditional institutions? Will the fundamental social safety nets of the developed world survive the transition, and if not, what will replace them?    </p>
<p>                    The digital revolution has transformed the world of media, upending centuries-old companies and business models. Now, it is restructuring every business, every job, and every sector of society. Yet the biggest changes are still ahead. To survive, every industry and organisation will have to transform itself in multiple ways. O&#8217;Reilly explores what the next economy will mean for the world and every aspect of our lives &#8211; and what we can do to shape it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/">WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Neoliberalism isn&#8217;t working. Austerity is forcing millions into poverty and many more into precarious work, while the left remains trapped in stagnant political practices that offer no respite. Inventing the Future is a bold new manifesto for life after capitalism. Against the confused understanding of our high-tech world by both the right and the left, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/">Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Neoliberalism isn&#8217;t working. Austerity is forcing millions into poverty and many more into precarious work, while the left remains trapped in stagnant political practices that offer no respite. Inventing the Future is a bold new manifesto for life after capitalism. Against the confused understanding of our high-tech world by both the right and the left, this book claims that the emancipatory and future-oriented possibilities of our society can be reclaimed. Instead of running from a complex future, Nick Srnicek and Alex Williams demand a postcapitalist economy capable of advancing standards, liberating humanity from work and developing technologies that expand our freedoms. This new edition includes a new chapter where they respond to their various critics.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/">Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller The Next 100 Years now focuses his geopolitical forecasting acumen on the next decade and the imminent events and challenges that will test America and the world, specifically addressing the skills that will be required by the decade&#8217;s leaders. In the long view, history is seen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/">The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller The Next 100 Years now focuses his geopolitical forecasting acumen on the next decade and the imminent events and challenges that will test America and the world, specifically addressing the skills that will be required by the decade&#8217;s leaders.     </p>
<p>                    In the long view, history is seen as a series of events&#8211;but the course of those events is determined by individuals and their actions. During the next ten years, individual leaders will face significant transitions for their nations: the United States&#8217; relationships with Iran and Israel will be undergoing changes, China will likely confront a major crisis, and the wars in the Islamic world will subside. Unexpected energy and technology developments will emerge, and labor shortages will begin to matter more than financial crises. Distinguished geopolitical forecaster George Friedman analyzes these events from the perspectives of the men and women leading these global changes, focusing in particular on the American president, who will require extraordinary skills to shepherd the United States through this transitional period. The Next Decade is a provocative and fascinating look at the conflicts and opportunities that lie ahead.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/">The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions by Mig Greengard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybernetics & Systems Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In May 1997, the world watched as Garry Kasparov, the greatest chess player in the world, was defeated for the first time by the IBM supercomputer Deep Blue. It was a watershed moment in the history of technology: machine intelligence had arrived at the point where it could best human intellect. It wasn&#8217;t a coincidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/">Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions by Mig Greengard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In May 1997, the world watched as Garry Kasparov, the greatest chess player in the world, was defeated for the first time by the IBM supercomputer Deep Blue. It was a watershed moment in the history of technology: machine intelligence had arrived at the point where it could best human intellect.    </p>
<p>                    It wasn&#8217;t a coincidence that Kasparov became the symbol of man&#8217;s fight against the machines. Chess has long been the fulcrum in development of machine intelligence; the hoax automaton &#8216;The Turk&#8217; in the 18th century and Alan Turing&#8217;s first chess program in 1952 were two early examples of the quest for machines to think like humans &#8212; a talent we measured by their ability to beat their creators at chess. As the pre-eminent chessmaster of the 80s and 90s, it was Kasparov&#8217;s blessing and his curse to play against each generation&#8217;s strongest computer champions, contributing to their development and advancing the field.     </p>
<p>                    Like all passionate competitors, Kasparov has taken his defeat and learned from it. He has devoted much energy to devising ways in which humans can partner with machines in order to produce results better than either can achieve alone. During the twenty years since playing Deep Blue, he&#8217;s played both with and against machines, learning a great deal about our vital relationship with our most remarkable creations. Ultimately, he&#8217;s become convinced that by embracing the competition between human and machine intelligence, we can spend less time worrying about being replaced and more thinking of new challenges to conquer.    </p>
<p>                    In this breakthrough book, Kasparov tells his side of the story of Deep Blue for the first time &#8212; what it was like to strategize against an implacable, untiring opponent &#8212; the mistakes he made and the reasons the odds were against him. But more than that, he tells his story of AI more generally, and how he&#8217;s evolved to embrace it, taking part in an urgent debate with philosophers worried about human values, programmers creating self-learning neural networks, and engineers of cutting edge robotics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/">Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions by Mig Greengard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Makers : The New Industrial Revolution &#8211; Chris Anderson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/makers-the-new-industrial-revolution-chris-anderson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/makers-the-new-industrial-revolution-chris-anderson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If a country wants to remain economically vibrant, it needs to manufacture things. In recent years, however, many nations have become obsessed with making money out of selling services, leaving the real business of manufacturing to others. Makers is about how all that is being reversed. Over the past ten years, the internet has democratised [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-the-new-industrial-revolution-chris-anderson-abridged/">Makers : The New Industrial Revolution &#8211; Chris Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If a country wants to remain economically vibrant, it needs to manufacture things. In recent years, however, many nations have become obsessed with making money out of selling services, leaving the real business of manufacturing to others.    </p>
<p>                    Makers is about how all that is being reversed. Over the past ten years, the internet has democratised publishing, broadcasting and communications, leading to a massive increase in the range of participation in everything digital &#8211; the world of bits. Now the same is happening to manufacturing &#8211; the world of things.    </p>
<p>                    Chris Anderson, bestselling author of The Long Tail, explains how this is happening: how such  technologies as 3D printing and electronics assembly are becoming available to everybody, and how people are building successful businesses as a result. Whereas once every aspiring entrepreneur needed the support of a major manufacturer, now anybody with a smart idea and a little expertise can make their ideas a reality. Just as Google, Facebook and others have created highly successful companies in the virtual world, so these new inventors and manufacturers are assuming positions of ever greater importance in the real world.    </p>
<p>                    The next industrial revolution is on its way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-the-new-industrial-revolution-chris-anderson-abridged/">Makers : The New Industrial Revolution &#8211; Chris Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power. In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power.    </p>
<p>                    In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a mass retirement that will enervate capital supplies; and how it is the ever-ravenous American economy that is rapidly approaching energy independence. Combined, these factors are overturning the global system and ushering in a new (dis)order. For most, that is a disaster-in-waiting, but not for the Americans. The shale revolution allows Americans to sidestep a dangerous energy market. Only the U.S. boasts a youth population large enough to escape the sucking maw of global aging. Geography will matter more than ever in a de-globalizing world, and America&#8217;s geography is simply sublime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A new age &#8211; the novacene &#8211; has already begun.    </p>
<p>                    New beings will emerge from existing artificial intelligence systems. They will think 10,000 times faster than we do and will regard us as we now regard plants. The cruel, violent machine takeover imagined by sci-fi writers will not happen: these hyper-intelligent beings will be as dependent on the health of the planet as we are. They will need the planetary cooling system of Gaia to defend from the increasing heat of the sun. Gaia depends on organic life. We will be partners in this project. It is crucial, Lovelock argues, that the intelligence of Earth survives and prospers. We are at present the only beings capable of understanding the cosmos, but he speculates that the novacene could be the beginning of a process that will see intelligence suffusing the entire cosmos. At the age 100, Lovelock has produced the most compelling work of his life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE ECONOMIST &#8220;The most important book on decision making since Daniel Kahneman&#8217;s Thinking, Fast and Slow.&#8221;&#8211;Jason Zweig, The Wall Street Journal Everyone would benefit from seeing further into the future, whether buying stocks, crafting policy, launching a new product, or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/">Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE ECONOMIST      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The most important book on decision making since Daniel Kahneman&#8217;s Thinking, Fast and Slow.&#8221;&#8211;Jason Zweig, The Wall Street Journal     </p>
<p>                     Everyone would benefit from seeing further into the future, whether buying stocks, crafting policy, launching a new product, or simply planning the week&#8217;s meals. Unfortunately, people tend to be terrible forecasters. As Wharton professor Philip Tetlock showed in a landmark 2005 study, even experts&#8217; predictions are only slightly better than chance. However, an important and underreported conclusion of that study was that some experts do have real foresight, and Tetlock has spent the past decade trying to figure out why. What makes some people so good? And can this talent be taught?     </p>
<p>                     In Superforecasting, Tetlock and coauthor Dan Gardner offer a masterwork on prediction, drawing on decades of research and the results of a massive, government-funded forecasting tournament. The Good Judgment Project involves tens of thousands of ordinary people&#8211;including a Brooklyn filmmaker, a retired pipe installer, and a former ballroom dancer&#8211;who set out to forecast global events. Some of the volunteers have turned out to be astonishingly good. They&#8217;ve beaten other benchmarks, competitors, and prediction markets. They&#8217;ve even beaten the collective judgment of intelligence analysts with access to classified information. They are superforecasters.     </p>
<p>                     In this groundbreaking and accessible book, Tetlock and Gardner show us how we can learn from this elite group. Weaving together stories of forecasting successes (the raid on Osama bin Laden&#8217;s compound) and failures (the Bay of Pigs) and interviews with a range of high-level decision makers, from David Petraeus to Robert Rubin, they show that good forecasting doesn&#8217;t require powerful computers or arcane methods. It involves gathering evidence from a variety of sources, thinking probabilistically, working in teams, keeping score, and being willing to admit error and change course.     </p>
<p>                    Superforecasting offers the first demonstrably effective way to improve our ability to predict the future&#8211;whether in business, finance, politics, international affairs, or daily life&#8211;and is destined to become a modern classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/">Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
