<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Dinosaurs &amp; The Prehistoric World Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/dinosaurs-the-prehistoric-world/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/dinosaurs-the-prehistoric-world/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Dinosaurs &amp; The Prehistoric World Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/dinosaurs-the-prehistoric-world/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dinosaurs & The Prehistoric World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Palaeontology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Times Science Book of the Year. A Sunday Times Bestseller. 66 million years ago the dinosaurs were wiped from the face of the earth. Today, Dr. Steve Brusatte, one of the leading scientists of a new generation of dinosaur hunters, armed with cutting edge technology, is piecing together the complete story of how the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/">The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Times Science Book of the Year.<br />
                    A Sunday Times Bestseller.    </p>
<p>                    66 million years ago the dinosaurs were wiped from the face of the earth. Today, Dr. Steve Brusatte, one of the leading scientists of a new generation of dinosaur hunters, armed with cutting edge technology, is piecing together the complete story of how the dinosaurs ruled the earth for 150 million years.    </p>
<p>                    The world of the dinosaurs has fascinated on book and screen for decades &#8211; from early science fiction classics like The Lost World, to Godzilla terrorizing the streets of Tokyo, and the monsters of Jurassic Park. But what if we got it wrong? In The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs, top dinosaur expert Brusatte, tells the real story of how dinosaurs rose to dominate the planet. Using the fossil clues that have been gathered using state of the art technology, Brusatte follows these magnificent creatures from their beginnings in the Early Triassic period, through the Jurassic period to their final days in the Cretaceous and the legacy that they left behind.    </p>
<p>                    Along the way, Brusatte introduces us to modern day dinosaur hunters and gives an insight into what it&#8217;s like to be a paleontologist. The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs is full of thrilling accounts of some of his personal discoveries, including primitive human-sized tyrannosaurs, monstrous carnivores even larger than T. rex, and feathered raptor dinosaurs preserved in lava from China.     </p>
<p>                    At a time when Homo sapiens has existed for less than 200,000 years and we are already talking about planetary extinction, The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs is a timely reminder of what humans can learn from the magnificent creatures who ruled the earth before us.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling . . . the best book on the subject written for the general reader since the 1980s.&#8217; &#8211;  The Sunday Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/">The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feathers : The Evolution of a Natural Miracle &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Birds (ornithology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dinosaurs & The Prehistoric World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Birds & Birdwatching]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Feathers are an evolutionary marvel: aerodynamic, insulating, beguiling. They date back more than 100 million years. Yet their story has never been fully told. In Feathers , biologist Thor Hanson details a sweeping natural history, as feathers have been used to fly, protect, attract, and adorn through time and place. Applying the research of paleontologists, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/">Feathers : The Evolution of a Natural Miracle &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Feathers are an evolutionary marvel: aerodynamic, insulating, beguiling. They date back more than 100 million years. Yet their story has never been fully told. In  Feathers , biologist Thor Hanson details a sweeping natural history, as feathers have been used to fly, protect, attract, and adorn through time and place. Applying the research of paleontologists, ornithologists, biologists, engineers, and even art historians, Hanson asks: What are feathers? How did they evolve? What do they mean to us? Engineers call feathers the most efficient insulating material ever discovered, and they are at the root of biology&#8217;s most enduring debate. They silence the flight of owls and keep penguins dry below the ice. They have decorated queens, jesters, and priests. And they have inked documents from the Constitution to the novels of Jane Austen.  Feathers  is a captivating and beautiful exploration of this most enchanting object.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/">Feathers : The Evolution of a Natural Miracle &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
