<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Food &amp; Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/food-society/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/food-society/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Food &amp; Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/food-society/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>This Is Your Mind On Plants : Opium-Caffeine-Mescaline &#8211; Michael Pollan</title>
		<link>/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Botany & Plant Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug-induced States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s a trip &#8211; engrossing, eye-opening, mind altering&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;Fascinating. Pollan is the perfect guide &#8230; curious, careful, open minded&#8217; The Guardian From the international bestselling author of How to Change Your Mind comes a ground-breaking exploration of our relationship with natural drugs Of all the many things humans rely on plants for, surely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/">This Is Your Mind On Plants : Opium-Caffeine-Mescaline &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s a trip &#8211; engrossing, eye-opening, mind altering&#8217; New Statesman</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating. Pollan is the perfect guide &#8230; curious, careful, open minded&#8217; The Guardian</p>
<p>                    From the international bestselling author of How to Change Your Mind comes a ground-breaking exploration of our relationship with natural drugs</p>
<p>                    Of all the many things humans rely on plants for, surely the most curious is our use of them to change consciousness: to stimulate, calm, or completely alter the qualities of our mental experience. In This Is Your Mind On Plants, Michael Pollan explores three very different drugs &#8211; opium, caffeine and mescaline &#8211; and throws the fundamental strangeness of our thinking about them into sharp relief. Exploring and participating in the cultures that have grown up around these drugs, while consuming (or in the case of caffeine, trying not to consume) them, Pollan reckons with the powerful human attraction to psychoactive plants, and the equally powerful taboos. </p>
<p>                    In a unique blend of history, science, memoir and reportage, Pollan shines a fresh light on a subject that is all too often treated reductively. In doing so, he proves that there is much more to say about these plants than simply debating their regulation, for when we take them into our bodies and let them change our minds, we are engaging with nature in one of the most profound ways we can. This ground-breaking and singular book holds up a mirror to our fundamental human needs and aspirations, the operations of our minds and our entanglement with the natural world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/">This Is Your Mind On Plants : Opium-Caffeine-Mescaline &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food    </p>
<p>                    There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; whole grains are healthy, whole grains are a disaster; eat everything in moderation; eat only certain foods&#8212;and on and on. In 100 Million Years of Food, biological anthropologist Stephen Le explains how cuisines of different cultures are a result of centuries of evolution, finely tuned to our biology and surroundings. Today many cultures have strayed from their ancestral diets, relying instead on mass-produced food often made with chemicals that may be contributing to a rise in so-called Western diseases, such as cancer, heart disease, and obesity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible. The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi    </p>
<p>                    Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic meal centred on a large cut of meat with few vegetables. On the &#8216;second plate&#8217;, championed by the farm-to-table movement, meat is free-range and vegetables are locally sourced. It&#8217;s better-tasting, and better for the planet, but the second plate&#8217;s architecture is identical to that of the first. It, too, disrupts ecological balances, causing soil depletion and nutrient loss &#8211; it just isn&#8217;t a sustainable way to farm or eat.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;third plate&#8217; offers a solution: an integrated system of vegetable, cereal and livestock production that is fully supported &#8211; in fact, dictated &#8211; by what we choose to cook for dinner. The Third Plate is where good farming and good food intersect.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Way We Eat Now : Strategies for Eating in a World of Change &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We never snacked like this and we never binged like this. We never had so many superfoods, or so many chips. We were never quite so confused about food, and what it actually is. This is a book about the good, the terrible and the avocado toast. A riveting exploration of the hidden forces behind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/">The Way We Eat Now : Strategies for Eating in a World of Change &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We never snacked like this and we never binged like this. We never had so many superfoods, or so many chips. We were never quite so confused about food, and what it actually is.    </p>
<p>                              This is a book about the good, the terrible and the avocado toast. A riveting exploration of the hidden forces behind what we eat, The Way We Eat Now explains how modern food, in all its complexity, has transformed our lives and our world. To re-establish eating as something that gives us both joy and health, we need to find out where we are right now, how we got here and what it is that we share.    </p>
<p>                              Award-winning food writer Bee Wilson explores everything from meal replacements such as Huel, the disappearing lunch hour, the rise of veganism, the lack of time to cook and prepare food and the rapid increase in food delivery services. And Bee provides her own doable strategies for how we might navigate the many options available to us to have a balanced, happier relationship with the food we eat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/">The Way We Eat Now : Strategies for Eating in a World of Change &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cod &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cod-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aquaculture & Fish-farming: Practice & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sea Life & The Seashore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cod-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Who would ever think that a book on cod would make a compulsive read? And yet this is precisely what Kurlansky has done&#8217; Express on Sunday The Cod. Wars have been fought over it, revolutions have been triggered by it, national diets have been based on it, economies and livelihoods have depended on it. To [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cod-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Cod &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who would ever think that a book on cod would make a compulsive read? And yet this is precisely what Kurlansky has done&#8217; Express on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    The Cod. Wars have been fought over it, revolutions have been triggered by it, national diets have been based on it, economies and livelihoods have depended on it. To the millions it has sustained, it has been a treasure more precious that gold. This book spans 1,000 years and four continents. From the Vikings to Clarence Birdseye, Mark Kurlansky introduces the explorers, merchants, writers, chefs and fisherman, whose lives have been interwoven with this prolific fish. He chronicles the cod wars of the 16th and 20th centuries. He blends in recipes and lore from the Middle Ages to the present. In a story that brings world history and human passions into captivating focus, he shows how the most profitable fish in history is today faced with extinction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cod-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Cod &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What shall we have for dinner? Such a simple question has grown to have a very complicated answer. We can eat almost anything nature has to offer, but deciding what we should eat stirs anxiety. Should we choose the organic apple or the conventional? If organic, local or imported? Wild fish or farmed? Low-carb or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What shall we have for dinner? Such a simple question has grown to have a very complicated answer. We can eat almost anything nature has to offer, but deciding what we should eat stirs anxiety. Should we choose the organic apple or the conventional? If organic, local or imported? Wild fish or farmed? Low-carb or low-cal? As the American culture of fast food and unlimited choice invades the world, Pollan follows his next meal from land to table, tracing the origin of everything consumed and the implications for ourselves and our planet. His astonishing findings will shock all who care about what they put on their plate.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agronomy & Crop Production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Husbandry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animals & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made the most courageous decision of her life: a commitment to change things.    </p>
<p>                     Driven by impulsive will and searing passion, Sonia left behind everything she knew and loved to search the planet for solutions to benefit animals, human health, and the environment. Over the course of living with farmers, hitchhiking with strangers, and risking her life, she developed surprising insights and solutions-both about the food industry and herself.    </p>
<p>                     Lively and heartfelt, Sonia takes readers on an unforgettable adventure from top-secret egg warehouses in Canada to dairy feedlots in the United States, from farm offices in Mexico to lush pastures in Belize, from flocks of village chickens in Indonesia to factory farms in Malaysia.    </p>
<p>                     Revelatory in scope, Project Animal Farm illuminates a hidden world that plays a part in all of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking For/with Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking With Meat & Game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fortnum &#038; Mason Food Book of the Year 2016 We are not born knowing what to eat; we each have to figure it out for ourselves. From childhood onwards, we learn how big a portion is and how sweet is too sweet. The way we learn to eat holds the key to why food has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/">First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fortnum &#038; Mason Food Book of the Year 2016    </p>
<p>                              We are not born knowing what to eat; we each have to figure it out for ourselves. From childhood onwards, we learn how big a portion is and how sweet is too sweet. The way we learn to eat holds the key to why food has gone so disastrously wrong for so many people. But how does this happen? And can we ever change our food habits for the better?    </p>
<p>                              An exploration of the extraordinary and surprising origins of our taste and eating habits, in First Bite award-winning food writer Bee Wilson explains how we can change our palates to lead healthier, happier lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/">First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lesser Beasts : A Snout-to-Tail History of the Humble Pig &#8211; Mark Essig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Husbandry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Mammals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlike other barnyard animals, which pull plows, give eggs or milk, or grow wool, a pig produces only one thing: meat. Incredibly efficient at converting almost any organic matter into nourishing, delectable protein, swine are nothing short of a gastronomic godsend,yet their flesh is banned in many cultures, and the animals themselves are maligned as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/">Lesser Beasts : A Snout-to-Tail History of the Humble Pig &#8211; Mark Essig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlike other barnyard animals, which pull plows, give eggs or milk, or grow wool, a pig produces only one thing: meat. Incredibly efficient at converting almost any organic matter into nourishing, delectable protein, swine are nothing short of a gastronomic godsend,yet their flesh is banned in many cultures, and the animals themselves are maligned as filthy, lazy brutes.As historian Mark Essig reveals in  Lesser Beasts , swine have such a bad reputation for precisely the same reasons they are so valuable as a source of food: they are intelligent, self-sufficient, and omnivorous. What&#8217;s more, he argues, we ignore our historic partnership with these astonishing animals at our peril. Tracing the interplay of pig biology and human culture from Neolithic villages 10,000 years ago to modern industrial farms, Essig blends culinary and natural history to demonstrate the vast importance of the pig and the tragedy of its modern treatment at the hands of humans. Pork, Essig explains, has long been a staple of the human diet, prized in societies from Ancient Rome to dynastic China to the contemporary American South. Yet pigs&#8217; ability to track down and eat a wide range of substances (some of them distinctly unpalatable to humans) and convert them into edible meat has also led people throughout history to demonize the entire species as craven and unclean. Today&#8217;s unconscionable system of factory farming, Essig explains, is only the latest instance of humans taking pigs for granted, and the most recent evidence of how both pigs and people suffer when our symbiotic relationship falls out of balance.An expansive, illuminating history of one of our most vital yet unsung food animals,  Lesser Beasts  turns a spotlight on the humble creature that, perhaps more than any other, has been a mainstay of civilization since its very beginnings,whether we like it or not.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/">Lesser Beasts : A Snout-to-Tail History of the Humble Pig &#8211; Mark Essig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Plant Ecology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Comfortably Unaware, Dr. Richard Oppenlander tackles the crucial issue of global depletion as it relates to food choice. We should all be committed, he tells us, to understanding the reality and consequences of our diet, the footprint it makes on our environment, and seek food products that are in the best interest of all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/">Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Comfortably Unaware, Dr. Richard Oppenlander tackles the crucial issue of global depletion as it relates to food choice. We should all be committed, he tells us, to understanding the reality and consequences of our diet, the footprint it makes on our environment, and seek food products that are in the best interest of all living things. His forthright information and stark mental images are often disturbing-and that&#8217;s how it should be. As the guardians of Planet Earth, we need to be shaken out of our complacency, to stop being comfortably unaware, and to understand the measures we must take to ensure the health and well-being of our planet-and of ourselves. Oppenlander</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/">Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Meat Racket : The Secret Takeover of America&#8217;s Food Business &#8211; Christopher Leonard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An investigative journalist takes you inside the corporate meat industry&#8211;a shocking, in-depth report every American should read. How much do you know about the meat on your dinner plate? Journalist Christopher Leonard spent more than a decade covering the country&#8217;s biggest meat companies, including four years as the national agribusiness reporter for the Associated Press. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/">The Meat Racket : The Secret Takeover of America&#8217;s Food Business &#8211; Christopher Leonard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An investigative journalist takes you inside the corporate meat industry&#8211;a shocking, in-depth report every American should read.     </p>
<p>                    How much do you know about the meat on your dinner plate? Journalist Christopher Leonard spent more than a decade covering the country&#8217;s biggest meat companies, including four years as the national agribusiness reporter for the Associated Press. Now he delivers the first comprehensive look inside the industrial meat system, exposing how a handful of companies executed an audacious corporate takeover of the nation&#8217;s meat supply.     </p>
<p>                    Leonard&#8217;s revealing account shines a light on the inner workings of Tyson Foods, a pioneer of the industrial system that dominates the market. You&#8217;ll learn how the food industry got to where it is today, and how companies like Tyson have escaped the scrutiny they deserve. You&#8217;ll discover how these companies are able to raise meat prices for consumers while pushing down the price they pay to farmers. And you&#8217;ll even see how big business and politics have derailed efforts to change the system, from a years-long legal fight in Iowa to the Obama administration&#8217;s recent failed attempt to pass reforms.     </p>
<p>                    Important, timely, and explosive, The Meat Racket is an unvarnished portrait of the food industry that now dominates America&#8217;s heartland.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/">The Meat Racket : The Secret Takeover of America&#8217;s Food Business &#8211; Christopher Leonard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agricultural Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainable Agriculture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever? At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world. She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever?    </p>
<p>                    At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world.    </p>
<p>                    She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, robot weedkillers, lab-grown meat, 3D-printed meals, water networks run by supercomputers, cloud seeding and sensors that monitor the microclimate of individual plants. She meets the creative and controversial minds changing the face of modern food production, and tackles fears over genetic modification with hard facts.    </p>
<p>                    The Fate of Food is a fascinating look at the threats and opportunities that lie ahead as we struggle for food security.    </p>
<p>                    Faced with a perilous future, it gives us reason to hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author). We are in the grip of a food [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author).<br />
                       We are in the grip of a food crisis. Obesity has become a leading cause of preventable death, after only smoking. For nearly half a century we&#8217;ve been trying to pin the blame somewhere, fat, carbs, sugar, wheat, high-fructose corn syrup. But that search has been in vain, because the food problem that&#8217;s killing us is not a nutrient problem. It&#8217;s a behavioural problem, and it&#8217;s caused by the changing flavour of the food we eat.<br />
                       Ever since the 1940s, with the rise of industrialized food production, we have been gradually leeching the taste out of what we grow. Simultaneously, we have taken great leaps forward in technology, creating a flavour industry, worth billions annually; in an attempt to put back the tastes we&#8217;ve engineered out of our food. The result is a cuisine that increasingly resembles the paragon of flavour manipulation: Doritos. As food becomes increasingly bland, we dress it up with calories and flavour chemicals to make it delicious again. We have rewired our palates and our brains, and the results are making us sick and killing us.<br />
                       With in-depth historical and scientific research, The Dorito Effect casts the food crisis in a fascinating new light, weaving an enthralling tale of how we got to this point and where we are headed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should We Eat Meat? : Evolution and Consequences of Modern Carnivory &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meat eating is often a contentious subject, whether considering the technical, ethical, environmental, political, or health-related aspects of production and consumption. This book is a wide-ranging and interdisciplinary examination and critique of meat consumption by humans, throughout their evolution and around the world. Setting the scene with a chapter on meat s role in human [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Should We Eat Meat? : Evolution and Consequences of Modern Carnivory &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meat eating is often a contentious subject, whether considering the technical, ethical, environmental, political, or health-related aspects of production and consumption. This book is a wide-ranging and interdisciplinary examination and critique of meat consumption by humans, throughout their evolution and around the world. Setting the scene with a chapter on meat s role in human evolution and its growing influence during the development of agricultural practices, the book goes on to examine modern production systems, their efficiencies, outputs, and impacts. The major global trends of meat consumption are described in order to find out what part its consumption plays in changing modern diets in countries around the world. The heart of the book addresses the consequences of the &#8220;massive carnivory&#8221; of western diets, looking at the inefficiencies of production and at the huge impacts on land, water, and the atmosphere. Health impacts are also covered, both positive and negative.<br />
                    In conclusion, the author looks forward at his vision of rational meat eating , where environmental and health impacts are reduced, animals are treated more humanely, and alternative sources of protein make a higher contribution. Should We Eat Meat? is not an ideological tract for or against carnivorousness but rather a careful evaluation of meat&#8217;s roles in human diets and the environmental and health consequences of its production and consumption. It will be of interest to a wide readership including professionals and academics in food and agricultural production, human health and nutrition, environmental science, and regulatory and policy making bodies around the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Should We Eat Meat? : Evolution and Consequences of Modern Carnivory &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice we receive from public health bodies is muddled, out of date, and frequently contradictory, and in many quarters still promotes the unproven hypothesis that fats are the greatest evil.    </p>
<p>                    With expert science and compelling storytelling, Gary Taubes investigates the history of nutritional science which, shaped by a handful of charismatic and misguided individuals, has for a hundred years denied the impact of sugar on our health. He exposes the powerful influence of the food industry which has lobbied for sugar&#8217;s ubiquity &#8211; the Sugar Association even today promoting &#8216;sugar&#8217;s goodness&#8217; &#8211;  and the extent that the industry has corrupted essential scientific research. He delves into the science of sugar, exposes conventional thinking that sugar is &#8217;empty calories&#8217; as a myth, and finds that its addictive pleasures are resulting in worldwide consumption as never experienced before, to devastating effect.     </p>
<p>                    The Case Against Sugar is a revelatory read, which will fundamentally change the way we eat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Pursuit of Garlic : An Intimate Look at the Divinely Odorous Bulb &#8211; Liz Primeau (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-pursuit-of-garlic-an-intimate-look-at-the-divinely-odorous-bulb-liz-primeau-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening: Growing Fruit & Vegetables]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening: Plants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Homoeopathy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-pursuit-of-garlic-an-intimate-look-at-the-divinely-odorous-bulb-liz-primeau-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Garlic has been used throughout history as a nourishing food and a magical medicine, healing everything from toothaches to dysentery. For much of this past century many dismissed its medicinal qualities as folk remedies more efficiently replaced by modern drugs &#8212; but today garlic is undergoing a renaissance. Not only are more people cooking with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-garlic-an-intimate-look-at-the-divinely-odorous-bulb-liz-primeau-abridged/">In Pursuit of Garlic : An Intimate Look at the Divinely Odorous Bulb &#8211; Liz Primeau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Garlic has been used throughout history as a nourishing food and a magical medicine, healing everything from toothaches to dysentery. For much of this past century many dismissed its medicinal qualities as folk remedies more efficiently replaced by modern drugs &#8212; but today garlic is undergoing a renaissance. Not only are more people cooking with garlic, they are also growing it in their backyards. And scientists are studying garlic&#8217;s antibiotic, antifungal, and antiparasitic qualities, as well as its potential for cancer treatment. In Pursuit of Garlic tells Liz Primeau&#8217;s story of her love affair with the divinely odorous bulb and leads us on a tour of garlic&#8217;s role in history, art, medicine, and science. Primeau shares her favorite garlic-centered recipes, visits garlic fairs, discusses the many varieties of garlic &#8212; from Russian Red to German Brown to Kettle River Giant &#8212; and gives invaluable tips for growing your own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-garlic-an-intimate-look-at-the-divinely-odorous-bulb-liz-primeau-abridged/">In Pursuit of Garlic : An Intimate Look at the Divinely Odorous Bulb &#8211; Liz Primeau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
