<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Taoism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/taoism/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/taoism/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Taoism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/taoism/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Become What You Are : Expanded Edition &#8211; Alan W. Watts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/become-what-you-are-expanded-edition-alan-w-watts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Non-Christian Religions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taoism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/become-what-you-are-expanded-edition-alan-w-watts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The prominent Zen Buddhist scholar and author of The Wisdom of Insecurity draws on Taoism, Christianity, and other world religions to explore the dilemma of seeking your true self In this collection of writings, including nine new chapters never before available in book form, Alan Watts displays the intelligence, playfulness of thought, and simplicity of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/become-what-you-are-expanded-edition-alan-w-watts-abridged/">Become What You Are : Expanded Edition &#8211; Alan W. Watts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The prominent Zen Buddhist scholar and author of The Wisdom of Insecurity draws on Taoism, Christianity, and other world religions to explore the dilemma of seeking your true self     </p>
<p>                    In this collection of writings, including nine new chapters never before available in book form, Alan Watts displays the intelligence, playfulness of thought, and simplicity of language that has made him so perennially popular as an interpreter of Eastern thought for Westerners. He draws on a variety of religious traditions, and covers topics such as the challenge of seeing one&#8217;s life &#8220;just as it is,&#8221; the Taoist approach to harmonious living, the limits of language in the face of ineffable spiritual truth, and the psychological symbolism of Christian thought.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/become-what-you-are-expanded-edition-alan-w-watts-abridged/">Become What You Are : Expanded Edition &#8211; Alan W. Watts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Change Your Thoughts &#8211; Change Your Life : Living the Wisdom of the Tao &#8211; Dr. Wayne W. Dyer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/change-your-thoughts-change-your-life-living-the-wisdom-of-the-tao-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chakras, Auras & Spiritual Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taoism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/change-your-thoughts-change-your-life-living-the-wisdom-of-the-tao-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Five hundred years before the birth of Jesus, a God-realized being named Lao-tzu in ancient China dictated 81 verses, which are regarded by many as the ultimate commentary on the nature of our existence. The classic text of these 81 verses, called the Tao Te Ching or the Great Way, offers advice and guidance that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/change-your-thoughts-change-your-life-living-the-wisdom-of-the-tao-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/">Change Your Thoughts &#8211; Change Your Life : Living the Wisdom of the Tao &#8211; Dr. Wayne W. Dyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Five hundred years before the birth of Jesus, a God-realized being named Lao-tzu in ancient China dictated 81 verses, which are regarded by many as the ultimate commentary on the nature of our existence. The classic text of these 81 verses, called the Tao Te Ching or the Great Way, offers advice and guidance that is balanced, moral, spiritual, and always concerned with working for the good. In this book, Dr. Wayne W. Dyer has reviewed hundreds of translations of the Tao Te Ching and has written 81 distinct essays on how to apply the ancient wisdom of Lao-tzu to today&#8217;s modern world. This work contains the entire 81 verses of the Tao, compiled from Wayne&#8217;s researching of 10 of the most well-respected translations of text that have survived for more than 25 centuries. Each chapter is designed for actually living the Tao or the Great Way today. Some of the chapter titles are &#8216;Living with Flexibility,&#8217; &#8216;Living Without Enemies,&#8217; and &#8216;Living by Letting Go.&#8217; Each of the 81 brief chapters focuses on living the Tao and concludes with a section called &#8216;Doing the Tao Now.&#8217;<br />
                    Wayne spent one entire year reading, researching, and meditating on Lao-tzu&#8217;s messages, practicing them each day and ultimately writing down these essays as he felt Lao-tzu wanted you to know them. This is a work to be read slowly, one essay a day. As Wayne says, &#8216;This is a book that will forever change the way you look at your life, and the result will be that you&#8217;ll live in a new world aligned with nature. Writing this book changed me forever, too. I now live in accord with the natural world and feel the greatest sense of peace I&#8217;ve ever experienced. I&#8217;m so proud to present this interpretation of the Tao Te Ching, and offer the same opportunity for change that it has brought me.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/change-your-thoughts-change-your-life-living-the-wisdom-of-the-tao-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/">Change Your Thoughts &#8211; Change Your Life : Living the Wisdom of the Tao &#8211; Dr. Wayne W. Dyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
