<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Advertising Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/advertising/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/advertising/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Advertising Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/advertising/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>This I Know : Marketing Lessons from Under the Influence &#8211; Terry O&#8217;Reilly</title>
		<link>/this-i-know-marketing-lessons-from-under-the-influence-terry-oreilly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-i-know-marketing-lessons-from-under-the-influence-terry-oreilly/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Terry O&#8217;Reilly, host of the popular radio show Under the Influence, provides the best stories about smart marketing for small business. In Terry&#8217;s gifted presentation, This I Know is more than applied business techniques. It offers a unique view of contemporary life through the lens of advertising. Skillfully revealing the machinations behind the marketing curtains, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-i-know-marketing-lessons-from-under-the-influence-terry-oreilly/">This I Know : Marketing Lessons from Under the Influence &#8211; Terry O&#8217;Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Terry O&#8217;Reilly, host of the popular radio show Under the Influence, provides the best stories about smart marketing for small business. In Terry&#8217;s gifted presentation, This I Know is more than applied business techniques. It offers a unique view of contemporary life through the lens of advertising. Skillfully revealing the machinations behind the marketing curtains, O&#8217;Reilly explains how small business can harness the tricks of the trade that the biggest corporations use to create their own marketing buzz.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-i-know-marketing-lessons-from-under-the-influence-terry-oreilly/">This I Know : Marketing Lessons from Under the Influence &#8211; Terry O&#8217;Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising. For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising.     </p>
<p>                     For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup founder, a small business owner, or part of a large corporation.     </p>
<p>                     No matter what your product or service, this book will help you reframe how it&#8217;s presented to the world, in order to meaningfully connect with people who want it. Seth employs his signature blend of insight, observation, and memorable examples to teach you:    </p>
<p>                     * How to build trust and permission with your target market.<br />
                     * The art of positioning&#8211;deciding not only who it&#8217;s for, but who it&#8217;s not for.<br />
                     * Why the best way to achieve your goals is to help others become who they want to be.<br />
                     * Why the old approaches to advertising and branding no longer work.<br />
                     * The surprising role of tension in any decision to buy (or not).<br />
                     * How marketing is at its core about the stories we tell ourselves about our social status.    </p>
<p>                     You can do work that matters for people who care. This book shows you the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This Is Marketing is a very accessible way into Godin&#8217;s thinking&#8230;. Godin writes in pacy, jargon-free prose and this book is interesting and useful for anyone who wants an insight into how, and why, we buy things or change our habits in any way.&#8221; &#8211; The Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s Purple Cow, a true business classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frenemies : The Epic Disruption of the Ad Business (and Everything Else) &#8211; Ken Auletta (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/frenemies-the-epic-disruption-of-the-ad-business-and-everything-else-ken-auletta-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/frenemies-the-epic-disruption-of-the-ad-business-and-everything-else-ken-auletta-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An intimate and profound reckoning with the changes buffeting the $2 trillion global advertising and marketing business from the perspective of its most powerful players, by the bestselling author of Googled Advertising and marketing touches on every corner of our lives, and the industry is the invisible fuel powering almost all media. Complain about it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/frenemies-the-epic-disruption-of-the-ad-business-and-everything-else-ken-auletta-abridged/">Frenemies : The Epic Disruption of the Ad Business (and Everything Else) &#8211; Ken Auletta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An intimate and profound reckoning with the changes buffeting the $2 trillion global advertising and marketing business from the perspective of its most powerful players, by the bestselling author of Googled    </p>
<p>                    Advertising and marketing touches on every corner of our lives, and the industry is the invisible fuel powering almost all media. Complain about it though we might, without it the world would be a darker place. But of all the industries wracked by change in the digital age, few have been turned on their heads as dramatically as this one. Mad Men are turning into Math Men (and women&#8211;though too few), an instinctual art is transforming into a science, and we are a long way from the days of Don Draper.      </p>
<p>                    Frenemies is Ken Auletta&#8217;s reckoning with an industry under existential assault. He enters the rooms of the ad world&#8217;s most important players, meeting the old guard as well as new powers and power brokers, investigating their perspectives. It&#8217;s essential reading, not simply because of what it reveals about this world, but because of the potential consequences: the survival of media as we know it depends on the money generated by advertising and marketing&#8211;revenue that is in peril in the face of technological changes and the fraying trust between the industry&#8217;s key players.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/frenemies-the-epic-disruption-of-the-ad-business-and-everything-else-ken-auletta-abridged/">Frenemies : The Epic Disruption of the Ad Business (and Everything Else) &#8211; Ken Auletta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Attention is the new commodity. Visual Storytelling is the new currency. Human brain processes visuals 60,000x faster than text.Web posts with visuals drive up to 180% more engagement than those without.Viewers spend 100% more time on web pages with videos. Filled with full-color images and thought-provoking examples from leading companies, The Power of Visual Storytelling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/">The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Attention is the new commodity. Visual Storytelling is the new currency.    </p>
<p>                    Human brain processes visuals 60,000x faster than text.Web posts with visuals drive up to 180% more engagement than those without.Viewers spend 100% more time on web pages with videos.<br />
                    Filled with full-color images and thought-provoking examples from leading companies, The Power of Visual Storytelling explains how to grow your business and strengthen your brand by leveraging photos, videos, infographics, presentations, and other rich media. The book delivers a powerful road map for getting started, while inspiring new levels of creativity within organizations of all types and sizes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book is not only a complete overview of [visual storytelling] but, most importantly, the key to doing it right, a total Right Hook!&#8221;<br />
                    -Gary Vaynerchuk, New York Times bestselling author of Crush It! and Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable guide to understanding how to develop powerful marketing programs using the art of visual storytelling.&#8221;<br />
                    -Guy Kawasaki, author of APE: Author, Publisher, Entrepreneur and former chief evangelist of Apple    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Power of Visual Storytelling is the new marketing bible!&#8221;<br />
                    -Nancy Bhagat, Vice President, Global Marketing Strategy and Campaigns, Intel    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If a picture is worth a thousand words, The Power of Visual Storytelling is worth a million.&#8221;<br />
                    -Scott Monty, Global Digital &#038; Multimedia Communications for Ford Motor Company</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/">The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Truth, Lies, and Advertising : The Art of Account Planning &#8211; Jon Steel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Account planning exists for the sole purpose of creating advertising that truly connects with consumers. While many in the industry are still dissecting consumer behavior, extrapolating demographic trends, developing complex behavioral models, and measuring Pavlovian salivary responses, Steel advocates an approach to consumer research that is based on simplicity, common sense, and creativity&#8211;an approach that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/">Truth, Lies, and Advertising : The Art of Account Planning &#8211; Jon Steel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Account planning exists for the sole purpose of creating advertising that truly connects with consumers. While many in the industry are still dissecting consumer behavior, extrapolating demographic trends, developing complex behavioral models, and measuring Pavlovian salivary responses, Steel advocates an approach to consumer research that is based on simplicity, common sense, and creativity&#8211;an approach that gains access to consumers&#8217; hearts and minds, develops ongoing relationships with them, and, most important, embraces them as partners in the process of developing and advertising. A witty, erudite raconteur and teacher, Steel describes how successful account planners work in partnership with clients, consumer, and agency creatives. He criticizes research practices that, far from creating relationships, drive a wedge between agencies and the people they aim to persuade; he suggests new ways of approaching research to cut through the BS and get people to show their true selves; and he shows how the right research, when translated into a motivating and inspiring brief, can be the catalyst for great creative ideas.<br />
                    He draws upon his own experiences and those of colleagues in the United States and abroad to illustrate those points, and includes examples of some of the most successful campaigns in recent years, including Polaroid, Norwegian Cruise Line, Porsche, Isuzu, &#8220;got milk?&#8221; and others. The message of this book is that well-thought-out account planning results in better, more effective marketing and advertising for both agencies and clients. And also makes an evening in front of the television easier to bear for the population at large.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/">Truth, Lies, and Advertising : The Art of Account Planning &#8211; Jon Steel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Post-Truth Business : How to Rebuild Brand Authenticity in a Distrusting World &#8211; Sean Pillot de Chenecey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FINALIST &#8211; Business Book Awards 2019 &#8211; Embracing Change Category Brands are built on trust, but in a post-truth world they&#8217;re faced with a serious challenge: so much of modern life is defined by mistrust. A shattering of the vital trust connection between brands and consumers, together with the evaporation of authenticity as a core [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/">The Post-Truth Business : How to Rebuild Brand Authenticity in a Distrusting World &#8211; Sean Pillot de Chenecey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FINALIST &#8211; Business Book Awards 2019 &#8211; Embracing Change Category    </p>
<p>                    Brands are built on trust, but in a post-truth world they&#8217;re faced with a serious challenge: so much of modern life is defined by mistrust. A shattering of the vital trust connection between brands and consumers, together with the evaporation of authenticity as a core brand pillar, is causing enormous problems for businesses on a global scale. If a brand isn&#8217;t seen as trustworthy, then when choice is available it will be rejected in favour of one that is.    </p>
<p>                    The Post-Truth Business provides a way forward for any organization wishing to rebuild brand authenticity in a distrustful world. It explains the interconnected problems facing businesses, with important topics including:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; The impact of fake news, disinformation and the weaponizing of lies<br />
                    &#8211; The safeguarding of privacy, alongside privacy as a tradable asset<br />
                    &#8211; Why and how brands must create communication with meaning<br />
                    &#8211; The dangers of inauthentic cultural marketing activities<br />
                    &#8211; Examples of conscious capitalism and brand activism<br />
                    &#8211; Lessons in authenticity from artisans and innovators<br />
                    &#8211; National branding and reputation capital<br />
                    &#8211; Leveraging the power of &#8216;brand trust&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    The Post-Truth Business shows how to strengthen consumer engagement by closing the &#8216;brand credibility gap&#8217;. It&#8217;s packed with examples of inspiring people, brands and international campaigns from the fashion, beauty, outdoor, motor, drinks, finance, media, technology, entertainment and health sectors. Each of them demonstrates a dynamic and positive way forward.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/">The Post-Truth Business : How to Rebuild Brand Authenticity in a Distrusting World &#8211; Sean Pillot de Chenecey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brand Gap, The : Revised Edition &#8211; Marty Neumeier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE BRAND GAP is the first book to present a unified theory of brand-building. Whereas most books on branding are weighted toward either a strategic or creative approach, this book shows how both ways of thinking can unite to produce a &#8220;charismatic brand&#8221;-a brand that customers feel is essential to their lives. In an entertaining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/">Brand Gap, The : Revised Edition &#8211; Marty Neumeier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE BRAND GAP is the first book to present a unified theory of brand-building.  Whereas most books on branding are weighted toward either a strategic or creative approach, this book shows how both ways of thinking can unite to produce a &#8220;charismatic brand&#8221;-a brand that customers feel is essential to their lives. In an entertaining two-hour read you&#8217;ll learn:     </p>
<p>                    * the new definition of brand<br />
                    * the five essential disciplines of brand-building<br />
                    * how branding is changing the dynamics of competition<br />
                    * the three most powerful questions to ask about any brand<br />
                    * why collaboration is the key to brand-building<br />
                    * how design determines a customer&#8217;s experience<br />
                    * how to test brand concepts quickly and cheaply<br />
                    * the importance of managing brands from the inside<br />
                    * 220-word brand glossary     </p>
<p>                    From the back cover:<br />
                    Not since McLuhan&#8217;s THE MEDIUM IS THE MESSAGE has a book compressed so many ideas into so few pages. Using the visual language of the boardroom, Neumeier presents the first unified theory of branding-a set of five disciplines to help companies bridge the gap between brand strategy and customer experience. Those with a grasp of branding will be inspired by the new perspectives they find here, and those who would like to understand it better will suddenly &#8220;get it.&#8221; This deceptively simple book offers everyone in the company access to &#8220;the most powerful business tool since the spreadsheet.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/">Brand Gap, The : Revised Edition &#8211; Marty Neumeier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The indispensable classic on marketing by the bestselling author of Tribes and Purple Cow. Legendary business writer Seth Godin has three essential questions for every marketer: &#8220;What&#8217;s your story?&#8221; &#8220;Will the people who need to hear this story believe it?&#8221; &#8220;Is it true?&#8221; All marketers tell stories. And if they do it right, we believe [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/">All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The indispensable classic on marketing by the bestselling author of Tribes and Purple Cow.    </p>
<p>                     Legendary business writer Seth Godin has three essential questions for every marketer:     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;What&#8217;s your story?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Will the people who need to hear this story believe it?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Is it true?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     All marketers tell stories. And if they do it right, we believe them. We believe that wine tastes better in a $20 glass than a $1 glass. We believe that an $80,000 Porsche is vastly superior to a $36,000 Volkswagen that&#8217;s virtually the same car. We believe that $225 sneakers make our feet feel better&#8211;and look cooler&#8211;than a $25 brand. And believing it makes it true.     </p>
<p>                     As Seth Godin has taught hundreds of thousands of marketers and students around the world, great marketers don&#8217;t talk about features or even benefits. Instead, they tell a story&#8211;a story we want to believe, whether it&#8217;s factual or not. In a world where most people have an infinite number of choices and no time to make them, every organization is a marketer, and all marketing is about telling stories.     </p>
<p>                     Marketers succeed when they tell us a story that fits our worldview, a story that we intuitively embrace and then share with our friends. Think of the Dyson vacuum cleaner, or Fiji water, or the iPod.     </p>
<p>                     But beware: If your stories are inauthentic, you cross the line from fib to fraud. Marketers fail when they are selfish and scurrilous, when they abuse the tools of their trade and make the world worse. That&#8217;s a lesson learned the hard way by telemarketers, cigarette companies, and sleazy politicians.     </p>
<p>                     But for the rest of us, it&#8217;s time to embrace the power of the story. As Godin writes, &#8220;Stories make it easier to understand the world. Stories are the only way we know to spread an idea. Marketers didn&#8217;t invent storytelling. They just perfected it.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/">All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that philosophy and illustrates how successful businesses have redefined themselves in the new customer universe.    </p>
<p>                    Personality Not Included is a powerhouse resource packed with bold new insights that show you how to shed the lifeless armor of your business and rediscover the soul of your brand. Sharing stories from the ethos of the world&#8217;s weirdest city, to how Manga has taken the comic book industry by storm, to showcasing brands like Intel, Boeing, ING, and Dyson, Bhargava shows you why personality matters from the inside out.    </p>
<p>                    In Part One, you&#8217;ll be introduced to the key components to building a personality and learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    Recognize the greatest myth that most marketers blindly follow, and how to get past itUse the &#8220;UAT Filter&#8221; to understand the personality of your organization and products in order to develop a communication strategy that drives your marketingCreate your company&#8217;s &#8220;marketing backstory&#8221; using techniques pioneered by Hollywood screenwritersHarness the influence of &#8220;accidental spokespeople&#8221; and use it to your advantageNavigate the roadblocks of using personality that come from bosses, peers, investors, and lawyers, without getting fired or flamedPinpoint and capitalize on the moments where personality can make a difference<br />
                    Part Two is packed with guides, tools, and techniques to help you flawlessly implement your plan. It features practical, step-by-step lessons that help you effectively move from theory to action, and includes a valuable collection of guides, checklists, question forms, printable resources, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Don&#8217;t be another faceless company-learn the new rules for succeeding in the social media era with Personality Not Included.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buyology : Truth and Lies About Why We Buy &#8211; Martin Lindstrom, Foreword by Paco Underhill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Purchasing & Supply Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; &#8220;A fascinating look at how consumers perceive logos, ads, commercials, brands, and products.&#8221;&#8211;Time How much do we know about why we buy? What truly influences our decisions in today&#8217;s message-cluttered world? In Buyology, Martin Lindstrom presents the astonishing findings from his groundbreaking three-year, seven-million-dollar neuromarketing study&#8211;a cutting-edge experiment that peered [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/">Buyology : Truth and Lies About Why We Buy &#8211; Martin Lindstrom, Foreword by Paco Underhill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; &#8220;A fascinating look at how consumers perceive logos, ads, commercials, brands, and products.&#8221;&#8211;Time     </p>
<p>                    How much do we know about why we buy? What truly influences our decisions in today&#8217;s message-cluttered world? In Buyology, Martin Lindstrom presents the astonishing findings from his groundbreaking three-year, seven-million-dollar neuromarketing study&#8211;a cutting-edge experiment that peered inside the brains of 2,000 volunteers from all around the world as they encountered various ads, logos, commercials, brands, and products. His startling results shatter much of what we have long believed about what captures our interest&#8211;and drives us to buy. Among the questions he explores:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Does sex actually sell?<br />
                    &#8211; Does subliminal advertising still surround us?<br />
                    &#8211; Can &#8220;cool&#8221; brands trigger our mating instincts?<br />
                    &#8211; Can our other senses&#8211;smell, touch, and sound&#8211;be aroused when we see a product?     </p>
<p>                    Buyology is a fascinating and shocking journey into the mind of today&#8217;s consumer that will captivate anyone who&#8217;s been seduced&#8211;or turned off&#8211;by marketers&#8217; relentless attempts to win our loyalty, our money, and our minds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/">Buyology : Truth and Lies About Why We Buy &#8211; Martin Lindstrom, Foreword by Paco Underhill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yes! : 50 Scientifically Proven Ways to Be Persuasive &#8211; Noah J Goldstein, Steve J Martin, Robert Cialdini (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/yes-50-scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-persuasive-noah-j-goldstein-steve-j-martin-robert-cialdini-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/yes-50-scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-persuasive-noah-j-goldstein-steve-j-martin-robert-cialdini-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how small changes can make a big difference in your powers of persuasion with this New York Times bestselling introduction to fifty scientifically proven techniques for increasing your persuasive powers in business and life. Every day we face the challenge of persuading others to do what we want. But what makes people say yes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/yes-50-scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-persuasive-noah-j-goldstein-steve-j-martin-robert-cialdini-abridged/">Yes! : 50 Scientifically Proven Ways to Be Persuasive &#8211; Noah J Goldstein, Steve J Martin, Robert Cialdini (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how small changes can make a big difference in your powers of persuasion with this New York Times bestselling introduction to fifty scientifically proven techniques for increasing your persuasive powers in business and life.     </p>
<p>                    Every day we face the challenge of persuading others to do what we want. But what makes people say yes to our requests? Persuasion is not only an art, it is also a science, and researchers who study it have uncovered a series of hidden rules for moving people in your direction. Based on more than sixty years of research into the psychology of persuasion, Yes! reveals fifty simple but remarkably effective strategies that will make you much more persuasive at work and in your personal life, too.     </p>
<p>                    Cowritten by the world&#8217;s most quoted expert on influence, Professor Robert Cialdini, Yes! presents dozens of surprising discoveries from the science of persuasion in short, enjoyable, and insightful chapters that you can apply immediately to become a more effective persuader.     </p>
<p>                    Often counterintuitive, the findings presented in Yes! will steer you away from common pitfalls while empowering you with little known but proven wisdom.     </p>
<p>                    Whether you are in advertising, marketing, management, on sales, or just curious about how to be more influential in everyday life, Yes! shows how making small, scientifically proven changes to your approach can have a dramatic effect on your persuasive powers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/yes-50-scientifically-proven-ways-to-be-persuasive-noah-j-goldstein-steve-j-martin-robert-cialdini-abridged/">Yes! : 50 Scientifically Proven Ways to Be Persuasive &#8211; Noah J Goldstein, Steve J Martin, Robert Cialdini (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paid Attention : Innovative Advertising for a Digital World &#8211; Faris Yakob (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/paid-attention-innovative-advertising-for-a-digital-world-faris-yakob-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/paid-attention-innovative-advertising-for-a-digital-world-faris-yakob-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The advertising attention marketplace is a confusing and vast playing field where the rules have changed drastically over the last decade. Make yourself heard and win the attention of your target audience with the new edition of this ultimate guide. Paid Attention delivers new and innovative insights into advertising ideas: what they are, why they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/paid-attention-innovative-advertising-for-a-digital-world-faris-yakob-abridged/">Paid Attention : Innovative Advertising for a Digital World &#8211; Faris Yakob (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The advertising attention marketplace is a confusing and vast playing field where the rules have changed drastically over the last decade. Make yourself heard and win the attention of your target audience with the new edition of this ultimate guide.    </p>
<p>                    Paid Attention delivers new and innovative insights into advertising ideas: what they are, why they are evolving and how to use them in day to day strategy to ensure commercial stability within a changing digital landscape. Packed with real-world examples of advertising campaigns such as Google, Sony and Old Spice, it provides a robust model for influencing human behaviour and toolkits that offer best practice on brand behaviour and effective communication.    </p>
<p>                    This second edition includes two new chapters exploring the latest evidence about attention spans and trends in online advertising, as well as new case studies on compelling brand ideas. In a world where being a consumer is confusing, learn to take control of the situation and make yourself heard in today&#8217;s crowded attention marketplace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/paid-attention-innovative-advertising-for-a-digital-world-faris-yakob-abridged/">Paid Attention : Innovative Advertising for a Digital World &#8211; Faris Yakob (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company     </p>
<p>                    What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and delivering value consistently, day in and day out.    </p>
<p>                    In Top of Mind, the cofounder of a leading content marketing company shows you how to create business opportunities by occupying the space at the top of your audience&#8217;s minds-and keeping it there. This groundbreaking book explains how consumer needs and expectations have changed and what this shift means for readers interested in building a brand-whether you&#8217;re a leader in marketing engaging potential customers, a VP of sales bringing in new business, or a director of HR who&#8217;s recruiting the best talent in the industry. It provides effective ways to establish trust and foster connections; maintain transparency and consistency; identify and clearly communicate the &#8220;why&#8221; behind the message; and create processes to make that message part of a brand&#8217;s DNA.     </p>
<p>                    Maintaining a prominent spot in your audience&#8217;s minds will increase the likelihood that the moment they need to make a choice, you&#8217;ll be the first one they call.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hug Your Customers : The Proven Way to Personalize Sales and Achieve Astounding Results &#8211; Jack Mitchell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hug-your-customers-the-proven-way-to-personalize-sales-and-achieve-astounding-results-jack-mitchell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hug-your-customers-the-proven-way-to-personalize-sales-and-achieve-astounding-results-jack-mitchell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Revised and updated for the first time since original publication! Here is the 200,000-copy staple, praised by Warren Buffett as a gem &#8230; I wish everyone at Berkshire would follow [Jack Mitchell&#8217;s] advice&#8211;we would own the world. If you want to put your arms around your business and bottom line, you&#8217;ll want all the updated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-customers-the-proven-way-to-personalize-sales-and-achieve-astounding-results-jack-mitchell-abridged/">Hug Your Customers : The Proven Way to Personalize Sales and Achieve Astounding Results &#8211; Jack Mitchell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Revised and updated for the first time since original publication!     </p>
<p>                     Here is the 200,000-copy staple, praised by Warren Buffett as a gem &#8230; I wish everyone at Berkshire would follow [Jack Mitchell&#8217;s] advice&#8211;we would own the world.     </p>
<p>                     If you want to put your arms around your business and bottom line, you&#8217;ll want all the updated information and practices found in the landmark business bestseller, Hug Your Customers. The only way to stay in business is to have customers; the only way to increase your profit is to attract more customer visits by providing exceptional customer service. It&#8217;s that simple says Jack Mitchell. Hug Your Customers shares the hands-on practical philosophy that has allowed Mitchell and his Family of Stores to thrive and excel in today&#8217;s challenging retail marketplace. Filled with accessible advice, personal case studies and tips any businessperson can use, Hug Your Customers is an energizing blueprint for customer and employee retention, increased per capita spending, and groundbreaking success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-customers-the-proven-way-to-personalize-sales-and-achieve-astounding-results-jack-mitchell-abridged/">Hug Your Customers : The Proven Way to Personalize Sales and Achieve Astounding Results &#8211; Jack Mitchell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>80/20 Internet Lead Generation : How a Few Simple, Profitable Strategies Can Lead to Marketplace Domination &#8211; Scott a Dennison (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/80-20-internet-lead-generation-how-a-few-simple-profitable-strategies-can-lead-to-marketplace-domination-scott-a-dennison-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/80-20-internet-lead-generation-how-a-few-simple-profitable-strategies-can-lead-to-marketplace-domination-scott-a-dennison-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>According to author and marketing expert Scott Dennison, business leaders from coast-to-coast told him the most important result they wanted from their advertising and marketing was to make the phone ring more often &#8211; to get calls from prospects interested in the products and services they&#8217;re selling. This book was the result. It will provide [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/80-20-internet-lead-generation-how-a-few-simple-profitable-strategies-can-lead-to-marketplace-domination-scott-a-dennison-abridged/">80/20 Internet Lead Generation : How a Few Simple, Profitable Strategies Can Lead to Marketplace Domination &#8211; Scott a Dennison (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to author and marketing expert Scott Dennison, business leaders from coast-to-coast told him the most important result they wanted from their advertising and marketing was to make the phone ring more often &#8211; to get calls from prospects interested in the products and services they&#8217;re selling. This book was the result. It will provide you with a simple, step-by-step process to follow, so you can build the pieces you&#8217;ll need to create an effective online lead generation campaign in your business and make that phone ring: &#8211; Clarity about exactly who your ideal client is &#8211; Your business USP (Unique Selling Proposition) &#8211; A process for effective keyword generation/targeting &#8211; Professional landing pages for PPC lead generation &#8211; A well-designed Website, built for lead conversion/generation &#8211; Great content, properly optimized for search (one part of SEO) &#8211; Professional back-link campaigns (the other part of SEO) With a foreword written by Perry Marshall, best-selling author of &#8220;80/20 Sales and Marketing: The Definitive Guide to Working Less and Making More,&#8221; Scott A. Dennison&#8217;s 80/20 Internet Lead Generation guides the reader to successful lead generation, following the strategic approach championed by his mentor as it specifically applies to generating more business leads online.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/80-20-internet-lead-generation-how-a-few-simple-profitable-strategies-can-lead-to-marketplace-domination-scott-a-dennison-abridged/">80/20 Internet Lead Generation : How a Few Simple, Profitable Strategies Can Lead to Marketplace Domination &#8211; Scott a Dennison (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Referral Engine &#8211; John Jantsch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The small business guru behind Duct Tape Marketing shares his most valuable lesson: how to get your customers to do your best marketing for you. The power of glitzy advertising and elaborate marketing campaigns is on the wane; word- of-mouth referrals are what drive business today. People trust the recommendation of a friend, family member, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/">The Referral Engine &#8211; John Jantsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The small business guru behind Duct Tape Marketing shares his most valuable lesson: how to get your customers to do your best marketing for you.   The power of glitzy advertising and elaborate marketing campaigns is on the wane; word- of-mouth referrals are what drive business today. People trust the recommendation of a friend, family member, colleague, or even stranger with similar tastes over anything thrust at them by a faceless company.  Most business owners believe that whether customers refer them is entirely out of their hands. But science shows that people can&#8217;t help recommending products and services to their friends-it&#8217;s an instinct wired deep in the brain. And smart businesses can tap into that hardwired desire.  Marketing expert John Jantsch offers practical techniques for harnessing the power of referrals to ensure a steady flow of new customers. Keep those customers happy, and they will refer your business to even more customers. Some of Jantsch&#8217;s strategies include:  -Talk with your customers, not at them. Thanks to social networking sites, companies of any size have the opportunity to engage with their customers on their home turf as never before-but the key is listening.  -The sales team is the most important part of your marketing team. Salespeople are the company&#8217;s main link to customers, who are the main source of referrals. Getting them on board with your referral strategy is critical.  -Educate your customers. Referrals are only helpful if they&#8217;re given to the right people. Educate your customers about whom they should be talking to.  The secret to generating referrals lies in understanding the Customer Referral Cycle-the way customers refer others to your company who, in turn, generate even more referrals. Businesses can ensure a healthy referral cycle by moving customers and prospects along the path of Know, Like, Trust, Try, Buy, Repeat, and Refer. If everyone in an organization keeps this sequence in mind, Jantsch argues, your business will generate referrals like a well-oiled machine.  This practical, smart, and original guide is essential reading for any company looking to grow without a fat marketing budget.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/">The Referral Engine &#8211; John Jantsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pop! : Create the Perfect Pitch, Title, and Tagline for Anything &#8211; Sam Horn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pop-create-the-perfect-pitch-title-and-tagline-for-anything-sam-horn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pop-create-the-perfect-pitch-title-and-tagline-for-anything-sam-horn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why do some ideas break out and others fade away? What causes people to become so excited about a product that they can&#8217;t wait to tell their friends? How can an idea be communicated so that it catches fire in people&#8217;s imaginations? Popular author, consultant, and workshop leader Sam Horn identifies what makes an idea, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pop-create-the-perfect-pitch-title-and-tagline-for-anything-sam-horn-abridged/">Pop! : Create the Perfect Pitch, Title, and Tagline for Anything &#8211; Sam Horn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why do some ideas break out and others fade away? What causes people to become so excited about a product that they can&#8217;t wait to tell their friends? How can an idea be communicated so that it catches fire in people&#8217;s imaginations?     </p>
<p>                     Popular author, consultant, and workshop leader Sam Horn identifies what makes an idea, message, or product break out, and presents a simple and proven process?POP! (Purposeful, Original, Pithy)?to create one-of-a-kind ideas, products, and messages that pop through the noise, off the shelf, and into consumers? imaginations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pop-create-the-perfect-pitch-title-and-tagline-for-anything-sam-horn-abridged/">Pop! : Create the Perfect Pitch, Title, and Tagline for Anything &#8211; Sam Horn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fascinate, Revised and Updated : How to Make Your Brand Impossible to Resist &#8211; Sally Hogshead (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fascinate-revised-and-updated-how-to-make-your-brand-impossible-to-resist-sally-hogshead-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fascinate-revised-and-updated-how-to-make-your-brand-impossible-to-resist-sally-hogshead-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why is Jagermeister the most popular brand nobody likes? Why do women pay more to be fascinating than they spend on food and clothes? What raises the price of gummy worms by 1000%? And then there&#8217;s the most important question of all: How can your brand become impossible to resist? Master marketer Sally Hogshead reveals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fascinate-revised-and-updated-how-to-make-your-brand-impossible-to-resist-sally-hogshead-abridged/">Fascinate, Revised and Updated : How to Make Your Brand Impossible to Resist &#8211; Sally Hogshead (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why is Jagermeister the most popular brand nobody likes? Why do women pay more to be fascinating than they spend on food and clothes? What raises the price of gummy worms by 1000%?  And then there&#8217;s the most important question of all: How can your brand become impossible to resist? Master marketer Sally Hogshead reveals the surprising answers, providing readers with a framework to fascinating anyone.  The word &#8220;fascinate&#8221; comes from the Latin word fascinare, meaning &#8220;to bewitch or hold captive so others are powerless to resist.&#8221; Fascination is the most powerful force of attraction, drawing customers into a state of intense focus. This extensively revised and updated edition includes Hogshead&#8217;s latest research on the science of fascination. Combining original case studies with award-winning copywriting experience, she gives you the exact words you need to capture the attention of a distracted world.  This new edition includes a free assessment tool called the Brand Fascination Profile, which will help you earn attention in any environment.<br />
                    Dive into the science of fascination and learn how to:  *Increase prices with ideas from poker to Play-Doh*Build revenue by learning about the $14 million license plate*Get better leads through hypnosis by Sigmund Freud and Steve Jobs*Attract raving fans by following the cult of pistachio ice cream Whether you realize it or not, your brand is already applying one of the seven Advantages Hogshead describes here:  Innovation, Passion, Power, Prestige, Mystique, Alert, or Trust. The question is, how can you apply these core Advantages to stand out in a crowded and distracted world? Hundreds of large corporations, small businesses, and universities-including Twitter, IBM, Porsche, and New York University-use the Fascinate system to captivate their customers. Why? The answers are in this book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fascinate-revised-and-updated-how-to-make-your-brand-impossible-to-resist-sally-hogshead-abridged/">Fascinate, Revised and Updated : How to Make Your Brand Impossible to Resist &#8211; Sally Hogshead (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creative Superpowers : Equip Yourself for the Age of Creativity &#8211; Laura Jordan Bambach, Mark Earls, Daniele Fiandaca, Scott Morrison (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/creative-superpowers-equip-yourself-for-the-age-of-creativity-laura-jordan-bambach-mark-earls-daniele-fiandaca-scott-morrison-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/creative-superpowers-equip-yourself-for-the-age-of-creativity-laura-jordan-bambach-mark-earls-daniele-fiandaca-scott-morrison-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every business leader should read it immediately&#8217; &#8211; Emma Gannon, author of The Multi-Hyphen Method &#8216;A book that made my brain fizz&#8217; &#8211; Bruce Daisley, VP EMEA, Twitter We are about to enter an Age of Creativity that requires a new set of skills. This book introduces you to four creative superpowers that will help [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/creative-superpowers-equip-yourself-for-the-age-of-creativity-laura-jordan-bambach-mark-earls-daniele-fiandaca-scott-morrison-abridged/">Creative Superpowers : Equip Yourself for the Age of Creativity &#8211; Laura Jordan Bambach, Mark Earls, Daniele Fiandaca, Scott Morrison (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every business leader should read it immediately&#8217; &#8211; Emma Gannon, author of The Multi-Hyphen Method     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book that made my brain fizz&#8217; &#8211; Bruce Daisley, VP EMEA, Twitter     </p>
<p>                    We are about to enter an Age of Creativity that requires a new set of skills. This book introduces you to four creative superpowers that will help solve your biggest business problems and open up fresh opportunities, namely the powers of: Hacking &#8211; learn how becoming a hacker will help you tackle problems in different ways. Making &#8211; learn how getting your hands dirty and making things stimulates new parts of the brain as well as creating happy accidents. Teaching &#8211; learn how teaching yourself and others consolidates experience in a fast-paced world. Thieving &#8211; learn how looking to what already exists helps you solve your problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/creative-superpowers-equip-yourself-for-the-age-of-creativity-laura-jordan-bambach-mark-earls-daniele-fiandaca-scott-morrison-abridged/">Creative Superpowers : Equip Yourself for the Age of Creativity &#8211; Laura Jordan Bambach, Mark Earls, Daniele Fiandaca, Scott Morrison (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>YouthNation : Building Remarkable Brands in a Youth-Driven Culture &#8211; Matt Britton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/youthnation-building-remarkable-brands-in-a-youth-driven-culture-matt-britton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/youthnation-building-remarkable-brands-in-a-youth-driven-culture-matt-britton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Youth is no longer an age it&#8217;s a commodity YouthNation is an indispensable brand roadmap to the youth-driven economy. Exploring the idea that youth is no longer an age it&#8217;s a commodity that&#8217;s available to everyone this book shows what it takes to stay connected, agile, authentic, and relevant in today&#8217;s marketplace. Readers will learn [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youthnation-building-remarkable-brands-in-a-youth-driven-culture-matt-britton-abridged/">YouthNation : Building Remarkable Brands in a Youth-Driven Culture &#8211; Matt Britton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Youth is no longer an age it&#8217;s a commodity YouthNation is an indispensable brand roadmap to the youth-driven economy. Exploring the idea that youth is no longer an age it&#8217;s a commodity that&#8217;s available to everyone this book shows what it takes to stay connected, agile, authentic, and relevant in today&#8217;s marketplace. Readers will learn the ins and outs of the new consumer, and the tools, methods, and techniques that ensure brand survival in the age of perpetual youth. Coverage includes marketing in a post-demographic world, crafting the story of the brand, building engaged communities, creating experiences that inspire loyalty and evangelism, and the cutting-edge tricks that help businesses large and small harness the enormous power of youth. The old marketing models are over, and the status quo is dead. Businesses today have to embody the ideals of youth culture in order to succeed, by tapping the new and rapidly evolving resources n business and in life. When everything is changing at the pace of a teenager&#8217;s attention span, how do businesses future-fit for long-term success?<br />
                    This book provides a plan, and the thoughts, strategies, and brass tacks advice for putting it into action. * Use New-Gen psychographics to target markets * Build stronger evangelism with a compelling brand narrative * Create loyal communities with immersive and engaging experiences * Navigate the radically-changed landscape of the future marketplace In today&#8217;s hyper-socialized, Facebook fanatic, selfie-obsessed world, youth is the primary driver of business and culture. Smart companies are looking to tap into the fountain of youth, and the others are sinking fast. YouthNation is a roadmap to brand relevancy in the new economy, giving businesses turn-by-turn direction to their market destination.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youthnation-building-remarkable-brands-in-a-youth-driven-culture-matt-britton-abridged/">YouthNation : Building Remarkable Brands in a Youth-Driven Culture &#8211; Matt Britton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Customer Winback : How to Recapture Lost Customers&#8211;And Keep Them Loyal &#8211; Jill Griffin, Michael W. Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/customer-winback-how-to-recapture-lost-customers-and-keep-them-loyal-jill-griffin-michael-w-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/customer-winback-how-to-recapture-lost-customers-and-keep-them-loyal-jill-griffin-michael-w-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most firms consider the lost customer a lost cause. But in this ground breaking book, Jill Griffin and Michael Lowenstein provide you with step-by-step solutions for winning back lost customers, saving customers on the brink of defection, and making your firm defection proof. Whether your business is small or large, product- or service-based, retail or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/customer-winback-how-to-recapture-lost-customers-and-keep-them-loyal-jill-griffin-michael-w-lowenstein-abridged/">Customer Winback : How to Recapture Lost Customers&#8211;And Keep Them Loyal &#8211; Jill Griffin, Michael W. Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most firms consider the lost customer a lost cause. But in this ground breaking book, Jill Griffin and Michael Lowenstein provide you with step-by-step solutions for winning back lost customers, saving customers on the brink of defection, and making your firm defection proof. Whether your business is small or large, product- or service-based, retail or wholesale, this book offers proven strategies for recognizing which lost customers have the highest win-back value and implementing a sure-fire plan to recover them. It includes the techniques of hundreds of innovative companies who are already working to recapture lost customers and keep them loyal. In today&#8217;s hyper-competitive marketplace, no customer retention program can be entirely foolproof, but with this guide gives you today&#8217;s best methods for winning back those customers you simply can&#8217;t afford to let go.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/customer-winback-how-to-recapture-lost-customers-and-keep-them-loyal-jill-griffin-michael-w-lowenstein-abridged/">Customer Winback : How to Recapture Lost Customers&#8211;And Keep Them Loyal &#8211; Jill Griffin, Michael W. Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rethinking Prestige Branding : Secrets of the Ueber-Brands &#8211; Wolfgang Schaefer, JP Kuehlwein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rethinking-prestige-branding-secrets-of-the-ueber-brands-wolfgang-schaefer-jp-kuehlwein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rethinking-prestige-branding-secrets-of-the-ueber-brands-wolfgang-schaefer-jp-kuehlwein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What makes someone covet a Kelly bag? Why are Cirque Du Soleil or Grey Goose so successful despite breaking all the conventions of their categories? What does Gucci&#8217;s approach to marketing have in common with Nespresso&#8217;s? And why do some people pay a relative fortune for Renova toilet paper or Aesop detergent even though they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rethinking-prestige-branding-secrets-of-the-ueber-brands-wolfgang-schaefer-jp-kuehlwein-abridged/">Rethinking Prestige Branding : Secrets of the Ueber-Brands &#8211; Wolfgang Schaefer, JP Kuehlwein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What makes someone covet a Kelly bag? Why are Cirque Du Soleil or Grey Goose so successful despite breaking all the conventions of their categories? What does Gucci&#8217;s approach to marketing have in common with Nespresso&#8217;s? And why do some people pay a relative fortune for Renova toilet paper or Aesop detergent even though they hardly ever &#8216;advertise&#8217; and seem to have none of the &#8216;functional performance advantages&#8217; conventional marketers would seek to demonstrate? Prestige brand experts JP Kuehlwein and Wolfgang Schaefer have dedicated themselves to studying what drives the success of prestige brands. Rethinking Prestige Branding collects their insights.    </p>
<p>                    Uncovering the secrets of why and how some brands are created more equal than others, Rethinking Prestige Branding  includes over 100 case studies from Apple and Abercrombie &#038; Fitch to Tate Modern and Tesla. Rather than re-telling brand success stories or re-hashing long-standing marketing principles, it takes readers on a colourful journey behind the scenes of today&#8217;s marketing pros. This book will fascinate marketing professional just as much as those who are simply curious as to how premium brands tick.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rethinking-prestige-branding-secrets-of-the-ueber-brands-wolfgang-schaefer-jp-kuehlwein-abridged/">Rethinking Prestige Branding : Secrets of the Ueber-Brands &#8211; Wolfgang Schaefer, JP Kuehlwein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller that explains why certain products and ideas become popular. &#8220;Jonah Berger knows more about what makes information &#8216;go viral&#8217; than anyone in the world.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, author of the bestseller Stumbling on Happiness What makes things popular? If you said advertising, think again. People don&#8217;t listen to advertisements, they listen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/">Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller that explains why certain products and ideas become popular.      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jonah Berger knows more about what makes information &#8216;go viral&#8217; than anyone in the world.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, author of the bestseller Stumbling on Happiness     </p>
<p>                    What makes things popular? If you said advertising, think again. People don&#8217;t listen to advertisements, they listen to their peers. But why do people talk about certain products and ideas more than others? Why are some stories and rumors more infectious? And what makes online content go viral?     </p>
<p>                    Wharton marketing professor Jonah Berger has spent the last decade answering these questions. He&#8217;s studied why New York Times articles make the paper&#8217;s own Most E-mailed list, why products get word of mouth, and how social influence shapes everything from the cars we buy to the clothes we wear to the names we give our children.     </p>
<p>                    In Contagious, Berger reveals the secret science behind word-of-mouth and social transmission. Discover how six basic principles drive all sorts of things to become contagious, from consumer products and policy initiatives to workplace rumors and YouTube videos. Learn how a luxury steakhouse found popularity through the lowly cheesesteak, why anti-drug commercials might have actually increased drug use, and why more than 200 million consumers shared a video about one of the most boring products there is: a blender.     </p>
<p>                    Contagious provides specific, actionable techniques for helping information spread&#8211;for designing messages, advertisements, and content that people will share. Whether you&#8217;re a manager at a big company, a small business owner trying to boost awareness, a politician running for office, or a health official trying to get the word out, Contagious will show you how to make your product or idea catch on.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/">Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be : The world&#8217;s best-selling book by Paul Arden &#8211; Paul Arden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/its-not-how-good-you-are-its-how-good-you-want-to-be-the-worlds-best-selling-book-by-paul-arden-paul-arden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[English Language: Reading & Writing Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/its-not-how-good-you-are-its-how-good-you-want-to-be-the-worlds-best-selling-book-by-paul-arden-paul-arden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be is a handbook of how to succeed in the world: a pocket bible for the talented and timid alike to help make the unthinkable thinkable and the impossible possible. The world&#8217;s top advertising guru, Paul Arden, offers up his wisdom on issues [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-how-good-you-are-its-how-good-you-want-to-be-the-worlds-best-selling-book-by-paul-arden-paul-arden-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be : The world&#8217;s best-selling book by Paul Arden &#8211; Paul Arden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be is a handbook of how to succeed in the world: a pocket bible for the talented and timid alike to help make the unthinkable thinkable and the impossible possible.    </p>
<p>                    The world&#8217;s top advertising guru, Paul Arden, offers up his wisdom on issues as diverse as problem solving, responding to a brief, communicating, playing your cards right, making mistakes, and creativity &#8211; all endeavours that can be applied to aspects of modern life.    </p>
<p>                    This uplifting and humorous little book provides a unique insight into the world of advertising and is a quirky compilation of quotes, facts, pictures, wit and wisdom &#8211; all packed into easy-to-digest, bite-sized spreads. If you want to succeed in life or business, this book is a must.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-how-good-you-are-its-how-good-you-want-to-be-the-worlds-best-selling-book-by-paul-arden-paul-arden-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be : The world&#8217;s best-selling book by Paul Arden &#8211; Paul Arden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Obstacle is the Way : The Ancient Art of Turning Adversity to Advantage &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-obstacle-is-the-way-the-ancient-art-of-turning-adversity-to-advantage-ryan-holiday-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-obstacle-is-the-way-the-ancient-art-of-turning-adversity-to-advantage-ryan-holiday-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD #1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#8216;Follow these precepts and you will revolutionize your life.&#8217; Steven Pressfield, author of The War of Art &#8216;A book for the bedside of every future &#8211; and current &#8211; leader in the world.&#8217; &#8211; Robert Greene, author of The 48 Laws of Power The Obstacle [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-obstacle-is-the-way-the-ancient-art-of-turning-adversity-to-advantage-ryan-holiday-abridged/">The Obstacle is the Way : The Ancient Art of Turning Adversity to Advantage &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD<br />
                    #1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller<br />
                    &#8216;Follow these precepts and you will revolutionize your life.&#8217;  Steven Pressfield, author of The War of Art<br />
                    &#8216;A book for the bedside of every future &#8211; and current &#8211; leader in the world.&#8217; &#8211; Robert Greene, author of The 48 Laws of Power    </p>
<p>                    The Obstacle is the Way has become a cult classic, beloved by men and women around the world who apply its wisdom to become more successful at whatever they do.     </p>
<p>                                    The book&#8217;s many fans include a former governor and movie star (Arnold Schwarzenegger), a hip hop icon (LL Cool J), an Irish tennis pro (James McGee), the World Number 1 golfer (Rory McIlroy) and the coaches and players of winning teams like English Rugby National Team, the New England Patriots, Seattle Seahawks and Chicago Cubs.    </p>
<p>                     The book draws its inspiration from stoicism, the ancient Greek philosophy of enduring pain or adversity with perseverance and resilience. Stoics focus on the things they can control, let go of everything else, and turn every new obstacle into an opportunity to get better, stronger, tougher. As Marcus Aurelius put it nearly 2000 years ago: &#8220;The impediment to action advances action. What stands in the way becomes the way.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     Ryan Holiday shows us how some of the most successful people in history-from John D. Rockefeller to Amelia Earhart to Ulysses S. Grant to Steve Jobs-have applied stoicism to overcome difficult or even impossible situations. Their embrace of these principles ultimately mattered more than their natural intelligence, talents, or luck.    </p>
<p>                     If you&#8217;re feeling frustrated, demoralized, or stuck in a rut, this book can help you turn your problems into your biggest advantages. And along the way it will inspire you with dozens of true stories of the greats from every age and era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-obstacle-is-the-way-the-ancient-art-of-turning-adversity-to-advantage-ryan-holiday-abridged/">The Obstacle is the Way : The Ancient Art of Turning Adversity to Advantage &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gen Z Frequency : How Brands Tune In and Build Credibility &#8211; Gregg L. Witt, Derek E. Baird (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gen-z-frequency-how-brands-tune-in-and-build-credibility-gregg-l-witt-derek-e-baird-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gen-z-frequency-how-brands-tune-in-and-build-credibility-gregg-l-witt-derek-e-baird-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Generation Z, ranging from tweens to young adults, has enormous spending power; yet it is one of the most challenging generational cohorts for brands to reach. It is projected to be the largest consumer demographic in history, driving a forecast from the HRC Retail Advisory of 40% of all US consumer spending, and another 40% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gen-z-frequency-how-brands-tune-in-and-build-credibility-gregg-l-witt-derek-e-baird-abridged/">The Gen Z Frequency : How Brands Tune In and Build Credibility &#8211; Gregg L. Witt, Derek E. Baird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Generation Z, ranging from tweens to young adults, has enormous spending power; yet it is one of the most challenging generational cohorts for brands to reach. It is projected to be the largest consumer demographic in history, driving a forecast from the HRC Retail Advisory of 40% of all US consumer spending, and another 40% of all consumers in the US, Europe and BRIC by 2020 (Brazil, Russia, India, China), according to other sources. Embodying an unrelenting relationship with information and mobile technology from a young age, Generation Z&#8217;s ecosystem is infinitely more complex and varied than any generation before. Staying tuned-in to this demographic&#8217;s impatience, confidence and constantly evolving trends can be daunting for any marketer trying to keep up.    </p>
<p>                    The Gen Z Frequency offers a comprehensive guide for any brand or organization trying to reach this demographic, covering fundamental truths, content creation, engagement strategies and tactics such as social media, experiential, emerging technologies, and much more. It is woven with fascinating case studies and real-world stories from the trenches, plus key insights from leading youth  brands and Gen Z themselves. Whether you are new to marketing or a seasoned expert, The Gen Z Frequency is the ultimate resource for tuning in to Generation Z.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gen-z-frequency-how-brands-tune-in-and-build-credibility-gregg-l-witt-derek-e-baird-abridged/">The Gen Z Frequency : How Brands Tune In and Build Credibility &#8211; Gregg L. Witt, Derek E. Baird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cashvertising : How to Use 50 Secrets of Ad-Agency Psychology to Make Big Money Selling Anything to Anyone &#8211; Drew Eric Whitman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cashvertising-how-to-use-50-secrets-of-ad-agency-psychology-to-make-big-money-selling-anything-to-anyone-drew-eric-whitman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cashvertising-how-to-use-50-secrets-of-ad-agency-psychology-to-make-big-money-selling-anything-to-anyone-drew-eric-whitman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Barely one in a hundred businesspeople knows these facts about creating powerful advertising. Do You? FACT! Sixty percent of people read only headlines. Your headline must stop them or your advertising will likely fail. FACT! Captions under photos get 200 percent greater readership than non-headline copy. FACT! Ads with sale prices draw 20 percent more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cashvertising-how-to-use-50-secrets-of-ad-agency-psychology-to-make-big-money-selling-anything-to-anyone-drew-eric-whitman-abridged/">Cashvertising : How to Use 50 Secrets of Ad-Agency Psychology to Make Big Money Selling Anything to Anyone &#8211; Drew Eric Whitman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Barely one in a hundred businesspeople knows these facts about creating powerful advertising. Do You?     </p>
<p>                    FACT! Sixty percent of people read only headlines. Your headline must stop them or your advertising will likely fail.<br />
                    FACT! Captions under photos get 200 percent greater readership than non-headline copy.<br />
                    FACT! Ads with sale prices draw 20 percent more attention.<br />
                    FACT! Half-page ads pull about 70 percent of full-page ads; quarter-page ads pull about 50 percent of full-page ads.<br />
                    FACT! Four-color ads are up to 45 percent more effective than black and white.     </p>
<p>                    New York&#8217;s biggest ad agencies use dozens of these little-known secrets every day to influence people to buy. And now&#8211;thanks to Cashvertising&#8211;you can, too. And it won&#8217;t matter one bit whether you&#8217;re a corporate giant or a mom-and-pop pizza shop. These techniques are based on human psychology. They work no matter where you&#8217;re located, no matter what kind of product or service you sell, and no matter where you advertise. In fact, most don&#8217;t cost a penny to use.     </p>
<p>                    Like a wild roller-coaster ride through the streets of Madison Avenue, Cashvertising teaches you the tips, tricks, and strategies that New York&#8217;s top gun copywriters and designers use to persuade people to buy like crazy. No matter what you sell&#8211;or how you sell it, this practical, fast-paced book will teach you:     </p>
<p>                    How to create powerful ads, brochures, sales letters, Websites, and more<br />
                    How to make people believe what you say<br />
                    Sneaky ways to persuade people to respond<br />
                    Effective tricks for writing magnetic headlines<br />
                    What mistakes to avoid&#8230;at all costs!<br />
                    What you should always/never do in your ads<br />
                    Expert formulas, guidance, tips and strategies</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cashvertising-how-to-use-50-secrets-of-ad-agency-psychology-to-make-big-money-selling-anything-to-anyone-drew-eric-whitman-abridged/">Cashvertising : How to Use 50 Secrets of Ad-Agency Psychology to Make Big Money Selling Anything to Anyone &#8211; Drew Eric Whitman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Enhance your copywriting skills with psychology-driven techniques to create stand out copy that taps into consumer decision making and sells, using this second edition of the ultimate copywriting survival guide for the 21st century &#8211; essential to every marketing or creative professional&#8217;s bookshelf. With many professionals now developing their skills on the job, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/">Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enhance your copywriting skills with psychology-driven techniques to create stand out copy that taps into consumer decision making and sells, using this second edition of the ultimate copywriting survival guide for the 21st century &#8211; essential to every marketing or creative professional&#8217;s bookshelf.    </p>
<p>                    With many professionals now developing their skills on the job, it is notoriously difficult to benchmark successful copy. This book provides a step up for those who already know the basics of writing copy, and are seeking more advanced, psychology-driven techniques to gain the competitive edge. With practical insight into human decision making and consumer engagement, it will inspire the clear-cut confidence needed to create, quantify, and sell stand out copy in a cluttered marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    Complementing the &#8216;how to&#8217; perspective of copywriting, with impressive interviews from leading ad agencies and copywriters across the globe, this second edition addresses the everyday issues faced in a multitude of roles, including:    </p>
<p>                    -Practical advice to measure and benchmark effective copy<br />
                    -Guidance on creating and critiquing briefs<br />
                    -New chapters on how to weave copywriting skills into the wider industry<br />
                    -Storytelling and content marketing<br />
                    -The impact of evolving channels like mobile and social media    </p>
<p>                    Practical, inspiring and extremely digestible, Persuasive Copywriting is the only vibrant, all-encompassing guide to copywriting that you need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/">Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eating the Big Fish : How Challenger Brands Can Compete Against Brand Leaders &#8211; A. T. Chandler, Adam Morgan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eating-the-big-fish-how-challenger-brands-can-compete-against-brand-leaders-a-t-chandler-adam-morgan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eating-the-big-fish-how-challenger-brands-can-compete-against-brand-leaders-a-t-chandler-adam-morgan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eating the Big Fish: How Challenger Brands Can Compete Against Brand Leaders, Second Edition, Revised and Expanded The second edition of the international bestseller, now revised and updated, just in time for the business challenges ahead. It contains over 25 new interviews and case histories, two completely new chapters, introduces a new typology of 12 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eating-the-big-fish-how-challenger-brands-can-compete-against-brand-leaders-a-t-chandler-adam-morgan-abridged/">Eating the Big Fish : How Challenger Brands Can Compete Against Brand Leaders &#8211; A. T. Chandler, Adam Morgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eating the Big Fish: How Challenger Brands Can Compete Against Brand Leaders, Second Edition, Revised and Expanded     </p>
<p>                    The second edition of the international bestseller, now revised and updated, just in time for the business challenges ahead.     </p>
<p>                    It contains over 25 new interviews and case histories, two completely new chapters, introduces a new typology of 12 different kinds of Challengers, has extensive updates of the main chapters, a range of new exercises, supplies weblinks to view interviews online, and offers supplementary downloadable information.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eating-the-big-fish-how-challenger-brands-can-compete-against-brand-leaders-a-t-chandler-adam-morgan-abridged/">Eating the Big Fish : How Challenger Brands Can Compete Against Brand Leaders &#8211; A. T. Chandler, Adam Morgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
