<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Financial Accounting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/financial-accounting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/financial-accounting/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Financial Accounting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/financial-accounting/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Picture Your Prosperity &#8211; Supplement by Ellen Rogin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/picture-your-prosperity-supplement-by-ellen-rogin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/picture-your-prosperity-supplement-by-ellen-rogin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone has a unique vision of a prosperous and secure future. What&#8217;s yours? If someone asked you to describe prosperity and security, what would you see in your mind&#8217;s eye? Is it finally taking that trip to Paris? A beautiful beach house? Or maybe making that last mortgage payment and staying right where you are? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/picture-your-prosperity-supplement-by-ellen-rogin-abridged/">Picture Your Prosperity &#8211; Supplement by Ellen Rogin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone has a unique vision of a prosperous and secure future. What&#8217;s yours?<br />
                    If someone asked you to describe prosperity and security, what would you see in your mind&#8217;s eye? Is it finally taking that trip to Paris? A beautiful beach house? Or maybe making that last mortgage payment and staying right where you are? In your vision are you captaining a sailboat? Hiking through a redwood forest? Or simply enjoying a precious moment of peace and contentment?<br />
                    When it comes to financial planning, it&#8217;s easy to jump right into the minutiae of investments, skipping over the deeper questions of what you really want from your money, both now and in the future. But in &#8220;Picture Your Prosperity,&#8221; Ellen Rogin and Lisa Kueng do the opposite. First they&#8217;ll help you figure out exactly what &#8220;you&#8221; need and want. Only then will they show you how to make the smart money decisions that can help turn your vision into reality.<br />
                    If the thought of financial planning and investing sounds about as appealing as a trip to the dentist, you&#8217;re not alone. Many of us avoid the process because it feels too stressful, boring, or difficult. But as Ellen and Lisa have learned from their years in financial services, thinking about money becomes exciting and fun when it&#8217;s tied to your personal vision instead of a pile of technical details. And it can be easier than you think.<br />
                    Once your goal is clear, the authors show you how to design your investments to create the life you&#8217;ve envisioned. Soon you&#8217;ll feel more in control of your finances and on the road to the things that matter most. You&#8217;ll be able to create a plan that&#8217;s broken down into manageable and, dare we say it, &#8220;enjoyable&#8221; steps. You&#8217;ll learn how to handle your money with more joy and less stress, even during turbulent times. And you&#8217;ll explore ways your financial moves can have a huge positive impact on other people.<br />
                    As Rogin and Kueng write, &#8220;Your money is important, but money is meaningless if it can&#8217;t be connected to the rest of your life. Who cares what the totals on your balance sheet or in your bank account are if you can&#8217;t use them to build the kind of future you want? What good is having a brilliant investment strategy if you worry incessantly about losing it, constantly fight with your partner about money, or come home and kick your dog on days the market drops? What if instead you felt positive, peaceful, and prosperous?<br />
                    Get ready to feel more excited than ever about your money, and about all the good things it can bring.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/picture-your-prosperity-supplement-by-ellen-rogin-abridged/">Picture Your Prosperity &#8211; Supplement by Ellen Rogin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Financial Diet : A Total Beginner&#8217;s Guide to Getting Good with Money &#8211; Chelsea Fagan, Lauren Ver Hage (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A Refinery29 Best Book of 2018* *One of Real Simple&#8217;s Most Inspiring Books for Graduates* *Indie Personal Finance Bestseller* How to get good with money, even if you have no idea where to start. The Financial Diet is the personal finance book for people who don&#8217;t care about personal finance. Whether you&#8217;re in need of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/">The Financial Diet : A Total Beginner&#8217;s Guide to Getting Good with Money &#8211; Chelsea Fagan, Lauren Ver Hage (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A Refinery29 Best Book of 2018*<br />
                    *One of Real Simple&#8217;s Most Inspiring Books for Graduates*<br />
                    *Indie Personal Finance Bestseller*     </p>
<p>                    How to get good with money, even if you have no idea where to start.     </p>
<p>                    The Financial Diet is the personal finance book for people who don&#8217;t care about personal finance. Whether you&#8217;re in need of an overspending detox, buried under student debt, or just trying to figure out how to live on an entry-level salary, The Financial Diet gives you tools to make a budget, understand investments, and deal with your credit. Chelsea Fagan has tapped a range of experts to help you make the best choices for you, but she also knows that being smarter with money isn&#8217;t just about what you put in the bank. It&#8217;s about everything&#8211;from the clothes you put in your closet, to your financial relationship habits, to the food you put in your kitchen (instead of ordering in again). So The Financial Diet gives you the tools to negotiate a raise and the perfect cocktail recipe to celebrate your new salary.     </p>
<p>                    The Financial Diet will teach you:<br />
                    &#8211; how to get good with money in a year.<br />
                    &#8211; the ingredients everyone needs to have a budget-friendly kitchen.<br />
                    &#8211; how to talk about awkward money stuff with your friends.<br />
                    &#8211; the best way to make (and stick to!) a budget.<br />
                    &#8211; how to take care of your house like a grown-up.<br />
                    &#8211; what the hell it means to invest (and how you can do it).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/">The Financial Diet : A Total Beginner&#8217;s Guide to Getting Good with Money &#8211; Chelsea Fagan, Lauren Ver Hage (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;brilliant and provocative&#8221; (Walter Isaacson) guide shares nine principles to adapt and survive the technological changes shaping our future from the director of the MIT Media Lab and a veteran Wired journalist. The world is more complex and volatile today than at any other time in our history. The tools of our modern existence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/">Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;brilliant and provocative&#8221; (Walter Isaacson) guide shares nine principles to adapt and survive the technological changes shaping our future from the director of the MIT Media Lab and a veteran Wired journalist.  The world is more complex and volatile today than at any other time in our history. The tools of our modern existence are getting faster, cheaper, and smaller at an exponential rate, transforming every aspect of society, from business to culture and from the public sphere to our most private moments. The people who succeed will be the ones who learn to think differently.  In Whiplash, Joi Ito and Jeff Howe distill that logic into nine organizing principles for navigating and surviving this tumultuous period: Emergence over Authority Pull over Push Compasses over Maps Risk over Safety Disobedience over Compliance Practice over Theory Diversity over Ability Resilience over Strength Systems over Objects   Filled with incredible case studies and cutting-edge research and philosophies from the MIT Media Lab and beyond, Whiplash will help you adapt and succeed in this unpredictable world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/">Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
