<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Anarchism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/anarchism/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/anarchism/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Anarchism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/anarchism/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Anarchism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Colin Ward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anarchism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The word &#8216;anarchism&#8217; tends to conjure up images of aggressive protest against government, and &#8211; recently &#8211; of angry demonstrations against bodies such as the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund. But is anarchism inevitably linked with violent disorder? Do anarchists adhere to a coherent ideology? What exactly is anarchism? In this Very Short [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/">Anarchism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Colin Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The word &#8216;anarchism&#8217; tends to conjure up images of aggressive protest against government, and &#8211; recently &#8211; of angry demonstrations against bodies such as the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund. But is anarchism inevitably linked with violent disorder? Do anarchists adhere to a coherent ideology? What exactly is anarchism?    </p>
<p>                    In this Very Short Introduction, Colin Ward considers anarchism from a variety of perspectives: theoretical, historical, and international, and by exploring key anarchist thinkers from Kropotkin to Chomsky. He looks critically at anarchism by evaluating key ideas within it, such as its blanket opposition to incarceration, and policy of &#8216;no compromise&#8217; with the apparatus of political decision-making. Among the questions he ponders are: can anarchy ever function effectively as a political force?<br />
                    Is it more &#8216;organized&#8217; and &#8216;reasonable&#8217; than is currently perceived? Whatever the politics of the reader, Ward&#8217;s argument ensures that anarchism will be much better understood after reading this book.    </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books are the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/">Anarchism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Colin Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
