<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Religious Groups: Social &amp; Cultural Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/religious-groups-social-cultural-aspects/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/religious-groups-social-cultural-aspects/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Religious Groups: Social &amp; Cultural Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/religious-groups-social-cultural-aspects/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism &#8211; Max Weber</title>
		<link>/the-protestant-ethic-and-the-spirit-of-capitalism-max-weber/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-protestant-ethic-and-the-spirit-of-capitalism-max-weber/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Max Weber&#8217;s best-known and most controversial work, The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism, first published in 1904, remains to this day a powerful and fascinating read. Weber&#8217;s highly accessible style is just one of many reasons for his continuing popularity. The book contends that the Protestant ethic made possible and encouraged the development [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-protestant-ethic-and-the-spirit-of-capitalism-max-weber/">The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism &#8211; Max Weber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Max Weber&#8217;s best-known and most controversial work, The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism, first published in 1904, remains to this day a powerful and fascinating read. Weber&#8217;s highly accessible style is just one of many reasons for his continuing popularity. The book contends that the Protestant ethic made possible and encouraged the development of capitalism in the West. Widely considered as the most informed work ever written on the social effects of advanced capitalism, The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism holds its own as one of the most significant books of the twentieth century. The book is one of those rare works of scholarship which no informed citizen can afford to ignore.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-protestant-ethic-and-the-spirit-of-capitalism-max-weber/">The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism &#8211; Max Weber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Should We Then Live? : The Rise and Decline of Western Thought and Culture &#8211; Francis A. Schaeffer, Foreword by Lane T. Dennis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-should-we-then-live-the-rise-and-decline-of-western-thought-and-culture-francis-a-schaeffer-foreword-by-lane-t-dennis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Ministry & Pastoral Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Social Thought & Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-should-we-then-live-the-rise-and-decline-of-western-thought-and-culture-francis-a-schaeffer-foreword-by-lane-t-dennis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Special 50th anniversary L&#8217;Abri Fellowship edition. Schaeffer&#8217;s seminal work which analyzed the reasons for modern society&#8217;s state of affairs and presented living a Christ-centered life as the only viable alternative</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-should-we-then-live-the-rise-and-decline-of-western-thought-and-culture-francis-a-schaeffer-foreword-by-lane-t-dennis-abridged/">How Should We Then Live? : The Rise and Decline of Western Thought and Culture &#8211; Francis A. Schaeffer, Foreword by Lane T. Dennis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Special 50th anniversary L&#8217;Abri Fellowship edition. Schaeffer&#8217;s seminal work which analyzed the reasons for modern society&#8217;s state of affairs and presented living a Christ-centered life as the only viable alternative</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-should-we-then-live-the-rise-and-decline-of-western-thought-and-culture-francis-a-schaeffer-foreword-by-lane-t-dennis-abridged/">How Should We Then Live? : The Rise and Decline of Western Thought and Culture &#8211; Francis A. Schaeffer, Foreword by Lane T. Dennis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Right Side of History : How Reason and Moral Purpose Made the West Great &#8211; Ben Shapiro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Intolerance, Persecution & Conflict]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Issues & Debates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! Human beings have never had it better than we have it now in the West. So why are we on the verge of throwing it all away? In 2016, New York Times bestselling author Ben Shapiro spoke at the University of California-Berkeley. Hundreds of police officers were required to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/">The Right Side of History : How Reason and Moral Purpose Made the West Great &#8211; Ben Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!    </p>
<p>                    Human beings have never had it better than we have it now in the West. So why are we on the verge of throwing it all away?    </p>
<p>                    In 2016, New York Times bestselling author Ben Shapiro spoke at the University of California-Berkeley. Hundreds of police officers were required to protect his speech. What was so frightening about Shapiro? He came to argue that Western civilization is in the midst of a crisis of purpose and ideas; that we have let grievances replace our sense of community and political expediency limit our individual rights; that we are teaching our kids that their emotions matter more than rational debate; and that the only meaning in life is arbitrary and subjective.    </p>
<p>                    As a society, we are forgetting that almost everything great that has ever happened in history happened because of people who believed in both Judeo-Christian values and in the Greek-born power of reason. In The Right Side of History, Shapiro sprints through more than 3,500 years, dozens of philosophers, and the thicket of modern politics to show how our freedoms are built upon the twin notions that every human being is made in God&#8217;s image and that human beings were created with reason capable of exploring God&#8217;s world.    </p>
<p>                    We can thank these values for the birth of science, the dream of progress, human rights, prosperity, peace, and artistic beauty. Jerusalem and Athens built America, ended slavery, defeated the Nazis and the Communists, lifted billions from poverty, and gave billions more spiritual purpose.     </p>
<p>                    Yet we are in the process of abandoning Judeo-Christian values and Greek natural law, watching our civilization collapse into age-old tribalism, individualistic hedonism, and moral subjectivism. We believe we can satisfy ourselves with intersectionality, scientific materialism, progressive politics, authoritarian governance, or nationalistic solidarity.    </p>
<p>                    We can&#8217;t.    </p>
<p>                    The West is special, and in The Right Side of History, Ben Shapiro bravely explains how we have lost sight of the moral purpose that drives each of us to be better, the sacred duty to work together for the greater good,.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-side-of-history-how-reason-and-moral-purpose-made-the-west-great-ben-shapiro-abridged/">The Right Side of History : How Reason and Moral Purpose Made the West Great &#8211; Ben Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Myth &#8211; Joseph Campbell, Bill Moyers (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-myth-joseph-campbell-bill-moyers-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Folklore, Myths & Legends]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-myth-joseph-campbell-bill-moyers-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The national bestseller, now available in a non-illustrated, standard format paperback edition The Power of Myth launched an extraordinary resurgence of interest in Joseph Campbell and his work. A preeminent scholar, writer, and teacher, he has had a profound influence on millions of people&#8211;including Star Wars creator George Lucas. To Campbell, mythology was the &#8220;song [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-myth-joseph-campbell-bill-moyers-abridged/">The Power of Myth &#8211; Joseph Campbell, Bill Moyers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The national bestseller, now available in a non-illustrated, standard format paperback edition    </p>
<p>                    The Power of Myth launched an extraordinary resurgence of interest in Joseph Campbell and his work. A preeminent scholar, writer, and teacher, he has had a profound influence on millions of people&#8211;including Star Wars creator George Lucas. To Campbell, mythology was the &#8220;song of the universe, the music of the spheres.&#8221; With Bill Moyers, one of America&#8217;s most prominent journalists, as his thoughtful and engaging interviewer, The Power of Myth touches on subjects from modern marriage to virgin births, from Jesus to John Lennon, offering a brilliant combination of intelligence and wit.     </p>
<p>                    This extraordinary book reveals how the themes and symbols of ancient narratives continue to bring meaning to birth, death, love, and war. From stories of the gods and goddesses of ancient Greece and Rome to traditions of Buddhism, Hinduism and Christianity, a broad array of themes are considered that together identify the universality of human experience across time and culture. An impeccable match of interviewer and subject, a timeless distillation of Campbell&#8217;s work, The Power of Myth continues to exert a profound influence on our culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-myth-joseph-campbell-bill-moyers-abridged/">The Power of Myth &#8211; Joseph Campbell, Bill Moyers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Boundaries Of Desire : A Century of Good Sex, Bad Laws, and Changing Identities &#8211; Eric Berkowitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-boundaries-of-desire-a-century-of-good-sex-bad-laws-and-changing-identities-eric-berkowitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sexual Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-boundaries-of-desire-a-century-of-good-sex-bad-laws-and-changing-identities-eric-berkowitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The act of reproduction, and its variants, never change much, but our ideas about the meaning of sex are in constant flux. Switch a decade, cross a border, or traverse class lines and the harmless pleasures of one group become the gravest crimes in another. Combining meticulous research and lively storytelling, The Boundaries of Desire [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boundaries-of-desire-a-century-of-good-sex-bad-laws-and-changing-identities-eric-berkowitz-abridged/">The Boundaries Of Desire : A Century of Good Sex, Bad Laws, and Changing Identities &#8211; Eric Berkowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The act of reproduction, and its variants, never change much, but our ideas about the meaning of sex are in constant flux. Switch a decade, cross a border, or traverse class lines and the harmless pleasures of one group become the gravest crimes in another.     </p>
<p>                    Combining meticulous research and lively storytelling, The Boundaries of Desire traces the fast-moving bloodsport of sex law over the past century, and challenges our most cherished notions about family, power, gender, and identity.     </p>
<p>                    Starting when courts censored birth control information as pornography and let men rape their wives, and continuing through the &#8220;sexual revolution&#8221; and into the present day (when rape, gay rights, sex trafficking, and sex on the internet saturate the news), Berkowitz shows how the law has remained out of synch with the convulsive changes in sexual morality.     </p>
<p>                    By focusing on the stories of real people, Berkowitz adds a compelling human element to what might otherwise be faceless legal battles. The law is made by people, after all, and nothing sparks intolerance &#8211; on the left and right &#8212; more than sex. Ultimately, Berkowitz shows the emptiness of sanctimonious condemnation, and argues that sexual questions are too subtle and volatile for simple, catch-all solutions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boundaries-of-desire-a-century-of-good-sex-bad-laws-and-changing-identities-eric-berkowitz-abridged/">The Boundaries Of Desire : A Century of Good Sex, Bad Laws, and Changing Identities &#8211; Eric Berkowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Religion? : A Personal Story &#8211; Elaine Pagels (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-religion-a-personal-story-elaine-pagels-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-religion-a-personal-story-elaine-pagels-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestseller One of PW&#8217;s Best Books of the Year One of Amazon&#8217;s Best Books of the Month Why is religion still around in the twenty-first century? Why do so many still believe? And how do various traditions still shape the way people experience everything from sexuality to politics, whether they are religious [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-religion-a-personal-story-elaine-pagels-abridged/">Why Religion? : A Personal Story &#8211; Elaine Pagels (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestseller    </p>
<p>                    One of PW&#8217;s Best Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    One of Amazon&#8217;s Best Books of the Month     </p>
<p>                    Why is religion still around in the twenty-first century? Why do so many still believe? And how do various traditions still shape the way people experience everything from sexuality to politics, whether they are religious or not? In Why Religion? Elaine Pagels looks to her own life to help address these questions.    </p>
<p>                    These questions took on a new urgency for Pagels when dealing with unimaginable loss&#8211;the death of her young son, followed a year later by the shocking loss of her husband. Here she interweaves a personal story with the work that she loves, illuminating how, for better and worse, religious traditions have shaped how we understand ourselves; how we relate to one another; and, most importantly, how to get through the most difficult challenges we face.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing upon the perspectives of neurologists, anthropologists, and historians, as well as her own research, Pagels opens unexpected ways of understanding persistent religious aspects of our culture.     </p>
<p>                    A provocative and deeply moving account from one of the most compelling religious thinkers at work today, Why Religion? explores the spiritual dimension of human experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-religion-a-personal-story-elaine-pagels-abridged/">Why Religion? : A Personal Story &#8211; Elaine Pagels (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The physiologist Benjamin Libet famously demonstrated that activity in the brain&#8217;s motor regions can be detected some 300 milliseconds before a person feels that he has decided to move. Another lab recently used fMRI data to show that some &#8220;conscious&#8221; decisions can be predicted up to 10 seconds before they enter awareness (long before the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/">Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The physiologist Benjamin Libet famously demonstrated that activity in the brain&#8217;s motor regions can be detected some 300 milliseconds before a person feels that he has decided to move. Another lab recently used fMRI data to show that some &#8220;conscious&#8221; decisions can be predicted up to 10 seconds before they enter awareness (long before the preparatory motor activity detected by Libet). Clearly, findings of this kind are difficult to reconcile with the sense that one is the conscious source of one&#8217;s actions.     </p>
<p>                    The question of free will is no mere curio of philosophy seminars. A belief in free will underwrites both the religious notion of &#8220;sin&#8221; and our enduring commitment to retributive justice. The Supreme Court has called free will a &#8220;universal and persistent&#8221; foundation for our system of law. Any scientific developments that threatened our notion of free will would seem to put the ethics of punishing people for their bad behaviour in question.In Free Will Harris debates these ideas and asks whether or not, given what brain science is telling us, we actually have free will?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/">Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
