<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Diplomacy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/diplomacy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/diplomacy/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Diplomacy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/diplomacy/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tough Love : My Story of the Things Worth Fighting For &#8211; Susan Rice</title>
		<link>/tough-love-my-story-of-the-things-worth-fighting-for-susan-rice/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tough-love-my-story-of-the-things-worth-fighting-for-susan-rice/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Susan E. Rice, National Security Advisor to President Barack Obama and US Ambassador to the United Nations, reveals her powerful story with unflinching candor in this New York Times bestseller. Mother, wife, scholar, diplomat, and fierce champion of American interests and values, Susan Rice powerfully connects the personal and the professional. Taught early, with tough [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tough-love-my-story-of-the-things-worth-fighting-for-susan-rice/">Tough Love : My Story of the Things Worth Fighting For &#8211; Susan Rice</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Susan E. Rice, National Security Advisor to President Barack Obama and US Ambassador to the United Nations, reveals her powerful story with unflinching candor in this New York Times bestseller.</p>
<p>                     Mother, wife, scholar, diplomat, and fierce champion of American interests and values, Susan Rice powerfully connects the personal and the professional. Taught early, with tough love, how to compete and excel as an African American woman in settings where people of color are few, Susan now shares the wisdom she learned along the way in this &#8220;personal and honest&#8230;ode to public service&#8221; (NPR).</p>
<p>                     Laying bare the family struggles that shaped her early life she also examines the ancestral legacies that influenced her. Rice&#8217;s elders-immigrants on one side and descendants of slaves on the other-encouraged each generation to rise. And rise they did, in uniform and in the pulpit, as educators, community leaders, and public servants.</p>
<p>                     Susan too rose rapidly. She served throughout the Clinton administration, becoming one of the nation&#8217;s youngest assistant secretaries of state and, later, one of President Obama&#8217;s most trusted advisors.</p>
<p>                     Rice provides an insider&#8217;s account of some of the most complex issues confronting the United States over three decades, from &#8220;Black Hawk Down&#8221; in Somalia to the genocide in Rwanda, and from conflicts in Libya and Syria to the Ebola epidemic, a secret channel to Iran, and the opening to Cuba during the Obama years.</p>
<p>                     With unmatched insight and characteristic bluntness, she reveals previously untold stories behind recent national security challenges, including confrontations with Russia and China, the war against ISIS, the fallout from Edward Snowden&#8217;s NSA leaks, the US response to Russian interference in the 2016 election, and the surreal transition to the Trump administration.</p>
<p>                     Although you might think you know Susan Rice-whose name became synonymous with Benghazi following her Sunday news show appearances after the deadly 2012 terrorist attacks in Libya-now, through these pages, you truly will know her for the first time. &#8220;An astute, analytical take on recent American political history,&#8221; (Publishers Weekly, starred review) Tough Love makes an urgent appeal to the American public to bridge our dangerous domestic divides in order to preserve our democracy and sustain our global leadership.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tough-love-my-story-of-the-things-worth-fighting-for-susan-rice/">Tough Love : My Story of the Things Worth Fighting For &#8211; Susan Rice</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two Nations Indivisible : Mexico, the United States, and the Road Ahead &#8211; Shannon K. O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Overlooked in today&#8217;s bloody headlines is Mexico&#8217;s fundamental transformation. In over three short decades it has gone from a poor to a middle class nation, a closed to an open economy, an authoritarian to a vibrant (if at times messy) democracy, and a local to an increasingly binational society. But while things are much better [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/">Two Nations Indivisible : Mexico, the United States, and the Road Ahead &#8211; Shannon K. O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Overlooked in today&#8217;s bloody headlines is Mexico&#8217;s fundamental transformation. In over three short decades it has gone from a poor to a middle class nation, a closed to an open economy, an authoritarian to a vibrant (if at times messy) democracy, and a local to an increasingly binational society. But while things are much better than portrayed, Mexico does face a true security challenge. It stands at a crossroads. It can follow a path toward a top ten economy, an<br />
                    open democracy, and a leading world voice, or one that spirals down into drug-fueled corruption and violence. Today&#8217;s choices will define not only Mexico&#8217;s future, but also that of the United States. Perhaps no other nation is as indelibly intertwined with our economy, society, and daily lives. What<br />
                    happens in Mexico will affect the United States for decades to come.    </p>
<p>                    Two Nations Indivisible tells the story of the making of modern Mexico, and what it means for the United States. Recounting the economic, political, social, and security changes of the last thirty years, it provides a roadmap for the greatest overlooked foreign policy challenge of our time -relations with our southern neighbor. For the good of both countries, it argues against walling the United States off from its neighbor; and instead for investing finally in a true<br />
                    partnership.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/">Two Nations Indivisible : Mexico, the United States, and the Road Ahead &#8211; Shannon K. O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes, it makes more sense to lose today in order to win tomorrow. What do you do when you know what you want, but you have no idea how to get it? &#8216;The greatest negotiation book of all time.&#8217; Inc. Magazine ________________ Never walk away. Learn to listen, then learn to understand, then learn to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/">Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes, it makes more sense to lose today in order to win tomorrow. What do you do when you know what you want, but you have no idea how to get it?    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The greatest negotiation book of all time.&#8217; Inc. Magazine<br />
                     ________________                           </p>
<p>                     Never walk away. Learn to listen, then learn to understand, then learn to win.    </p>
<p>                    Negotiation is part of every human encounter, and most of us do it badly. Whether dealing with family, a business, or diplomacy, people often fail to meet their goals in every country and context. They focus on power and &#8220;win-win&#8221; instead of relationships and perceptions. They don&#8217;t find enough things to trade. They think others should be rational when they should be dealing with emotions. They get distracted from their goals.    </p>
<p>                    In this revolutionary and seminal bestselling book, leading negotiation practitioner, coach and professor Stuart Diamond shows how emotional intelligence, perceptions, cultural diversity and collaboration produce four times as much value as old-school, conflictive, power, leverage and logic. Drawing on thirty-plus years of research involving 30,000 people across 45 countries &#8211; ranging from political and corporate leaders to administrative assistants, lawyers, housewives, students, and labourers &#8211; he outlines specific, practical and better ways to deal with others. To this, he adds his 40-year experience as a corporate executive, Harvard-trained attorney, and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist.    </p>
<p>                    Getting More is based on Professor Diamond&#8217;s award-winning negotiations course at The Wharton Business School, where it has been the most sought-after course by students for almost two decades. It contains a powerful toolkit that can be used in any situation: with kids and jobs, travel and shopping, business, politics, relationships, cultures, partners and competitors. His advice is brought to life in an accessible and entertaining manner through the stories of hundreds of people who have used the toolkit with great success.<br />
                    ________________    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;From advising on how to negotiate with terrorists, to industrial disputes, to children, Diamond&#8217;s twelve rules of negotiation promise to open new doors every day.&#8217; Radio One    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Practical, immediately applicable and highly effective.&#8217; Evan Wittenberg, co-founder of TRUE and former Head of Global Leadership Development at Google    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I rely on Stuart Diamond&#8217;s negotiation tools every day.&#8217; Christian Hernandez, venture capitalist and former Head of International Business Development at Facebook</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/">Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Gathering : How We Meet and Why It Matters &#8211; Priya Parker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to create the most transformative meetings and moments &#8216;Priya Parker has created both an art and a science to gathering in ways that can bring joy and fulfilment to any meeting&#8217; Deepak Chopra &#8216;Hosts of all kinds, this is a must-read!&#8217; Chris Anderson, creator of TED &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; Being deprived of gathering has revealed just [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/">The Art of Gathering : How We Meet and Why It Matters &#8211; Priya Parker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to create the most transformative meetings and moments    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Priya Parker has created both an art and a science to gathering in ways that can bring joy and fulfilment to any meeting&#8217; Deepak Chopra     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hosts of all kinds, this is a must-read!&#8217; Chris Anderson, creator of TED    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;     </p>
<p>                    Being deprived of gathering has revealed just how important it is to us; to connect with others, collaborate, share ideas and create moving, life-affirming experiences.    </p>
<p>                    At a time when coming together is more crucial than ever, Priya Parker sets forth a human-centered approach to gathering that can help everyone create meaningful, memorable experiences in their lives, large and small, for work and for play.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on her wide expertise as a facilitator of high-powered gatherings around the world, Parker takes us inside events of all kinds to show what works, what doesn&#8217;t, and why. She investigates a wide array of gatherings &#8211; a court hearing, a flash-mob party, an Arab-Israeli summer camp &#8211; and explains how simple changes can invigorate any group experience. The result is a book full of exciting ideas of real-world applications and one that will forever alter the way you look at your next business meeting, dinner party and garden barbecue.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A long overdue and urgent manifesto&#8217; Seth Godin, New York Times bestselling author of This is Marketing</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/">The Art of Gathering : How We Meet and Why It Matters &#8211; Priya Parker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon    </p>
<p>                    For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With vivid stories of his closed-door sessions with warring political groups, disputing businesspeople, and families in crisis, Daniel Shapiro presents a universally applicable method to successfully navigate conflict.  A deep, provocative book to reflect on and wrestle with, this book can change your life.    </p>
<p>                     Be warned: This book is not a quick fix. Real change takes work. You will learn how to master five emotional dynamics that can sabotage conflict outside your awareness:    </p>
<p>                    1. Vertigo: How can you avoid      getting emotionally consumed in conflict?<br />
                    2. Repetition compulsion: How can you stop      repeating the same conflicts again and again?<br />
                    3. Taboos: How can you discuss      sensitive issues at the heart of the conflict?<br />
                    4. Assault on the sacred: What should you do if      your values feel threatened?<br />
                    5. Identity politics: What can you do if      others use politics against you?     </p>
<p>                    In our era of discontent, this is just the book we need to resolve conflict in our own lives and in the world around us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A World In Disarray : American Foreign Policy and the Crisis of the Old Order &#8211; Richard Haass (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A valuable primer on foreign policy: a primer that concerned citizens of all political persuasions&#8211;not to mention the president and his advisers&#8211;could benefit from reading.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times An examination of a world increasingly defined by disorder and a United States unable to shape the world in its image, from the president of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/">A World In Disarray : American Foreign Policy and the Crisis of the Old Order &#8211; Richard Haass (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A valuable primer on foreign policy: a primer that concerned citizens of all political persuasions&#8211;not to mention the president and his advisers&#8211;could benefit from reading.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times An examination of a world increasingly defined by disorder and a United States unable to shape the world in its image, from the president of the Council on Foreign Relations Things fall apart; the center cannot hold. The rules, policies, and institutions that have guided the world since World War II have largely run their course. Respect for sovereignty alone cannot uphold order in an age defined by global challenges from terrorism and the spread of nuclear weapons to climate change and cyberspace. Meanwhile, great power rivalry is returning. Weak states pose problems just as confounding as strong ones. The United States remains the world&#8217;s strongest country, but American foreign policy has at times made matters worse, both by what the U.S. has done and by what it has failed to do. The Middle East is in chaos, Asia is threatened by China&#8217;s rise and a reckless North Korea, and Europe, for decades the world&#8217;s most stable region, is now anything but. As Richard Haass explains, the election of Donald Trump and the unexpected vote for &#8220;Brexit&#8221; signals that many in modern democracies reject important aspects of globalization, including borders open to trade and immigrants.  In A World in Disarray, Haass argues for an updated global operating system&#8211;call it world order 2.0&#8211;that reflects the reality that power is widely distributed and that borders count for less. One critical element of this adjustment will be adopting a new approach to sovereignty, one that embraces its obligations and responsibilities as well as its rights and protections. Haass also details how the U.S. should act towards China and Russia, as well as in Asia, Europe, and the Middle East. He suggests, too, what the country should do to address its dysfunctional politics, mounting debt, and the lack of agreement on the nature of its relationship with the world.  A World in Disarray is a wise examination, one rich in history, of the current world, along with how we got here and what needs doing. Haass shows that the world cannot have stability or prosperity without the United States, but that the United States cannot be a force for global stability and prosperity without its politicians and citizens reaching a new understanding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/">A World In Disarray : American Foreign Policy and the Crisis of the Old Order &#8211; Richard Haass (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Back Channel to Cuba : The Hidden History of Negotiations between Washington and Havana, Updated Edition &#8211; William M. Leogrande, Peter Kornbluh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>History is being made in U.S.-Cuban relations. Now updated to tell the story behind the stunning December 17, 2014, announcement by President Obama and President Castro of their move to restore full diplomatic relations, this powerful book is essential to understanding ongoing efforts towards normalization. Challenging the conventional wisdom of perpetual conflict and aggression between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/">Back Channel to Cuba : The Hidden History of Negotiations between Washington and Havana, Updated Edition &#8211; William M. Leogrande, Peter Kornbluh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>History is being made in U.S.-Cuban relations. Now updated to tell the story behind the stunning December 17, 2014, announcement by President Obama and President Castro of their move to restore full diplomatic relations, this powerful book is essential to understanding ongoing efforts towards normalization. Challenging the conventional wisdom of perpetual conflict and aggression between the United States and Cuba since 1959, Back Channel to Cuba chronicles a surprising, untold history of bilateral efforts toward rapprochement and reconciliation. William M. LeoGrande and Peter Kornbluh here present a remarkably new and relevant account, describing how, despite the intense political clamor surrounding efforts to improve relations with Havana, negotiations have been conducted by every presidential administration since Eisenhower&#8217;s through secret, back-channel diplomacy. From John F. Kennedy&#8217;s offering of an olive branch to Fidel Castro after the missile crisis, to Henry Kissinger&#8217;s top secret quest for normalization, to Barack Obama&#8217;s promise of a new approach, LeoGrande and Kornbluh uncovered hundreds of formerly secret U.S. documents and conducted interviews with dozens of negotiators, intermediaries, and policy makers, including Fidel Castro and Jimmy Carter. They reveal a fifty-year record of dialogue and negotiations, both open and furtive, that provides the historical foundation for the dramatic breakthrough in U.S.-Cuba ties.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/">Back Channel to Cuba : The Hidden History of Negotiations between Washington and Havana, Updated Edition &#8211; William M. Leogrande, Peter Kornbluh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Grand Strategy &#8211; John Lewis Gaddis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-grand-strategy-john-lewis-gaddis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-grand-strategy-john-lewis-gaddis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A training manual for our troubled times &#8230; It makes sense of our world, but is also capable of beautifully crafted pithy historical judgements. &#8230; It is a book that cares about liberty, choice and a moral compass, that warns against hubris&#8217; Roger Boyes, The Times John Lewis Gaddis, the distinguished historian and acclaimed author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-grand-strategy-john-lewis-gaddis-abridged/">On Grand Strategy &#8211; John Lewis Gaddis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A training manual for our troubled times &#8230; It  makes sense of our world, but is also capable of beautifully crafted  pithy historical judgements. &#8230; It is a book that cares about liberty,  choice and a moral compass, that warns against hubris&#8217; Roger Boyes, The Times    </p>
<p>                    John Lewis Gaddis, the distinguished historian and acclaimed author of The Cold War,   has for almost two decades co-taught the grand strategy seminar at  Yale  University with his colleagues Charles Hill and Paul Kennedy. Now,  in On Grand Strategy, Gaddis reflects with insight and wit on what he has learned.    </p>
<p>                    In   chapters extending from the ancient world through World War II, Gaddis   assesses grand strategic theory and practice in Herodotus, Thucydides,   Sun Tzu, Octavian/Augustus, Saint Augustine, Machiavelli,Elizabeth I,   Philip II, the American Founding Fathers, Clausewitz, Tolstoy,Lincoln,   Wilson, Franklin D. Roosevelt, and Isaiah Berlin.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;For the past 16 years Gaddis has taught a course on grand strategy to   students at Yale University. Reading his book, you wish every  university  could offer it. Gaddis roves across the centuries, offering  advice on  subjects from statecraft and warfare to leading a worthwhile  life&#8217;  Phillip Delves Broughton, Evening Standard</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-grand-strategy-john-lewis-gaddis-abridged/">On Grand Strategy &#8211; John Lewis Gaddis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Run The World &#8211; Parag Khanna (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-run-the-world-parag-khanna-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-run-the-world-parag-khanna-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a stunning and provocative guide to the future of international relations&#8211;a system for managing global problems beyond the stalemates of business versus government, East versus West, rich versus poor, democracy versus authoritarianism, free markets versus state capitalism. Written by the most esteemed and innovative adventurer-scholar of his generation, Parag Khanna&#8217;s &#8220;How to Run [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-run-the-world-parag-khanna-abridged/">How To Run The World &#8211; Parag Khanna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here is a stunning and provocative guide to the future of international relations&#8211;a system for managing global problems beyond the stalemates of business versus government, East versus West, rich versus poor, democracy versus authoritarianism, free markets versus state capitalism. Written by the most esteemed and innovative adventurer-scholar of his generation, Parag Khanna&#8217;s &#8220;How to Run the World&#8221; posits a chaotic modern era that resembles the Middle Ages, with Asian empires, Western militaries, Middle Eastern sheikhdoms, magnetic city-states, wealthy multinational corporations, elite clans, religious zealots, tribal hordes, and potent media seething in an ever more unpredictable and dangerous storm. But just as that initial &#8220;dark age&#8221; ended with the Renaissance, Khanna believes that our time can become a great and enlightened age as well&#8211;only, though, if we harness our technology and connectedness to forge new networks among governments, businesses, and civic interest groups to tackle the crises of today and avert those of tomorrow.<br />
                    With his trademark energy, intellect, and wit, Khanna reveals how a new &#8220;mega-diplomacy&#8221; consisting of coalitions among motivated technocrats, influential executives, super-philanthropists, cause-mopolitan activists, and everyday churchgoers can assemble the talent, pool the money, and deploy the resources to make the global economy fairer, rebuild failed states, combat terrorism, promote good governance, deliver food, water, health care, and education to those in need, and prevent environmental collapse. With examples taken from the smartest capital cities, most progressive boardrooms, and frontline NGOs, Khanna shows how mega-diplomacy is more than an ad hoc approach to running a world where no one is in charge&#8211;it is the playbook for creating a stable and self-correcting world for future generations.<br />
                    &#8220;How to Run the World&#8221; is the cutting-edge manifesto for diplomacy in a borderless world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-run-the-world-parag-khanna-abridged/">How To Run The World &#8211; Parag Khanna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
