<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Christian Spirituality &amp; Religious Experience Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/christian-spirituality-religious-experience/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/christian-spirituality-religious-experience/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Christian Spirituality &amp; Religious Experience Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/christian-spirituality-religious-experience/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Unmasking The Devil &#8211; John Ramirez</title>
		<link>/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Satanist-Turned-Evangelist Gives You the Inside Strategy to Defeat the Devil&#8217;s Plans! Many people, even Christians, deny the devil&#8217;s power. John Ramirez doesn&#8217;t have that luxury&#8211;he experienced the prince of darkness up close and personal. In the impoverished streets of the South Bronx, John Ramirez found &#8220;acceptance&#8221; from a family of witches and warlocks. These practitioners [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/">Unmasking The Devil &#8211; John Ramirez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Satanist-Turned-Evangelist Gives You the Inside Strategy to Defeat the Devil&#8217;s Plans!</p>
<p>                     Many people, even Christians, deny the devil&#8217;s power. John Ramirez doesn&#8217;t have that luxury&#8211;he experienced the prince of darkness up close and personal.</p>
<p>                     In the impoverished streets of the South Bronx, John Ramirez found &#8220;acceptance&#8221; from a family of witches and warlocks. These practitioners of dark arts trained him to be a high-ranking satanic priest&#8211;a story told in his first book, Out of the Devil&#8217;s Cauldron. However, everything changed when he met the living Christ.</p>
<p>                     In Unmasking the Devil, John Ramirez shares an insider view of how satan operates so you can avoid his traps and learn how to:<br />
                     discern between the voice of God that directs to victory and satan&#8217;s voice that leads to destruction.close the demonic doors satan uses to enter your life: entertainment, unhealthy relationships, greed, and false religion.activate the spiritual weapons of prayer, intercession, and Scripture to render hell powerless over your life.recognize how the spirits of Jezebel and Delilah attempt to infiltrate the church, create disunity, and render God&#8217;s people powerless.<br />
                     No army goes into battle without first knowing the tactics of their enemy. Receive behind-the-scene glimpses of satan&#8217;s strategies and equip yourself to live victoriously over the powers of darkness! </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Spiritual warfare is a must for every Christian if they are going to survive in the coming years,&#8221; says John Ramirez. &#8220;It&#8217;s time to stop playing patty-cake with the devil and learn how to put hell on notice.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/">Unmasking The Devil &#8211; John Ramirez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus : How the Jewish Words of Jesus Can Change Your Life &#8211; Lois Tverberg</title>
		<link>/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aspects Of Religion (non-Christian)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus, Lois Tverberg challenges readers to follow their Rabbi more closely by reexamining his words in the light of their Jewish context. Doing so will provide a richer, deeper understanding of his ministry, compelling us to live differently, to become more Christ-like. We&#8217;ll begin to understand why his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/">Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus : How the Jewish Words of Jesus Can Change Your Life &#8211; Lois Tverberg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus, Lois Tverberg challenges readers to follow their Rabbi more closely by reexamining his words in the light of their Jewish context. Doing so will provide a richer, deeper understanding of his ministry, compelling us to live differently, to become more Christ-like. We&#8217;ll begin to understand why his first Jewish disciples abandoned everything to follow him, to live out his commands.    </p>
<p>                    Our modern society, with its individualism and materialism, is very different than the tight-knit, family-oriented setting Jesus lived and taught in. What wisdom can we glean from his Eastern, biblical attitude toward life? How can knowing Jesus within this context shed light on his teachings for us today?    </p>
<p>                    In Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus we&#8217;ll journey back in time to eavesdrop on the conversations that arose among the rabbis of Jesus&#8217; day, and consider how hearing Rabbi Jesus with the ears of a first-century disciple can bring new meaning to our faith. And we&#8217;ll listen to Jewish thinkers through the ages, discovering how ideas that germinated in Jesus&#8217; time have borne fruit. Doing so will yield fresh, practical insights for following our Rabbi&#8217;s teachings from a Jewish point of view.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/">Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus : How the Jewish Words of Jesus Can Change Your Life &#8211; Lois Tverberg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let God Change Your Life &#8211; Greg Laurie</title>
		<link>/let-god-change-your-life-greg-laurie/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-god-change-your-life-greg-laurie/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Evangelist Greg Laurie calls all Christians back to radical New Testament living in his latest offering, Let God Change Your Life. Imagine what it would have been like to be a follower of Jesus; first-century Christians walked away from their old lives just to be where He was. What they learned, sitting at His feet, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-god-change-your-life-greg-laurie/">Let God Change Your Life &#8211; Greg Laurie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Evangelist Greg Laurie calls all Christians back to radical New Testament living in his latest offering, Let God Change Your Life. Imagine what it would have been like to be a follower of Jesus; first-century Christians walked away from their old lives just to be where He was. What they learned, sitting at His feet, was discipleship. And when His work on earth was done, first-century Christians took His words and example and spread out, teaching the gospel to everyone. The good news is that we, too, can participate in this lifestyle. Laurie drills it down in three simple ideas: get to know Jesus, follow His plan for discipleship, and use it to tell others what we know. Laurie&#8217;s tone is clear, direct, and biblical.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-god-change-your-life-greg-laurie/">Let God Change Your Life &#8211; Greg Laurie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Road Back to You : An Enneagram Journey to Self-Discovery &#8211; Ian Morgan Cron, Suzanne Stabile (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over 750,000 Copies Sold Worldwide! Foreword INDIES Book of the Year Awards Finalist Missio Alliance Essential Reading List Ignorance is bliss-except in self-awareness. What you don&#8217;t know about yourself can hurt you and your relationships-and even keep you in the shallows with God. Do you want help figuring out who you are and why you&#8217;re [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/">The Road Back to You : An Enneagram Journey to Self-Discovery &#8211; Ian Morgan Cron, Suzanne Stabile (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over 750,000 Copies Sold Worldwide!    </p>
<p>                                Foreword INDIES Book of the Year Awards Finalist    </p>
<p>                    Missio Alliance Essential Reading List<br />
                             Ignorance is bliss-except in self-awareness.<br />
                    What you don&#8217;t know about yourself can hurt you and your relationships-and even keep you in the shallows with God. Do you want help figuring out who you are and why you&#8217;re stuck in the same ruts?<br />
                    The Enneagram is an ancient personality typing system with an uncanny accuracy in describing how human beings are wired, both positively and negatively. In The Road Back to You Ian Morgan Cron and Suzanne Stabile forge a unique approach-a practical, comprehensive way of accessing Enneagram wisdom and exploring its connections with Christian spirituality for a deeper knowledge of ourselves, compassion for others, and love for God.<br />
                    Witty and filled with stories, this book allows you to peek inside each of the nine Enneagram types, keeping you turning the pages long after you have read the chapter about your own number. Not only will you learn more about yourself, but you will also start to see the world through other people&#8217;s eyes, understanding how and why people think, feel, and act the way they do.<br />
                    Beginning with changes you can start making today, the wisdom of the Enneagram can help take you further along into who you really are-leading you into places of spiritual discovery you would never have found on your own, and paving the way to the wiser, more compassionate person you want to become.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/">The Road Back to You : An Enneagram Journey to Self-Discovery &#8211; Ian Morgan Cron, Suzanne Stabile (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Purpose Driven Life &#8211; Rick Warren (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-purpose-driven-life-rick-warren-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-purpose-driven-life-rick-warren-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rick Warren, founding pastor of Saddleback Church in Lake Forest, California, one of America&#8217;s largest and best-known churches, shows you how to lead a Purpose-Driven Life. This Miniature Edition (TM) will help you understand why you are alive and God&#8217;s amazing plan for you- both here and now, and for eternity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-purpose-driven-life-rick-warren-abridged/">The Purpose Driven Life &#8211; Rick Warren (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rick Warren, founding pastor of Saddleback Church in Lake Forest, California, one of America&#8217;s largest and best-known churches, shows you how to lead a Purpose-Driven Life. This Miniature Edition (TM) will help you understand why you are alive and God&#8217;s amazing plan for you- both here and now, and for eternity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-purpose-driven-life-rick-warren-abridged/">The Purpose Driven Life &#8211; Rick Warren (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody, Always : Becoming Love in a World Full of Setbacks and Difficult People &#8211; Bob Goff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if we stopped avoiding the difficult people in our lives and committed to simply loving everybody? What happens when we give away love like we&#8217;re made of it? In Everybody, Always, Bob Goff&#8217;s joyful New York Times bestselling follow-up to Love Does, you&#8217;ll discover the secret to living without fear, constraint, or worry. Bob [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/">Everybody, Always : Becoming Love in a World Full of Setbacks and Difficult People &#8211; Bob Goff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What if we stopped avoiding the difficult people in our lives and committed to simply loving everybody? What happens when we give away love like we&#8217;re made of it? In Everybody, Always, Bob Goff&#8217;s joyful New York Times bestselling follow-up to Love Does, you&#8217;ll discover the secret to living without fear, constraint, or worry.     </p>
<p>                    Bob teaches us that the path toward the outsized, unfettered, liberated existence we all long for is found in one simple truth: love people, even the difficult ones, without distinction and without limits.    </p>
<p>                    In Everybody, Always, Bob shows us the simple truths about life that have the power to shift our mindset forever:    </p>
<p>                    Jesus uses our blind spots to reveal himself to us<br />
                    It&#8217;s easy to love kind, lovely, humble people, but you have to tackle fear in order to love people who are difficult<br />
                    What we do with our love will become the conversations we have with God<br />
                    Dark and scary places are filled with beautiful people who need our unconditional love<br />
                    Extravagant love has extraordinary power to change lives, including our own    </p>
<p>                    Driven by Bob&#8217;s trademark storytelling, this book reveals the wisdom Bob learned&#8211;often the hard way&#8211;about what it means to love without inhibition, insecurity, or restriction. From finding the right friends to discovering the upside of failure, Everybody, Always points the way to embodying love by doing the unexpected, the intimidating, the seemingly impossible.    </p>
<p>                    Whether losing his shoes while skydiving solo or befriending a Ugandan witch doctor, Bob steps into life with a no-limits embrace of others that is as infectious as it is extraordinarily ordinary. Everybody, Always reveals how we can do the same.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/">Everybody, Always : Becoming Love in a World Full of Setbacks and Difficult People &#8211; Bob Goff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Falling Upward : A Spirituality For The Two Halves Of Life &#8211; Richard Rohr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/falling-upward-a-spirituality-for-the-two-halves-of-life-richard-rohr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/falling-upward-a-spirituality-for-the-two-halves-of-life-richard-rohr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We grow more spiritually by doing it wrong than by doing it right In Falling Upward, Fr Richard Rohr offers a new understanding of one of life&#8217;s most profound mysteries: how our failing can be the foundation for our ongoing spiritual growth. Drawing on the wisdom from time-honoured myths, heroic poems, great thinkers and sacred [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/falling-upward-a-spirituality-for-the-two-halves-of-life-richard-rohr-abridged/">Falling Upward : A Spirituality For The Two Halves Of Life &#8211; Richard Rohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We grow more spiritually by doing it wrong than by doing it right     </p>
<p>                    In Falling Upward, Fr Richard Rohr offers a new understanding of one of life&#8217;s most profound mysteries: how our failing can be the foundation for our ongoing spiritual growth. Drawing on the wisdom from time-honoured myths, heroic poems, great thinkers and sacred religious texts, the author explores the two halves of life to show that those who have fallen, failed, or &#8216;gone down&#8217; are the only ones who understand &#8216;up&#8217;. The heartbreaks, disappointments and loves of the first half of life are actually stepping stones to the spiritual joys that the second half has in store for us.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I thank God for Richard Rohr&#8217;s sage-like presence in our culture: I honestly don&#8217;t know where I&#8217;d be without it.&#8217;<br />
                    Brian Draper    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Richard Rohr at his vintage best: prophetic, pastoral, practical.&#8217;<br />
                    Cynthia Bourgeault    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A voyage into the mystery and beauty of healthy spiritual maturity.&#8217;<br />
                    Mehmet Oz, MD, host of the Dr Oz Show</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/falling-upward-a-spirituality-for-the-two-halves-of-life-richard-rohr-abridged/">Falling Upward : A Spirituality For The Two Halves Of Life &#8211; Richard Rohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
