<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Biography: Historical, Political &amp; Military Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/biography-historical-political-military/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/biography-historical-political-military/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Biography: Historical, Political &amp; Military Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/biography-historical-political-military/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cold War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*The No.1 Sunday Times Bestseller* *A BBC Between the Covers book club pick* *Shortlisted for the 2018 Baillie Gifford Prize* &#8216;THE BEST TRUE SPY STORY I HAVE EVER READ&#8217; JOHN LE CARRE An exciting Cold War story about a KGB double agent, by one of Britain&#8217;s greatest historians and the ultimate gift for anyone who [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/">The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*The No.1 Sunday Times Bestseller*<br />
                    *A BBC Between the Covers book club pick*<br />
                    *Shortlisted for the 2018 Baillie Gifford Prize*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;THE BEST TRUE SPY STORY I HAVE EVER READ&#8217; JOHN LE CARRE        </p>
<p>                    An exciting Cold War story about a KGB double agent, by one of Britain&#8217;s greatest historians and the ultimate gift for anyone who loves a good spy thriller!    </p>
<p>                    On a warm July evening in 1985, a middle-aged man stood on the pavement of a busy avenue in the heart of Moscow, holding a plastic carrier bag. In his grey suit and tie, he looked like any other Soviet citizen. The bag alone was mildly conspicuous, printed with the red logo of Safeway, the British supermarket.    </p>
<p>                    The man was a spy. A senior KGB officer, for more than a decade he had supplied his British spymasters with a stream of priceless secrets from deep within the Soviet intelligence machine. No spy had done more to damage the KGB. The Safeway bag was a signal: to activate his escape plan to be smuggled out of Soviet Russia. So began one of the boldest and most extraordinary episodes in the history of spying. Ben Macintyre reveals a tale of espionage, betrayal and raw courage that changed the course of the Cold War forever&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    BEN MACINTYRE&#8217;S NEXT BOOK AGENT SONYA IS AVAILABLE TO BUY NOW</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/">The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alexander the Great &#8211; Philip Freeman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alexander-the-great-philip-freeman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alexander-the-great-philip-freeman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Alexander the Great (Alexander III of Macedon) was one of history&#8217;s great generals, a man studied by Caesar and Napoleon, among hundreds of others. He was born to the king of Macedon and educated by Aristotle, whose inquiring mind Alexander appreciated. After his father, Philip II, was assassinated, the 19-year-old Alexander succeeded to the throne [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alexander-the-great-philip-freeman-abridged/">Alexander the Great &#8211; Philip Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Alexander the Great (Alexander III of Macedon) was one of history&#8217;s great generals, a man studied by Caesar and Napoleon, among hundreds of others. He was born to the king of Macedon and educated by Aristotle, whose inquiring mind Alexander appreciated. After his father, Philip II, was assassinated, the 19-year-old Alexander succeeded to the throne and swiftly consolidated power. Over the next 13 years until his death at age 32, Alexander created one of the great empires of history, covering an area as far south as Egypt and as far east as Afghanistan and India. Most of the world that he conquered had been the province of the Persian Empire. Upon his death his empire was broken up and ruled by his generals, the best known were the Ptolemies, who ruled Egypt until Cleopatra was defeated by Caesar. Alexandria, Egypt and many other Alexandrias throughout that part of the world were named in his honour.     </p>
<p>                    Alexander&#8217;s greatest influence was not his leadership (his empire was eventually conquered by Rome), but spreading Greek culture throughout the lands east of the Mediterranean. He is the reason that gold coins from Afghanistan depicted Greek gods and heroes until as recently as several centuries ago. It is because of Alexander that St. Paul, a Jew who lived in modern-day Syria before travelling to modern-day Israel, spoke Greek, and it is because of Alexander that the earliest Christian documents, including the scriptures, were written in Greek.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alexander-the-great-philip-freeman-abridged/">Alexander the Great &#8211; Philip Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benjamin Franklin : An American Life &#8211; Walter Isaacson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/benjamin-franklin-an-american-life-walter-isaacson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dictionaries Of Biography (Who's Who)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/benjamin-franklin-an-american-life-walter-isaacson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>During his 84-year life Benjamin Franklin was America&#8217;s best scientist, inventor, publisher, business strategist, diplomat, and writer. He was also one of its most practical political thinkers. America&#8217;s first great publicist, he carefully crafted his own persona, portrayed it in public and polished it for posterity. In this riveting new biography Walter Isaacson provides readers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/benjamin-franklin-an-american-life-walter-isaacson-abridged/">Benjamin Franklin : An American Life &#8211; Walter Isaacson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During his 84-year life Benjamin Franklin was America&#8217;s best scientist, inventor, publisher, business strategist, diplomat, and writer. He was also one of its most practical political thinkers. America&#8217;s first great publicist, he carefully crafted his own persona, portrayed it in public and polished it for posterity. In this riveting new biography Walter Isaacson provides readers with a full portrait of Franklin&#8217;s public and private life &#8211; his loyal but neglected wife, his bastard son with whom he broke over going to war with England, his endless replacement families and his many amorous, but probably unconsummated, liaisons. But this is not just a biography of Benjamin Franklin but rather a fascinating look at American and European political history at that time. Isaacson examines the run up to the Revolutionary War, the intimate relations between Britain, France and the colonies and the decisive events that led to America&#8217;s independence. Just as David McCullough brought life to the historic figure of John Adams, Isaacson portrays Franklin in the flesh, showing readers how this radical man helped define America&#8217;s national character and personality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/benjamin-franklin-an-american-life-walter-isaacson-abridged/">Benjamin Franklin : An American Life &#8211; Walter Isaacson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge. When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality. In Leaders Eat Last, Simon [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge.    </p>
<p>                    When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality.    </p>
<p>                    In Leaders Eat Last, Simon Sinek, internationally bestselling author of Start With Why, investigates these great leaders from Marine Corps Officers, who don&#8217;t just sacrifice their place at the table but often their own comfort and even their lives for those in their care, to the heads of big business and government &#8211; each putting aside their own interests to protect their teams.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Simple and elegant, it shows us how leaders should lead&#8217; William Ury, co-author of Getting to Yes</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From a preeminent presidential historian comes a &#8220;superb and important&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) saga of America&#8217;s wartime chief executives &#8220;Fascinating and heartbreaking . . . timely . . . Beschloss&#8217;s broad scope lets you draw important crosscutting lessons about presidential leadership.&#8221;&#8211;Bill Gates Widely acclaimed and ten years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/">Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From a preeminent presidential historian comes a &#8220;superb and important&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) saga of America&#8217;s wartime chief executives    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Fascinating and heartbreaking . . . timely . . . Beschloss&#8217;s broad scope lets you draw important crosscutting lessons about presidential leadership.&#8221;&#8211;Bill Gates     </p>
<p>                    Widely acclaimed and ten years in the making, Michael Beschloss&#8217;s Presidents of War is an intimate and irresistibly readable chronicle of the Chief Executives who took the United States into conflict and mobilized it for victory. From the War of 1812 to Vietnam, we see these leaders considering the difficult decision to send hundreds of thousands of Americans to their deaths; struggling with Congress, the courts, the press, and antiwar protesters; seeking comfort from their spouses and friends; and dropping to their knees in prayer. Through Beschloss&#8217;s interviews with surviving participants and findings in original letters and once-classified national security documents, we come to understand how these Presidents were able to withstand the pressures of war&#8211;or were broken by them.     </p>
<p>                    Presidents of War combines this sense of immediacy with the overarching context of two centuries of American history, traveling from the time of our Founders, who tried to constrain presidential power, to our modern day, when a single leader has the potential to launch nuclear weapons that can destroy much of the human race.    </p>
<p>                    Praise for Presidents of War     </p>
<p>                    A marvelous narrative. . . . As Beschloss explains, the greatest wartime presidents successfully leaven military action with moral concerns. . . . Beschloss&#8217;s writing is clean and concise, and he admirably draws upon new documents. Some of the more titillating tidbits in the book are in the footnotes. . . . There are fascinating nuggets on virtually every page of Presidents of War. It is a superb and important book, superbly rendered.&#8221;&#8211;Jay Winik, The New York Times Book Review     </p>
<p>                    Sparkle and bite. . . . Valuable and engrossing study of how our chief executives have discharged the most significant of all their duties. . . . Excellent. . . . A fluent narrative that covers two centuries of national conflict.&#8221; &#8211;Richard Snow,  The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/">Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Silk to Silicon: The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives : The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives &#8211; Jeffrey E Garten (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/from-silk-to-silicon-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-jeffrey-e-garten-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/from-silk-to-silicon-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-jeffrey-e-garten-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The story of globalization, the most powerful force in history, as told through the life and times of ten people who changed the world by their singular, spectacular accomplishments. This is the first book to look at the history of globalization through the lens of individuals who did something transformative, as opposed to describing globalization [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-silk-to-silicon-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-jeffrey-e-garten-abridged/">From Silk to Silicon: The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives : The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives &#8211; Jeffrey E Garten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The story of globalization, the most powerful force in history, as told through the life and times of ten people who changed the world by their singular, spectacular accomplishments.    </p>
<p>                    This is the first book to look at the history of globalization through the lens of individuals who did something transformative, as opposed to describing globalization through trends, policies, or particular industries. From Silk to Silicon tells the story of who these men and women were, what they did, how they did it and how their achievements continue to shape our world today. They include:    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Genghis Khan, who united east and west by conquest and by opening new trade routes built on groundbreaking transportation, communications, and management innovations.    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Mayer Amschel Rothschild, who arose from an oppressive Jewish ghetto to establish the most powerful bank the world has seen, and ushered in an era of global finance.    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Cyrus Field, who became the father of global communications by leading the effort to build the transatlantic telegraph, the forerunner to global radio, TV, and the worldwide Internet.    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Margaret Thatcher, whose controversial policies opened the gusher of substantially free markets that linked economies across borders.    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Andy Grove, a Hungarian refugee from the Nazis who built the company&#8217;Intel&#8217;that figured out how to manufacture complex computer chips on a mass, commercial scale and laid the foundation for Silicon Valley&#8217;s computer revolution.    </p>
<p>                    Through these stories Jeffrey E. Garten finds the common links between these figure and probes critical questions including: How much influence can any one person have in fundamentally changing the world? And how have past trends in globalization affected the present and how will they shape the future? From Silk to Silicon is an essential book to understanding the past&#8217;and the future&#8217;of the most powerful force of our times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-silk-to-silicon-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-jeffrey-e-garten-abridged/">From Silk to Silicon: The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives : The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives &#8211; Jeffrey E Garten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gatekeepers : How the White House Chiefs of Staff Define Every Presidency &#8211; Chris Whipple (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gatekeepers-how-the-white-house-chiefs-of-staff-define-every-presidency-chris-whipple-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gatekeepers-how-the-white-house-chiefs-of-staff-define-every-presidency-chris-whipple-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now with a chapter on the chaos in the Trump administration, the New York Times bestselling, behind-the-scenes look at the White House Chiefs of Staff, whose actions&#8211;and inactions&#8211;have defined the course of our country. What do Dick Cheney and Rahm Emanuel have in common? Aside from polarizing personalities, both served as chief of staff to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gatekeepers-how-the-white-house-chiefs-of-staff-define-every-presidency-chris-whipple-abridged/">The Gatekeepers : How the White House Chiefs of Staff Define Every Presidency &#8211; Chris Whipple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now with a chapter on the chaos in the Trump administration, the New York Times bestselling, behind-the-scenes look at the White House Chiefs of Staff, whose actions&#8211;and inactions&#8211;have defined the course of our country.     </p>
<p>                     What do Dick Cheney and Rahm Emanuel have in common? Aside from polarizing personalities, both served as chief of staff to the president of the United States&#8211;as did Donald Rumsfeld, Leon Panetta, and a relative handful of others. The chiefs of staff, often referred to as the gatekeepers, wield tremendous power in Washington and beyond; they decide who is allowed to see the president, negotiate with Congress to push POTUS&#8217;s agenda, and&#8211;most crucially&#8211;enjoy unparalleled access to the leader of the free world. Each chief can make or break an administration, and each president reveals himself by the chief he picks.     </p>
<p>                     Through extensive, intimate interviews with eighteen living chiefs (including Reince Priebus) and two former presidents, award-winning journalist and producer Chris Whipple pulls back the curtain on this unique fraternity. In doing so, he revises our understanding of presidential history, showing us how James Baker&#8217;s expert managing of the White House, the press, and Capitol Hill paved the way for the Reagan Revolution&#8211;and, conversely, how Watergate, the Iraq War, and even the bungled Obamacare rollout might have been prevented by a more effective chief.     </p>
<p>                     Filled with shrewd analysis and never-before-reported details, The Gatekeepers offers an essential portrait of the toughest job in Washington.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gatekeepers-how-the-white-house-chiefs-of-staff-define-every-presidency-chris-whipple-abridged/">The Gatekeepers : How the White House Chiefs of Staff Define Every Presidency &#8211; Chris Whipple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alexander Hamilton &#8211; Ron Chernow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alexander-hamilton-ron-chernow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alexander-hamilton-ron-chernow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestseller, and the inspiration for the hit Broadway musical Hamilton! Pulitzer Prize-winning author Ron Chernow presents a landmark biography of Alexander Hamilton, the Founding Father who galvanized, inspired, scandalized, and shaped the newborn nation. Grand-scale biography at its best&#8211;thorough, insightful, consistently fair, and superbly written . . . A genuinely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alexander-hamilton-ron-chernow-abridged/">Alexander Hamilton &#8211; Ron Chernow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestseller, and the inspiration for the hit Broadway musical Hamilton!    </p>
<p>                    Pulitzer Prize-winning author Ron Chernow presents a landmark biography of Alexander Hamilton, the Founding Father who galvanized, inspired, scandalized, and shaped the newborn nation.     </p>
<p>                    Grand-scale biography at its best&#8211;thorough, insightful, consistently fair, and superbly written . . . A genuinely great book. &#8211;David McCullough     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A robust full-length portrait, in my view the best ever written, of the most brilliant, charismatic and dangerous founder of them all. &#8211;Joseph Ellis    </p>
<p>                    Few figures in American history have been more hotly debated or more grossly misunderstood than Alexander Hamilton. Chernow&#8217;s biography gives Hamilton his due and sets the record straight, deftly illustrating that the political and economic greatness of today&#8217;s America is the result of Hamilton&#8217;s countless sacrifices to champion ideas that were often wildly disputed during his time. &#8220;To repudiate his legacy,&#8221; Chernow writes, &#8220;is, in many ways, to repudiate the modern world.&#8221; Chernow here recounts Hamilton&#8217;s turbulent life: an illegitimate, largely self-taught orphan from the Caribbean, he came out of nowhere to take America by storm, rising to become George Washington&#8217;s aide-de-camp in the Continental Army, coauthoring The Federalist Papers, founding the Bank of New York, leading the Federalist Party, and becoming the first Treasury Secretary of the United States.Historians have long told the story of America&#8217;s birth as the triumph of Jefferson&#8217;s democratic ideals over the aristocratic intentions of Hamilton. Chernow presents an entirely different man, whose legendary ambitions were motivated not merely by self-interest but by passionate patriotism and a stubborn will to build the foundations of American prosperity and power. His is a Hamilton far more human than we&#8217;ve encountered before&#8211;from his shame about his birth to his fiery aspirations, from his intimate relationships with childhood friends to his titanic feuds with Jefferson, Madison, Adams, Monroe, and Burr, and from his highly public affair with Maria Reynolds to his loving marriage to his loyal wife Eliza. And never before has there been a more vivid account of Hamilton&#8217;s famous and mysterious death in a duel with Aaron Burr in July of 1804.     </p>
<p>                    Chernow&#8217;s biography is not just a portrait of Hamilton, but the story of America&#8217;s birth seen through its most central figure. At a critical time to look back to our roots, Alexander Hamilton will remind readers of the purpose of our institutions and our heritage as Americans.     </p>
<p>                    9780143034759</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alexander-hamilton-ron-chernow-abridged/">Alexander Hamilton &#8211; Ron Chernow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Harriet Tubman : The Road to Freedom &#8211; Catherine Clinton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/harriet-tubman-the-road-to-freedom-catherine-clinton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American Civil War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Slavery & Abolition Of Slavery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/harriet-tubman-the-road-to-freedom-catherine-clinton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the most important and enduring figures in the history of 19th century America, the legendary conductor on the Underground Railroad whose courageous exploits have been described in countless books for young readers, is here revealed for the first time as a singular and complex character, a woman who defied simple categorisation. &#124;In this, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/harriet-tubman-the-road-to-freedom-catherine-clinton-abridged/">Harriet Tubman : The Road to Freedom &#8211; Catherine Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the most important and enduring figures in the history of 19th century America, the legendary conductor on the Underground Railroad whose courageous exploits have been described in countless books for young readers, is here revealed for the first time as a singular and complex character, a woman who defied simple categorisation. |In this, the first major biography of Harriet Tubman in more than 100 years, we see the heroine of children&#8217;s books and biopics with a new clarity and richness of detail.| &#8211; Time</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/harriet-tubman-the-road-to-freedom-catherine-clinton-abridged/">Harriet Tubman : The Road to Freedom &#8211; Catherine Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Education Of Brett Kavanaugh &#8211; Robin Pogrebin, Kate Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A remarkable work of slowed-down journalism&#8230;They are doing their jobs as journalists and writing the first draft of history. &#8211;Jill Filipovic, The Washington Post &#8230;Generous but also damning. &#8211;Hanna Rosin, The New York Times From two New York Times reporters, a deeper look at the formative years of Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh and his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/">The Education Of Brett Kavanaugh &#8211; Robin Pogrebin, Kate Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A remarkable work of slowed-down journalism&#8230;They are doing their jobs as journalists and writing the first draft of history. &#8211;Jill Filipovic, The Washington Post &#8230;Generous but also damning. &#8211;Hanna Rosin, The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    From two New York Times reporters, a deeper look at the formative years of Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh and his confirmation. In September 2018, the F.B.I. was given only a week to investigate allegations of sexual misconduct against Brett Kavanaugh, President Trump&#8217;s Supreme Court nominee. But even as Kavanaugh was sworn in to his lifetime position, many questions remained unanswered, leaving millions of Americans unsettled. During the Senate confirmation hearings that preceded the bureau&#8217;s brief probe, New York Times reporters Robin Pogrebin and Kate Kelly broke critical stories about Kavanaugh&#8217;s past, including the Renate Alumni yearbook story. They were inundated with tips from former classmates, friends, and associates that couldn&#8217;t be fully investigated before the confirmation process closed. Now, their book fills in the blanks and explores the essential question: Who is Brett Kavanaugh? The Education of Brett Kavanaugh paints a picture of the prep-school and Ivy-League worlds that formed our newest Supreme Court Justice. By offering commentary from key players from his confirmation process who haven&#8217;t yet spoken publicly and pursuing lines of inquiry that were left hanging, it will be essential reading for anyone who wants to understand our political system and Kavanaugh&#8217;s unexpectedly emblematic role in it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/">The Education Of Brett Kavanaugh &#8211; Robin Pogrebin, Kate Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Faith : A Journey for All &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/faith-a-journey-for-all-jimmy-carter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Christian Testimony & Popular Inspirational Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/faith-a-journey-for-all-jimmy-carter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful and personal reflection, a New York Times bestseller, President Jimmy Carter contemplates how faith has sustained him in happiness and disappointment and considers how we may find it in our own lives. All his life, President Jimmy Carter has been a courageous exemplar of faith. Now he shares the lessons he learned. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/faith-a-journey-for-all-jimmy-carter-abridged/">Faith : A Journey for All &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful and personal reflection, a New York Times bestseller, President Jimmy Carter contemplates how faith has sustained him in happiness and disappointment and considers how we may find it in our own lives.     </p>
<p>                    All his life, President Jimmy Carter has been a courageous exemplar of faith. Now he shares the lessons he learned. He writes, &#8220;The issue of faith arises in almost every area of human existence, so it is important to understand its multiple meanings. In this book, my primary goal is to explore the broader meaning of faith, its far-reaching effect on our lives, and its relationship to past, present, and future events in America and around the world. The religious aspects of faith are also covered, since this is how the word is most often used, and I have included a description of the ways my faith has guided and sustained me, as well as how it has challenged and driven me to seek a closer and better relationship with people and with God.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Quoting eminent Protestant theologians, in Faith President Carter describes his belief in religious freedom, moral politics, and the place of prayer in his daily life. He examines faith&#8217;s many meanings, he describes how to accept it, live it, how to doubt and find faith again. This is a serious and moving reflection from one of America&#8217;s most admired and respected citizens.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/faith-a-journey-for-all-jimmy-carter-abridged/">Faith : A Journey for All &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Autobiography &#8211; M. K. Gandhi, Translated by Mahadev Desai, Introduction by Sunil Khilnani (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-autobiography-m-k-gandhi-translated-by-mahadev-desai-introduction-by-sunil-khilnani-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Liberation & Independence, Post-colonialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-autobiography-m-k-gandhi-translated-by-mahadev-desai-introduction-by-sunil-khilnani-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gandhi&#8217;s non-violent struggles against racism, violence, and colonialism in South Africa and India had brought him to such a level of notoriety, adulation that when asked to write an autobiography midway through his career, he took it as an opportunity to explain himself. He feared the enthusiasm for his ideas tended to exceed a deeper [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-autobiography-m-k-gandhi-translated-by-mahadev-desai-introduction-by-sunil-khilnani-abridged/">An Autobiography &#8211; M. K. Gandhi, Translated by Mahadev Desai, Introduction by Sunil Khilnani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gandhi&#8217;s non-violent struggles against racism, violence, and colonialism in South Africa and India had brought him to such a level of notoriety, adulation that when asked to write an autobiography midway through his career, he took it as an opportunity to explain himself.  He feared the enthusiasm for his ideas tended to exceed a deeper understanding of his quest for truth rooted in devotion to God. His attempts to get closer to this divine power led him to seek purity through simple living, dietary practices, celibacy, and a life without violence. This is not a straightforward narrative biography, in The Story of My Experiments with Truth, Gandhi offers his life story as a reference for those who would follow in his footsteps.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-autobiography-m-k-gandhi-translated-by-mahadev-desai-introduction-by-sunil-khilnani-abridged/">An Autobiography &#8211; M. K. Gandhi, Translated by Mahadev Desai, Introduction by Sunil Khilnani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years and now the longest-serving independent in U.S. political history. An extensive afterword by The Nation&#8217;s National Affairs correspondent John Nichols continues the story with Sanders&#8217;s entrance into the Senate, the drama of the 2016 Democratic Primary, his ongoing resistance to Trump, and the thrilling launch of his 2020 bid for the White House. A new foreword by Nina Turner, former president of Our Revolution and co-chair of the Sanders for President campaign, provides a rare glimpse of Bernie as a person. Outsider in the White House tells the story of a passionate and principled political life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bully Pulpit : Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, and the Golden Age of Journalism &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the Best Books of the Year as chosen by The New York Times, The Washington Post, The Economist, Time, USA TODAY, Christian Science Monitor, and more. &#8220;A tale so gripping that one questions the need for fiction when real life is so plump with drama and intrigue&#8221; (Associated Press). Doris Kearns Goodwin&#8217;s The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">The Bully Pulpit : Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, and the Golden Age of Journalism &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the Best Books of the Year as chosen by The New York Times, The Washington Post, The Economist, Time, USA TODAY, Christian Science Monitor, and more. &#8220;A tale so gripping that one questions the need for fiction when real life is so plump with drama and intrigue&#8221; (Associated Press).     </p>
<p>                    Doris Kearns Goodwin&#8217;s The Bully Pulpit is a dynamic history of the first decade of the Progressive era, that tumultuous time when the nation was coming unseamed and reform was in the air.     </p>
<p>                    The story is told through the intense friendship of Theodore Roosevelt and William Howard Taft&#8211;a close relationship that strengthens both men before it ruptures in 1912, when they engage in a brutal fight for the presidential nomination that divides their wives, their children, and their closest friends, while crippling the progressive wing of the Republican Party, causing Democrat Woodrow Wilson to be elected, and changing the country&#8217;s history.     </p>
<p>                    The Bully Pulpit is also the story of the muckraking press, which arouses the spirit of reform that helps Roosevelt push the government to shed its laissez-faire attitude toward robber barons, corrupt politicians, and corporate exploiters of our natural resources. The muckrakers are portrayed through the greatest group of journalists ever assembled at one magazine&#8211;Ida Tarbell, Ray Stannard Baker, Lincoln Steffens, and William Allen White&#8211;teamed under the mercurial genius of publisher S.S. McClure.     </p>
<p>                    Goodwin&#8217;s narrative is founded upon a wealth of primary materials. The correspondence of more than four hundred letters between Roosevelt and Taft begins in their early thirties and ends only months before Roosevelt&#8217;s death. Edith Roosevelt and Nellie Taft kept diaries. The muckrakers wrote hundreds of letters to one another, kept journals, and wrote their memoirs. The letters of Captain Archie Butt, who served as a personal aide to both Roosevelt and Taft, provide an intimate view of both men.     </p>
<p>                    The Bully Pulpit, like Goodwin&#8217;s brilliant chronicles of the Civil War and World War II, exquisitely demonstrates her distinctive ability to combine scholarly rigor with accessibility. It is a major work of history&#8211;an examination of leadership in a rare moment of activism and reform that brought the country closer to its founding ideals.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">The Bully Pulpit : Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, and the Golden Age of Journalism &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestselling &#8220;deep dive into the terms of eight former presidents is chock-full of political hijinks-and deja vu&#8221; (Vanity Fair) and provides a fascinating look at the men who came to the office without being elected to it, showing how each affected the nation and world. The strength and prestige of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/">Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestselling &#8220;deep dive into the terms of eight former presidents is chock-full of political hijinks-and deja vu&#8221; (Vanity Fair) and provides a fascinating look at the men who came to the office without being elected to it, showing how each affected the nation and world.    </p>
<p>                    The strength and prestige of the American presidency has waxed and waned since George Washington. Eight men have succeeded to the presidency when the incumbent died in office. In one way or another they vastly changed our history. Only Theodore Roosevelt would have been elected in his own right. Only TR, Truman, Coolidge, and LBJ were re-elected.    </p>
<p>                    John Tyler succeeded William Henry Harrison who died 30 days into his term. He was kicked out of his party and became the first president threatened with impeachment. Millard Fillmore succeeded esteemed General Zachary Taylor. He immediately sacked the entire cabinet and delayed an inevitable Civil War by standing with Henry Clay&#8217;s compromise of 1850. Andrew Johnson, who succeeded our greatest president, sided with remnants of the Confederacy in Reconstruction. Chester Arthur, the embodiment of the spoils system, was so reviled as James Garfield&#8217;s successor that he had to defend himself against plotting Garfield&#8217;s assassination; but he reformed the civil service. Theodore Roosevelt broke up the trusts. Calvin Coolidge silently cooled down the Harding scandals and preserved the White House for the Republican Herbert Hoover and the Great Depression. Harry Truman surprised everybody when he succeeded the great FDR and proved an able and accomplished president. Lyndon B. Johnson was named to deliver Texas electorally. He led the nation forward on Civil Rights but failed on Vietnam.    </p>
<p>                    Accidental Presidents shows that &#8220;history unfolds in death as well as in life&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal) and adds immeasurably to our understanding of the power and limits of the American presidency in critical times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/">Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For more than a year, Hillary Clinton has laid out an ambitious agenda to improve the lives of the American people and make the country stronger and safer. Stronger Together presents that agenda in full, relating stories from the American people and outlining the Clinton/Kaine campaign&#8217;s plans on everything from apprenticeships to the Zika virus, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/">Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For more than a year, Hillary Clinton has laid out an ambitious agenda to improve the lives of the American people and make the country stronger and safer. Stronger Together presents that agenda in full, relating stories from the American people and outlining the Clinton/Kaine campaign&#8217;s plans on everything from apprenticeships to the Zika virus, including:<br />
                     -Building an economy that works for everyone.<br />
                     -Making investment in good-paying jobs, including infrastructure, manufacturing, clean energy and small business.<br />
                     -Making debt-free college a reality and tackling the student debt crisis.<br />
                     -A course of action to defeat global terrorist networks and support allies.<br />
                     -Breaking down the barriers that hold Americans back by reforming a broken immigration system, ending mass incarceration, protecting voting rights, and fixing the campaign finance system.<br />
                     -Putting families first through universal, affordable health care; paid family and medical leave, and affordable child care.<br />
                        Stronger Together offers specific solutions and a bold vision for building a more perfect union.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/">Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First They Killed My Father : A Daughter of Cambodia Remembers &#8211; Loung Ung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/first-they-killed-my-father-a-daughter-of-cambodia-remembers-loung-ung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Postwar 20th Century History, From C 1945 To C 2000]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-they-killed-my-father-a-daughter-of-cambodia-remembers-loung-ung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major film, co-written and directed by Angelina Jolie Pitt Until the age of five, Loung Ung lived in Phnom Penh, one of seven children of a high-ranking government official. She was a precocious child who loved the open city markets, fried crickets, chicken fights and being cheeky to her parents. When [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-they-killed-my-father-a-daughter-of-cambodia-remembers-loung-ung-abridged/">First They Killed My Father : A Daughter of Cambodia Remembers &#8211; Loung Ung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major film, co-written and directed by Angelina Jolie Pitt    </p>
<p>                    Until the age of five, Loung Ung lived in Phnom Penh, one of seven children of a high-ranking government official. She was a precocious child who loved the open city markets, fried crickets, chicken fights and being cheeky to her parents.    </p>
<p>                    When Pol Pot&#8217;s Khmer Rouge army stormed into Phnom Penh in April 1975, Loung&#8217;s family fled their home and were eventually forced to disperse to survive. Loung was trained as a child soldier while her brothers and sisters were sent to labour camps. The surviving siblings were only finally reunited after the Vietnamese penetrated Cambodia and started to destroy the Khmer Rouge.    </p>
<p>                    Bolstered by the bravery of one brother, the vision of the others and the gentle kindness of her sister, Loung forged on to create for herself a courageous new life.    </p>
<p>                    First They Killed My Father is an unforgettable book told through the voice of the young and fearless Loung. It is a shocking and tragic tale of a girl who was determined to survive despite the odds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-they-killed-my-father-a-daughter-of-cambodia-remembers-loung-ung-abridged/">First They Killed My Father : A Daughter of Cambodia Remembers &#8211; Loung Ung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Long Way Gone : The True Story of a Child Soldier &#8211; Ishmael Beah (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-long-way-gone-the-true-story-of-a-child-soldier-ishmael-beah-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True War & Combat Stories]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-long-way-gone-the-true-story-of-a-child-soldier-ishmael-beah-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first-person account of a 26-year-old who fought in the war in Sierra Leone as a 12-year-old boy. &#8216;My new friends have begun to suspect that I haven&#8217;t told them the full story of my life. &#8220;Why did you leave Sierra Leone?&#8221; &#8220;Because there is a war.&#8221; &#8220;You mean, you saw people running around with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-long-way-gone-the-true-story-of-a-child-soldier-ishmael-beah-abridged/">A Long Way Gone : The True Story of a Child Soldier &#8211; Ishmael Beah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first-person account of a 26-year-old who fought in the war in Sierra Leone as a 12-year-old boy.    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;My new friends have begun to suspect that I haven&#8217;t told them the full story of my life.<br />
                    &#8220;Why did you leave Sierra Leone?&#8221;<br />
                    &#8220;Because there is a war.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8220;You mean, you saw people running around with guns and shooting each other?&#8221;<br />
                    &#8220;Yes, all the time.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8220;Cool.&#8221;<br />
                    I smile a little.<br />
                    &#8220;You should tell us about it sometime.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8220;Yes, sometime.&#8221;&#8216;    </p>
<p>                              This is how wars are fought now: by children, hopped-up on drugs and wielding AK-47s. There are more than fifty conflicts going on worldwide and it is estimated there are some 300,000 child soldiers fighting. Ishmael Beah used to be one of them.    </p>
<p>                              What is war like through the eyes of a child soldier? How does one become a killer? How does one stop? Child soldiers have been profiled by journalists, and novelists have struggled to imagine their lives. But until now, there has not been a first-person account from someone who came through this hell and survived. Ishmael Beah, now twenty-five years old, tells a riveting story: how at the age of twelve in Sierra Leone, he fled attacking rebels and wandered a land rendered unrecognizable by violence. By thirteen, he&#8217;d been picked up by the government army, and Beah, at heart a gentle boy, found he was capable of truly terrible acts.    </p>
<p>                              This is a rare and mesmerizing account, told with real literary force and heartbreaking honesty.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-long-way-gone-the-true-story-of-a-child-soldier-ishmael-beah-abridged/">A Long Way Gone : The True Story of a Child Soldier &#8211; Ishmael Beah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team of Rivals : The Political Genius of Abraham Lincoln &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/team-of-rivals-the-political-genius-of-abraham-lincoln-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/team-of-rivals-the-political-genius-of-abraham-lincoln-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling and prize-winning study of one of the most legendary American Presidents in history, Team of Rivals by Doris Kearns Goodwin is the book that inspired Barack Obama in his presidency. When Barack Obama was asked which book he could not live without in the White House, his answer was instant: Team of Rivals. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-rivals-the-political-genius-of-abraham-lincoln-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">Team of Rivals : The Political Genius of Abraham Lincoln &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling and prize-winning study of one of the most legendary American Presidents in history, Team of Rivals by Doris Kearns Goodwin is the book that inspired Barack Obama in his presidency.    </p>
<p>                    When Barack Obama was asked which book he could not live without in the White House, his answer was instant: Team of Rivals. This monumental and brilliant work has given Obama the model for his presidency, showing how Abraham Lincoln saved America by appointing his fiercest rival to key cabinet positions. As well as a thrilling piece of narrative history, it&#8217;s an inspiring study of one of the greatest leaders the world has ever seen.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wonderful book . . . a remarkable study in leadership&#8217; Barack Obama    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A portrait of Lincoln as a virtuosic politician and managerial genius&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I have not enjoyed a history book as much for years&#8217; Robert Harris    </p>
<p>                    Doris Kearns Goodwin is the doyenne of US presidential historians, and one of the most acclaimed non-fiction authors in the world. Her works include Lyndon Johnson and the American Dream, The Fitzgeralds and the Kennedys: An American Saga, and No Ordinary Time: Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt, for which she won the Pulitzer Prize for History in 1995.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-rivals-the-political-genius-of-abraham-lincoln-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">Team of Rivals : The Political Genius of Abraham Lincoln &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tesla: Man out of Time : Man out of Time &#8211; Margaret Cheney (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tesla-man-out-of-time-man-out-of-time-margaret-cheney-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tesla-man-out-of-time-man-out-of-time-margaret-cheney-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In `Tesla: Man Out of Time, ` Margaret Cheney explores the brilliant and prescient mind of one of the twentieth century&#8217;s greatest scientists and inventors. Called a madman by his enemies, a genius by others, and an enigma by nearly everyone, Nikola Tesla was, without a doubt, a trailblazing inventor who created astonishing, sometimes world-transforming [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tesla-man-out-of-time-man-out-of-time-margaret-cheney-abridged/">Tesla: Man out of Time : Man out of Time &#8211; Margaret Cheney (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In `Tesla: Man Out of Time, ` Margaret Cheney explores the brilliant and prescient mind of one of the twentieth century&#8217;s greatest scientists and inventors. Called a madman by his enemies, a genius by others, and an enigma by nearly everyone, Nikola Tesla was, without a doubt, a trailblazing inventor who created astonishing, sometimes world-transforming devices that were virtually without theoretical precedent. Tesla not only discovered the rotating magnetic field &#8212; the basis of most alternating-current machinery &#8212; but also introduced us to the fundamentals of robotics, computers, and missile science. Almost supernaturally gifted, unfailingly flamboyant and neurotic, Tesla was troubled by an array of compulsions and phobias and was fond of extravagant, visionary experimentations. He was also a popular man-about-town, admired by men as diverse as Mark Twain and George Westinghouse, and adored by scores of society beauties.  From Tesla&#8217;s childhood in Yugoslavia to his death in New York in the 1940s, Cheney paints a compelling human portrait and chronicles a lifetime of discoveries that radically altered &#8212; and continue to alter &#8212; the world in which we live. `Tesla: Man Out of Time` is an in-depth look at the seminal accomplishments of a scientific wizard and a thoughtful examination of the obsessions and eccentricities of the man behind the science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tesla-man-out-of-time-man-out-of-time-margaret-cheney-abridged/">Tesla: Man out of Time : Man out of Time &#8211; Margaret Cheney (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Spy Among Friends : Philby and the Great Betrayal &#8211; Ben Macintyre (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-spy-among-friends-philby-and-the-great-betrayal-ben-macintyre-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cold War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-spy-among-friends-philby-and-the-great-betrayal-ben-macintyre-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A SUNDAY TIMES No. 1 BESTSELLER WITH AN AFTERWORD BY JOHN LE CARRE &#8216;Riveting, astounding &#8230; An unputdownable postwar thriller&#8217; Observer &#8216;Irresistibly readable&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Worthy of John le Carre at his best&#8217; John Banville, Guardian &#8216;Hugely engrossing &#8230; Both authoritative and enthralling&#8217; William Boyd ________________ Kim Philby was the most notorious British defector and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-spy-among-friends-philby-and-the-great-betrayal-ben-macintyre-abridged/">A Spy Among Friends : Philby and the Great Betrayal &#8211; Ben Macintyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A SUNDAY TIMES No. 1 BESTSELLER<br />
                    WITH AN AFTERWORD BY JOHN LE CARRE    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Riveting, astounding &#8230; An unputdownable postwar thriller&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Irresistibly readable&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Worthy of John le Carre at his best&#8217; John Banville, Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hugely engrossing &#8230; Both authoritative and enthralling&#8217; William Boyd<br />
                    ________________    </p>
<p>                    Kim Philby was the most notorious British defector and Soviet mole in history. Agent, double agent, charmer and traitor, he betrayed every secret of Allied operations to the Russians in the early years of the Cold War. In the aftermath of the Second World War, Philby, Nicholas Elliott and James Jesus Angleton were rising stars in the intelligence world and shared every secret. Elliott and Angleton thought they knew Philby better than anyone &#8211; and then discovered they had not known him at all.    </p>
<p>                    This is a story of loyalty, trust and treachery, class and conscience, of male friendships forged, and then systematically betrayed. With access to newly released MI5 files and previously unseen papers, A Spy Among Friends unlocks what is perhaps the last great secret of the Cold War.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-spy-among-friends-philby-and-the-great-betrayal-ben-macintyre-abridged/">A Spy Among Friends : Philby and the Great Betrayal &#8211; Ben Macintyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States. &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times    </p>
<p>                    The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about social justice. As she rose to prominence as a political leader, her experiences would become her guiding light as she grappled with an array of complex issues and learned to bring a voice to the voiceless.    </p>
<p>                    Now, in The Truths We Hold, Harris reckons with the big challenges we face together. Drawing on the hard-won wisdom and insight from her own career and the work of those who have most inspired her, she communicates a vision of shared struggle, shared purpose, and shared values as we confront the great work of our day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Personal integrity shines through every page&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Queen of Fashion : What Marie Antoinette Wore to the Revolution &#8211; Caroline Weber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/queen-of-fashion-what-marie-antoinette-wore-to-the-revolution-caroline-weber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Royalty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fashion & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fashion & Textiles: Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Fashion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions, Uprisings, Rebellions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/queen-of-fashion-what-marie-antoinette-wore-to-the-revolution-caroline-weber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Washington Post Book World Best Book of the Year When her carriage first crossed over from her native Austria into France, fourteen-year-old Marie Antoinette was taken out, stripped naked before an entourage, and dressed in French attire to please the court of her new king. For a short while, the young girl played the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/queen-of-fashion-what-marie-antoinette-wore-to-the-revolution-caroline-weber-abridged/">Queen of Fashion : What Marie Antoinette Wore to the Revolution &#8211; Caroline Weber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Washington Post Book World Best Book of the Year     </p>
<p>                    When her carriage first crossed over from her native Austria into France, fourteen-year-old Marie Antoinette was taken out, stripped naked before an entourage, and dressed in French attire to please the court of her new king. For a short while, the young girl played the part.     </p>
<p>                    But by the time she took the throne, everything had changed. In Queen of Fashion,  Caroline Weber tells of the radical restyling that transformed the young queen into an icon and shaped the future of the nation. With her riding gear, her white furs, her pouf hairstyles, and her intricate ballroom disguises, Marie Antoinette came to embody&#8211;gloriously and tragically&#8211;all the extravagance of the monarchy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/queen-of-fashion-what-marie-antoinette-wore-to-the-revolution-caroline-weber-abridged/">Queen of Fashion : What Marie Antoinette Wore to the Revolution &#8211; Caroline Weber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Woman of No Importance : The Untold Story of Virginia Hall, WWII&#8217;s Most Dangerous Spy &#8211; Sonia Purnell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A METICULOUS HISTORY THAT READS LIKE A THRILLER&#8217; BEN MACINTYRE, TEN BEST BOOKS TO READ ABOUT WORLD WAR II An astounding story of heroism, spycraft, resistance and personal triumph over shocking adversity. &#8216;A rousing tale of derring-do&#8217; THE TIMES * &#8216;Riveting&#8217; MICK HERRON * &#8216;Superb&#8217; IRISH TIMES THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER In September 1941, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/">A Woman of No Importance : The Untold Story of Virginia Hall, WWII&#8217;s Most Dangerous Spy &#8211; Sonia Purnell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A METICULOUS HISTORY THAT READS LIKE A THRILLER&#8217; BEN MACINTYRE, TEN BEST BOOKS TO READ ABOUT WORLD WAR II    </p>
<p>                        An astounding story of heroism, spycraft, resistance and personal triumph over shocking adversity.    </p>
<p>                       &#8216;A rousing tale of derring-do&#8217; THE TIMES   *   &#8216;Riveting&#8217; MICK HERRON   *   &#8216;Superb&#8217; IRISH TIMES    </p>
<p>                                                                           THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    In September 1941, a young American woman strides up the steps of a hotel in Lyon, Vichy France. Her papers say she is a journalist. Her wooden leg is disguised by a determined gait and a distracting beauty. She is there to spark the resistance.    </p>
<p>                    By 1942 Virginia Hall was the Gestapo&#8217;s most urgent target, having infiltrated Vichy command, trained civilians in guerrilla warfare and sprung soldiers from Nazi prison camps. The first woman to go undercover for British SOE, her intelligence changed the course of the war &#8211; but her fight was still not over.     </p>
<p>                    This is a spy history like no other, telling the story of the hunting accident that disabled her, the discrimination she fought and the secret life that helped her triumph over shocking adversity.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A cracking story about an extraordinarily brave woman&#8217; TELEGRAPH    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Gripping &#8230; superb &#8230; a rounded portrait of a complicated, resourceful, determined and above all brave woman&#8217; IRISH TIMES    </p>
<p>                    WINNER of the PLUTARCH AWARD FOR BEST BIOGRAPHY</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/">A Woman of No Importance : The Untold Story of Virginia Hall, WWII&#8217;s Most Dangerous Spy &#8211; Sonia Purnell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Full Life : Reflections at Ninety &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his major New York Times bestseller, Jimmy Carter looks back from ninety years of age and &#8220;reveals private thoughts and recollections over a fascinating career as businessman, politician, evangelist, and humanitarian&#8221; (Booklist). At ninety, Jimmy Carter reflects on his public and private life with a frankness that is disarming. He adds detail and emotion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/">A Full Life : Reflections at Ninety &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his major New York Times bestseller, Jimmy Carter looks back from ninety years of age and &#8220;reveals private thoughts and recollections over a fascinating career as businessman, politician, evangelist, and humanitarian&#8221; (Booklist).    </p>
<p>                    At ninety, Jimmy Carter reflects on his public and private life with a frankness that is disarming. He adds detail and emotion about his youth in rural Georgia that he described in his magnificent An Hour Before Daylight. He writes about racism and the isolation of the Carters. He describes the brutality of the hazing regimen at Annapolis, and how he nearly lost his life twice serving on submarines and his amazing interview with Admiral Rickover. He describes the profound influence his mother had on him, and how he admired his father even though he didn&#8217;t emulate him. He admits that he decided to quit the Navy and later enter politics without consulting his wife, Rosalynn, and how appalled he is in retrospect.    </p>
<p>                    In his &#8220;warm and detailed memoir&#8221; (Los Angeles Times), Carter tells what he is proud of and what he might do differently. He discusses his regret at losing his re-election, but how he and Rosalynn pushed on and made a new life and second and third rewarding careers. He is frank about the presidents who have succeeded him, world leaders, and his passions for the causes he cares most about, particularly the condition of women and the deprived people of the developing world.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Always warm and human&#8230;even inspirational&#8221; (Buffalo News), A Full Life is a wise and moving look back from this remarkable man. Jimmy Carter has lived one of our great American lives-from rural obscurity to world fame, universal respect, and contentment. A Full Life is an extraordinary read from a &#8220;force to be reckoned with&#8221; (Christian Science Monitor).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/">A Full Life : Reflections at Ninety &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The First Conspiracy : The Secret Plot to Kill George Washington &#8211; Brad Meltzer, Josh Mensch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-first-conspiracy-the-secret-plot-to-kill-george-washington-brad-meltzer-josh-mensch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-first-conspiracy-the-secret-plot-to-kill-george-washington-brad-meltzer-josh-mensch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Taking place during the most critical period of our nation&#8217;s birth, The First Conspiracy tells a remarkable and previously untold piece of American history that not only reveals George Washington&#8217;s character, but also illuminates the origins of America&#8217;s counterintelligence movement that led to the modern day CIA. In 1776, an elite group of soldiers were [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-conspiracy-the-secret-plot-to-kill-george-washington-brad-meltzer-josh-mensch-abridged/">The First Conspiracy : The Secret Plot to Kill George Washington &#8211; Brad Meltzer, Josh Mensch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Taking place during the most critical period of our nation&#8217;s birth, The First Conspiracy tells a remarkable and previously untold piece of American history that not only reveals George Washington&#8217;s character, but also illuminates the origins of America&#8217;s counterintelligence movement that led to the modern day CIA.     </p>
<p>                    In 1776, an elite group of soldiers were handpicked to serve as George Washington&#8217;s bodyguards. Washington trusted them; relied on them. But unbeknownst to Washington, some of them were part of a treasonous plan. In the months leading up to the Revolutionary War, these traitorous soldiers, along with the Governor of New York, William Tryon, and Mayor David Mathews, launched a deadly plot against the most important member of the military: George Washington himself.     </p>
<p>                    This is the story of the secret plot and how it was revealed. It is a story of leaders, liars, counterfeiters, and jailhouse confessors. It also shows just how hard the battle was for George Washington and how close America was to losing the Revolutionary War.     </p>
<p>                    In this historical page-turner, New York Times bestselling author Brad Meltzer teams up with American history writer and documentary television producer, Josh Mensch to unravel the shocking true story behind what has previously been a footnote in the pages of history. Drawing on extensive research, Meltzer and Mensch capture in riveting detail how George Washington not only defeated the most powerful military force in the world, but also uncovered the secret plot against him in the tumultuous days leading up to July 4, 1776.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for The First Conspiracy:     </p>
<p>                    This is American history at its finest, a gripping story of spies, killers, counterfeiters, traitors and a mysterious prostitute who may or may not have even existed. Anyone with an interest in American history will love this book. &#8211;Douglas Preston, #1 bestselling author of The Lost City of the Monkey God     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A wonderful book about leadership and it shows why George Washington and his moral lessons are just as vital today. What a book. You&#8217;ll love it.&#8221; &#8211;former president George H.W. Bush</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-conspiracy-the-secret-plot-to-kill-george-washington-brad-meltzer-josh-mensch-abridged/">The First Conspiracy : The Secret Plot to Kill George Washington &#8211; Brad Meltzer, Josh Mensch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On His Own Terms : A Life of Nelson Rockefeller &#8211; Richard Norton Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-his-own-terms-a-life-of-nelson-rockefeller-richard-norton-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-his-own-terms-a-life-of-nelson-rockefeller-richard-norton-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-his-own-terms-a-life-of-nelson-rockefeller-richard-norton-smith-abridged/">On His Own Terms : A Life of Nelson Rockefeller &#8211; Richard Norton Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-his-own-terms-a-life-of-nelson-rockefeller-richard-norton-smith-abridged/">On His Own Terms : A Life of Nelson Rockefeller &#8211; Richard Norton Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bloody Brilliant Women : The Pioneers, Revolutionaries and Geniuses Your History Teacher Forgot to Mention &#8211; Cathy Newman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bloody-brilliant-women-the-pioneers-revolutionaries-and-geniuses-your-history-teacher-forgot-to-mention-cathy-newman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[British & Irish History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bloody-brilliant-women-the-pioneers-revolutionaries-and-geniuses-your-history-teacher-forgot-to-mention-cathy-newman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A litany of fresh heroes to make the embattled heart sing&#8217; Caitlin Moran &#8216;Newman is a brilliant writer&#8217; Observer A fresh, opinionated history of all the brilliant women you should have learned about in school but didn&#8217;t. For hundreds of years we have heard about the great men of history, but what about herstory? In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bloody-brilliant-women-the-pioneers-revolutionaries-and-geniuses-your-history-teacher-forgot-to-mention-cathy-newman-abridged/">Bloody Brilliant Women : The Pioneers, Revolutionaries and Geniuses Your History Teacher Forgot to Mention &#8211; Cathy Newman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A litany of fresh heroes to make the embattled heart sing&#8217; Caitlin Moran<br />
                              &#8216;Newman is a brilliant writer&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                                A fresh, opinionated history of all the brilliant women you should have learned about in school but didn&#8217;t.    </p>
<p>                              For hundreds of years we have heard about the great men of history, but what about herstory?    </p>
<p>                              In this freewheeling history of modern Britain, Cathy Newman writes about the pioneering women who defied the odds to make careers for themselves and alter the course of modern history; women who achieved what they achieved while dismantling hostile, entrenched views about their place in society. Their role in transforming Britain is fundamental, far greater than has generally been acknowledged, and not just in the arts or education but in fields like medicine, politics, law, engineering and the military.    </p>
<p>                              While a few of the women in this book are now household names, many have faded into oblivion, their personal and collective achievements mere footnotes in history. We know of Emmeline Pankhurst, Vera Brittain, Marie Stopes and Beatrice Webb. But who remembers engineer and motorbike racer Beatrice Shilling, whose ingenious device for the Spitfires&#8217; Rolls-Royce Merlin fixed an often-fatal flaw, allowing the RAF&#8217;s planes to beat the German in the Battle of Britain? Or Dorothy Lawrence, the journalist who achieved her ambition to become a WW1 correspondent by pretending to be a man? And developmental biologist Anne McLaren, whose work in genetics paved the way for in vitro fertilisation?    </p>
<p>                              Blending meticulous research with information gleaned from memoirs, diaries, letters, novels and other secondary sources, Bloody Brilliant Women uses the stories of some extraordinary lives to tell the tale of 20th and 21st century Britain. It is a history for women and men. A history for our times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bloody-brilliant-women-the-pioneers-revolutionaries-and-geniuses-your-history-teacher-forgot-to-mention-cathy-newman-abridged/">Bloody Brilliant Women : The Pioneers, Revolutionaries and Geniuses Your History Teacher Forgot to Mention &#8211; Cathy Newman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal: to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221; major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal:  to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221;  major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair way.     </p>
<p>                    Breitbart burst on to the national media scene thanks to his coverage of  the ACORN controversy, where a local ACORN community group leader was videotaped giving business advice to a &#8220;gentleman&#8221; who ran a prostitution ring. When the major news media at first tried to bury the story, Breitbart used his extraordinary marketing savvy to make sure the story got full national attention.     </p>
<p>                    More recently, Congressman Anthony Weiner took on Breitbart, claiming that scurrilous photos of Weiner were being sent on the internet by the conservative right. In a new chapter in RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart details how &#8220;Weinergate&#8221; was entirely the personal fault of Congressman Weiner, and how Weiner derailed his own promising career by trying to implicate Breitbart and conservative journalists.    </p>
<p>                    In short, RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart talks about the key issues that Americans face, how he has aligned himself with the Tea Party, and how one needs to deal with the liberal news world head on. Along the way, he details his early years, working with Matt Drudge, the Huffington Post, and so on, and how Breitbart developed his unique style of launching key websites to help get the word out to conservatives all over.     </p>
<p>                    A rollicking and controversial read, Breitbart will certainly raise your blood pressure, one way or another.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Threat : How the FBI Protects America in the Age of Terror and Trump &#8211; Andrew G. McCabe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-threat-how-the-fbi-protects-america-in-the-age-of-terror-and-trump-andrew-g-mccabe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Police & Security Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-threat-how-the-fbi-protects-america-in-the-age-of-terror-and-trump-andrew-g-mccabe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller #1 Washington Post Bestseller #1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller On March 16, 2018, just twenty-six hours before his scheduled retirement from the organization he had served with distinction for more than two decades, Andrew G. McCabe was fired from his position as deputy director of the FBI. President Donald Trump [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-threat-how-the-fbi-protects-america-in-the-age-of-terror-and-trump-andrew-g-mccabe-abridged/">The Threat : How the FBI Protects America in the Age of Terror and Trump &#8211; Andrew G. McCabe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller<br />
                    #1 Washington Post Bestseller<br />
                    #1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    On March 16, 2018, just twenty-six hours before his scheduled retirement from the organization he had served with distinction for more than two decades, Andrew G. McCabe was fired from his position as deputy director of the FBI. President Donald Trump celebrated on Twitter: &#8220;Andrew McCabe FIRED, a great day for the hard working men and women of the FBI &#8211; A great day for Democracy.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    In The Threat: How the FBI Protects America in the Age of Terror and Trump, Andrew G. McCabe offers a dramatic and candid account of his career, and an impassioned defense of the FBI&#8217;s agents, and of the institution&#8217;s integrity and independence in protecting America and upholding our Constitution.    </p>
<p>                    McCabe started as a street agent in the FBI&#8217;s New York field office, serving under director Louis Freeh. He became an expert in two kinds of investigations that are critical to American national security: Russian organized crime&#8211;which is inextricably linked to the Russian state&#8211;and terrorism. Under Director Robert Mueller, McCabe led the investigations of major attacks on American soil, including the Boston Marathon bombing, a plot to bomb the New York subways, and several narrowly averted bombings of aircraft. And under James Comey, McCabe was deeply involved in the controversial investigations of the Benghazi attack, the Clinton Foundation&#8217;s activities, and Hillary Clinton&#8217;s use of a private email server when she was secretary of state.    </p>
<p>                    The Threat recounts in compelling detail the time between Donald Trump&#8217;s November 2016 election and McCabe&#8217;s firing, set against a page-turning narrative spanning two decades when the FBI&#8217;s mission shifted to a new goal: preventing terrorist attacks on Americans. But as McCabe shows, right now the greatest threat to the United States comes from within, as President Trump and his administration ignore the law, attack democratic institutions, degrade human rights, and undermine the U.S. Constitution that protects every citizen.     </p>
<p>                    Important, revealing, and powerfully argued, The Threat tells the true story of what the FBI is, how it works, and why it will endure as an institution of integrity that protects America.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-threat-how-the-fbi-protects-america-in-the-age-of-terror-and-trump-andrew-g-mccabe-abridged/">The Threat : How the FBI Protects America in the Age of Terror and Trump &#8211; Andrew G. McCabe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genghis Khan : And the Making of the Modern World &#8211; Jack Weatherford (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/genghis-khan-and-the-making-of-the-modern-world-jack-weatherford-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early History: C 500 To C 1450/1500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medieval History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/genghis-khan-and-the-making-of-the-modern-world-jack-weatherford-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller &#8211; The startling true history of how one extraordinary man from a remote cornerof the world created an empire that led the world into the modern age. The Mongol army led by Genghis Khan subjugated more lands and people in twenty-five years than the Romans did in four hundred. In nearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genghis-khan-and-the-making-of-the-modern-world-jack-weatherford-abridged/">Genghis Khan : And the Making of the Modern World &#8211; Jack Weatherford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller &#8211; The startling true history of how one extraordinary man from a remote cornerof the world created an empire that led the world into the modern age.     </p>
<p>                    The Mongol army led by Genghis Khan subjugated more lands and people in twenty-five years than the Romans did in four hundred. In nearly every country the Mongols conquered, they brought an unprecedented rise in cultural communication, expanded trade, and a blossoming of civilization. Vastly more progressive than his European or Asian counterparts, Genghis Khan abolished torture, granted universal religious freedom, and smashed feudal systems of aristocratic privilege.     </p>
<p>                    From the story of his rise through the tribal culture to the explosion of civilization that the Mongol Empire unleashed, this brilliant work of revisionist history is nothing less than the epic story of how the modern world was made.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genghis-khan-and-the-making-of-the-modern-world-jack-weatherford-abridged/">Genghis Khan : And the Making of the Modern World &#8211; Jack Weatherford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sea Stories : My Life in Special Operations &#8211; William H. McRaven (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sea-stories-my-life-in-special-operations-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Afghan War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Iraq War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History: Post WW2 Conflicts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Veterans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Special & Elite Forces]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sea-stories-my-life-in-special-operations-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Admiral William H. McRaven is a part of American military history, having been involved in some of the most famous missions in recent memory, including the capture of Saddam Hussein, the rescue of Captain Richard Phillips, and the raid to kill Osama bin Laden.Sea Stories begins in 1960 at the American Officers&#8217; Club in France, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-stories-my-life-in-special-operations-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Sea Stories : My Life in Special Operations &#8211; William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Admiral William H. McRaven is a part of American military history, having been involved in some of the most famous missions in recent memory, including the capture of Saddam Hussein, the rescue of Captain Richard Phillips, and the raid to kill Osama bin Laden.Sea Stories begins in 1960 at the American Officers&#8217; Club in France, where Allied officers and their wives gathered to have drinks and tell stories about their adventures during World War II &#8212; the place where a young Bill McRaven learned the value of a good story. Sea Stories is an unforgettable look back on one man&#8217;s incredible life, from childhood days sneaking into high-security military sites to a day job of hunting terrorists and rescuing hostages.Action-packed, inspiring, and full of thrilling stories from life in the special operations world, Sea Stories is a remarkable memoir from one of America&#8217;s most accomplished leaders.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-stories-my-life-in-special-operations-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Sea Stories : My Life in Special Operations &#8211; William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rise Up Women! : The Remarkable Lives of the Suffragettes &#8211; Dr Diane Atkinson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rise-up-women-the-remarkable-lives-of-the-suffragettes-dr-diane-atkinson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rise-up-women-the-remarkable-lives-of-the-suffragettes-dr-diane-atkinson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Telegraph Book of 2018 An Observer Pick of 2018 A New Statesman Book of 2018 A definitive history and anarchic celebration of the fight for women&#8217;s right to vote; &#8216;A huge achievement&#8217; Rachel Cooke, Observer &#8216;Glorious&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;A definitive history of the suffragettes&#8217; The Times &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Telegraph Between the death of Queen Victoria [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rise-up-women-the-remarkable-lives-of-the-suffragettes-dr-diane-atkinson-abridged/">Rise Up Women! : The Remarkable Lives of the Suffragettes &#8211; Dr Diane Atkinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Telegraph Book of 2018<br />
                    An Observer Pick of 2018<br />
                    A New Statesman Book of 2018    </p>
<p>                    A definitive history and anarchic celebration of the fight for women&#8217;s right to vote; &#8216;A huge achievement&#8217; Rachel Cooke, Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Glorious&#8217; Sunday Times     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A definitive history of the suffragettes&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    Between the death of Queen Victoria and the outbreak of the First World War, while the patriarchs of the Liberal and Tory parties vied for supremacy in parliament, the campaign for women&#8217;s suffrage was fought with flair and imagination in the public arena. From their marches on Parliament and 10 Downing Street, to the selling of their paper, Votes for Women, through to the more militant activities of the Women&#8217;s Social and Political Union, whose slogan &#8216;Deeds Not Words!&#8217; resided over bombed pillar-boxes, acts of arson and the slashing of great works of art, the women who participated in the movement endured police brutality, assault, imprisonment and force-feeding, all in the relentless pursuit of one goal: the right to vote.    </p>
<p>                     A hundred years on, Diane Atkinson celebrates the lives of the women who answered the call to &#8216;Rise Up&#8217;; a richly diverse group of actresses and mill-workers, teachers and doctors, bootmakers and sweated workers. Meticulously researched, vividly rendered and definitive, Rise Up, Women! brings these women to life in a stirring celebration of their grace, resilience and determination that changed the world forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rise-up-women-the-remarkable-lives-of-the-suffragettes-dr-diane-atkinson-abridged/">Rise Up Women! : The Remarkable Lives of the Suffragettes &#8211; Dr Diane Atkinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Are Displaced : My Journey and Stories from Refugee Girls Around the World &#8211; From Nobel Peace Prize Winner Malala Yousafzai &#8211; Malala Yousafzai (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-are-displaced-my-journey-and-stories-from-refugee-girls-around-the-world-from-nobel-peace-prize-winner-malala-yousafzai-malala-yousafzai-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Migration, Immigration & Emigration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Refugees & Political Asylum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-are-displaced-my-journey-and-stories-from-refugee-girls-around-the-world-from-nobel-peace-prize-winner-malala-yousafzai-malala-yousafzai-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful and emotional New York Times bestseller, Nobel Peace Prize winner and activist Malala Yousafzai shares various stories of displacement, including her own. Part memoir, part communal storytelling, We Are Displaced introduces readers to some of the incredible girls Malala has met on her many journeys and lets each tell her story &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-displaced-my-journey-and-stories-from-refugee-girls-around-the-world-from-nobel-peace-prize-winner-malala-yousafzai-malala-yousafzai-abridged/">We Are Displaced : My Journey and Stories from Refugee Girls Around the World &#8211; From Nobel Peace Prize Winner Malala Yousafzai &#8211; Malala Yousafzai (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful and emotional New York Times bestseller, Nobel Peace Prize winner and activist Malala Yousafzai shares various stories of displacement, including her own. Part memoir, part communal storytelling, We Are Displaced introduces readers to some of the incredible girls Malala has met on her many journeys and lets each tell her story &#8211; girls who have lost their community, relatives and often the only world they&#8217;ve ever known, but have not lost hope.    </p>
<p>                    Longing for home and fear of an uncertain future binds all of these young women, but each is unique. In a time of immigration crises, war and border conflicts, We Are Displaced is an important reminder that every single one of the 79.5 million currently displaced is a person &#8211; often a young person &#8211; with dreams for a better, safer world.    </p>
<p>                    Includes a new Afterword by the author</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-displaced-my-journey-and-stories-from-refugee-girls-around-the-world-from-nobel-peace-prize-winner-malala-yousafzai-malala-yousafzai-abridged/">We Are Displaced : My Journey and Stories from Refugee Girls Around the World &#8211; From Nobel Peace Prize Winner Malala Yousafzai &#8211; Malala Yousafzai (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mighty Be Our Powers : How Sisterhood, Prayer, and Sex Changed a Nation at War &#8211; Carol Mithers, Leymah Gbowee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The winner of the Nobel Peace Prize shares her inspirational, powerful story of how a group of women working together created an unstoppable force that brought peace to Liberia. As a young woman, Leymah Gbowee was broken by the Liberian civil war, a brutal conflict that destroyed her country and claimed the lives of countless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/">Mighty Be Our Powers : How Sisterhood, Prayer, and Sex Changed a Nation at War &#8211; Carol Mithers, Leymah Gbowee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The winner of the Nobel Peace Prize shares her inspirational, powerful story of how a group of women working together created an unstoppable force that brought peace to Liberia.     </p>
<p>                     As a young woman, Leymah Gbowee was broken by the Liberian civil war, a brutal conflict that destroyed her country and claimed the lives of countless relatives and friends. Propelled by her realization that it is women and girls who suffer most during conflicts, she found the courage to turn her bitterness into action.     </p>
<p>                     She helped organize and then lead the Liberian Mass Action for Peace, which brought together Christian and Muslim women in a nonviolent movement that engaged in public protest, confronted Liberia&#8217;s ruthless president and rebel warlords, and even held a sex strike.     </p>
<p>                     With an army of women, Gbowee helped lead her nation to peace-and became an international leader who changed history, won the Nobel Peace Prize for her work, and fiercely advocates for girls&#8217; empowerment and leadership. Mighty Be Our Powers is the gripping chronicle of a journey from hopelessness to liberation that will touch all who dream of a better world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/">Mighty Be Our Powers : How Sisterhood, Prayer, and Sex Changed a Nation at War &#8211; Carol Mithers, Leymah Gbowee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Call Sign Chaos : Learning to Lead &#8211; Jim Mattis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A clear-eyed account of learning how to lead in a chaotic world, by General Jim Mattis&#8211;the former Secretary of Defense and one of the most formidable strategic thinkers of our time&#8211;and Bing West, a former assistant secretary of defense and combat Marine. &#8220;A four-star general&#8217;s five-star memoir.&#8221;&#8211;The Wall Street [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis-abridged/">Call Sign Chaos : Learning to Lead &#8211; Jim Mattis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A clear-eyed account of learning how to lead in a chaotic world, by General Jim Mattis&#8211;the former Secretary of Defense and one of the most formidable strategic thinkers of our time&#8211;and Bing West, a former assistant secretary of defense and combat Marine.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A four-star general&#8217;s five-star memoir.&#8221;&#8211;The Wall Street Journal     </p>
<p>                     Call Sign Chaos is the account of Jim Mattis&#8217;s storied career, from wide-ranging leadership roles in three wars to ultimately commanding a quarter of a million troops across the Middle East. Along the way, Mattis recounts his foundational experiences as a leader, extracting the lessons he has learned about the nature of warfighting and peacemaking, the importance of allies, and the strategic dilemmas&#8211;and short-sighted thinking&#8211;now facing our nation. He makes it clear why America must return to a strategic footing so as not to continue winning battles but fighting inconclusive wars.     </p>
<p>                     Mattis divides his book into three parts: Direct Leadership, Executive Leadership, and Strategic Leadership. In the first part, Mattis recalls his early experiences leading Marines into battle, when he knew his troops as well as his own brothers. In the second part, he explores what it means to command thousands of troops and how to adapt your leadership style to ensure your intent is understood by your most junior troops so that they can own their mission. In the third part, Mattis describes the challenges and techniques of leadership at the strategic level, where military leaders reconcile war&#8217;s grim realities with political leaders&#8217; human aspirations, where complexity reigns and the consequences of imprudence are severe, even catastrophic.     </p>
<p>                     Call Sign Chaos is a memoir of a life of warfighting and lifelong learning, following along as Mattis rises from Marine recruit to four-star general. It is a journey about learning to lead and a story about how he, through constant study and action, developed a unique leadership philosophy, one relevant to us all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis-abridged/">Call Sign Chaos : Learning to Lead &#8211; Jim Mattis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yes We (Still) Can : Politics in the age of Obama, Twitter and Trump &#8211; Dan Pfeiffer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/yes-we-still-can-politics-in-the-age-of-obama-twitter-and-trump-dan-pfeiffer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/yes-we-still-can-politics-in-the-age-of-obama-twitter-and-trump-dan-pfeiffer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Barack Obama was the breath of fresh air the Democrats didn&#8217;t even realise they needed. Running on a platform of hope, change and progress, he won his first term with a decisive landslide, completely rewriting the rules of politics. So how did we go from Obama to Trump &#8211; and how can the Democrats turn [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/yes-we-still-can-politics-in-the-age-of-obama-twitter-and-trump-dan-pfeiffer-abridged/">Yes We (Still) Can : Politics in the age of Obama, Twitter and Trump &#8211; Dan Pfeiffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Barack Obama was the breath of fresh air the Democrats didn&#8217;t even realise they needed. Running on a platform of hope, change and progress, he won his first term with a decisive landslide, completely rewriting the rules of politics.    </p>
<p>                    So how did we go from Obama to Trump &#8211; and how can the Democrats turn the tide? Once his communications director, and now co-host of Pod Save America, Dan Pfeiffer was at Obama&#8217;s side through two presidential elections and six years in the White House. Offering up surreal stories from behind the scenes, Pfeiffer explains how Obama navigated the forces that propelled Trump to power, and metes out critical wisdom on how the Democrats can reverse the country&#8217;s fate.    </p>
<p>                    A funny, thoughtful and humble account of Pfeiffer&#8217;s time on the front line of politics, Yes We (Still) Can is not just a memoir but an action plan for those who still dare to hope for change &#8211; and for the end of the Trump era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/yes-we-still-can-politics-in-the-age-of-obama-twitter-and-trump-dan-pfeiffer-abridged/">Yes We (Still) Can : Politics in the age of Obama, Twitter and Trump &#8211; Dan Pfeiffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A River in Darkness : One Man&#8217;s Escape from North Korea &#8211; Masaji Ishikawa, Translated by Risa Kobayashi, Translated by Martin Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-river-in-darkness-one-mans-escape-from-north-korea-masaji-ishikawa-translated-by-risa-kobayashi-translated-by-martin-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-river-in-darkness-one-mans-escape-from-north-korea-masaji-ishikawa-translated-by-risa-kobayashi-translated-by-martin-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An Amazon Charts Most Read and Most Sold book. The harrowing true story of one man&#8217;s life in&#8211;and subsequent escape from&#8211;North Korea, one of the world&#8217;s most brutal totalitarian regimes. Half-Korean, half-Japanese, Masaji Ishikawa has spent his whole life feeling like a man without a country. This feeling only deepened when his family moved from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-river-in-darkness-one-mans-escape-from-north-korea-masaji-ishikawa-translated-by-risa-kobayashi-translated-by-martin-brown-abridged/">A River in Darkness : One Man&#8217;s Escape from North Korea &#8211; Masaji Ishikawa, Translated by Risa Kobayashi, Translated by Martin Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An Amazon Charts Most Read and Most Sold book.    </p>
<p>                    The harrowing true story of one man&#8217;s life in&#8211;and subsequent escape from&#8211;North Korea, one of the world&#8217;s most brutal totalitarian regimes.    </p>
<p>                    Half-Korean, half-Japanese, Masaji Ishikawa has spent his whole life feeling like a man without a country. This feeling only deepened when his family moved from Japan to North Korea when Ishikawa was just thirteen years old, and unwittingly became members of the lowest social caste. His father, himself a Korean national, was lured to the new Communist country by promises of abundant work, education for his children, and a higher station in society. But the reality of their new life was far from utopian.    </p>
<p>                    In this memoir translated from the original Japanese, Ishikawa candidly recounts his tumultuous upbringing and the brutal thirty-six years he spent living under a crushing totalitarian regime, as well as the challenges he faced repatriating to Japan after barely escaping North Korea with his life. A River in Darkness is not only a shocking portrait of life inside the country but a testament to the dignity&#8211;and indomitable nature&#8211;of the human spirit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-river-in-darkness-one-mans-escape-from-north-korea-masaji-ishikawa-translated-by-risa-kobayashi-translated-by-martin-brown-abridged/">A River in Darkness : One Man&#8217;s Escape from North Korea &#8211; Masaji Ishikawa, Translated by Risa Kobayashi, Translated by Martin Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this highly anticipated follow-up to his blockbuster New York Times bestseller The Amateur, former New York Times Magazine editor-in-chief Edward Klein delves into the rocky relationship between the Obamas and the Clintons. An old-school reporter with incredible insider contacts, Klein reveals just how deep the rivalry between the Obamas and the Clintons runs, with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/">Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this highly anticipated follow-up to his blockbuster New York Times bestseller The Amateur, former New York Times Magazine editor-in-chief Edward Klein delves into the rocky relationship between the Obamas and the Clintons. An old-school reporter with incredible insider contacts, Klein reveals just how deep the rivalry between the Obamas and the Clintons runs, with details on closed-door meetings buttressed by hundreds of interviews. Blood Feud is a stunning expose of the animosity, jealousy, and competition between America&#8217;s two most powerful political couples.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/">Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his rich and nuanced portrait of the remarkable, elusive Rothschild family, Oxford scholar and bestselling author Niall Ferguson uncovers the secrets behind the family&#8217;s phenomenal economic success. He reveals for the first time the details of the family&#8217;s vast political network, which gave it access to and influence over many of the greatest statesmen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his rich and nuanced portrait of the remarkable, elusive Rothschild  family, Oxford scholar and bestselling author Niall Ferguson uncovers  the secrets behind the family&#8217;s phenomenal economic success. He reveals  for the first time the details of the family&#8217;s vast political network,  which gave it access to and influence over many of the greatest  statesmen of the age. And he tells a family saga, tracing the importance  of unity and the profound role of Judaism in the lives of a dynasty  that rose from the confines of the Frankfurt ghetto and later used its  influence to assist oppressed Jews throughout Europe. A definitive work  of impeccable scholarship with a thoroughly engaging narrative, &#8216;The  House of Rothschild&#8217; is a biography of the rarest kind, in which  mysterious and fascinating historical figures finally spring to life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diaries, Letters & Journals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geographical Discovery & Exploration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transplant Surgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories: Discovery / Historical / Scientific]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jauhar weaves his own personal and family story into his history of the heart&#8230;very effectively&#8230; This gives a certain dramatic tension to the book, as it tells the fascinating and rather wonderful history of cardiology.&#8217; -Henry Marsh, New Statesman A Mail on Sunday Book of the Year The heart lies at the centre of life. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/">Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jauhar weaves his own personal and family story into his history of the heart&#8230;very effectively&#8230; This gives a certain dramatic tension to the book, as it tells the fascinating and rather wonderful history of cardiology.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    -Henry Marsh, New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    A Mail on Sunday Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    The heart lies at the centre of life. For cardiologist Sandeep Jauhar it is an obsession.    </p>
<p>                    In this fascinating history he interweaves gripping scenes from the operating theatre with the moving tale of his family&#8217;s history of heart problems &#8211; from the death of his grandfather to the ominous signs of how he himself might die.    </p>
<p>                    Jauhar looks at the pioneers who risked patients&#8217; lives and their own careers, and confronts the limits of medical technology, arguing that how we live is more important than any device or drug we may invent. Heart is the all-encompassing story of the engine of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/">Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>And the Good News Is&#8230; : Lessons and Advice from the Bright Side &#8211; Dana Perino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thoughtful, inspiring and often surprising, AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230; traces Dana&#8217;s unlikely journey through politics, the White House, and television. She has an uncanny ability for knowing what to say and how best to say it. A recurring theme in AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230;is that planning has never worked for Dana; every time [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/">And the Good News Is&#8230; : Lessons and Advice from the Bright Side &#8211; Dana Perino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thoughtful, inspiring and often surprising, AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230; traces Dana&#8217;s unlikely journey through politics, the White House, and television. She has an uncanny ability for knowing what to say and how best to say it. A recurring theme in AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230;is that planning has never worked for Dana; every time she has made a plan, something unexpected-and often better-has happened.<br />
                    AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230; blends a candid self-portrait with advice for allowing one&#8217;s very best personality traits to shine through, emphasizing that dignity and civility are choices we make for ourselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/">And the Good News Is&#8230; : Lessons and Advice from the Bright Side &#8211; Dana Perino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Trial of Henry Kissinger &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-trial-of-henry-kissinger-christopher-hitchens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Postwar 20th Century History, From C 1945 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[War Crimes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-trial-of-henry-kissinger-christopher-hitchens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Hitchens goes straight for the jugular in The Trial of Henry Kissinger. Under his fearsome gaze, the former Secretary of State and National Security Advisor is accused of being a war criminal whose reckless actions and heinous disregard for international law have led to torture, kidnapping, and murder. This book is a polemical masterpiece [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-trial-of-henry-kissinger-christopher-hitchens-abridged/">The Trial of Henry Kissinger &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Hitchens goes straight for the jugular in The Trial of Henry Kissinger. Under his fearsome gaze, the former Secretary of State and National Security Advisor is accused of being a war criminal whose reckless actions and heinous disregard for international law have led to torture, kidnapping, and murder.    </p>
<p>                    This book is a polemical masterpiece by a man who, for forty years, was the Angloshpere&#8217;s preeminent man of letters. In The Trial of Henry Kissinger, Hitchens&#8217; verve, style and firebrand wit are on show at the height of their potency.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A good liar must have a good memory: Kissinger is a stupendous liar with a remarkable memory.&#8217; Christopher Hitchens</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-trial-of-henry-kissinger-christopher-hitchens-abridged/">The Trial of Henry Kissinger &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frederick Douglass : Prophet of Freedom &#8211; David W. Blight (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/frederick-douglass-prophet-of-freedom-david-w-blight-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Slavery & Abolition Of Slavery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/frederick-douglass-prophet-of-freedom-david-w-blight-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**Winner of the Pulitzer Prize in History** &#8220;Extraordinary&#8230;a great American biography&#8221; (The New Yorker) of the most important African-American of the nineteenth century: Frederick Douglass, the escaped slave who became the greatest orator of his day and one of the leading abolitionists and writers of the era. As a young man Frederick Douglass (1818-1895) escaped [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/frederick-douglass-prophet-of-freedom-david-w-blight-abridged/">Frederick Douglass : Prophet of Freedom &#8211; David W. Blight (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**Winner of the Pulitzer Prize in History**    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Extraordinary&#8230;a great American biography&#8221; (The New Yorker) of the most important African-American of the nineteenth century: Frederick Douglass, the escaped slave who became the greatest orator of his day and one of the leading abolitionists and writers of the era.    </p>
<p>                    As a young man Frederick Douglass (1818-1895) escaped from slavery in Baltimore, Maryland. He was fortunate to have been taught to read by his slave owner mistress, and he would go on to become one of the major literary figures of his time. His very existence gave the lie to slave owners: with dignity and great intelligence he bore witness to the brutality of slavery.    </p>
<p>                    Initially mentored by William Lloyd Garrison, Douglass spoke widely, using his own story to condemn slavery. By the Civil War, Douglass had become the most famed and widely travelled orator in the nation. In his unique and eloquent voice, written and spoken, Douglass was a fierce critic of the United States as well as a radical patriot. After the war he sometimes argued politically with younger African Americans, but he never forsook either the Republican party or the cause of black civil and political rights.    </p>
<p>                    In this &#8220;cinematic and deeply engaging&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) biography, David Blight has drawn on new information held in a private collection that few other historian have consulted, as well as recently discovered issues of Douglass&#8217;s newspapers. &#8220;Absorbing and even moving&#8230;a brilliant book that speaks to our own time as well as Douglass&#8217;s&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal), Blight&#8217;s biography tells the fascinating story of Douglass&#8217;s two marriages and his complex extended family. &#8220;David Blight has written the definitive biography of Frederick Douglass&#8230;a powerful portrait of one of the most important American voices of the nineteenth century&#8221; (The Boston Globe).    </p>
<p>                    In addition to the Pulitzer Prize, Frederick Douglass won the Bancroft, Parkman, Los Angeles Times (biography), Lincoln, Plutarch, and Christopher awards and was named one of the Best Books of 2018 by The New York Times Book Review, The Wall Street Journal, The Boston Globe, The Chicago Tribune, The San Francisco Chronicle, and Time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/frederick-douglass-prophet-of-freedom-david-w-blight-abridged/">Frederick Douglass : Prophet of Freedom &#8211; David W. Blight (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shattered : Inside Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Doomed Campaign &#8211; Jonathan Allen, Amie Parnes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/shattered-inside-hillary-clintons-doomed-campaign-jonathan-allen-amie-parnes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shattered-inside-hillary-clintons-doomed-campaign-jonathan-allen-amie-parnes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER It was never supposed to be this close. And of course she was supposed to win. How Hillary Clinton lost the 2016 election to Donald Trump is the riveting story of a sure thing gone off the rails. For every Comey revelation or hindsight acknowledgment about the electorate, no explanation [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shattered-inside-hillary-clintons-doomed-campaign-jonathan-allen-amie-parnes-abridged/">Shattered : Inside Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Doomed Campaign &#8211; Jonathan Allen, Amie Parnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER It was never supposed to be this close. And of course she was supposed to win. How Hillary Clinton lost the 2016 election to Donald Trump is the riveting story of a sure thing gone off the rails. For every Comey revelation or hindsight acknowledgment about the electorate, no explanation of defeat can begin with anything other than the core problem of Hillary&#8217;s campaign&#8211;the candidate herself. Through deep access to insiders from the top to the bottom of the campaign, political writers Jonathan Allen and Amie Parnes have reconstructed the key decisions and unseized opportunities, the well-intentioned misfires and the hidden thorns that turned a winnable contest into a devastating loss. Drawing on the authors&#8217; deep knowledge of Hillary from their previous book, the acclaimed biography HRC, Shattered offers an object lesson in how Hillary herself made victory an uphill battle, how her difficulty articulating a vision irreparably hobbled her impact with voters, and how the campaign failed to internalize the lessons of populist fury from the hard-fought primary against Bernie Sanders. Moving blow-by-blow from the campaign&#8217;s difficult birth through the bewildering terror of election night, Shattered tells an unforgettable story with urgent lessons both political and personal, filled with revelations that will change the way readers understand just what happened to America on November 8, 2016.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shattered-inside-hillary-clintons-doomed-campaign-jonathan-allen-amie-parnes-abridged/">Shattered : Inside Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Doomed Campaign &#8211; Jonathan Allen, Amie Parnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Napoleonic Wars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions, Uprisings, Rebellions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217; Simon Sebag Montefiore &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon. Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the  momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217;   Simon Sebag Montefiore<br />
                    &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell    </p>
<p>                    From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon.    </p>
<p>                    Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of all human lives. In the space of just twenty years, from October 1795 when as a young artillery captain he cleared the streets of Paris of insurrectionists, to his final defeat at the (horribly mismanaged) battle of Waterloo in June 1815, Napoleon transformed France and Europe. After seizing power in a coup d&#8217;etat he ended the corruption and incompetence into which the Revolution had descended. In a series of dazzling battles he reinvented the art of warfare; in peace, he completely remade the laws of France, modernised her systems of education and administration, and presided over a flourishing of the beautiful &#8216;Empire style&#8217; in the arts. The impossibility of defeating his most persistent enemy, Great Britain, led him to make draining and ultimately fatal expeditions into Spain and Russia, where half a million Frenchmen died and his Empire began to unravel.    </p>
<p>                    More than any other modern biographer, Andrew Roberts conveys Napoleon&#8217;s tremendous energy, both physical and intellectual, and the attractiveness of his personality, even to his enemies. He has walked 53 of Napoleon&#8217;s 60 battlefields, and has absorbed the gigantic new French edition of Napoleon&#8217;s letters, which allows a complete re-evaluation of this exceptional man. He overturns many received opinions, including the myth of a great romance with Josephine: she took a lover immediately after their marriage, and, as Roberts shows, he had three times as many mistresses as he acknowledged.    </p>
<p>                    Of the climactic Battle of Leipzig in 1813, as the fighting closed around them, a French sergeant-major wrote, &#8216;No-one who has not experienced it can have any idea of the enthusiasm that burst forth among the half-starved, exhausted soldiers when the Emperor was there in person. If all were demoralised and he appeared, his presence was like an electric shock. All shouted &#8220;Vive l&#8217;Empereur!&#8221; and everyone charged blindly into the fire.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    The reader of this biography will understand why this was so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Without a Face : The Unlikely Rise of Vladimir Putin &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-without-a-face-the-unlikely-rise-of-vladimir-putin-masha-gessen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-without-a-face-the-unlikely-rise-of-vladimir-putin-masha-gessen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Vladimir Putin, an unimportant, low-level KGB operative, was rushed to power by a group of Oligarchs in 1999, he was a man without a history. Within a few brief years, Putin had dismantled Russia&#8217;s media, wrested control and wealth from the country&#8217;s burgeoning business class, and decimated the fragile mechanisms of democracy. Virtually every [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-without-a-face-the-unlikely-rise-of-vladimir-putin-masha-gessen-abridged/">The Man Without a Face : The Unlikely Rise of Vladimir Putin &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Vladimir Putin, an unimportant,  low-level KGB operative, was rushed to power by a group of Oligarchs in 1999, he was a man without a history. Within a few brief years, Putin had dismantled Russia&#8217;s media, wrested control and wealth from the country&#8217;s burgeoning business class, and decimated the fragile mechanisms of democracy.  Virtually every obstacle to his unbridled control was removed and every opposing voice silenced, with political rivals and critics driven into exile or to the grave.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on information and sources no other writer has tapped, Masha Gessen&#8217;s fearless account charts Putin&#8217;s rise from the boy who had scrapped his way through post-war Leningrad schoolyards, to the &#8216;faceless&#8217; man who manoeuvred his way into absolute &#8211; and absolutely corrupt &#8211; power.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-without-a-face-the-unlikely-rise-of-vladimir-putin-masha-gessen-abridged/">The Man Without a Face : The Unlikely Rise of Vladimir Putin &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Books, Manuscripts, Ephemera & Printed Matter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that a bank be established to issue paper money with the credit based on the value of land. But Queen Anne was not about to take advice from a gambler and felon. So, in exile in Paris, he convinced the bankrupt court of Louis XV of the value of his idea.<br />
                     Law soon engineered the revival of the French economy and found himself one of the most powerful men in Europe. In August 1717, he founded the Mississippi Company, and the Court granted him the right to trade in France&#8217;s vast territory in America. The shareholders in his new trading company made such enormous profits that the term millionaire was coined to describe them. Paris was soon in a frenzy of speculation, conspiracies, and insatiable consumption. Before this first boom-and-bust cycle was complete, markets throughout Europe crashed, the mob began calling for Law&#8217;s head, and his visionary ideas about what money could do were abandoned and forgotten.<br />
                     In Millionaire,  Janet Gleeson lucidly reconstructs this epic drama where fortunes were made and lost, paupers grew rich, and lords fell into penury &#8212; and a modern fiscal philosophy was born. Her enthralling tragicomic tale reveals two great characters: John Law, with his complex personality and inscrutable motives, and money itself, whose true nature even to this day remains elusive</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Isaac Newton &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/isaac-newton-james-gleick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/isaac-newton-james-gleick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Isaac Newton was born in a stone farmhouse in 1642, fatherless and unwanted by his mother. When he died in London in 1727 he was so renowned he was given a state funeral&#8211;an unheard-of honor for a subject whose achievements were in the realm of the intellect. During the years he was an irascible presence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/isaac-newton-james-gleick-abridged/">Isaac Newton &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Isaac Newton was born in a stone farmhouse in 1642, fatherless and unwanted by his mother. When he died in London in 1727 he was so renowned he was given a state funeral&#8211;an unheard-of honor for a subject whose achievements were in the realm of the intellect. During the years he was an irascible presence at Trinity College, Cambridge, Newton imagined properties of nature and gave them names&#8211;mass, gravity, velocity&#8211;things our science now takes for granted. Inspired by Aristotle, spurred on by Galileo&#8217;s discoveries and the philosophy of Descartes, Newton grasped the intangible and dared to take its measure, a leap of the mind unparalleled in his generation. James Gleick, the author of Chaos and Genius, and one of the most acclaimed science writers of his generation, brings the reader into Newton&#8217;s reclusive life and provides startlingly clear explanations of the concepts that changed forever our perception of bodies, rest, and motion&#8211;ideas so basic to the twenty-first century, it can truly be said: We are all Newtonians.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/isaac-newton-james-gleick-abridged/">Isaac Newton &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy & Data Protection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down. In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down.    </p>
<p>                    In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden shocked the world when he broke with the American intelligence establishment and revealed that the United States government was secretly pursuing the means to collect every single phone call, text message, and email. The result would be an unprecedented system of mass surveillance with the ability to pry into the private lives of every person on earth. Six years later, Snowden reveals for the very first time how he helped to build this system and why he was moved to expose it.    </p>
<p>                    Spanning the bucolic Beltway suburbs of his childhood and the clandestine CIA and NSA postings of his adulthood, Permanent Record is the extraordinary account of a bright young man who grew up online &#8211; a man who became a spy, a whistleblower, and, in exile, the Internet&#8217;s conscience. Written with wit, grace, passion, and an unflinching candor, Permanent Record is a crucial memoir of our digital age and destined to be a classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Lion : Andrew Jackson in the White House &#8211; Jon Meacham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/american-lion-andrew-jackson-in-the-white-house-jon-meacham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-lion-andrew-jackson-in-the-white-house-jon-meacham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The definitive biography of a larger-than-life president who defied norms, divided a nation, and changed Washington forever Andrew Jackson, his intimate circle of friends, and his tumultuous times are at the heart of this remarkable book about the man who rose from nothing to create the modern presidency. Beloved and hated, venerated and reviled, Andrew [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-lion-andrew-jackson-in-the-white-house-jon-meacham-abridged/">American Lion : Andrew Jackson in the White House &#8211; Jon Meacham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The definitive biography of a larger-than-life president who defied norms, divided a nation, and changed Washington forever Andrew Jackson, his intimate circle of friends, and his tumultuous times are at the heart of this remarkable book about the man who rose from nothing to create the modern presidency. Beloved and hated, venerated and reviled, Andrew Jackson was an orphan who fought his way to the pinnacle of power, bending the nation to his will in the cause of democracy. Jackson&#8217;s election in 1828 ushered in a new and lasting era in which the people, not distant elites, were the guiding force in American politics. Democracy made its stand in the Jackson years, and he gave voice to the hopes and the fears of a restless, changing nation facing challenging times at home and threats abroad. To tell the saga of Jackson&#8217;s presidency, acclaimed author Jon Meacham goes inside the Jackson White House. Drawing on newly discovered family letters and papers, he details the human drama-the family, the women, and the inner circle of advisers- that shaped Jackson&#8217;s private world through years of storm and victory.  One of our most significant yet dimly recalled presidents, Jackson was a battle-hardened warrior, the founder of the Democratic Party, and the architect of the presidency as we know it. His story is one of violence, sex, courage, and tragedy. With his powerful persona, his evident bravery, and his mystical connection to the people, Jackson moved the White House from the periphery of government to the center of national action, articulating a vision of change that challenged entrenched interests to heed the popular will- or face his formidable wrath. The greatest of the presidents who have followed Jackson in the White House-from Lincoln to Theodore Roosevelt to FDR to Truman-have found inspiration in his example, and virtue in his vision.  Jackson was the most contradictory of men. The architect of the removal of Indians from their native lands, he was warmly sentimental and risked everything to give more power to ordinary citizens. He was, in short, a lot like his country: alternately kind and vicious, brilliant and blind; and a man who fought a lifelong war to keep the republic safe-no matter what it took.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-lion-andrew-jackson-in-the-white-house-jon-meacham-abridged/">American Lion : Andrew Jackson in the White House &#8211; Jon Meacham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Boating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olympic Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rowing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism, Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Sports & Recreations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year, this is the bestselling story about a rowing team&#8217;s quest for Olympic gold in Nazi Germany. Cast aside by his family at an early age, abandoned and left to fend for himself in the woods of Washington State, young Joe Rantz turns to rowing as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/">The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year, this is the bestselling story about a rowing team&#8217;s quest for Olympic gold in Nazi Germany.     </p>
<p>                    Cast aside by his family at an early age, abandoned and left to fend for himself in the woods of Washington State, young Joe Rantz turns to rowing as a way of escaping his past.    </p>
<p>                     What follows is an extraordinary journey, as Joe and eight other working-class boys exchange the sweat and dust of life in 1930s America for the promise of glory at the heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin. Stroke by stroke, a remarkable young man strives to regain his shattered self-regard, to dare again to trust in others &#8211; and to find his way back home.    </p>
<p>                     Told against the backdrop of the Great Depression, Daniel James Brown&#8217;s The Boys in the Boat is narrative non-fiction of the first order; a personal story full of lyricism and unexpected beauty that rises above the grand sweep of history, and captures instead the purest essence of what it means to be alive.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;I really can&#8217;t rave enough about this book . . . I read the last fifty pages with white knuckles, and the last twenty-five with tears in my eyes&#8217; &#8211; David Laskin, author of The Children&#8217;s Blizzard and The Long Way Home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/">The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Happened &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-happened-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-happened-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; &#8211; Financial Times &#8216;A sporadically absorbing, pleasingly vengeful and often darkly funny account of one woman&#8217;s bid for presidential history.&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Her new book is more gossipy, it is meaner, more entertaining and more wrong-headed than anything she or her speechwriters have written before.&#8217; Observer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-happened-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">What Happened &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; &#8211; Financial Times<br />
                     &#8216;A sporadically absorbing, pleasingly vengeful and often darkly funny account of one woman&#8217;s bid for presidential history.&#8217; Sunday Times<br />
                     &#8216;Her new book is more gossipy, it is meaner, more entertaining and more wrong-headed than anything she or her speechwriters have written before.&#8217; Observer<br />
                     &#8216;What Happened is highly entertaining. It is spirited, well-written and informative.&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In the past, for reasons I try to explain, I&#8217;ve often felt I had to be careful in public, like I was up on a wire without a net. Now I&#8217;m letting my guard down.&#8217; &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, from the introduction of What Happened    </p>
<p>                     For the first time, Hillary Rodham Clinton reveals what she was thinking and feeling during one of the most controversial and unpredictable presidential elections in history. Now free from the constraints of running, Hillary takes you inside the intense personal experience of becoming the first woman nominated for president by a major party in an election marked by rage, sexism, exhilarating highs and infuriating lows, stranger-than-fiction twists, Russian interference and an opponent who broke all the rules. This is her most personal memoir yet.    </p>
<p>                     In these pages, she describes what it was like to run against Donald Trump, the mistakes she made, how she has coped with a shocking and devastating loss, and how she found the strength to pick herself back up afterwards. With humour and candour, she tells readers what it took to get back on her feet &#8211; the rituals, relationships and reading that got her through, and what the experience has taught her about life. She speaks about the challenges of being a strong woman in the public eye, the criticism over her voice, age and appearance, and the double standard confronting women in politics.     </p>
<p>                     She lays out how the 2016 election was marked by an unprecedented assault on democracy by a foreign adversary. By analysing the evidence and connecting the dots, Hillary shows just how dangerous the forces are that shaped the outcome, and why Americans need to understand them to protect their values and democracy in the future.    </p>
<p>                     The election of 2016 was unprecedented and historic. What Happened is the story of that campaign and its aftermath &#8211; both a deeply intimate account and a cautionary tale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-happened-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">What Happened &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jerusalem : The Biography &#8211; Simon Sebag Montefiore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/jerusalem-the-biography-simon-sebag-montefiore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Earliest Times To Present Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/jerusalem-the-biography-simon-sebag-montefiore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new, updated, revised edition of JERUSALEM: THE BIOGRAPHY, the wider history of the Middle East through the lens of the Holy City, covering from pre-history to 2020, from King David to Donald Trump. The story of Jerusalem is the story of the world. Jerusalem is the universal city, the capital of two peoples, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jerusalem-the-biography-simon-sebag-montefiore-abridged/">Jerusalem : The Biography &#8211; Simon Sebag Montefiore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new, updated, revised edition of JERUSALEM: THE BIOGRAPHY, the wider history of the Middle East through the lens of the Holy City, covering from pre-history to 2020, from King David to Donald Trump.     </p>
<p>                    The story of Jerusalem is the story of the world.    </p>
<p>                    Jerusalem is the universal city, the capital of two peoples, the shrine of three faiths; it is the site of Judgement Day and the battlefield of today&#8217;s clash of civilisations. How did this small, remote town become the Holy City, the &#8216;centre of the world&#8217; and now the key to peace in the Middle East? Drawing on new archives and a lifetime&#8217;s study, Montefiore reveals this ever-changing city through the wars, love affairs and revelations of the kings, empresses, prophets, poets, saints, conquerors and whores who created, destroyed, chronicled and believed in Jerusalem.    </p>
<p>                    A classic of modern literature, this is not only the epic story of 3,000 years of faith, slaughter, fanaticism and co-existence, but also a freshly-updated history of the entire Middle East, from King David to the twenty-first century, from the birth of Judaism, Christianity and Islam to the Israel-Palestine conflict and the wars of today. This is how Jerusalem became Jerusalem &#8211; the only city that exists twice &#8211; in heaven and on earth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jerusalem-the-biography-simon-sebag-montefiore-abridged/">Jerusalem : The Biography &#8211; Simon Sebag Montefiore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING * &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING *     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly written haymaker&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly three years of reporting, hundreds of hours of interviews and more than two hundred sources, including some of the most senior members of the administration, friends and first-hand witnesses who have never spoken before, Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig take us inside some of the most controversial moments of Trump&#8217;s presidency. They peer deeply into Trump&#8217;s White House &#8211; at the aides pressured to lie to the public, the lawyers scrambling to clear up norm-breaking disasters, and the staffers whose careers have been reduced to ashes &#8211; to paint an unparalleled group portrait of an administration driven by self-preservation and paranoia.     </p>
<p>                    Rucker and Leonnig reveal Trump at his most unvarnished, showing the unhinged decision-making and incompetence that has floored officials and stunned foreign leaders. They portray unscripted calls with Vladimir Putin, steak dinners with Kim Jong-un, and calls with Theresa May so hostile that they left her aides shaken. They also take a hard look at Robert Mueller, Trump&#8217;s greatest antagonist to date, and how his investigation slowly unravelled an administration whose universal value is loyalty &#8211; not to country, but to the president himself.    </p>
<p>                    Grippingly told, A Very Stable Genius is a behind-the-scenes account of Trump&#8217;s vainglorious pursuit of power in his first term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Making Of Donald Trump &#8211; David Cay Johnston (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-making-of-donald-trump-david-cay-johnston-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-making-of-donald-trump-david-cay-johnston-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER that first revealed the Russia connection The culmination of nearly 30 years of reporting on Donald Trump, this in-depth report by Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter David Cay Johnston takes a revealingly close look at the mogul&#8217;s rise to prominence &#8212; and, now, ultimate power Covering the long arc of Trump&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-making-of-donald-trump-david-cay-johnston-abridged/">The Making Of Donald Trump &#8211; David Cay Johnston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER that first revealed the Russia connection The culmination of nearly 30 years of reporting on Donald Trump, this in-depth report by Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter David Cay Johnston takes a revealingly close look at the mogul&#8217;s rise to prominence &#8212; and, now, ultimate power  Covering the long arc of Trump&#8217;s career, Johnston tells the full story of how a boy from a quiet section of Queens, NY would become an entirely new, and complex, breed of public figure. Trump is a man of great media savvy, entrepreneurial spirit, and political clout. Yet his career has been plagued by legal troubles and mounting controversy.  From the origins of his family&#8217;s fortune, to his own too-big-to-fail business empire; from his education and early career, to his whirlwind and ultimately successful presidential bid, The Making of Donald Trump provides the fullest picture yet of Trump&#8217;s extraordinary ascendency. Love him or hate him, Trump&#8217;s massive influence is undeniable, and figures as diverse as Woody Guthrie (who wrote a scathing song about Trump&#8217;s father) and Red Scare prosecutor Roy Cohn, mob bosses and high rollers, as well as the average American voter, have all been pulled into his orbit.  Drawing on decades of interviews, financial records, court documents, and public statements, David Cay Johnston, who has covered Trump longer and more closely than any other journalist working today, gives us the most in-depth look yet at the man who has shocked the world. &#8220;Provides useful, vigorously reported overviews of Mr. Trump&#8217;s life and career &#8230; Mr. Johnston, who has followed the real estate impresario for nearly three decades, offers a searing indictment of his business practices and creative accounting.&#8221;&#8211;Michiko Kakutani, The New York Times &#8220;David Cay Johnston has given us this year&#8217;s must-read Trump book.&#8221;&#8211;Lawrence O&#8217;Donnell, MSNBC&#8217;s The Last Word &#8220;Johnston devastatingly covers ground he broke open as a reporter on the Trump beat in Philadelphia and at The New York Times&#8230;The best of investigative reporting is brought to bear on a man who could potentially lead the free world.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today &#8220;Carefully fleshes out the details of Trump&#8217;s known biography&#8230;with solid documentation.&#8221;&#8211;Tampa Bay Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-making-of-donald-trump-david-cay-johnston-abridged/">The Making Of Donald Trump &#8211; David Cay Johnston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>For the Record &#8211; David Cameron (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Administration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Opinion & Polls]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The political memoir of the decade&#8217; Sunday Times The referendum on Britain&#8217;s membership of the EU is one of the most controversial political events of our times. For the first time, the man who called that vote talks about the decision and its origins, as well as giving a candid account of his time at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/">For the Record &#8211; David Cameron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The political memoir of the decade&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                                The referendum on Britain&#8217;s membership of the EU is one of the most controversial political events of our times. For the first time, the man who called that vote talks about the decision and its origins, as well as giving a candid account of his time at the top of British politics.    </p>
<p>                              David Cameron was Conservative Party leader during the largest financial crash in living memory. The Arab Spring and the Eurozone crisis both started during his first year as prime minister. The backdrop to his time in office included the advent of ISIS, surging migration and a rapidly changing EU.    </p>
<p>                              Here he talks about how he confronted those challenges, from modernising a party that had suffered three successive electoral defeats to forming the first coalition government for seventy years. He sets out how he helped turn around Britain&#8217;s economy, implementing a modern, compassionate agenda that included education and welfare reform, the legalisation of gay marriage, the referendum on Scottish independence and world-leading environmental policies.    </p>
<p>                              David Cameron is searingly honest about the key players from his time in politics. And he is frank about himself &#8211; the things he got right and the things he got wrong. He opens up about family life too, including the tragic loss of his eldest son.    </p>
<p>                              We learn why he kept Britain&#8217;s promise on overseas aid spending and what it was like to commit British troops to conflicts in Libya, Iraq and Syria. He sets out how he won the first outright Conservative majority in nearly a quarter of a century, and describes the events leading up to the EU referendum, the renegotiation, the campaign &#8211; and his thoughts on it all today.    </p>
<p>                              It is the most compelling record yet of what it&#8217;s like to lead in modern times and to live behind the most famous door in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/">For the Record &#8211; David Cameron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life. Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life.    </p>
<p>                     Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a movie star. By the age of 21, he was living in Los Angeles and had been crowned Mr Universe. Within five years, he had learned English and become the greatest bodybuilder in the world. Within ten years, he had earned his college degree and was a millionaire from his business enterprises in real estate, landscaping and bodybuilding. He was also the winner of a Golden Globe Award for his debut as a dramatic actor in Stay Hungry.    </p>
<p>                     But that was only the beginning. The Terminator spawned numerous sequels and made him one of Hollywood&#8217;s biggest stars, as he had a series of hit films including Predator, Total Recall, True Lies and Twins. He married Maria Shriver, becoming part of the Kennedy clan, while going on to become the Republican governor of California, where he led the state through a budget crisis, natural disasters and political turmoil.     </p>
<p>                    It is the greatest immigrant success story of our time. His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. Until now, he has never told the full story of his life, in his own voice. Here is Arnold, with total recall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lawrence in Arabia : War, Deceit, Imperial Folly and the Making of the Modern Middle East &#8211; Scott Anderson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Battles & Campaigns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 1 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Arab Revolt against the Turks in World War One was, in the words of T.E. Lawrence, &#8216;a sideshow of a sideshow&#8217;. Amidst the slaughter in European trenches, the Western combatants paid scant attention to the Middle Eastern theatre. As a result, the conflict was shaped to a remarkable degree by a small handful of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/">Lawrence in Arabia : War, Deceit, Imperial Folly and the Making of the Modern Middle East &#8211; Scott Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Arab Revolt against the Turks in World War One was, in the words of T.E. Lawrence, &#8216;a sideshow of a sideshow&#8217;. Amidst the slaughter in European trenches, the Western combatants paid scant attention to the Middle Eastern theatre. As a result, the conflict was shaped to a remarkable degree by a small handful of adventurers and low-level officers far removed from the corridors of power.   At the centre of it all was Lawrence. In early 1914 he was an archaeologist excavating ruins in the sands of Syria; by 1917 he was battling both the enemy and his own government to bring about the vision he had for the Arab people. Operating in the Middle East at the same time, but to wildly different ends, were three other important players: a German attache, an American oilman and a committed Zionist. The intertwined paths of these four young men &#8211; the schemes they put in place, the battles they fought, the betrayals they endured and committed &#8211; mirror the grandeur, intrigue and tragedy of the war in the desert.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/">Lawrence in Arabia : War, Deceit, Imperial Folly and the Making of the Modern Middle East &#8211; Scott Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Autobiography of Malcolm X &#8211; Alex Haley, Malcolm X, Introduction by Paul Gilroy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Malcolm X&#8217;s The Autobiography of Malcolm X was written in collaboration with Alex Haley, author of Roots, and includes an introduction by Paul Gilroy, author of The Black Atlantic, in Penguin Modern Classics. From hustling, drug addiction and armed violence in America&#8217;s black ghettos Malcolm X turned, in a dramatic prison conversion, to the puritanical [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/">The Autobiography of Malcolm X &#8211; Alex Haley, Malcolm X, Introduction by Paul Gilroy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Malcolm X&#8217;s The Autobiography of Malcolm X was written in collaboration with Alex Haley, author of Roots, and includes an introduction by Paul Gilroy, author of The Black Atlantic, in Penguin Modern Classics.    </p>
<p>                    From hustling, drug addiction and armed violence in America&#8217;s black ghettos Malcolm X turned, in a dramatic prison conversion, to the puritanical fervour of the Black Muslims. As their spokesman he became identified in the white press as a terrifying teacher of race hatred; but to his direct audience, the oppressed American blacks, he brought hope and self-respect. This autobiography (written with Alex Haley) reveals his quick-witted integrity, usually obscured by batteries of frenzied headlines, and the fierce idealism which led him to reject both liberal hypocrisies and black racialism.    </p>
<p>                    Vilified by his critics as an anti-white demagogue, Malcolm X gave a voice to unheard African-Americans, bringing them pride, hope and fearlessness, and remains an inspirational and controversial figure.    </p>
<p>                    Malcolm X (1925-65), born Malcolm Little in Omaha, and also known as El-Hajj Malik El-Shabazz, lost both his parents at a young age. Leaving school early, he soon became part of Harlem&#8217;s underworld, and in 1946 he was sentenced to ten years&#8217; imprisonment. It was in prison that Malcolm X converted to Islam. Paroled in 1952, he became an outspoken defender of Muslim doctrines, formed the Organization of Afro-American Unity in 1963, and had received considerable publicity by the time of his assassination in 1965.    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed The Autobiography of Malcolm X, you might like Nelson Mandela&#8217;s No Easy Walk to Freedom, also available in Penguin Modern Classics.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This extraordinary autobiography is a brilliant, painful, important book&#8217;<br />
                    The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/">The Autobiography of Malcolm X &#8211; Alex Haley, Malcolm X, Introduction by Paul Gilroy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Truth Sounds Like : Robert F. Kennedy, James Baldwin, and Our Unfinished Conversation About Race in America &#8211; Michael Eric Dyson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-truth-sounds-like-robert-f-kennedy-james-baldwin-and-our-unfinished-conversation-about-race-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-truth-sounds-like-robert-f-kennedy-james-baldwin-and-our-unfinished-conversation-about-race-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Named a 2018 Notable Work of Nonfiction by The Washington Post NOW A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Winner, The 2018 Southern Book Prize NAMED A BEST/MOST ANTICIPATED BOOK OF 2018 BY: Chicago Tribune &#8211; Time &#8211; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly A stunning follow up to New York Times bestseller Tears We Cannot Stop The Washington Post: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-truth-sounds-like-robert-f-kennedy-james-baldwin-and-our-unfinished-conversation-about-race-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/">What Truth Sounds Like : Robert F. Kennedy, James Baldwin, and Our Unfinished Conversation About Race in America &#8211; Michael Eric Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Named a 2018 Notable Work of Nonfiction by The Washington Post     </p>
<p>                    NOW A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Winner, The 2018 Southern Book Prize    </p>
<p>                    NAMED A BEST/MOST ANTICIPATED BOOK OF 2018 BY: Chicago Tribune &#8211; Time &#8211; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly     </p>
<p>                    A stunning follow up to New York Times bestseller Tears We Cannot Stop     </p>
<p>                    The Washington Post: Passionately written.<br />
                    Chris Matthews, MSNBC: A beautifully written book.<br />
                    Shaun King: &#8220;I kid you not-I think it&#8217;s the most important book I&#8217;ve read all year&#8230;&#8221;      </p>
<p>                    Harry Belafonte: &#8220;Dyson has finally written the book I always wanted to read&#8230;a tour de force.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Joy-Ann Reid: A work of searing prose and seminal brilliance&#8230; Dyson takes that once in a lifetime conversation between black excellence and pain and the white heroic narrative, and drives it right into the heart of our current politics and culture, leaving the reader reeling and reckoning.     </p>
<p>                    Robin D. G. Kelley: &#8220;Dyson masterfully refracts our present racial conflagration&#8230; he reminds us that Black artists and intellectuals bear an awesome responsibility to speak truth to power.     </p>
<p>                    President Barack Obama:  Everybody who speaks after Michael Eric Dyson pales in comparison.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    In 2015 BLM activist Julius Jones confronted Presidential candidate Hillary Clinton with an urgent query: &#8220;What in your heart has changed that&#8217;s going to change the direction of this country?&#8221; &#8220;I don&#8217;t believe you just change hearts,&#8221; she protested. &#8220;I believe you change laws.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    The fraught conflict between conscience and politics &#8211; between morality and power &#8211; in addressing race hardly began with Clinton. An electrifying and traumatic encounter in the sixties crystallized these furious disputes.     </p>
<p>                    In 1963 Attorney General Robert Kennedy sought out James Baldwin to explain the rage that threatened to engulf black America. Baldwin brought along some friends, including playwright Lorraine Hansberry, psychologist Kenneth Clark, and a valiant activist, Jerome Smith. It was Smith&#8217;s relentless, unfiltered fury that set Kennedy on his heels, reducing him to sullen silence.     </p>
<p>                    Kennedy walked away from the nearly three-hour meeting angry &#8211; that the black folk assembled didn&#8217;t understand politics, and that they weren&#8217;t as easy to talk to as Martin Luther King. But especially that they were more interested in witness than policy. But Kennedy&#8217;s anger quickly gave way to empathy, especially for Smith. &#8220;I guess if I were in his shoes&#8230;I might feel differently about this country.&#8221; Kennedy set about changing policy &#8211; the meeting having transformed his thinking in fundamental ways.     </p>
<p>                    There was more: every big argument about race that persists to this day got a hearing in that room. Smith declaring that he&#8217;d never fight for his country given its racist tendencies, and Kennedy being appalled at such lack of patriotism, tracks the disdain for black dissent in our own time. His belief that black folk were ungrateful for the Kennedys&#8217; efforts to make things better shows up in our day as the charge that black folk wallow in the politics of ingratitude and victimhood. The contributions of black queer folk to racial progress still cause a stir. BLM has been accused of harboring a covert queer agenda. The immigrant experience, like that of Kennedy &#8211; versus the racial experience of Baldwin &#8211; is a cudgel to excoriate black folk for lacking hustle and ingenuity. The questioning of whether folk who are interracially partnered can authentically communicate black interests persists. And we grapple still with the responsibility of black intellectuals and artists to bring about social change.     </p>
<p>                    What Truth Sounds Like exists at the tense intersection of the conflict between politics and prophecy &#8211; of whether we embrace political resolution or moral redemption to fix our fractured racial landscape. The future of race and democracy hang in the balance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-truth-sounds-like-robert-f-kennedy-james-baldwin-and-our-unfinished-conversation-about-race-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/">What Truth Sounds Like : Robert F. Kennedy, James Baldwin, and Our Unfinished Conversation About Race in America &#8211; Michael Eric Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
