<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Health Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/health-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/health-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Health Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/health-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</title>
		<link>/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Break the rules, not the fast with world-renowned biohacker and New York Times bestselling author Dave Asprey. For more than a decade, the Bulletproof founder Dave Asprey has shared his unique point of view and expertise to help fans become the best versions of themselves. From living longer to getting smarter, maximising performance to practising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/">Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Break the rules, not the fast with world-renowned biohacker and New York Times bestselling author Dave Asprey.</p>
<p>                              For more than a decade, the Bulletproof founder Dave Asprey has shared his unique point of view and expertise to help fans become the best versions of themselves. From living longer to getting smarter, maximising performance to practising mindfulness, Dave&#8217;s followers look to him for his take on the most effective techniques to become healthier and more powerful than most doctors think is possible.</p>
<p>                              Asprey has been fasting for years, long before it gained widespread popularity, and if you&#8217;re a fan of The Bulletproof Diet, you have been enjoying some of the benefits of Intermittent Fasting too.</p>
<p>                              In Fast This Way, Dave asks readers to forget everything they think they know about the ancient practice and takes them on a journey through cutting-edge science to examine the ways novice fasters and Intermittent Fasting loyalists can up-end their relationship with food and upgrade their fasting game beyond calorie restriction.  </p>
<p>                     What IF eating the right foods at the right time can actually enhance your fast?<br />
                     What IF how you work out and sleep could trick your body into thinking you are fasting?<br />
                     What IF it were easy to skip a meal, or two, or three?<br />
                     What IF fasting is different for women, can be personalised to your genes, and can impact your mental health?<br />
                     What IF all fasts could be created equal?</p>
<p>                              Fast This Way is a compelling read through the latest thinking on fasting and gives readers the manual and toolkit to make the most of their fasts and their personal biology.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/">Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hidden Valley Road &#8211; Robert Kolker</title>
		<link>/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unforgettable&#8217; The Times &#8216;Grippingly told and brilliantly reported&#8217; Mail on Sunday &#8216;Startlingly intimate&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Groundbreaking&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Exceptional and moving&#8217; Spectator &#8216;Hidden Valley Road contains everything: scientific intrigue, meticulous reporting, startling revelations, and, most of all, a profound sense of humanity. It is that rare book that can be read again [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/">Hidden Valley Road &#8211; Robert Kolker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unforgettable&#8217; The Times &#8216;Grippingly told and brilliantly reported&#8217; Mail on Sunday &#8216;Startlingly intimate&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Groundbreaking&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Exceptional and moving&#8217; Spectator &#8216;Hidden Valley Road contains everything: scientific intrigue, meticulous reporting, startling revelations, and, most of all, a profound sense of humanity. It is that rare book that can be read again and again.&#8217; -David Grann, author of Killers of the Flower Moon One of the New York Times&#8217; &#8217;20 most anticipated books of 2020&#8242;: the heartrending story of a mid-century American family with twelve children, six of them diagnosed with schizophrenia, that became science&#8217;s great hope in the quest to understand the disease. &#8216;An extraordinary case study and tour de force of reporting.&#8217; -Sylvia Nasar, author of A Beautiful Mind Don and Mimi Galvin seemed to be living the American dream. After World War II, Don&#8217;s work with the Air Force brought them to Colorado, where their twelve children perfectly spanned the baby boom: the oldest born in 1945, the youngest in 1965. In those years, there was an established script for a family like the Galvins &#8211; aspiration, hard work, upward mobility, domestic harmony &#8211; and they worked hard to play their parts. But behind the scenes was a different story: psychological breakdown, sudden shocking violence, hidden abuse. By the mid-1970s, six of the ten Galvin boys, one after the other, were diagnosed as schizophrenic. How could all this happen to one family? What took place inside the house on Hidden Valley Road was so extraordinary that the Galvins became one of the first families to be studied by the National Institutes of Mental Health. Their story offers a shadow history of the science of schizophrenia, from the era of institutionalization, lobotomy, and the schizophrenogenic mother, to the search for genetic markers for the disease, always amidst profound disagreements about the nature of the illness itself. And unbeknownst to the Galvins, samples of their DNA informed decades of genetic research that continues today, offering paths to treatment, prediction, and even eradication of the disease for future generations. With clarity and compassion, bestselling and award-winning author Robert Kolker uncovers one family&#8217;s unforgettable legacy of suffering, love and hope. &#8216;This book tore my heart out. It is a revelation-about the history of mental health treatment, about trauma, foremost about family-and a more-than-worthy follow-up to Robert Kolker&#8217;s brilliant Lost Girls.&#8217; -Megan Abbott, Edgar Award-winning author of Dare Me and Give Me Your Hand</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/">Hidden Valley Road &#8211; Robert Kolker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</title>
		<link>/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8211; Over five million copies sold worldwide! From renowned psychiatrist Dr. David D. Burns, the revolutionary volume that popularized Dr. Aaron T. Beck&#8217;s cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) and has helped millions combat feelings of depression and develop greater self-esteem. Anxiety and depression are the most common mental illnesses in the world, affecting 18% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/">Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8211; Over five million copies sold worldwide!</p>
<p>                    From renowned psychiatrist Dr. David D. Burns, the revolutionary volume that popularized Dr. Aaron T. Beck&#8217;s cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) and has helped millions combat feelings of depression and develop greater self-esteem.</p>
<p>                    Anxiety and depression are the most common mental illnesses in the world, affecting 18% of the U.S. population every year. But for many, the path to recovery seems daunting, endless, or completely out of reach.</p>
<p>                    The good news is that anxiety, guilt, pessimism, procrastination, low self-esteem, and other black holes of depression can be alleviated. In Feeling Good, eminent psychiatrist, David D. Burns, M.D., outlines the remarkable, scientifically proven techniques that will immediately lift your spirits and help you develop a positive outlook on life, enabling you to: Nip negative feelings in the budRecognize what causes your mood swingsDeal with guiltHandle hostility and criticismOvercome addiction to love and approvalBuild self-esteemFeel good everyday</p>
<p>                    This groundbreaking, life-changing book has helped millions overcome negative thoughts and discover joy in their daily lives. You owe it to yourself to FEEL GOOD!</p>
<p>                    I would personally evaluate David Burns&#8217; Feeling Good as one of the most significant books to come out of the last third of the Twentieth Century. ?- Dr. David F. Maas, Professor of English, Ambassador University</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/">Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Vitamin Solution : Two Doctors Clear the Confusion about Vitamins and Your Health &#8211; Dr. Romy Block, Dr. Arielle Levitan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-vitamin-solution-two-doctors-clear-the-confusion-about-vitamins-and-your-health-dr-romy-block-dr-arielle-levitan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-vitamin-solution-two-doctors-clear-the-confusion-about-vitamins-and-your-health-dr-romy-block-dr-arielle-levitan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you confused about vitamins? Unsure of which ones you need for optimal health, and what levels are safe? You&#8217;re not alone. Many people&#8217;s health issues could be improved with vitamins-if they only knew how to use them. In this award-winning book, The Vitamin Solution, Drs. Romy Block and Arielle Levitan provide a common-sense, medically [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-vitamin-solution-two-doctors-clear-the-confusion-about-vitamins-and-your-health-dr-romy-block-dr-arielle-levitan-abridged/">The Vitamin Solution : Two Doctors Clear the Confusion about Vitamins and Your Health &#8211; Dr. Romy Block, Dr. Arielle Levitan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you confused about vitamins? Unsure of which ones you need for optimal health, and what levels are safe? You&#8217;re not alone. Many people&#8217;s health issues could be improved with vitamins-if they only knew how to use them.     </p>
<p>                    In this award-winning book, The Vitamin Solution, Drs. Romy Block and Arielle Levitan provide a common-sense, medically sound approach to using vitamins to improve your diet, exercise plan, and overall health. In clear, accessible, language, they explain which vitamins and supplements can be helpful, which can be harmful, and which are altogether unnecessary; explore health topics including migraine, hair loss, fatigue, irritable bowel syndrome, hot flashes, and more; and address preventive care, providing insights on topics such as screening tests, weight loss, and preserving memory. Illuminating and accessible, The Vitamin Solution is an indispensable guide to safely incorporating vitamins and supplements into any lifestyle-one that will leave readers educated, informed, and armed with simple, everyday strategies for bettering their health.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-vitamin-solution-two-doctors-clear-the-confusion-about-vitamins-and-your-health-dr-romy-block-dr-arielle-levitan-abridged/">The Vitamin Solution : Two Doctors Clear the Confusion about Vitamins and Your Health &#8211; Dr. Romy Block, Dr. Arielle Levitan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Lucky Years : How to Thrive in the Brave New World of Health &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-lucky-years-how-to-thrive-in-the-brave-new-world-of-health-david-b-agus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-lucky-years-how-to-thrive-in-the-brave-new-world-of-health-david-b-agus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bestselling author David Agus unveils the brave new world of medicine, one in which we can take control of our health like never before and doctors can fine-tune strategies and weapons to prevent illness. In his first bestseller, The End of Illness, David Agus revealed how to add vibrant years to your life by knowing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-lucky-years-how-to-thrive-in-the-brave-new-world-of-health-david-b-agus-abridged/">The Lucky Years : How to Thrive in the Brave New World of Health &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bestselling author David Agus unveils the brave new world of medicine, one in which we can take control of our health like never before and doctors can fine-tune strategies and weapons to prevent illness.    </p>
<p>                    In his first bestseller, The End of Illness, David Agus revealed how to add vibrant years to your life by knowing the real facts of health. In this book, he builds on that theme by showing why this is the luckiest time yet to be alive, giving you the keys to the new kingdom of wellness.     </p>
<p>                    Medicine is undergoing rapid change. In the old world, you followed general principles and doctors treated you based on broad, one-size-fits-all solutions. In this new golden age, you&#8217;ll be able to take full advantage of the latest scientific findings and leverage the power of technology to customize your care. Only those who know how to access and adapt to these breakthroughs &#8211; without being distracted by hyped ideas and bad medicine &#8211; will benefit. Imagine being able to get fit and lose weight without dieting, train your immune system to fight cancer, edit your DNA to avoid a certain fate, erase the risk of a heart attack, reverse aging, and know exactly which drugs to take to optimize health with zero side effects.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-lucky-years-how-to-thrive-in-the-brave-new-world-of-health-david-b-agus-abridged/">The Lucky Years : How to Thrive in the Brave New World of Health &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Vagina Bible : The vulva and the vagina &#8211; separating the myth from the medicine &#8211; Dr. Jennifer Gunter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-vagina-bible-the-vulva-and-the-vagina-separating-the-myth-from-the-medicine-dr-jennifer-gunter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-vagina-bible-the-vulva-and-the-vagina-separating-the-myth-from-the-medicine-dr-jennifer-gunter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does eating sugar cause yeast infections? Does pubic hair have a function? Should you have a vulvovaginal care regimen? Will your vagina shrivel up if you go without sex? What&#8217;s the truth about the HPV vaccine? So many important questions, so much convincing, confusing, contradictory misinformation! In this age of click bait, pseudoscience, and celebrity-endorsed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-vagina-bible-the-vulva-and-the-vagina-separating-the-myth-from-the-medicine-dr-jennifer-gunter-abridged/">The Vagina Bible : The vulva and the vagina &#8211; separating the myth from the medicine &#8211; Dr. Jennifer Gunter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does eating sugar cause yeast infections? Does pubic hair have a function?<br />
                    Should you have a vulvovaginal care regimen?<br />
                    Will your vagina shrivel up if you go without sex?<br />
                    What&#8217;s the truth about the HPV vaccine?    </p>
<p>                    So many important questions, so much convincing, confusing, contradictory misinformation! In this age of click bait, pseudoscience, and celebrity-endorsed products, it&#8217;s easy to be overwhelmed-whether it&#8217;s websites, advice from well-meaning friends, uneducated partners, and even healthcare providers. So how do you separate facts from fiction? Obstetrician Jen Gunter, an expert on women&#8217;s health-and the internet&#8217;s most popular go-to doc-comes to the rescue with a book that debunks the myths and educates and empowers women. From reproductive health to the impact of antibiotics and probiotics, and the latest trends, including vaginal steaming, vaginal marijuana products, and jade eggs, Gunter takes us on a factual, fun-filled journey.     </p>
<p>                    Discover the truth about:    </p>
<p>                    *         The vaginal microbiome<br />
                    *         Genital hygiene, lubricants, and hormone myths and fallacies<br />
                    *         How diet impacts vaginal health<br />
                    *         Stem cells and the vagina<br />
                    *         Cosmetic vaginal surgery<br />
                    *         What changes to expect during pregnancy, after childbirth, and through menopause<br />
                    *         How medicine fails women by dismissing symptoms    </p>
<p>                    Plus:<br />
                    *         Thongs vs. lace: the best underwear for vaginal health<br />
                    *         How to select a tampon<br />
                    *         The full glory of the clitoris and the myth of the G Spot    </p>
<p>                    &#8230; And so much more. Whether you&#8217;re a twenty-six-year-old worried that her labia are &#8216;uncool&#8217; or a sixty-six-year-old dealing with painful sex, this comprehensive guide is sure to become a lifelong trusted resource.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-vagina-bible-the-vulva-and-the-vagina-separating-the-myth-from-the-medicine-dr-jennifer-gunter-abridged/">The Vagina Bible : The vulva and the vagina &#8211; separating the myth from the medicine &#8211; Dr. Jennifer Gunter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone struggles with sleep from time to time, but when sleepless nights and overtired days become the norm, your well-being is compromised, and frustration and worry increase-including concerns about what&#8217;s stopping you from getting the sleep you need, and what can be done about it. So, how do you stop the cycle of relentless worries [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/">End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone struggles with sleep from time to time, but when sleepless nights and overtired days become the norm, your well-being is compromised, and frustration and worry increase-including concerns about what&#8217;s stopping you from getting the sleep you need, and what can be done about it. So, how do you stop the cycle of relentless worries and restless nights?    </p>
<p>                    End the Insomnia Struggle offers a comprehensive, medication-free program that can be individually tailored for anyone who struggles with insomnia. Integrating the physiology of sleep, and proven-effective approaches from cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I) and acceptance and commitment therapy (ACT), this book provides step-by-step guidance for developing your own treatment plan according to your particular challenges with insomnia.    </p>
<p>                    With this book, you&#8217;ll have everything you need to overcome the relentless thoughts, ruminations, and stress of insomnia. Utilizing these evidence-based strategies and easy-to-use tools, you&#8217;ll finally get to sleep, stay asleep, and wake up rested and ready to face the world as your best self, day after day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/">End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spark &#8211; Dr John J. Ratey, Eric Hagerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exercise is not only good for the body: it can transform your mind too. This new scientific revolution will teach you how to boost brain cells, protect yourself against mental illness and dementia, and ensure success in exams and the workplace. We all know that exercise is good for the body. But did you know [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/">Spark &#8211; Dr John J. Ratey, Eric Hagerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exercise is not only good for the body: it can transform your mind  too. This new scientific revolution will teach you how to boost brain  cells, protect yourself against mental illness and dementia, and ensure  success in exams and the workplace.    </p>
<p>                    We all know that exercise is good for the body. But did you know that it can transform your mind? This new scientific revolution will teach you how to boost brain cells, protect yourself against mental illness and dementia, and ensure success in exams and the workplace.     </p>
<p>                    Follow the SPARK! training regimen and build your brain to its peak performance. This book will change the way you think about exercise &#8211; and, for that matter, the way you think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/">Spark &#8211; Dr John J. Ratey, Eric Hagerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Period Power : Harness Your Hormones and Get Your Cycle Working For You &#8211; Maisie Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gynaecology & Obstetrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Reproduction, Growth & Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Midwifery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hill&#8217;s advice is straightforward and no-nonsense&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian &#8216;A life-transforming book&#8230; fascinating &#8211; Daily Mail &#8216;Maisie Hill has written a bloody brilliant book (pun intended). Everything you need to know about periods and how they affect you and your life is here. It&#8217;s revolutionary&#8217; &#8211; Miranda Sawyer &#8216;Thank GOODNESS for Maisie Hill! Flipping open [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/">Period Power : Harness Your Hormones and Get Your Cycle Working For You &#8211; Maisie Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hill&#8217;s advice is straightforward and no-nonsense&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A life-transforming book&#8230; fascinating &#8211; Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Maisie Hill has written a bloody brilliant book (pun intended). Everything you need to know about periods and how they affect you and your life is here. It&#8217;s revolutionary&#8217; &#8211; Miranda Sawyer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thank GOODNESS for Maisie Hill! Flipping open the lid on a vital conversation. It&#8217;s about time we claimed the power of our periods!&#8217; &#8211; Gemma Cairney, broadcaster &#038; co-founder of Boom Shakalaka Productions    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is such an important book. Maisie&#8217;s insights and cycle strategy have changed my life and my cycle. Period Power is written with such intelligence, humour and a deep understanding of women&#8217;s health. If you have a period you need to read this book.&#8217; &#8211; Anna Jones, author of The Modern Cook&#8217;s Year    </p>
<p>                    A profound and practical blueprint for aligning daily life with your menstrual cycle.    </p>
<p>                    Period Power is the handbook to periods and hormones that will leave you wondering why the hell nobody told you this sooner.    </p>
<p>                    The hormones of the menstrual cycle profoundly influence our energy, mood and behaviour, but all too often we&#8217;re taught that our hormones make us unreliable, moody bitches, or that it&#8217;s our lot in life to put up with &#8216;women&#8217;s problems&#8217;. Maisie Hill, a women&#8217;s health practitioner, knows the power of working with the menstrual cycle and refuses to accept this theory. Instead, Maisie believes that our hormones are there to serve us and, if utilized correctly, can be used to help you get what you want out of life. Yes, we are hormonal, and that&#8217;s a very good thing.    </p>
<p>                    This revolutionary book reveals everything you need to know about taking control of your menstrual cycle and outlines The Cycle Strategy to help us perform at our best, throughout our cycle. In Period Power you will discover how to:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; maximise your natural superpowers each month while making adjustments for the darker days, and use Maisie&#8217;s favourite tips to improve them<br />
                    &#8211; identify your personal patterns, powers and pitfalls for each phase of the menstrual cycle<br />
                    &#8211; plan your month to perform at your best in all aspects of your life<br />
                    &#8211; figure out if you have a hormonal imbalance and what to do about it.    </p>
<p>                    Period Power is a no-nonsense guide with all the tools you need to improve your menstrual health.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/">Period Power : Harness Your Hormones and Get Your Cycle Working For You &#8211; Maisie Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ultimate Introduction to NLP: How to build a successful life &#8211; Richard Bandler, Alessio Roberti, Owen Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ultimate-introduction-to-nlp-how-to-build-a-successful-life-richard-bandler-alessio-roberti-owen-fitzpatrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neuro Linguistic Programming (NLP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ultimate-introduction-to-nlp-how-to-build-a-successful-life-richard-bandler-alessio-roberti-owen-fitzpatrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Bandler, co-creator of NLP and the man who inspired Paul McKenna to greatness, collaborates with Alessio Roberti and Owen Fitzpatrick to reveal how to unleash your true potential and transform your life. Richard Bandler &#8211; the world-renowned co-creator of NLP who has helped millions around the world change their lives for the better &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultimate-introduction-to-nlp-how-to-build-a-successful-life-richard-bandler-alessio-roberti-owen-fitzpatrick-abridged/">The Ultimate Introduction to NLP: How to build a successful life &#8211; Richard Bandler, Alessio Roberti, Owen Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Richard Bandler, co-creator of NLP and the man who inspired Paul McKenna to greatness, collaborates with Alessio Roberti and Owen Fitzpatrick to reveal how to unleash your true potential and transform your life.    </p>
<p>                              Richard Bandler &#8211; the world-renowned co-creator of NLP who has helped millions around the world change their lives for the better &#8211; has teamed up with Italian NLP Master Trainer Alessio and co-founder of the Irish Institute of NLP Owen, to craft a simple yet engaging story of one man&#8217;s personal change and discovery, to help readers understand the remarkable principles of NLP.    </p>
<p>                              Inspiring and easy-to-read, this fable recreates the experience of being at a workshop with Bandler. Rather than explaining the theories, An Introduction to NLP illustrates the principles and simple techniques that Bandler has developed over the past 35 years in action.    </p>
<p>                              This inspirational book gives you the tools to change your life, overcoming the things that are holding you back: your phobias, depression, habits, psychosomatic illnesses or learning disorders.    </p>
<p>                              Through the simple techniques of NLP, you too can become a strong, happy, successful person and achieve your goals.    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;The must have self-help book!&#8217; Paul McKenna</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultimate-introduction-to-nlp-how-to-build-a-successful-life-richard-bandler-alessio-roberti-owen-fitzpatrick-abridged/">The Ultimate Introduction to NLP: How to build a successful life &#8211; Richard Bandler, Alessio Roberti, Owen Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Game Changers : What Leaders, Innovators and Mavericks Do to Win at Life &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/game-changers-what-leaders-innovators-and-mavericks-do-to-win-at-life-dave-asprey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/game-changers-what-leaders-innovators-and-mavericks-do-to-win-at-life-dave-asprey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet answers the question &#8220;How do I kick more ass?&#8221;-providing proven techniques for becoming happier, healthier, and smarter, culled from the wisdom and insight of world-class thought leaders and mavericks of science and business. When Dave Asprey started his Bulletproof Radio podcast more than five years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/game-changers-what-leaders-innovators-and-mavericks-do-to-win-at-life-dave-asprey-abridged/">Game Changers : What Leaders, Innovators and Mavericks Do to Win at Life &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet answers the question &#8220;How do I kick more ass?&#8221;-providing proven techniques for becoming happier, healthier, and smarter, culled from the wisdom and insight of world-class thought leaders and mavericks of science and business.    </p>
<p>                              When Dave Asprey started his Bulletproof Radio podcast more than five years ago, he sought out thought leaders and influencers in an array of disciplines, from biochemists to business titans to mediation masters. These folks were some of the top performing humans in the world, people who had changed their areas of study or even pioneered entirely new fields. Dave wanted to know: What did they have in common? What mattered most to them? What makes them so successful at what they do-and what makes them happiest? And so, at the end of each interview, Dave began asking the same question: &#8220;What are your top three recommendations for people who want to kick more ass?&#8221;<br />
                    Combing through the recordings, looking for patterns and common threads, he found that the wisdom gleaned from these highly successful people can be distilled into three main categories: body, mind, and spirit. Game Changers is the culmination of Dave&#8217;s years-long statistical analysis of these conversations, offering forty-six science-backed, high performance &#8220;laws&#8221; that are a virtual playbook for how to become not only more successful, but also happier and healthier.<br />
                    Each chapter of Game Changers is structured around one of these laws. Dave combines anecdotes from game changers like Daniel Amen, David Perlmutter, Arianna Huffington, Dan Harris, and Tim Ferriss with his own research and practical advice that readers can put into action immediately. From practising gratitude and mindfulness to prioritising social connections and sex, taming fear and anxiety to optimising nutrition and movement, Dave brings together the wisdom of today&#8217;s game-changers to help everyone optimise their lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/game-changers-what-leaders-innovators-and-mavericks-do-to-win-at-life-dave-asprey-abridged/">Game Changers : What Leaders, Innovators and Mavericks Do to Win at Life &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Stress : Four Steps to Rewire Your Brain &#8211; Don Joseph Goewey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-stress-four-steps-to-rewire-your-brain-don-joseph-goewey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-stress-four-steps-to-rewire-your-brain-don-joseph-goewey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With this simple, straightforward solution, you can switch your brain&#8217;s autopilot from habitual stress and anxiety to a mindset that is calm and wired for success. Stress debilitates and even damages the brain, inhibiting you from living life to the fullest. From your career to your family to your golf score, everything depends on higher [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-stress-four-steps-to-rewire-your-brain-don-joseph-goewey-abridged/">The End of Stress : Four Steps to Rewire Your Brain &#8211; Don Joseph Goewey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With this simple, straightforward solution, you can switch your brain&#8217;s autopilot from habitual stress and anxiety to a mindset that is calm and wired for success.     </p>
<p>                    Stress debilitates and even damages the brain, inhibiting you from living life to the fullest. From your career to your family to your golf score, everything depends on higher brain networks functioning at optimum. That&#8217;s why alleviating stress is the key to success-and why changing your brain is the first step to sustaining more joy, peace, and fulfilment at every level of life.     </p>
<p>                    In The End of Stress, Don Joseph Goewey offers an easy, four-step method that will increase your brainpower and end anxiety. Drawing on the latest research in neuroscience and neuroplasticity, Goewey&#8217;s cutting-edge approach has been tested through webinars and seminars in high-stress environments and proven effective from chief executives, managers, and engineers to blue-collar construction workers.     </p>
<p>                    You have the power to reach your highest potential-but it all starts with the brain. The End of Stress gives you the tools you need to transcend stress and make every day your best day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-stress-four-steps-to-rewire-your-brain-don-joseph-goewey-abridged/">The End of Stress : Four Steps to Rewire Your Brain &#8211; Don Joseph Goewey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simplicity Parenting : Using the Extraordinary Power of Less to Raise Calmer, Happier, and More Secure Kids &#8211; Kim John Payne, Lisa M. Ross (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s busier, faster society is waging an undeclared war on childhood. With too much stuff, too many choices, and too little time, children can become anxious, have trouble with friends and school, or even be diagnosed with behavioral problems. Now internationally renowned family consultant Kim John Payne helps parents reclaim for their children the space [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/">Simplicity Parenting : Using the Extraordinary Power of Less to Raise Calmer, Happier, and More Secure Kids &#8211; Kim John Payne, Lisa M. Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s busier, faster society is waging an undeclared war on childhood. With too much stuff, too many choices, and too little time, children can become anxious, have trouble with friends and school, or even be diagnosed with behavioral problems. Now internationally renowned family consultant Kim John Payne helps parents reclaim for their children the space and freedom that all kids need for their attention to deepen and their individuality to flourish. Simplicity Parenting offers inspiration, ideas, and a blueprint for change:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Streamline your home environment. Reduce the amount of toys, books, and clutter&#8211;as well as the lights, sounds, and general sensory overload.<br />
                    &#8211; Establish rhythms and rituals. Discover ways to ease daily tensions, create battle-free mealtimes and bedtimes, and tell if your child is overwhelmed.<br />
                    &#8211; Schedule a break in the schedule. Establish intervals of calm and connection in your child&#8217;s daily torrent of constant doing.<br />
                    &#8211; Scale back on media and parental involvement. Manage your children&#8217;s &#8220;screen time&#8221; to limit the endless deluge of information and stimulation.     </p>
<p>                    A manifesto for protecting the grace of childhood, Simplicity Parenting is an eloquent guide to bringing new rhythms to bear on the lifelong art of raising children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/">Simplicity Parenting : Using the Extraordinary Power of Less to Raise Calmer, Happier, and More Secure Kids &#8211; Kim John Payne, Lisa M. Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers -Revised Edition &#8211; M. Sapolsky, M. Sapolsky, Robert, Robert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmetics, Hair & Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now in a third edition, Robert M. Sapolsky&#8217;s acclaimed and successful Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers features new chapters on how stress affects sleep and addiction, as well as new insights into anxiety and personality disorder and the impact of spirituality on managing stress. As Sapolsky explains, most of us do not lie awake at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/">Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers -Revised Edition &#8211; M. Sapolsky, M. Sapolsky, Robert, Robert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now in a third edition, Robert M. Sapolsky&#8217;s acclaimed and successful Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers features new chapters on how stress affects sleep and addiction, as well as new insights into anxiety and personality disorder and the impact of spirituality on managing stress. As Sapolsky explains, most of us do not lie awake at night worrying about whether we have leprosy or malaria. Instead, the diseases we fear &#8211; and the ones that plague us now &#8211; are illnesses brought on by the slow accumulation of damage, such as heart disease and cancer. When we worry or experience stress, our body turns on the same physiological responses that an animal&#8217;s does, but we do not resolve conflict in the same way &#8211; through fighting or fleeing. Over time, this activation of a stress response makes us literally sick. Combining cutting-edge research with a healthy dose of good humour and practical advice, Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers explains how prolonged stress causes or intensifies a range of physical and mental afflictions, including depression, ulcers, colitis, heart disease, and more. It also provides essential guidance to controlling our stress responses.<br />
                    This new edition promises to be the most comprehensive and engaging one yet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/">Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers -Revised Edition &#8211; M. Sapolsky, M. Sapolsky, Robert, Robert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat Move Sleep : Why Small Choices Make a Big Difference &#8211; Tom Rath (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eat-move-sleep-why-small-choices-make-a-big-difference-tom-rath-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eat-move-sleep-why-small-choices-make-a-big-difference-tom-rath-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eat Move Sleep will help make good decisions automatic &#8211; more than a book &#8211; this is a new way to live. From Tom Rath, author of StrengthsFinders 2.0, comes a powerful book about what people can do to lead healthier lives. Eat Move Sleep features Tom&#8217;s deeply personal story, supported by practical, credible, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-move-sleep-why-small-choices-make-a-big-difference-tom-rath-abridged/">Eat Move Sleep : Why Small Choices Make a Big Difference &#8211; Tom Rath (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eat Move Sleep will help make good decisions automatic &#8211; more than a book &#8211; this is a new way to live. From Tom Rath, author of StrengthsFinders 2.0, comes a powerful book about what people can do to lead healthier lives. Eat Move Sleep features Tom&#8217;s deeply personal story, supported by practical, credible, and timeless ideas from more than a decade of research. Eat Move Sleep focuses on all three components and their interconnectedness. Comprehensive yet simple, rooted in cutting edge research, and sound advice that&#8217;s valuable to everyone.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-move-sleep-why-small-choices-make-a-big-difference-tom-rath-abridged/">Eat Move Sleep : Why Small Choices Make a Big Difference &#8211; Tom Rath (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oncology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases. Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases.      </p>
<p>                    Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to identify the strategies and dosages for using food to transform your resilience and health in Eat to Beat Disease.     </p>
<p>                    We have radically underestimated our body&#8217;s power to transform and restore our health. Pioneering physician scientist, Dr. William Li, empowers readers by showing them the evidence behind over 200 health-boosting foods that can starve cancer, reduce your risk of dementia, and beat dozens of avoidable diseases. Eat to Beat Disease isn&#8217;t about what foods to avoid, but rather is a life-changing guide to the hundreds of healing foods to add to your meals that support the body&#8217;s defense systems, including: PlumsCinnamonJasmine teaRed wine and beerBlack BeansSan Marzano tomatoesOlive oilPacific oystersCheeses like Jarlsberg, Camembert and cheddarSourdough bread<br />
                    The book&#8217;s plan shows you how to integrate the foods you already love into any diet or health plan to activate your body&#8217;s health defense systems-Angiogenesis, Regeneration, Microbiome, DNA Protection, and Immunity-to fight cancer, diabetes, cardiovascular, neurodegenerative autoimmune diseases, and other debilitating conditions.     </p>
<p>                    Both informative and practical, Eat to Beat Disease explains the science of healing and prevention, the strategies for using food to actively transform health, and points the science of wellbeing and disease prevention in an exhilarating new direction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Algebra of Happiness : The pursuit of success, love and what it all means &#8211; Scott Galloway (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author, a provocative book of hard-won wisdom for achieving a fulfilling career and life. &#8211; How can you have a meaningful career, not just a lucrative one? &#8211; Is a work/life balance really possible? &#8211; What does it take to make a long-term relationship succeed? &#8211; What can you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/">The Algebra of Happiness : The pursuit of success, love and what it all means &#8211; Scott Galloway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author, a provocative book of hard-won wisdom for achieving a  fulfilling career and life.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; How can you have a meaningful career, not just a lucrative one?<br />
                    &#8211; Is a work/life balance really possible?<br />
                    &#8211; What does it take to make a long-term relationship succeed?<br />
                    &#8211; What can you do now so there are no regrets aged 40, 50 or 80?    </p>
<p>                                   As Scott Galloway puts it, by the time you hit your mid twenties sh*t gets real. Life become stressful. Even the smart, the hard working and the elite can feel lost in a chaotic, noisy and unpredictable world. As a professor at New York University&#8217;s Stern School of Business, the debate in Galloway&#8217;s MBA class often veers away from business strategy to the challenging issue of life strategies. Which is why Galloway, in his signature, take-no-prisoners style, has developed a dynamic formula for a life well lived.    </p>
<p>                     In The Algebra of Happiness Galloway tells you how life can be navigated and negotiated better to maximise happiness and minimise the inevitable stress. Delivering practical advice and hard-won wisdom on everything from when to own property to how hard to work, this is self-help for anyone struggling with life&#8217;s big questions. Through simple equations that measure the relationship between success, resilience and failure or the correlation between happiness and money, Galloway attempts to convert intangible advice to tangible equations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/">The Algebra of Happiness : The pursuit of success, love and what it all means &#8211; Scott Galloway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beat Sugar Addiction Now! : The Cutting-Edge Program That Cures Your Type of Sugar Addiction and Puts You on the Road to Feeling Great &#8211; and Losing Weight! &#8211; Jacob Teitelbaum, Chrystle Fiedler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Normal0MicrosoftInternetExplorer4 The No-Fail Plan to Beating Sugar Addiction! With one-third of our calories coming from sugar and white flour added to processed foods, sugar addiction is a rapidly growing epidemic. However, unlike other addictions, going &#8220;cold turkey&#8221; won&#8217;t fix it. In this groundbreaking book, nationally recognized physician Dr. Jacob Teitelbaum uncovers four types of sugar [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/">Beat Sugar Addiction Now! : The Cutting-Edge Program That Cures Your Type of Sugar Addiction and Puts You on the Road to Feeling Great &#8211; and Losing Weight! &#8211; Jacob Teitelbaum, Chrystle Fiedler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Normal0MicrosoftInternetExplorer4    </p>
<p>                    The No-Fail Plan to Beating Sugar Addiction!    </p>
<p>                    With one-third of our calories coming from sugar and white flour added to processed foods, sugar addiction is a rapidly growing epidemic. However, unlike other addictions, going &#8220;cold turkey&#8221; won&#8217;t fix it. In this groundbreaking book, nationally recognized physician Dr. Jacob Teitelbaum uncovers four types of sugar addiction and gives a step-by-step plan for resolving their underlying causes, breaking sugar cravings forever, and achieving dramatically improved health and energy levels&#8211;while also making it easier to lose weight!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/">Beat Sugar Addiction Now! : The Cutting-Edge Program That Cures Your Type of Sugar Addiction and Puts You on the Road to Feeling Great &#8211; and Losing Weight! &#8211; Jacob Teitelbaum, Chrystle Fiedler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Revolutionise your life one day at a time with this empowering handbook designed for men and women which provides simple strategies for each element of your day. Marcus Aubrey, author of the book is CEO of Onnit, a human performance company that he has built into one of the fastest growing companies in the world. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/">Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Revolutionise your life one day at a time with this empowering handbook designed for men and women which provides simple strategies for each element of your day. Marcus Aubrey, author of the book is CEO of Onnit, a human performance company that he has built into one of the fastest growing companies in the world.    </p>
<p>                              How can we get the most out of our body and mind on a daily basis? Want to change your life for the better?    </p>
<p>                              Aubrey Marcus answers these questions in this handbook that guides the reader to optimise each moment of the day. With small, actionable changes implemented throughout the course of one day we can feel better, perform more efficiently and live happier. And these habits turn into weekly routines, ultimately becoming part of a lifelong healthy choice.    </p>
<p>                              From workouts and diet to inbox triage, mindfulness, shower temperature and sex this groundbreaking manual provides strategies for each element of your day. Drawing on the latest studies and traditional practices from around the world, this book delivers cutting-edge life hacks, nutritional expertise, brain upgrades and fitness regimes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/">Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clean : The Revolutionary Program to Restore the Body&#8217;s Natural Ability to Heal Itself &#8211; Alejandro Junger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Life-Changing Medical Breakthrough Clean is an M.D.&#8217;s program designed to be easily incorporated into our busy schedule while providing all the practical tools necessary to support and rejuvenate our bodies. The effect is transformative: nagging health problems will suddenly disappear, extra weight will drop away, and for the first time in our lives, we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/">Clean : The Revolutionary Program to Restore the Body&#8217;s Natural Ability to Heal Itself &#8211; Alejandro Junger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Life-Changing Medical Breakthrough Clean is an M.D.&#8217;s program designed to be easily incorporated into our busy schedule while providing all the practical tools necessary to support and rejuvenate our bodies. The effect is transformative: nagging health problems will suddenly disappear, extra weight will drop away, and for the first time in our lives, we will experience what it truly means to feel healthy.  Expanded Edition Includes: New Introduction * New Recipes * How to Become Clean for Life</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/">Clean : The Revolutionary Program to Restore the Body&#8217;s Natural Ability to Heal Itself &#8211; Alejandro Junger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Productivity Project : Proven Ways to Become More Awesome &#8211; Chris Bailey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-productivity-project-proven-ways-to-become-more-awesome-chris-bailey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-productivity-project-proven-ways-to-become-more-awesome-chris-bailey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fun, interesting, and useful read!&#8217; David Allen, bestselling author of Getting Things Done Nearly all of us want to be more productive, but finding the method that works for you among the hundreds and hundreds of different tips, tricks and hacks can be a daunting prospect. After graduating college, Chris Bailey decided to dedicate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-productivity-project-proven-ways-to-become-more-awesome-chris-bailey-abridged/">The Productivity Project : Proven Ways to Become More Awesome &#8211; Chris Bailey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fun, interesting, and useful read!&#8217; David Allen, bestselling author of Getting Things Done    </p>
<p>                    Nearly all of us want to be more productive, but finding the method that works for you among the hundreds and hundreds of different tips, tricks and hacks can be a daunting prospect. After graduating college, Chris Bailey decided to dedicate a whole year to doing just that &#8211; experimenting with as many of the techniques as he could, and finding the things that work. Among the experiments that he undertook are: going several weeks on little to no sleep; cutting out caffeine and sugar; taking a daily siesta; living in total isolation for 10 days; stretching his workweek to 90 hours; and getting up at 5:30 every morning,  all the while monitoring the impact of his experiments on the quality and quantity of his work. The results were often surprising!     </p>
<p>                    This book is the result of Chris&#8217;s year-long journey, distilling the lessons he learned into a few core truths about how we get things done (or, indeed, don&#8217;t).  Among the many counterintuitive insights Chris discovered that had the biggest impact on his productivity were striving for imperfection; scheduling less time for important tasks; the 20 second rule to distract yourself from distractions; and the concept of productive procrastination.     </p>
<p>                    In this accessible and fun guide, Chris Bailey offers over 30 tried-and-tested best practices that will help everyone to accomplish more &#8211; and become more awesome.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-productivity-project-proven-ways-to-become-more-awesome-chris-bailey-abridged/">The Productivity Project : Proven Ways to Become More Awesome &#8211; Chris Bailey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Sleep : The New Science of Sleep and Dreams &#8211; Matthew Walker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-sleep-the-new-science-of-sleep-and-dreams-matthew-walker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Methodology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-sleep-the-new-science-of-sleep-and-dreams-matthew-walker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Astonishing . . . an amazing book . . . absolutely chocker full of things that we need to know&#8217; Chris Evans &#8216;Matthew Walker is probably one of the most influential people on the planet&#8217; Evening Standard THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER TLS, OBSERVER, SUNDAY TIMES, FT, GUARDIAN, DAILY MAIL AND EVENING STANDARD BOOKS OF [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-sleep-the-new-science-of-sleep-and-dreams-matthew-walker-abridged/">Why We Sleep : The New Science of Sleep and Dreams &#8211; Matthew Walker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Astonishing . . . an amazing book . . . absolutely chocker full of things that we need to know&#8217; Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Matthew Walker is probably one of the most influential people on the planet&#8217; Evening Standard    </p>
<p>                    THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    TLS, OBSERVER, SUNDAY TIMES, FT, GUARDIAN, DAILY MAIL AND EVENING STANDARD BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2017    </p>
<p>                    Sleep is one of the most important aspects of our life, health and longevity and yet it is increasingly neglected in twenty-first-century society, with devastating consequences: every major disease in the developed world &#8211; Alzheimer&#8217;s, cancer, obesity, diabetes &#8211; has very strong causal links to deficient sleep.    </p>
<p>                    In this book, the first of its kind written by a scientific expert, Professor Matthew Walker explores twenty years of cutting-edge research to solve the mystery of why sleep matters. Looking at creatures from across the animal kingdom as well as major human studies, Why We Sleep delves into everything from what really happens during REM sleep to how caffeine and alcohol affect sleep and why our sleep patterns change across a lifetime, transforming our appreciation of the extraordinary phenomenon that safeguards our existence.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Startling, vital &#8230; a life-raft&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A top sleep scientist argues that sleep is more important for our health than diet or exercise&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Passionate, urgent . . . it had a powerful effect on me&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-sleep-the-new-science-of-sleep-and-dreams-matthew-walker-abridged/">Why We Sleep : The New Science of Sleep and Dreams &#8211; Matthew Walker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Better Than Before : What I Learned About Making and Breaking Habits &#8211; to Sleep More, Quit Sugar, Procrastinate Less, and Generally Build a Happier Life &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/better-than-before-what-i-learned-about-making-and-breaking-habits-to-sleep-more-quit-sugar-procrastinate-less-and-generally-build-a-happier-life-gretchen-rubin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/better-than-before-what-i-learned-about-making-and-breaking-habits-to-sleep-more-quit-sugar-procrastinate-less-and-generally-build-a-happier-life-gretchen-rubin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A LOT OF US WOULD LIKE A RUBIN IN OUR LIVES&#8217; The Times &#8216;EXTRAORDINARY&#8217; Viv Groskop &#8216;FASCINATING, PERSUASIVE&#8217; Guardian &#8216;A LIFE-CHANGER&#8217; The Pool HABITS ARE THE INVISIBLE ARCHITECTURE OF EVERYDAY LIFE. Most of us have a habit we&#8217;d like to change, and there&#8217;s no shortage of expert advice. But as we all know from tough [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-than-before-what-i-learned-about-making-and-breaking-habits-to-sleep-more-quit-sugar-procrastinate-less-and-generally-build-a-happier-life-gretchen-rubin-abridged/">Better Than Before : What I Learned About Making and Breaking Habits &#8211; to Sleep More, Quit Sugar, Procrastinate Less, and Generally Build a Happier Life &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A LOT OF US WOULD LIKE A RUBIN IN OUR LIVES&#8217; The Times<br />
                    &#8216;EXTRAORDINARY&#8217; Viv Groskop<br />
                    &#8216;FASCINATING, PERSUASIVE&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;A LIFE-CHANGER&#8217; The Pool    </p>
<p>                    HABITS ARE THE INVISIBLE ARCHITECTURE OF EVERYDAY LIFE.    </p>
<p>                    Most of us have a habit we&#8217;d like to change, and there&#8217;s no shortage of  expert advice. But as we all know from tough experience, there is no magic &#8216;one-size-fits-all&#8217; solution for everything from weight loss to personal organisation. In Better Than Before, Gretchen Rubin explores her theory of &#8216;The Four Tendencies&#8217; dividing people into four basic groups: Upholder, Obliger, Questioner and Rebel. She answers the most perplexing questions about habits with her signature mix of rigorous research and engaging storytelling (and a personality quiz to establish which of the Four Tendencies fits you):    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Why do we find it tough to create a habit for something we love to do?<br />
                     &#8211; How can we keep our healthy habits when we&#8217;re surrounded by temptations?<br />
                     &#8211; How can we help someone else change a habit?    </p>
<p>                    Rubin reveals the true secret to habit change: first, we must know ourselves. When we shape our habits to suit ourselves, we can find success- even if we&#8217;ve failed before.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you want to eat more healthfully, stop checking your phone, or finish a project, the invaluable ideas in Better Than Before will start you working on your own habits &#8211; even before you&#8217;ve finished the book.    </p>
<p>                    ALSO BY GRETCHEN RUBIN    </p>
<p>                    The Four Tendencies: the indispensable personality profiles that reveal how to make your life better    </p>
<p>                    AND    </p>
<p>                    Outer Order Inner Calm: declutter and organize to make more room for happiness    </p>
<p>                    AND    </p>
<p>                    Happier At Home: a year-long experiment in making the everyday extraordinary</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-than-before-what-i-learned-about-making-and-breaking-habits-to-sleep-more-quit-sugar-procrastinate-less-and-generally-build-a-happier-life-gretchen-rubin-abridged/">Better Than Before : What I Learned About Making and Breaking Habits &#8211; to Sleep More, Quit Sugar, Procrastinate Less, and Generally Build a Happier Life &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal & Public Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it. Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it.    </p>
<p>                    Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer understanding of how we live and how we die. While it is one of the largest scientific projects ever attempted&#8211;as breathtaking as the first moon landing or the Human Genome Project&#8211;the questions it answers are meaningful for every one of us: What are the world&#8217;s health problems? Who do they hurt? How much? Where? Why?    </p>
<p>                    Murray argues that the ideal existence isn&#8217;t simply the longest but the one lived well and with the least illness. Until we can accurately measure how people live and die, we cannot understand what makes us sick or do much to improve it. Challenging the accepted wisdom of the WHO and the UN, the charismatic and controversial health maverick has made enemies&#8211;and some influential friends, including Bill Gates who gave Murray a $100 million grant.    </p>
<p>                    In Epic Measures, journalist Jeremy N. Smith offers an intimate look at Murray and his groundbreaking work. From ranking countries&#8217; healthcare systems (the U.S. is 37th) to unearthing the shocking reality that world governments are funding developing countries at only 30% of the potential maximum efficiency when it comes to health, Epic Measures introduces a visionary leader whose unwavering determination to improve global health standards has already changed the way the world addresses issues of health and wellness, sets policy, and distributes funding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jog On : How Running Saved My Life &#8211; Bella Mackie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/jog-on-how-running-saved-my-life-bella-mackie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Separation & Divorce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Track & Field Sports, Athletics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/jog-on-how-running-saved-my-life-bella-mackie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Bella&#8217;s brilliant love letter to running turns into an extraordinarily brave and frank account of her battle with anxiety. A compassionate and important book&#8217; Joe Lycett &#8216;Perfect for resetting a glum January mindset&#8217; Alexandra Heminsley &#8216;My kind of role model&#8217; Ben Fogle Divorced and struggling with deep-rooted mental health problems, Bella [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jog-on-how-running-saved-my-life-bella-mackie-abridged/">Jog On : How Running Saved My Life &#8211; Bella Mackie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Bella&#8217;s brilliant love letter to running turns into an extraordinarily brave and frank account of her battle with anxiety. A compassionate and important book&#8217; Joe Lycett    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Perfect for resetting a glum January mindset&#8217; Alexandra Heminsley    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;My kind of role model&#8217; Ben Fogle    </p>
<p>                              Divorced and struggling with deep-rooted mental health problems, Bella Mackie ended her twenties in tears. She could barely find the strength to get off the sofa, let alone piece her life back together. Until one day she did something she had never done of her own free will &#8211; she pulled on a pair of trainers and went for a run.    </p>
<p>                              That first attempt didn&#8217;t last very long. But to her surprise, she was back out there the next day. And the day after that. She began to set herself achievable goals &#8211; to run 5k in under 30 minutes, to walk to work every day for a week, to attempt 10 push-ups in a row. Before she knew it, her mood was lifting for the first time in years.    </p>
<p>                              In Jog On, Bella explains with hilarious and unfiltered honesty how she used running to battle crippling anxiety and depression, without having to sacrifice her main loves: booze, cigarettes and ice cream. With the help of a supporting cast of doctors, psychologists, sportspeople and friends, she shares a wealth of inspirational stories, research and tips that show how exercise often can be the best medicine. This funny, moving and motivational book will encourage you to say &#8216;jog on&#8217; to your problems and get your life back on track &#8211; no matter how small those first steps may be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jog-on-how-running-saved-my-life-bella-mackie-abridged/">Jog On : How Running Saved My Life &#8211; Bella Mackie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Morning Routine : How Successful People Start Every Day Inspired &#8211; Benjamin Spall, Michael Xander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-morning-routine-how-successful-people-start-every-day-inspired-benjamin-spall-michael-xander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-morning-routine-how-successful-people-start-every-day-inspired-benjamin-spall-michael-xander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ONE OF AMAZON&#8217;S BEST BUSINESS BOOKS OF 2018 SO FAR ONE OF THE FINANCIAL TIMES&#8217; BUSINESS BOOKS OF THE MONTH UPON RELEASE ONE OF BUSINESS INSIDER&#8217;S BEST BUSINESS BOOKS TO READ THIS SUMMER &#8216;This small book carries the irresistible implicit promise that if you follow the morning routines of famous, important and successful people, you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-morning-routine-how-successful-people-start-every-day-inspired-benjamin-spall-michael-xander-abridged/">My Morning Routine : How Successful People Start Every Day Inspired &#8211; Benjamin Spall, Michael Xander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ONE OF AMAZON&#8217;S BEST BUSINESS BOOKS OF 2018 SO FAR<br />
                    ONE OF THE FINANCIAL TIMES&#8217; BUSINESS BOOKS OF THE MONTH UPON RELEASE<br />
                    ONE OF BUSINESS INSIDER&#8217;S BEST BUSINESS BOOKS TO READ THIS SUMMER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This small book carries the irresistible implicit promise that if you follow the morning routines of famous, important and successful people, you will become famous, important and successful yourself.&#8217; Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    How are you spending your most valuable hours? The first few choices you make each morning can unlock greater productivity, creativity, and calm &#8211; or bring out your worst self.    </p>
<p>                    Marie Kondo performs a quick tidying ritual to quiet her mind before leaving the house. The president of Pixar and Walt Disney Animation Studios, Ed Catmull, mixes three shots of espresso with three scoops of cocoa powder and two sweeteners. Retired U.S.Army Four-Star General Stanley McChrystal works out at 4:00 AM every day for at least an hour.     </p>
<p>                     Part instruction manual, part someone else&#8217;s diary, My Morning Routine interviews sixty-four of today&#8217;s most successful people &#8211; including Biz Stone, the co-founder of Twitter; Arianna Huffington, founder of The Huffington Post; and Michael Acton Smith, the CEO of Calm &#8211; and offers timeless advice on creating a routine of your own.    </p>
<p>                     Some routines are all about early-morning exercise and spartan living; others are more leisurely and self-indulgent. Whether you want to boost your productivity, implement a workout or meditation routine, or learn to roll with the punches in the morning, this book has you covered.     </p>
<p>                    Once you land on the right routine, you&#8217;ll look forward to waking up.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    From inside the book:     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A big part of my morning routine is about what I don&#8217;t do: when I wake up, I don&#8217;t start the day by looking at my phone&#8217; &#8211; ARIANNA HUFFINGTON, founder of the Huffington Post and Thrive Global    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;I travel a lot for work, so my days are always different. Having a morning routine really means fitting things in around everything else&#8217; &#8211; CAMERON RUSSELL, fashion model and cultural activist I    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;if I don&#8217;t get a chance to play with my son in the morning I feel like I missed something that I&#8217;ll never get back&#8217; &#8211; BIZ STONE, cofounder of Twitter    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Find certain things you know you should do, don&#8217;t like to do, or make excuses to avoid, and then do them every day&#8217; &#8211; STANLEY McCHRYSTAL, retired U.S. Army four-star general    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;    </p>
<p>                     BENJAMIN SPALL AND MICHAEL XANDER are the founders of mymorningroutine.com. Spall has written for outlets including The Huffington Post, 99U, and The Next Web. Xander is a product designer and engineer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-morning-routine-how-successful-people-start-every-day-inspired-benjamin-spall-michael-xander-abridged/">My Morning Routine : How Successful People Start Every Day Inspired &#8211; Benjamin Spall, Michael Xander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weird Parenting Wins : Bathtub Dining, Family Screams, and Other Hacks from the Parenting Trenches &#8211; Hillary Frank (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unconventional&#8211;yet effective&#8211;parenting strategies, carefully curated by the creator of the popular podcast The Longest Shortest Time Some of the best parenting advice that Hillary Frank ever received did not come from parenting experts, but from friends and podcast listeners who acted on a whim, often in moments of desperation. These weird parenting wins were born [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/">Weird Parenting Wins : Bathtub Dining, Family Screams, and Other Hacks from the Parenting Trenches &#8211; Hillary Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unconventional&#8211;yet effective&#8211;parenting strategies, carefully curated by the creator of the popular podcast The Longest Shortest Time     </p>
<p>                    Some of the best parenting advice that Hillary Frank ever received did not come from parenting experts, but from friends and podcast listeners who acted on a whim, often in moments of desperation. These weird parenting wins were born of moments when the expert advice wasn&#8217;t working, and instead of freaking out, these parents had a stroke of genius. For example, there&#8217;s the dad who pig-snorted in his baby&#8217;s ear to get her to stop crying, and the mom who made a flat daddy out of cardboard and sat it at the dinner table when her kids were missing their deployed military father.<br />
                     Every parent and kid is unique, and as we get to know our kids, we can figure out what makes them tick. Because this is an ongoing process, Weird Parenting Wins covers children of all ages, ranging in topics from The Art of Getting Your Kid to Act Like a Person (on hygiene, potty training, and manners) to The Art of Getting Your Kid to Tell You Things (because eventually, they&#8217;re going to be tight-lipped). You may find that someone else&#8217;s weird parenting win works for you, or you might be inspired to try something new the next time you&#8217;re stuck in a parenting rut. Or maybe you&#8217;ll just get a good laugh out of the mom who got her kid to try beets because&#8230;it might turn her poop pink.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/">Weird Parenting Wins : Bathtub Dining, Family Screams, and Other Hacks from the Parenting Trenches &#8211; Hillary Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report, Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report,  Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by Medicare when offered virtually at home.     </p>
<p>                     Dean Ornish, M.D., has directed revolutionary research proving, for the first time, that lifestyle changes can often reverse&#8211;undo!&#8211;the progression of many of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level.     </p>
<p>                     Medicare and many insurance companies now cover Dr. Ornish&#8217;s lifestyle medicine program for reversing chronic disease because it consistently achieves bigger changes in lifestyle, better clinical outcomes, larger cost savings, and greater adherence than have ever been reported&#8211;based on forty years of research published in the leading peer-reviewed medical and scientific journals.     </p>
<p>                     Now, in this landmark book, he and Anne Ornish present a simple yet powerful new unifying theory explaining why these same lifestyle changes can reverse so many different chronic diseases and how quickly these benefits occur. They describe what it is, why it works, and how you can do it:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Eat well a whole foods, plant-based diet naturally low in fat and sugar and high in flavor. The &#8220;Ornish diet&#8221; has been rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report for eleven years since 2011.<br />
                     &#8211; Move more moderate exercise such as walking<br />
                     &#8211; Stress less including meditation and gentle yoga practices<br />
                     &#8211; Love more how love and intimacy transform loneliness into healing     </p>
<p>                    With seventy recipes, easy-to-follow meal plans, tips for stocking your kitchen and eating out, recommended exercises, stress-reduction advice, and inspiring patient stories of life-transforming benefits&#8211;for example, several people improved so much after only nine weeks they were able to avoid a heart transplant&#8211;Undo It! empowers readers with new hope and new choices.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Undo It!     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Ornishes&#8217; work is elegant and simple and deserving of a Nobel Prize, since it can change the world!&#8221;&#8211;Richard Carmona, M.D., MPH, FACS, seventeenth Surgeon General of the United States     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;If you want to see what medicine will be like ten years from now, read this book today.&#8221;&#8211;Rita F. Redberg, M.D., editor in chief, JAMA Internal Medicine     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This is one of the most important books on health ever written.&#8221;&#8211;John Mackey, CEO, Whole Foods Market</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Necessity : Adventures In The World Of Human Waste &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Produced behind closed doors, disposed of discreetly, hidden by euphemism, shit is rarely out in the open in &#8216;civilized&#8217; society, but the world of waste &#8211; and the people who deal with it, work with it and in it &#8211; is a rich one.This book takes us underground to the sewers of New York and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/">The Big Necessity : Adventures In The World Of Human Waste &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Produced behind closed doors, disposed of discreetly, hidden by euphemism, shit is rarely out in the open in &#8216;civilized&#8217; society, but the world of waste &#8211; and the people who deal with it, work with it and in it &#8211; is a rich one.This book takes us underground to the sewers of New York and London and overground to meet the heroes of India&#8217;s sanitation movement, American sewage schoolteachers, the Japanese genius at the cutting edge of toilet technology and the biosolids lobbying team. With a journalist&#8217;s nose for story and a campaigner&#8217;s desire for change, Rose George also addresses the politics of this under-reported social and environmental effluent, and the consequences of our reluctance to talk about it. Witty and original, The Big Necessity proves that shit doesn&#8217;t have to be a dirty word.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/">The Big Necessity : Adventures In The World Of Human Waste &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the revolutionary science behind the power of thought, this book will forever change how you think about your own thinking. This new updated and expanded 10th anniversary edition of The Biology of Belief contains stunning new scientific discoveries about the biochemical effects of the brain&#8217;s functioning that show all the cells of your body [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/">The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the revolutionary science behind the power of thought, this book will forever change how you think about your own thinking.    </p>
<p>                    This new updated and expanded 10th anniversary edition of The Biology of Belief contains stunning new scientific discoveries about the biochemical effects of the brain&#8217;s functioning that show all the cells of your body are affected by your thoughts. Bruce H. Lipton PhD, a renowned cell biologist, describes the precise molecular pathways through which this occurs. Using simple language, illustrations, humour and everyday examples, he demonstrates how the new science of epigenetics is revolutionizing our understanding of the link between mind and matter, and the profound effects it has on our personal lives and the collective life of our species.    </p>
<p>                    It has been 10 years since the publication of The Biology of Belief, Bruce Lipton&#8217;s seminal book on the relationship between mind and body that changed the way we think about our lives, our health and our planet. During that time, research in this field has grown exponentially &#8211; Lipton&#8217;s ground-breaking experiments have now been endorsed by more than a decade of rigorous scientific study.    </p>
<p>                    In this greatly expanded edition, Lipton explores his own experiments and those of other leading-edge scientists that have unravelled in ever greater detail how truly connected the mind, body and spirit are. It is now widely recognized that genes and DNA do not control our biology. Instead, they are controlled by signals from outside the cell, including energetic messages emanating from our thoughts.    </p>
<p>                    This profoundly hopeful synthesis of the latest and best research in cell biology and quantum physics puts the power to create a healthy, joyous life back in our own hands. When we transform our conscious and subconscious thoughts, we transform our lives, and in the process help humanity evolve to a new level of understanding and peace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/">The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER From the UK&#8217;s favourite therapist, as seen on Channel 4&#8217;s Grayson&#8217;s Art Club. &#8216;A wonderful book&#8217; Richard Osman &#8216;So clear and true &#8230; Helpful for all relationships in life&#8217; Nigella Lawson &#8216;A fascinating read on the emotional baggage we all carry&#8217; Elizabeth Day ______________________________________________________________________________________ How can we have better relationships? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/">The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    From the UK&#8217;s favourite therapist, as seen on Channel 4&#8217;s Grayson&#8217;s Art Club.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wonderful book&#8217; Richard Osman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;So clear and true &#8230; Helpful for all relationships in life&#8217; Nigella Lawson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fascinating read on the emotional baggage we all carry&#8217; Elizabeth Day<br />
                    ______________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    How can we have better relationships?    </p>
<p>                    In this Sunday Times bestseller, leading psychotherapist Philippa Perry reveals the vital do&#8217;s and don&#8217;ts of relationships. This is a book for us all. Whether you are interested in understanding how your upbringing has shaped you, looking to handle your child&#8217;s feelings or wishing to support your partner, you will find indispensable information and realistic tips in these pages. Philippa Perry&#8217;s sane, sage and judgement-free advice is an essential resource on how to have the best possible relationships with the people who matter to you most.<br />
                    _____________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It gave me hope as a new parent&#8217; Babita Sharma    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This has genuinely had such a positive impact on my life and my relationship with my daughter&#8217; Josh Widdicombe    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;She writes with an inquisitive elegance rarely found in parenting guides &#8230; it is forgiving and persuasive&#8217;   Hadley Freeman, the Guardian      </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Philippa Perry is one of the wisest, most sane and secure people I&#8217;ve ever met&#8217; Decca Aitkenhead, Sunday Times Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/">The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tribe of Mentors : Short Life Advice from the Best in the World &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tribe-of-mentors-short-life-advice-from-the-best-in-the-world-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tribe-of-mentors-short-life-advice-from-the-best-in-the-world-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tim Ferriss, the #1 New York Times best-selling author of The 4-Hour Workweek, shares the ultimate choose-your-own-adventure book-a compilation of tools, tactics, and habits from 130+ of the world&#8217;s top performers. From iconic entrepreneurs to elite athletes, from artists to billionaire investors, their short profiles can help you answer life&#8217;s most challenging questions, achieve extraordinary [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tribe-of-mentors-short-life-advice-from-the-best-in-the-world-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Tribe of Mentors : Short Life Advice from the Best in the World &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tim Ferriss, the #1 New York Times best-selling author of The 4-Hour Workweek, shares the ultimate choose-your-own-adventure book-a compilation of tools, tactics, and habits from 130+ of the world&#8217;s top performers. From iconic entrepreneurs to elite athletes, from artists to billionaire investors, their short profiles can help you answer life&#8217;s most challenging questions, achieve extraordinary results, and transform your life.    </p>
<p>                    From the author:    </p>
<p>                    In 2017, several of my close friends died in rapid succession. It was a very hard year, as it was for many people.    </p>
<p>                    It was also a stark reminder that time is our scarcest, non-renewable resource.    </p>
<p>                    With a renewed sense of urgency, I began asking myself many questions:    </p>
<p>                    Were my goals my own, or simply what I thought I should want?<br />
                    How much of life had I missed from underplanning or overplanning?<br />
                    How could I be kinder to myself?<br />
                    How could I better say &#8220;no&#8221; to the trivial many to better say &#8220;yes&#8221; to the critical few?<br />
                    How could I best reassess my priorities and my purpose in this world?    </p>
<p>                    To find answers, I reached out to the most impressive world-class performers in the world, ranging from wunderkinds in their 20s to icons in their 70s and 80s. No stone was left unturned.    </p>
<p>                    This book contains their answers-practical and tactical advice from mentors who have found solutions. Whether you want to 10x your results, get unstuck, or reinvent yourself, someone else has traveled a similar path and taken notes.    </p>
<p>                    This book, Tribe of Mentors, includes many of the people I grew up viewing as idols or demi-gods. Less than 10% have been on my podcast (The Tim Ferriss Show, more than 200 million downloads), making this a brand-new playbook of playbooks.    </p>
<p>                    No matter your challenge or opportunity, something in these pages can help.    </p>
<p>                    Among other things, you will learn:    </p>
<p>                    More than 50 morning routines-both for the early riser and those who struggle to get out of bed.<br />
                    How TED curator Chris Anderson realized that the best way to get things done is to let go.<br />
                    The best purchases of $100 or less (you&#8217;ll never have to think about the right gift again).<br />
                    How to overcome failure and bounce back towards success.<br />
                    Why Humans of New York creator Brandon Stanton believes that the best art will always be the riskiest.<br />
                    How to meditate and be more mindful (and not just for those that find it easy).<br />
                    Why tennis champion Maria Sharapova believe that &#8220;losing makes you think in ways victories can&#8217;t.&#8221;<br />
                    How to truly achieve work-life balance (and why most people tell you it isn&#8217;t realistic).<br />
                    How billionaire Facebook co-founder Dustin Moskovitz transformed the way he engages with difficult situations to reduce suffering.<br />
                    Ways to thrive (and survive) the overwhelming amount of information you process every day.<br />
                    How to achieve clarity on your purpose and assess your priorities.<br />
                    And much more.    </p>
<p>                    This reference book, which I wrote for myself, has already changed my life. I certainly hope the same for you.    </p>
<p>                    I wish you luck as you forge your own path.    </p>
<p>                    All the best,    </p>
<p>                    Tim Ferriss</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tribe-of-mentors-short-life-advice-from-the-best-in-the-world-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Tribe of Mentors : Short Life Advice from the Best in the World &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Invisible Orientation : An Introduction to Asexuality * Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT * &#8211; Julie Sondra Decker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-invisible-orientation-an-introduction-to-asexuality-next-generation-indie-book-awards-winner-in-lgbt-julie-sondra-decker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay Studies (Gay Men)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-invisible-orientation-an-introduction-to-asexuality-next-generation-indie-book-awards-winner-in-lgbt-julie-sondra-decker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT . &#8220;An important resource for readers of any age who are struggling to understand their sexual orientation, or those who would like to better understand asexuality.&#8221; -Library Journal, starred review Julie Sondra Decker&#8217;s book functions as a starting point for people interested in asexuality. It covers the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-invisible-orientation-an-introduction-to-asexuality-next-generation-indie-book-awards-winner-in-lgbt-julie-sondra-decker-abridged/">The Invisible Orientation : An Introduction to Asexuality * Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT * &#8211; Julie Sondra Decker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT . &#8220;An important resource for readers of any age who are struggling to understand their sexual orientation, or those who would like to better understand asexuality.&#8221; -Library Journal, starred review<br />
                    Julie Sondra Decker&#8217;s book functions as a starting point for people interested in asexuality. It covers the basics of what asexuality is and isn&#8217;t, explores the most common issues asexual people may be dealing with, presents some pointers for newly asexual-identified people and the people who love them, and includes some resources to find out more. It&#8217;s for the layperson, written in everyday language.    </p>
<p>                    She writes for people who are on the asexual spectrum, people who think they might be asexual, friends and family and partners of people who have come out as asexual, curious parties, and those looking for information on the subject for their school papers, sexuality studies, and alternative sexuality resources. And it&#8217;s for people who think asexuality doesn&#8217;t exist. Chapters include:    </p>
<p>                    Asexuality as a Sexual Orientation<br />
                    Romantic Orientation<br />
                    Libido and Masturbation<br />
                    Intimate and Sexual Activity<br />
                    Asexual Relationships<br />
                    Asexual Community<br />
                    Should Asexual People Get Therapy and Be Fixed<br />
                    Am I Asexual?<br />
                    Should I Come Out?<br />
                    And much more    </p>
<p>                    If you think you may be asexual, or if you have a friend or partner who may be a sexual, this personal book will help you better understand what it means to be asexual in a world dominated by sexuality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-invisible-orientation-an-introduction-to-asexuality-next-generation-indie-book-awards-winner-in-lgbt-julie-sondra-decker-abridged/">The Invisible Orientation : An Introduction to Asexuality * Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT * &#8211; Julie Sondra Decker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Take a break and read Rest: you&#8217;ll make smarter decisions, have better relationships, and be happier and more creative&#8221; James Wallman, author of Stuffocation Do you regularly find yourself too tired after a long day at your desk to do anything other than binge TV, or scroll mindlessly through social media? Do you go on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/">Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Take a break and read Rest: you&#8217;ll make smarter decisions, have better relationships, and be happier and more creative&#8221; James Wallman, author of Stuffocation    </p>
<p>                     Do you regularly find yourself too tired after a long day at your desk to do anything other than binge TV, or scroll mindlessly through social media? Do you go on holiday and still compulsively check your email? Do you work through your lunch-break, often not even leaving your desk to get some fresh air?    </p>
<p>                     For most of us, overwork is the new norm, and we never truly take the time to rest and recharge. But as Silicon Valley consultant Alex Soojung-Kim Pang explains in this groundbreaking book, rest needs to be taken seriously and to be done properly, because when you rest better you work better.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on emerging neuroscience, Rest is packed with easy practical tips for incorporating rest into our everyday:    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Go for a long walk to stimulate and sustain creativity<br />
                     &#8211; Schedule deliberate active rest periods into your diary to try out new activities like painting or learning a language<br />
                     &#8211; Stop working on a task when you know what the next step will be, this will make it easier to get started the next day<br />
                    &#8211; Establish clear boundaries between work and rest time<br />
                     &#8211; Take a nap during the day to increase alertness, boost your concentration and decrease fatigue<br />
                     &#8211; Get good quality sleep at night to stay healthy, solidify memories and generate new ideas    </p>
<p>                     When you rest better you&#8217;ll find that it won&#8217;t just be your work which improves &#8211; you&#8217;ll have more time for hobbies, stronger relationships and you&#8217;ll sleep better, too.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;An incredibly timely read for my own increasingly rest-starved life. This might be the book to finally persuade us that downtime isn&#8217;t in conflict with good work; rather, it&#8217;s an essential ingredient of it&#8221; Oliver Burkeman, Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/">Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, WithGene Stone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book. Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, WithGene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book.     </p>
<p>                    Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. Why suffer from disease and ill health when the right food is proven to keep you healthy, and without the side effects of drugs? We can avoid heart disease, cancer and our other biggest killers if we use food as medicine, and the How Not To Die Cookbook offers a sustainable and delicious guide to preparing and eating the foods that will prevent and reverse fatal diseases.    </p>
<p>                    Featuring over 100 easy-to-follow, beautifully photographed plant-based recipes, with plenty of recipes suitable for vegetarians and vegans, the How Not To Die Cookbook merges cutting-edge science with everyday ingredients from the supermarket to help you and your family eat your way to better health and a longer life.    </p>
<p>                    All recipes in this cookbook have been fully anglicized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, WithGene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whole : Rethinking the Science of Nutrition &#8211; T. Colin Campbell, Howard Jacobson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller What happens when you eat an apple? The answer is vastly more complex than you imagine. Every apple contains thousands of antioxidants whose names, beyond a few like vitamin C, are unfamiliar to us, and each of these powerful chemicals has the potential to play an important role in supporting our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/">Whole : Rethinking the Science of Nutrition &#8211; T. Colin Campbell, Howard Jacobson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller  What happens when you eat an apple? The answer is vastly more complex than you imagine.  Every apple contains thousands of antioxidants whose names, beyond a few like vitamin C, are unfamiliar to us, and each of these powerful chemicals has the potential to play an important role in supporting our health. They impact thousands upon thousands of metabolic reactions inside the human body. But calculating the specific influence of each of these chemicals isn&#8217;t nearly sufficient to explain the effect of the apple as a whole. Because almost every chemical can affect every other chemical, there is an almost infinite number of possible biological consequences.  And that&#8217;s just from an apple.  Nutritional science, long stuck in a reductionist mindset, is at the cusp of a revolution. The traditional &#8220;gold standard&#8221; of nutrition research has been to study one chemical at a time in an attempt to determine its particular impact on the human body.<br />
                    These sorts of studies are helpful to food companies trying to prove there is a chemical in milk or pre-packaged dinners that is &#8220;good&#8221; for us, but they provide little insight into the complexity of what actually happens in our bodies or how those chemicals contribute to our health.  In The China Study, T. Colin Campbell (alongside his son, Thomas M. Campbell) revolutionized the way we think about our food with the evidence that a whole food, plant-based diet is the healthiest way to eat. Now, in Whole, he explains the science behind that evidence, the ways our current scientific paradigm ignores the fascinating complexity of the human body, and why, if we have such overwhelming evidence that everything we think we know about nutrition is wrong, our eating habits haven&#8217;t changed.  Whole is an eye-opening, paradigm-changing journey through cutting-edge thinking on nutrition, a scientific tour de force with powerful implications for our health and for our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/">Whole : Rethinking the Science of Nutrition &#8211; T. Colin Campbell, Howard Jacobson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nine Pints : A Journey Through the Mysterious, Miraculous World of Blood &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most humans contain between nine and twelve pints of blood. Here Rose George, who probably contains nine pints, tells nine different stories about the liquid that sustains us, discovering what it reveals about who we are. In Nepal, she meets girls challenging the taboos surrounding menstruation; in the Canadian prairies, she visits a controversial plasma [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/">Nine Pints : A Journey Through the Mysterious, Miraculous World of Blood &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most humans contain between nine and twelve pints of blood. Here Rose George, who probably contains nine pints, tells nine different stories about the liquid that sustains us, discovering what it reveals about who we are. In Nepal, she meets girls challenging the taboos surrounding menstruation; in the Canadian prairies, she visits a controversial plasma clinic; in Wales she gets a tour of the UK&#8217;s only leech farm to learn about the vital role the creatures still play in modern surgery; and in a London hospital she accompanies a medical team revolutionising the way we treat trauma.    </p>
<p>                     Nine Pints reveals the richness and wonder of the potent red fluid that courses around our bodies, unseen but miraculous.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/">Nine Pints : A Journey Through the Mysterious, Miraculous World of Blood &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let Love Have the Last Word : A Memoir &#8211; Common (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/let-love-have-the-last-word-a-memoir-common-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-love-have-the-last-word-a-memoir-common-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER Common-the Grammy Award, Academy Award, and Golden Globe-winning musician, actor, and activist-follows up his New York Times bestselling memoir One Day It&#8217;ll All Make Sense with this inspiring exploration of how love and mindfulness can build communities and allow you to take better control of your life through actions [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-have-the-last-word-a-memoir-common-abridged/">Let Love Have the Last Word : A Memoir &#8211; Common (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    Common-the Grammy Award, Academy Award, and Golden Globe-winning musician, actor, and activist-follows up his New York Times bestselling memoir One Day It&#8217;ll All Make Sense with this inspiring exploration of how love and mindfulness can build communities and allow you to take better control of your life through actions and words.    </p>
<p>                    Common believes that the phrase &#8220;let love have the last word&#8221; is not just a declaration; it is a statement of purpose, a daily promise. Love is the most powerful force on the planet and ultimately, the way you love determines who you are and how you experience life.    </p>
<p>                    Touching on God, self-love, partners, children, family, and community, Common explores the core tenets of love to help others understand what it means to receive and, most important, to give love. He moves from the personal-writing about his daughter, to whom he wants to be a better father-to the universal, where he observes that our society has become fractured under issues of race and politics. He knows there&#8217;s no quick remedy for all of the hurt in the world, but love-for yourself and for others-is where the healing begins.    </p>
<p>                    Courageous, insightful, brave, and characteristically authentic, Let Love Have the Last Word shares Common&#8217;s own unique and personal stories of the people and experiences that have led to a greater understanding of love and all it has to offer. It is a powerful call to action for a new generation of open hearts and minds, one that is sure to resonate for years to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-have-the-last-word-a-memoir-common-abridged/">Let Love Have the Last Word : A Memoir &#8211; Common (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now the subject of a film by Richard Linklater, Eric Schlosser&#8217;s explosive bestseller Fast Food Nation: What the All-American Meal is Doing to the World tells the story of our love affair with fast food. Britain eats more fast food than any other country in Europe. It looks good, tastes good, and it&#8217;s cheap. But [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now the subject of a film by Richard Linklater, Eric Schlosser&#8217;s explosive bestseller Fast Food Nation: What the All-American Meal is Doing to the World tells the story of our love affair with fast food.    </p>
<p>                      Britain eats more fast food than any other country in Europe. It looks good, tastes good, and it&#8217;s cheap. But the real cost never appears on the menu.    </p>
<p>                      Eric Schlosser visits the lab that re-creates the smell of strawberries; examines the safety records of abattoirs; reveals why the fries really taste so good and what lurks between the sesame buns &#8211; and shows how fast food is transforming not only our diets but our world.    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Fast Food Nation has lifted the polystyrene lid on the global fast food industry &#8230; and sparked a storm&#8217;<br />
                      Observer    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Has wiped that smirk off the Happy Meal &#8230; Thanks to this man, you&#8217;ll never eat a burger again&#8217;<br />
                      Evening Standard    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Startling &#8230; Junk food, we learn, is just that &#8230; left this reader vowing never to set foot in one of those outlets again&#8217;<br />
                      Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;This book tells you more than you really want to know when you&#8217;re chomping on that hamburger &#8230; Have a nice day? Listen &#8211; you should live so long&#8217;<br />
                      The Times    </p>
<p>                      Eric Schlosser is a correspondent for the Atlantic Monthly. His first book, Fast Food Nation, was a major international bestseller. His work has appeared in the Atlantic Monthly, Rolling Stone and the Guardian. He has received a number of journalistic honours, including a National Magazine Award for an Atlantic Review article on the drug trade, which was later adapted into the book Reefer Madness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Longevity Project : Surprising Discoveries for Health and Long Life from the Landmark Eight Decade Study &#8211; Howard S. Friedman, Leslie R. Martin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-longevity-project-surprising-discoveries-for-health-and-long-life-from-the-landmark-eight-decade-study-howard-s-friedman-leslie-r-martin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-longevity-project-surprising-discoveries-for-health-and-long-life-from-the-landmark-eight-decade-study-howard-s-friedman-leslie-r-martin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We have been told that the key to longevity involves obsessing over what we eat, how much we stress, and how fast we run. Based on the most extensive study of longevity ever conducted, The Longevity Project exposes what really impacts our lifespan-including friends, family, personality and work. Gathering new information and using modern statistics [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-project-surprising-discoveries-for-health-and-long-life-from-the-landmark-eight-decade-study-howard-s-friedman-leslie-r-martin-abridged/">The Longevity Project : Surprising Discoveries for Health and Long Life from the Landmark Eight Decade Study &#8211; Howard S. Friedman, Leslie R. Martin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have been told that the key to longevity involves obsessing over what we eat, how much we stress, and how fast we run. Based on the most extensive study of longevity ever conducted, The Longevity Project exposes what really impacts our lifespan-including friends, family, personality and work.     </p>
<p>                    Gathering new information and using modern statistics to study participants across eight decades, Dr Howard Friedman and Dr Leslie Martin bust myths about achieving health and long life. For example, people do not die from working long hours at a challenging job &#8211; many who worked the hardest lived the longest. Getting and staying married is not the magic ticket to long life, especially if you&#8217;re a woman. And it&#8217;s not the happy-go-lucky ones who thrive &#8211; it&#8217;s the prudent and persistent who flourish through the years.     </p>
<p>                    With questionnaires that help you determine where you are heading on the longevity spectrum and advice about how to stay healthy, this book changes the conversation about living a long, healthy life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-project-surprising-discoveries-for-health-and-long-life-from-the-landmark-eight-decade-study-howard-s-friedman-leslie-r-martin-abridged/">The Longevity Project : Surprising Discoveries for Health and Long Life from the Landmark Eight Decade Study &#8211; Howard S. Friedman, Leslie R. Martin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-alcoholic Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217; &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217;  &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller      </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice O&#8217;Keeffe, Guardian     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Truthful, modern and real&#8217; &#8211; Stylist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Brave, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober came to me at a time when I much needed it&#8230; The book became my best friend, and got me through, and took me on a journey.&#8217; &#8211; Sadie Frost     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Particularly lovely, because it&#8217;s not a deep and dark dive into someone&#8217;s terrible addiction. It&#8217;s a celebration of everything that she has gained from not drinking&#8217; &#8211; Laura Donnelly     </p>
<p>                    Ever sworn off alcohol for a month and found yourself drinking by the 7th? Think there&#8217;s &#8216;no point&#8217; in just one drink? Welcome! There are millions of us. 64% of Brits want to drink less.    </p>
<p>                    Catherine Gray was stuck in a hellish whirligig of Drink, Make horrible decisions, Hangover, Repeat. She had her fair share of &#8216;drunk tank&#8217; jail cells and topless-in-a-hot-tub misadventures.    </p>
<p>                    But this book goes beyond the binges and blackouts to deep-dive into uncharted territory: What happens after you quit drinking? This gripping, heart-breaking and witty book takes us down the rabbit-hole of an alternative reality. A life with zero hangovers, through sober weddings, sex, Christmases and breakups.     </p>
<p>                    In The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober, Catherine Gray shines a light on society&#8217;s drink-pushing and talks to top neuroscientists and psychologists about why we drink, delving into the science behind what it does to our brains and bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Much more than a tale from the netherworld of addicted drinking, this book is about the escape, and why a sober life can be more intoxicating than you ever imagined. Whether you&#8217;re a hopelessly devoted drinker, merely sober-curious, or you&#8217;ve already ditched the drink, you will love this book.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Haunting, admirable and enlightening&#8217; &#8211; The Pool     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A riveting, raw, yet humorous memoir with actionable advice. A truly unique blend of storytelling and science that holds a universe of hope.&#8217; &#8211; Annie Grace, author of This Naked Mind     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Like listening to your best friend teach you to be sober. Lighthearted but serious, it&#8217;s packed with ideas, tools, tips and, most importantly, reasons for living a sober life. This book is excellent.&#8217;- Eric Zimmer, host of podcast The One You Feed     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s fizzy writing succeeds in making this potentially boring-as-hell subject both engaging and highly seductive&#8217; &#8211; The Bookseller     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray is an exceptional writer. Her exquisitely crafted thoughts on the joys of being sober are not only deeply honest and pragmatic, but she manages to infuse tons of humor. This is a delightful, informative, and compelling read for all those who are sober or seeking sobriety.&#8217; &#8211; Sasha Tozzi, Huffington Post columnist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine&#8217;s writing style and voice captivate me. She has a way of translating her story into an experience I don&#8217;t want to end. I want to drink every drop she produces.&#8217; &#8211; Holly Whitaker, founder of Hip Sobriety School and co-presenter of Home podcast     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book is great. A balanced, informative and entertaining melange of memoir, sociology and psychology. I identified very strongly with huge sections of it.&#8217; &#8211; Jon Stewart, guitarist of Sleeper and Leaving AA, Staying Sober blogger >    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Sober is too often equated with &#8220;sombre&#8221; in our culture. Gray&#8217;s book turns that idea on its head. Her experience of sobriety is joyful and life-affirming. A must-read for anyone who has a nagging suspicion that alcohol may be taking away more than it&#8217;s giving.&#8217; &#8211; Hilda Burke, psychotherapist and couples counsellor     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray really captures the FUN we can have in sobriety. This book challenges the status quo; sobriet sounds as liberating as taking a trip to the jungle. Fun and inspirational. What an important book for our time! A joy to read.&#8217; &#8211; Samantha Moyo, founder of Morning Gloryville     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;No other author writes about sober living with as much warmth or emotional range as Catherine Gray. Her deep insight into the subtle psychologies of drinking, and of life, means that everything she writes is both utterly relatable and stretches our minds. Hers is a rare wisdom.&#8217; &#8211; Dr Richard Piper, CEO, Alcohol Change UK</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What the Fork are You Eating? : An Action Plan for Your Pantry and Plate &#8211; Stefanie Sacks, Foreword byKathie Madonna Swift (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s labeled natural, grass-fed, or free-roaming; yet it might be anything but. It&#8217;s time to find out what you&#8217;re actually eating&#8230; When your groceries are labeled &#8220;low-fat,&#8221; &#8220;sugar-free,&#8221; and even &#8220;natural&#8221; and antibiotic-free, it&#8217;s easy to assume that you&#8217;re making healthy choices. Yet even some of those seemingly wholesome offerings contain chemical preservatives, pesticides, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/">What the Fork are You Eating? : An Action Plan for Your Pantry and Plate &#8211; Stefanie Sacks, Foreword byKathie Madonna Swift (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s labeled natural, grass-fed, or free-roaming; yet it might be anything but. It&#8217;s time to find out what you&#8217;re actually eating&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    When your groceries are labeled &#8220;low-fat,&#8221; &#8220;sugar-free,&#8221; and even &#8220;natural&#8221; and antibiotic-free, it&#8217;s easy to assume that you&#8217;re making healthy choices. Yet even some of those seemingly wholesome offerings contain chemical preservatives, pesticides, and artificial flavors and coloring that negatively affect your health. In What the Fork Are You Eating?, a practical guide written by certified chef and nutritionist Stefanie Sacks, MS, CNS, CDN, we learn exactly what the most offensive ingredients in our food are and how we can remove (or at least minimize) them in our diets. Sacks gives us an aisle-by-aisle rundown of how to shop for healthier items and create simple, nutritious, and delicious meals, including fifty original recipes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/">What the Fork are You Eating? : An Action Plan for Your Pantry and Plate &#8211; Stefanie Sacks, Foreword byKathie Madonna Swift (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diaries, Letters & Journals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geographical Discovery & Exploration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transplant Surgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories: Discovery / Historical / Scientific]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jauhar weaves his own personal and family story into his history of the heart&#8230;very effectively&#8230; This gives a certain dramatic tension to the book, as it tells the fascinating and rather wonderful history of cardiology.&#8217; -Henry Marsh, New Statesman A Mail on Sunday Book of the Year The heart lies at the centre of life. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/">Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jauhar weaves his own personal and family story into his history of the heart&#8230;very effectively&#8230; This gives a certain dramatic tension to the book, as it tells the fascinating and rather wonderful history of cardiology.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    -Henry Marsh, New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    A Mail on Sunday Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    The heart lies at the centre of life. For cardiologist Sandeep Jauhar it is an obsession.    </p>
<p>                    In this fascinating history he interweaves gripping scenes from the operating theatre with the moving tale of his family&#8217;s history of heart problems &#8211; from the death of his grandfather to the ominous signs of how he himself might die.    </p>
<p>                    Jauhar looks at the pioneers who risked patients&#8217; lives and their own careers, and confronts the limits of medical technology, arguing that how we live is more important than any device or drug we may invent. Heart is the all-encompassing story of the engine of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/">Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 3 MILLION COPIES SOLD Do you ever suspect that everyone else has life figured out and you don&#8217;t have a clue? If so, Rachel Hollis has something to tell you: that&#8217;s a lie. If you have ever said any of these things to yourself . . . Something [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/">Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 3 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    Do you ever suspect that everyone else has life figured out and you don&#8217;t have a clue? If so, Rachel Hollis has something to tell you: that&#8217;s a lie.    </p>
<p>                    If you have ever said any of these things to yourself . . .    </p>
<p>                    Something else will make me happy.<br />
                    I&#8217;m not a good mom.<br />
                    I will never get past this.<br />
                    I am defined by my weight.<br />
                    I should be further along by now.    </p>
<p>                    . . . then you could benefit from the unflinching faith and rock-hard tenacity Rachel Hollis has in store for you. In this challenging but conversational book, Rachel exposes the twenty lies and misconceptions that too often hold us back from living joyfully and productively, lies we&#8217;ve told ourselves so often we don&#8217;t even hear them anymore.    </p>
<p>                    Rachel is real and talks about real issues. More than that, she reveals the specific practical strategies that helped her move past them. In the process, she encourages, entertains, and even kicks a little butt, all to convince you to do whatever it takes to get real and become the joyous, confident woman you were meant to be. Because you really can live with passion and hustle &#8211; and give yourself grace without giving up.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/">Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age. Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age.    </p>
<p>                              Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more than twenty years, he has been on a quest to find innovative, science-backed methods to upgrade human biology and redefine the limits of the mind, body, and spirit. The results speak for themselves. Now in his forties, Dave is smarter, happier, and more fit and successful than ever before.    </p>
<p>                              In Super Human, he shows how this is level of health and performance possible for all of us. While we assume we will peak in middle age and then decline, Asprey&#8217;s research reveals there is another way. It is possible to make changes on the sub-cellular level to dramatically extend life span. And the tools to live longer also give you more energy and brainpower right now.    </p>
<p>                              The answers lie in Dave&#8217;s Seven Pillars of Ageing that contribute to degeneration and disease while diminishing your performance in the moment. Using simple interventions &#8211; like diet, sleep, light, exercise, and little-known but powerful hacks from ozone therapy to proper jaw alignment, you can decelerate cellular ageing and supercharge your body&#8217;s ability to heal and rejuvenate.    </p>
<p>                              A self-proclaimed human guinea pig, Asprey arms readers with practical advice to maximize their lives at every age with his signature mix of science-geek wonder, candour, and enthusiasm. Getting older no longer has to mean decline. Now it&#8217;s an opportunity to become Super Human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller from the author of How to Change Your Mind, The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, and Food Rules Food. There&#8217;s plenty of it around, and we all love to eat it. So why should anyone need to defend it? Because in the so-called Western diet, food has been replaced by nutrients, and common [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/">In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller from the author of How to Change Your Mind, The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, and Food Rules      </p>
<p>                     Food. There&#8217;s plenty of it around, and we all love to eat it. So why should anyone need to defend it?     </p>
<p>                     Because in the so-called Western diet, food has been replaced by nutrients, and common sense by confusion&#8211;most of what we&#8217;re consuming today is longer the product of nature but of food science. The result is what Michael Pollan calls the American Paradox: The more we worry about nutrition, the less healthy we see to become. With In Defense of Food, Pollan proposes a new (and very old) answer to the question of what we should eat that comes down to seven simple but liberating words: Eat food. Not too much. Mostly plants. Pollan&#8217;s bracing and eloquent manifesto shows us how we can start making thoughtful food choices that will enrich our lives, enlarge our sense of what it means to be healthy, and bring pleasure back to eating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/">In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4-Hour Body : An Uncommon Guide to Rapid Fat-loss, Incredible Sex and Becoming Superhuman &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to lose fat, double testosterone, get the perfect posterior or give your partner a fifteen-minute female orgasm? Whatever your physical goal, The 4-Hour Body eclipses every other health manual by sharing the best kept secrets in the latest science and research to provide new strategies for redesigning the human body. And you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">The 4-Hour Body : An Uncommon Guide to Rapid Fat-loss, Incredible Sex and Becoming Superhuman &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to lose fat, double testosterone, get the perfect posterior or give your partner a fifteen-minute female orgasm? Whatever your physical goal, The 4-Hour Body eclipses every other health manual by sharing the best kept secrets in the latest science and research to provide new strategies for redesigning the human body.     </p>
<p>                    And you don&#8217;t need to exhaust yourself. International bestselling author, Timothy Ferriss, helps you reach your true genetic potential in 3-6 months with a commitment of less than four hours per week. You can pick and choose from a menu of options, from simple to extreme, for dramatic body changes.     </p>
<p>                    Based on over 15 years of research and with personal stories, amazing before and after photos, recipes and sidebars, The 4-Hour Body will give unbelievable results and change the way you look forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">The 4-Hour Body : An Uncommon Guide to Rapid Fat-loss, Incredible Sex and Becoming Superhuman &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sleep Smarter : 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to a Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success &#8211; Shawn Stevenson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your body&#8217;s natural ability to sleep soundly and learn how to boost your energy, lose weight, and improve your overall health and wellbeing. When it comes to health, there is one criminally overlooked element: sleep. Good sleep helps you shed fat for good, stave off disease, stay productive and improve virtually every function of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/">Sleep Smarter : 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to a Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success &#8211; Shawn Stevenson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your body&#8217;s natural ability to sleep soundly and learn how to boost your energy, lose weight, and improve your overall health and wellbeing.    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to health, there is one criminally overlooked element: sleep. Good sleep helps you shed fat for good, stave off disease, stay productive and improve virtually every function of your mind and body. When a degenerative bone disease crushed Shawn Stevenson&#8217;s dream of becoming a professional athlete and restricted his ability to function normally in daily life, Shawn took his health into his own hands. Through better sleep and optimized nutrition, he not only healed his body but also achieved fitness and business goals he never thought possible.    </p>
<p>                    Now in Sleep Smarter, Shawn shares easy tips and tricks to discover the best sleep and best health of your life. With a 14-Day Sleep Makeover, you&#8217;ll learn:<br />
                    &#8211; How to create the ideal sleep sanctuary<br />
                    &#8211; How to hack sunlight to regulate your circadian rhythms<br />
                    &#8211; Which clinically proven sleep nutrients and supplements you need and why<br />
                    &#8211; Stress-reduction exercises and fitness tips to keep you mentally and physically sharp&#8230; and more!    </p>
<p>                    Sleep Smarter is the much-needed guide for achieving the rest, energy and life you truly deserve.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/">Sleep Smarter : 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to a Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success &#8211; Shawn Stevenson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dreams & Their Interpretation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now! __________________________________________________________________________________ FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now!<br />
                    __________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver    </p>
<p>                    Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in his Sunday Times bestselling book, The 4 Pillar Plan, BBC One&#8217;s Dr Rangan Chatterjee creates an easily accessible plan for taking control of your health and your life.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Chatterjee believes that everyday health revolves around the following four pillars: relaxation, food, movement and sleep. By making small, achievable changes in each of these key areas you can create and maintain good health &#8211; and avoid illness. Top tips in each area include:     </p>
<p>                    * an electronic &#8216;sabbath&#8217; once a week<br />
                     * 12 hours every day without food<br />
                     * exposure to sunlight first thing each morning<br />
                     * walking at least 10,000 steps a day    </p>
<p>                    Based on cutting edge research and his own two decades&#8217; worth of experience as a doctor, this book contains fascinating case studies from real patients and is an inspiring and easy-to-follow guide to better health and happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a New Afterword Must We Age? Nearly all scientists who study the biology of aging agree that we will someday be able to substantially slow down the aging process, extending our productive, youthful lives. Dr. Aubrey de Grey is perhaps the most bullish of all such researchers. As has been reported in media outlets [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/">Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a New Afterword     </p>
<p>                    Must We Age?     </p>
<p>                    Nearly all scientists who study the biology of aging agree that we will someday be able to substantially slow down the aging process, extending our productive, youthful lives. Dr. Aubrey de Grey is perhaps the most bullish of all such researchers. As has been reported in media outlets ranging from 60 Minutes to The New York Times,  Dr. de Grey believes that the key biomedical technology required to eliminate aging-derived debilitation and death entirely&#8211;technology that would not only slow but periodically reverse age-related physiological decay, leaving us biologically young into an indefinite future&#8211;is now within reach.     </p>
<p>                    In Ending Aging,  Dr. de Grey and his research assistant Michael Rae describe the details of this biotechnology. They explain that the aging of the human body, just like the aging of man-made machines, results from an accumulation of various types of damage. As with man-made machines, this damage can periodically be repaired, leading to indefinite extension of the machine&#8217;s fully functional lifetime, just as is routinely done with classic cars. We already know what types of damage accumulate in the human body, and we are moving rapidly toward the comprehensive development of technologies to remove that -damage. By demystifying aging and its postponement for the nonspecialist reader, de Grey and Rae systematically dismantle the fatalist presumption that aging will forever defeat the efforts of medical science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/">Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author). We are in the grip of a food [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author).<br />
                       We are in the grip of a food crisis. Obesity has become a leading cause of preventable death, after only smoking. For nearly half a century we&#8217;ve been trying to pin the blame somewhere, fat, carbs, sugar, wheat, high-fructose corn syrup. But that search has been in vain, because the food problem that&#8217;s killing us is not a nutrient problem. It&#8217;s a behavioural problem, and it&#8217;s caused by the changing flavour of the food we eat.<br />
                       Ever since the 1940s, with the rise of industrialized food production, we have been gradually leeching the taste out of what we grow. Simultaneously, we have taken great leaps forward in technology, creating a flavour industry, worth billions annually; in an attempt to put back the tastes we&#8217;ve engineered out of our food. The result is a cuisine that increasingly resembles the paragon of flavour manipulation: Doritos. As food becomes increasingly bland, we dress it up with calories and flavour chemicals to make it delicious again. We have rewired our palates and our brains, and the results are making us sick and killing us.<br />
                       With in-depth historical and scientific research, The Dorito Effect casts the food crisis in a fascinating new light, weaving an enthralling tale of how we got to this point and where we are headed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health    </p>
<p>                    Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, bacteria and human cells have co-existed in a relationship that has ensured the health and equilibrium of our body. But now, much like the natural world outside of us, our internal environment is being irrevocably destroyed. The culprit: some of our most revered medical advances &#8211; antibiotics &#8211; which appear to be linked to the epidemics of asthma, eczema, obesity, certain forms of cancer, and other diseases plaguing modern society.    </p>
<p>                    In a book that stands as the Silent Spring of its day, Blaser sounds a provocative alarm that we ignore at our peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, WithBrendan Buhler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more. In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, WithBrendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more.     </p>
<p>                    In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly within our intestines&#8211;has an astonishing impact on our lives. Your health, mood, sleep patterns, eating preferences&#8211;even your likelihood of getting bitten by mosquitoes&#8211;can be traced in part to the tiny creatures that live on and inside of us.     </p>
<p>                    In Follow Your Gut,  pioneering scientist Rob Knight pairs with award-winning science journalist Brendan Buhler to explain&#8211;with good humor and easy-to-grasp examples&#8211;why these new findings matter to everyone. They lead a detailed tour of the previously unseen world inside our bodies, calling out the diseases and conditions believed to be most directly impacted by them.     </p>
<p>                    With a practical eye toward deeper knowledge and better decisions, they also explore the known effects of antibiotics, probiotics, diet choice and even birth method on our children&#8217;s lifelong health. Ultimately, this pioneering book explains how to learn about your own microbiome and take steps toward understanding and improving your health, using the latest research as a guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, WithBrendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax    </p>
<p>                    Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world has become a word-of-mouth bestseller and global phenomenon. It reveals a set of simple yet powerful practices that you can incorporate into daily life to break the cycle of anxiety, stress unhappiness and exhaustion. It promotes the kind of happiness that gets into your bones and allows you to meet the worst that life throws at you with new courage.     </p>
<p>                    Mindfulness is based on mindfulness-based cognitive therapy (MBCT). Co-developed by Professor Mark Williams of Oxford University, MBCT is recommended by the UK&#8217;s National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and is as effective as drugs for preventing depression. But, equally, it works for the rest of us who aren&#8217;t depressed but who are struggling to keep up with the relentless demands of the modern world.     </p>
<p>                    By investing just a few minutes each day, this classic guide to mindfulness will put you back in control of your life once again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Nurture Assumption : Why Children Turn Out the Way They Do &#8211; Judith Rich Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-nurture-assumption-why-children-turn-out-the-way-they-do-judith-rich-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-nurture-assumption-why-children-turn-out-the-way-they-do-judith-rich-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This groundbreaking book, a Pulitzer Prize finalist and New York Times notable pick, rattled the psychological establishment when it was first published in 1998 by claiming that parents have little impact on their children&#8217;s development. In this tenth anniversary edition of The Nurture Assumption, Judith Harris has updated material throughout and provided a fresh introduction. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-nurture-assumption-why-children-turn-out-the-way-they-do-judith-rich-harris-abridged/">The Nurture Assumption : Why Children Turn Out the Way They Do &#8211; Judith Rich Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This groundbreaking book, a Pulitzer Prize finalist and New York Times notable pick, rattled the psychological establishment when it was first published in 1998 by claiming that parents have little impact on their children&#8217;s development. In this tenth anniversary edition of The Nurture Assumption, Judith Harris has updated material throughout and provided a fresh introduction.     </p>
<p>                    Combining insights from psychology, sociology, anthropology, primatology, and evolutionary biology, she explains how and why the tendency of children to take cues from their peers works to their evolutionary advantage. This electrifying book explodes many of our unquestioned beliefs about children and parents and gives us a radically new view of childhood.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-nurture-assumption-why-children-turn-out-the-way-they-do-judith-rich-harris-abridged/">The Nurture Assumption : Why Children Turn Out the Way They Do &#8211; Judith Rich Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trauma & Shock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;An astonishing and important book. The trauma Bible. I cannot recommend it enough for anyone struggling with&#8230;well&#8230;anything&#8217; Tara Westover The effects of trauma can be devastating for sufferers, their families and future generations. Here one of the world&#8217;s experts on traumatic stress offers a bold new paradigm for treatment, moving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/">The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An astonishing and important book. The trauma Bible. I  cannot recommend it enough for anyone struggling with&#8230;well&#8230;anything&#8217; Tara Westover    </p>
<p>                    The effects of trauma can be devastating for sufferers, their families and future generations. Here one of the world&#8217;s experts on traumatic stress offers a bold new paradigm for treatment, moving away from standard talking and drug therapies and towards an alternative approach that heals mind, brain and body.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Dr. van der Kolk&#8217;s masterpiece combines the boundless curiosity of the scientist, the erudition of the scholar, and the passion of the truth teller&#8217; Judith Herman, author of Trauma and Recovery</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/">The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling work that overturns conventional conceptions of health and illness to offer new methods for increasing vital longevity. CAN WE LIVE ROBUSTLY UNTIL OUR LAST BREATH? Do we have to suffer from debilitating conditions and sickness? Is it possible to add more vibrant years to our lives? In the #1 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/">The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling work that overturns conventional conceptions of health and illness to offer new methods for increasing vital longevity. CAN WE LIVE ROBUSTLY UNTIL OUR LAST BREATH? Do we have to suffer from debilitating conditions and sickness? Is it possible to add more vibrant years to our lives? In the #1 New York Times bestselling The End of Illness, Dr. David Agus tackles these fundamental questions and dismantles misperceptions about what &#8220;health&#8221; really means. Presenting an eye-opening picture of the human body and all the ways it works&#8211;and fails&#8211;Dr. Agus shows us how a new perspective on our individual health will allow us to achieve a long, vigorous life. Offering insights and access to powerful new technologies that promise to transform medicine, Dr. Agus emphasizes his belief that there is no &#8220;right&#8221; answer, no master guide that is &#8220;one size fits all.&#8221; Each one of us must get to know our bodies in uniquely personal ways, and he shows us exactly how to do that. A bold call for all of us to become our own personal health advocates, The End of Illness is a moving departure from orthodox thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/">The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking study that reveals how decades of misleading science and policy unjustly demonized the high-fat diet, which might actually be our healthiest option. For the past 60 years we have been told that a low-fat diet can protect against obesity, diabetes, and heart disease. Yet despite many of us taking this advice in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking study that reveals how decades of misleading science and policy unjustly demonized the high-fat diet, which<br />
                    might actually be our healthiest option.    </p>
<p>                    For the past 60 years we have been told that a low-fat diet can protect against obesity, diabetes, and heart disease. Yet despite<br />
                    many of us taking this advice in the developed West, we are now in the midst of an obesity epidemic that is breeding serious<br />
                    health problems.    </p>
<p>                    Recent more rigorous scientific work has overturned some of the shoddier theories of earlier decades to demonstrate conclusively that we have been needlessly avoiding red meat, cheese, whole milk, and eggs for decades, and that we can now, guilt-free, welcome these delicious foods back into our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Body Kindness : Transform Your Health from the Inside Out&#8211;and Never Say Diet Again &#8211; Rebecca Scritchfield (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/body-kindness-transform-your-health-from-the-inside-out-and-never-say-diet-again-rebecca-scritchfield-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/body-kindness-transform-your-health-from-the-inside-out-and-never-say-diet-again-rebecca-scritchfield-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is not a diet book &#8211; there are no menu plans or fitness routines here! Body Kindness addresses overall health (with a focus on both food and movement throughout) in four sections: What you do: the choices you make about food and nutrition, including mindful eating and eating with joy how you feel: your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/body-kindness-transform-your-health-from-the-inside-out-and-never-say-diet-again-rebecca-scritchfield-abridged/">Body Kindness : Transform Your Health from the Inside Out&#8211;and Never Say Diet Again &#8211; Rebecca Scritchfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is not a diet book &#8211; there are no menu plans or fitness routines here! Body Kindness addresses overall health (with a focus on both food and movement throughout) in four sections: What you do: the choices you make about food and nutrition, including mindful eating and eating with joy how you feel: your emotions, and how to change the voice in your head who you are: identifying your values and choices where you belong: finding your community each section includes inspiration as well as fun, scientifically based activities and exercises that focus on incremental, sustainable change. The exercises lead the emotions to &#8220;spiral up,&#8221; giving the reader insight and j rewards for positive change. The author makes a revolutionary yet scientifically proven declaration: You can lose weight only if you stop having weight loss as your goal. When you make choices about your health that are in line with your values, the result is a healthier body that you love. The goal of the book: to resolve the conflict where health and happiness diverge and help reconnect the two.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/body-kindness-transform-your-health-from-the-inside-out-and-never-say-diet-again-rebecca-scritchfield-abridged/">Body Kindness : Transform Your Health from the Inside Out&#8211;and Never Say Diet Again &#8211; Rebecca Scritchfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The ADHD Advantage : What You Thought Was a Diagnosis May Be Your Greatest Strength &#8211; Dale Archer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-adhd-advantage-what-you-thought-was-a-diagnosis-may-be-your-greatest-strength-dale-archer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-adhd-advantage-what-you-thought-was-a-diagnosis-may-be-your-greatest-strength-dale-archer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times-bestselling author of Better Than Normal, esteemed psychiatrist Dale Archer, M.D., reveals how ADHD might be the key to your success. For decades, in the United States and in countries around the world, physicians delivered the diagnosis of ADHD to patients as bad news and warned them about a lifelong struggle of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-adhd-advantage-what-you-thought-was-a-diagnosis-may-be-your-greatest-strength-dale-archer-abridged/">The ADHD Advantage : What You Thought Was a Diagnosis May Be Your Greatest Strength &#8211; Dale Archer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times-bestselling author of Better Than Normal, esteemed psychiatrist Dale Archer, M.D., reveals how ADHD might be the key to your success.     </p>
<p>                     For decades, in the United States and in countries around the world, physicians delivered the diagnosis of ADHD to patients as bad news and warned them about a lifelong struggle of managing symptoms. But The ADHD Advantage explodes this outlook, arguing that some of the most highly successful entrepreneurs, leaders, and entertainers have reached the pinnacle of success not in spite of their ADHD but because of it.     </p>
<p>                    People with ADHD are restless, endlessly curious, often adventurous, willing to take smart risks, and unusually resilient, and their ranks include some of the greatest entrepreneurs of our time. Sharing the stories of highly successful people with ADHD, Archer offers a vitally important and inspiring new way to recognize ADHD traits in oneself or in one&#8217;s loved ones and then leverage them to great advantage. Readers will learn to harness mental energy for greater creativity, embrace multitasking, and build a path to great success&#8211;without medication. As someone who not only has ADHD himself but has never used medication to treat it, Dr. Archer understands the condition from a unique professional and personal standpoint. Armed with new science and research, and his own personal experience, he teaches readers to embrace their natural strengths and innate potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-adhd-advantage-what-you-thought-was-a-diagnosis-may-be-your-greatest-strength-dale-archer-abridged/">The ADHD Advantage : What You Thought Was a Diagnosis May Be Your Greatest Strength &#8211; Dale Archer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of The Willpower Instinct introduces a surprising science-based book that doesn&#8217;t tell us why we should exercise but instead shows us how to fall in love with movement. Exercise is health-enhancing and life-extending, yet many of us feel it&#8217;s a chore. But, as Kelly McGonigal reveals, it doesn&#8217;t have to be. Movement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of The Willpower Instinct introduces a surprising science-based book that doesn&#8217;t tell us why we should exercise but instead shows us how to fall in love with movement.    </p>
<p>                    Exercise is health-enhancing and life-extending, yet many of us feel it&#8217;s a chore. But, as Kelly McGonigal reveals, it doesn&#8217;t have to be. Movement can and should be a source of joy.    </p>
<p>                    Through her trademark blend of science and storytelling, McGonigal draws on insights from neuroscience, psychology, anthropology, and evolutionary biology, as well as memoirs, ethnographies, and philosophers. She shows how movement is intertwined with some of the most basic human joys, including self-expression, social connection, and mastery&#8211;and why it is a powerful antidote to the modern epidemics of depression, anxiety, and loneliness.    </p>
<p>                    McGonigal tells the stories of people who have found fulfillment and belonging through running, walking, dancing, swimming, weightlifting, and more, with examples that span the globe, from Tanzania, where one of the last hunter-gatherer tribes on the planet live, to a dance class at Juilliard for people with Parkinson&#8217;s disease, to the streets of London, where volunteers combine fitness and community service, to races in the remote wilderness, where athletes push the limits of what a human can endure. Along the way, McGonigal paints a portrait of human nature that highlights our capacity for hope, cooperation, and self-transcendence.    </p>
<p>                    The result is a revolutionary narrative that goes beyond familiar arguments in favor of exercise, to illustrate why movement is integral to both our happiness and our humanity. Readers will learn what they can do in their own lives and communities to harness the power of movement to create happiness, meaning, and connection.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Will You Measure Your Life? &#8211; Clayton Christensen, James Allworth, Karen Dillon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-will-you-measure-your-life-clayton-christensen-james-allworth-karen-dillon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-will-you-measure-your-life-clayton-christensen-james-allworth-karen-dillon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How do you lead a fulfilling life? That profound question animates this book of inspiration and insight from world-class business strategist and bestselling author of The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma, Clayton Christensen. After beating a heart attack, advanced-stage cancer and a stroke in three successive years, the world-renowned innovation expert and author of one of the best [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-will-you-measure-your-life-clayton-christensen-james-allworth-karen-dillon-abridged/">How Will You Measure Your Life? &#8211; Clayton Christensen, James Allworth, Karen Dillon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do you lead a fulfilling life? That profound question animates this book of inspiration and insight from world-class business strategist and bestselling author of The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma, Clayton Christensen.    </p>
<p>                              After beating a heart attack, advanced-stage cancer and a stroke in three successive years, the world-renowned innovation expert and author of one of the best selling and most influential business books of all time &#8211; The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma &#8211; Clayton M. Christensen delivered a short but powerful speech to the Harvard Business School graduating class. He presented a set of personal guidelines that have helped him find meaning and happiness in his life &#8211; a challenge even the brightest and most motivated of students find daunting.    </p>
<p>                              Akin to The Last Lecture in its revelatory perspective following life-altering events, that speech subsequently became a hugely popular article in the Harvard Business Review and is now a groundbreaking book, putting forth a series of questions and models for success that have long been applied in the world of business, but also can be used to find cogent answers to pressing life questions: How can I be sure that I&#8217;ll find satisfaction in my career? How can I be sure that my relationships with my spouse, my family and my close friends become enduring sources of happiness? How can I avoid compromising my integrity (and stay out of jail)?    </p>
<p>                              How Will You Measure Your Life? is a highly original, surprising book from a singular business figure. It&#8217;s a book sure to inspire and educate readers &#8211; companies and individuals, students of business, mid-career professionals, and even parents &#8211; the world over.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-will-you-measure-your-life-clayton-christensen-james-allworth-karen-dillon-abridged/">How Will You Measure Your Life? &#8211; Clayton Christensen, James Allworth, Karen Dillon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret &#8211; Rhonda Byrne (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2006, a groundbreaking feature-length film revealed the great mystery of the universe &#8211; The Secret. Later that year, Rhonda Byrne followed with a book that became a worldwide bestseller. Fragments of a Great Secret have been found in the oral traditions, in literature, in religions and philosophies throughout the centuries. For the first time, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/">The Secret &#8211; Rhonda Byrne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2006, a groundbreaking feature-length film revealed the great mystery of the universe &#8211; The Secret. Later that year, Rhonda Byrne followed with a book that became a worldwide bestseller.     </p>
<p>                    Fragments of a Great Secret have been found in the oral traditions, in literature, in religions and philosophies throughout the centuries. For the first time, all the pieces of The Secret come together in an incredible revelation that will be life-transforming for all who experience it.    </p>
<p>                    In this book, you&#8217;ll learn how to use The Secret in every aspect of your life &#8211; money, health, relationships, happiness, and in every interaction you have in the world. You&#8217;ll begin to understand the hidden, untapped power that&#8217;s within you, and this revelation can bring joy to every aspect of your life.    </p>
<p>                    The Secret contains wisdom from modern-day teachers &#8211; men and women who have used it to achieve health, wealth and happiness. By applying the knowledge of The Secret, they bring to light compelling stories of eradicating obstacles, and achieving what many would regard as impossible.    </p>
<p>                    Discover the book which has been changing millions of lives around the world. No matter who you are, where you are right now, no matter what you want &#8211; when you realise The Secret you can have anything.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/">The Secret &#8211; Rhonda Byrne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Geography & Topography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel With Children / Family Holidays]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>By the beloved and wildly popular host of the PBS Kids show Dinosaur Train, here is the book every parent needs: a rousing call to connect our kids to the natural world, filled with tips and advice. The average North American child now spends about seven hours a day staring at screens and mere minutes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/">How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By the beloved and wildly popular host of the PBS Kids show Dinosaur Train, here is the book every parent needs: a rousing call to connect our kids to the natural world, filled with tips and advice.    </p>
<p>                    The average North American child now spends about seven hours a day staring at screens and mere minutes engaged in unstructured play outdoors. Yet recent research indicates that experiences in nature are essential for healthy growth.     </p>
<p>                    Regular exposure to nature can help relieve stress, depression, and attention deficits. It can reduce bullying, combat obesity, and boost academic scores. Most critical of all, abundant time in natural settings seems to yield long-term benefits in kids&#8217; cognitive, emotional, and social development.     </p>
<p>                    How to Raise a Wild Child is a timely and engaging antidote, offering teachers, parents, and other caregivers the necessary tools to engender a meaningful, lasting connection between children and the natural world.     </p>
<p>                    Distilling the latest research in multiple disciplines, Sampson reveals how adults can help kids fall in love with nature&#8211;enlisting technology as an ally, taking advantage of urban nature, and instilling a sense of place along the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In a time when the connection between humans and the rest of nature is most vulnerable, Scott offers parents and teachers a book of encouragement and knowledge, and to children, the priceless gift of wonder.&#8221;&#8211;Richard Louv, author of Last Child in the Woods and The Nature Principle</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/">How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Notes on a Nervous Planet &#8211; Matt Haig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Order THE COMFORT BOOK. Available now! THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The world is messing with our minds. What if there was something we could do about it? Looking at sleep, news, social media, addiction, work and play, Matt Haig invites us to feel calmer, happier and to question the habits of the digital [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/">Notes on a Nervous Planet &#8211; Matt Haig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Order THE COMFORT BOOK. Available now!    </p>
<p>                    THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The world is messing with our minds. What if there was something we could do about it?    </p>
<p>                    Looking at sleep, news, social media, addiction, work and play, Matt Haig invites us to feel calmer, happier and to question the habits of the digital age. This book might even change the way you spend your precious time on earth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/">Notes on a Nervous Planet &#8211; Matt Haig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat to Live : The Amazing Nutrient-Rich Program for Fast and Sustained Weight Loss &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hailed a &#8220;medical breakthrough&#8221; by Dr. Mehmet Oz, Eat to Live offers a highly effective, scientifically proven way to lose weight quickly. The key to Dr. Joel Fuhrman&#8217;s revolutionary six-week plan is simple: health = nutrients / calories. When the ratio of nutrients to calories in the food you eat is high, you lose weight. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Eat to Live : The Amazing Nutrient-Rich Program for Fast and Sustained Weight Loss &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hailed a &#8220;medical breakthrough&#8221; by Dr. Mehmet Oz, Eat to Live offers a highly effective, scientifically proven way to lose weight quickly.     </p>
<p>                     The key to Dr. Joel Fuhrman&#8217;s revolutionary six-week plan is simple: health = nutrients / calories. When the ratio of nutrients to calories in the food you eat is high, you lose weight. The more nutrient-dense food you eat, the less you crave fat, sweets, and high-caloric foods.     </p>
<p>                    Eat to Live has been revised to include inspiring success stories from people who have used the program to lose shockingly large amounts of weight and recover from life-threatening illnesses; Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s nutrient density index; up-to-date scientific research supporting the principles behind Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s plan; new recipes and meal ideas; and much more. This easy-to-follow, nutritionally sound diet can help anyone shed pounds quickly-and keep them off.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Furhman&#8217;s formula is simple, safe, and solid.&#8221; &#8211;Body and Soul</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Eat to Live : The Amazing Nutrient-Rich Program for Fast and Sustained Weight Loss &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle, from the bestselling author of How Not to Die. Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle,  from the bestselling author of How Not to Die.    </p>
<p>                    Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any happier or healthier. As obesity rates and associated disease and impairments continue to rise, it&#8217;s time for a different approach.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet is a treasure trove of buried data and cutting-edge dietary research that Dr Michael Greger has translated into accessible, actionable advice with exciting tools and tricks that will help you to safely lose weight and eliminate unwanted body fat &#8211; for good.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Greger, renowned nutrition expert, physician, and founder of the NutritionFacts website, explores the many causes of obesity &#8211; from our genes to the portions on our plate to other environmental factors &#8211; and the many consequences, from diabetes to cancer to mental health issues. From there, Dr Greger breaks down a variety of approaches to weight loss, honing in on the optimal criteria that enable success, including: a diet high in fibre and water, a diet low in fat, salt, and sugar, and diet full of anti-inflammatory foods.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet then goes beyond food to explore the many other weight-loss accelerators available to us in our body&#8217;s systems, revealing how plant-based meals can be eaten at specific times to maximize our bodies&#8217; natural fat-burning activities. Dr Greger provides a clear plan not only for the ultimate weight loss diet, but also the approach we must take to unlock its greatest efficacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From world-renowned health expert and New York Times bestselling author of Eat to Live and Eat for Life Dr. Joel Fuhrman comes a practical nutritional plan to prevent and reverse disease&#8211;no shots, drugs or sick days required. Why do some of us get sick with greater frequency than others? What makes us more susceptible to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From world-renowned health expert and New York Times bestselling author of Eat to Live and Eat for Life Dr. Joel Fuhrman comes a practical nutritional plan to prevent and reverse disease&#8211;no shots, drugs or sick days required.    </p>
<p>                     Why do some of us get sick with greater frequency than others? What makes us more susceptible to illness? Is there a secret to staying healthy? Dr. Fuhrman doesn&#8217;t believe the secret to staying healthy lies in medical care&#8211;rather, the solution is to change the way we eat.    </p>
<p>                     With more than 85 plant-based recipes, a two-week menu plan, and lists of super foods that boost immunity, Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s proven strategies in Super Immunity combine the latest data from clinical tests, nutritional research, and results from thousands of patients .    </p>
<p>                    Inside Super Immunity, you&#8217;ll find: The big picture&#8211;Learn everything you need to know about healthy eating for a healthy life.A 2-week meal plan&#8211;Take the guesswork out of changing your diet with planned meals for breakfast, lunch, and dinner every day of the week.85 immunity-boosting recipes&#8211;These delicious plant based recipes make eating healthy easy and crave-worthy.    </p>
<p>                     Live longer, stronger, and disease free with this proven plan to change your diet and change your life.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Super Immunity is a much needed book that contains the key to ending the cycle of sickness that plagues many of our lives. This is enlightened medicine, at last!&#8221; (Dr. Alejandro Junger, New York Times bestselling author of CLEAN)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
