<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Occupational &amp; Industrial Psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/occupational-industrial-psychology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/occupational-industrial-psychology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Occupational &amp; Industrial Psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/occupational-industrial-psychology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stretch : Unlock the Power of Less -and Achieve More Than You Ever Imagined &#8211; Scott Sonenshein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stretch-unlock-the-power-of-less-and-achieve-more-than-you-ever-imagined-scott-sonenshein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stretch-unlock-the-power-of-less-and-achieve-more-than-you-ever-imagined-scott-sonenshein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking approach to succeeding in business and life, using the science of resourcefulness. We often think the key to success and satisfaction is to get more: more money, time, and possessions; bigger budgets, job titles, and teams; and additional resources for our professional and personal goals. It turns out we&#8217;re wrong. Using captivating stories [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stretch-unlock-the-power-of-less-and-achieve-more-than-you-ever-imagined-scott-sonenshein-abridged/">Stretch : Unlock the Power of Less -and Achieve More Than You Ever Imagined &#8211; Scott Sonenshein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking approach to succeeding in business and life, using the science of resourcefulness.  We often think the key to success and satisfaction is to get more: more money, time, and possessions; bigger budgets, job titles, and teams; and additional resources for our professional and personal goals. It turns out we&#8217;re wrong. Using captivating stories to illustrate research in psychology and management, Rice University professor Scott Sonenshein examines why some people and organizations succeed with so little, while others fail with so much.  People and organizations approach resources in two different ways: &#8220;chasing&#8221; and &#8220;stretching.&#8221; When chasing, we exhaust ourselves in the pursuit of more. When stretching, we embrace the resources we already have. This frees us to find creative and productive ways to solve problems, innovate, and engage our work and lives more fully.  Stretch shows why everyone-from executives to entrepreneurs, professionals to parents, athletes to artists-performs better with constraints; why seeking too many resources undermines our work and well-being; and why even those with a lot benefit from making the most out of a little.<br />
                    Drawing from examples in business, education, sports, medicine, and history, Scott Sonenshein advocates a powerful framework of resourcefulness that allows anybody to work and live better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stretch-unlock-the-power-of-less-and-achieve-more-than-you-ever-imagined-scott-sonenshein-abridged/">Stretch : Unlock the Power of Less -and Achieve More Than You Ever Imagined &#8211; Scott Sonenshein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Work &#8211; Barry Schwartz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Part of the TED series: Why We Work Why do we work? The question seems so simple. But Professor Barry Schwartz proves that the answer is surprising, complex and urgent. We&#8217;ve long been taught that the reason we work is primarily for a paycheck. In fact, we&#8217;ve shaped much of the infrastructure of our society [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/">Why We Work &#8211; Barry Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Part of the TED series: Why We Work    </p>
<p>                    Why do we work? The question seems so simple. But Professor Barry Schwartz proves that the answer is surprising, complex and urgent.     </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve long been taught that the reason we work is primarily for a paycheck. In fact, we&#8217;ve shaped much of the infrastructure of our society to accommodate this belief. Then why are so many people dissatisfied with their work, despite healthy compensation? And why do so many people find immense fulfillment and satisfaction through &#8220;menial&#8221; jobs?     </p>
<p>                    Schwartz reveals exactly how the false idea that the goal for work should be pay came to be, how we came to believe that paying workers more leads to better work, and why this has made our society confused, unhappy and has established a dangerously misguided system.     </p>
<p>                    Ultimately, Schwartz proves that the root of what drives us to good work can rarely be incentivized, and that the cause of bad work is often an attempt to do just that. With great insight and wisdom, Schwartz illuminates the path for readers to take their first steps toward understanding, empowering us all to find great work.     </p>
<p>                    Schwartz is also the author of The Paradox of Choice: Why More Is Less, which has been translated into twenty languages. He can be seen discussing his ideas in his TEDTalks The Paradox of Choiceand Using Our Practical Wisdom.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/">Why We Work &#8211; Barry Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Primed to Perform : How to Build the Highest Performing Cultures Through the Science of Total Motivation &#8211; Neel Doshi, Lindsay Mcgregor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/primed-to-perform-how-to-build-the-highest-performing-cultures-through-the-science-of-total-motivation-neel-doshi-lindsay-mcgregor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/primed-to-perform-how-to-build-the-highest-performing-cultures-through-the-science-of-total-motivation-neel-doshi-lindsay-mcgregor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The revolutionary book that teaches you how to use the cutting edge of human psychology to build high performing workplace cultures. Too often, great cultures feel like magic. While most leaders believe culture is critical to success, few know how to build one, or sustain it over time. What if you knew the science behind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/primed-to-perform-how-to-build-the-highest-performing-cultures-through-the-science-of-total-motivation-neel-doshi-lindsay-mcgregor-abridged/">Primed to Perform : How to Build the Highest Performing Cultures Through the Science of Total Motivation &#8211; Neel Doshi, Lindsay Mcgregor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The revolutionary book that teaches you how to use the cutting edge of human psychology to build high performing workplace cultures.  Too often, great cultures feel like magic. While most leaders believe culture is critical to success, few know how to build one, or sustain it over time.  What if you knew the science behind the magic-a science so predictive and powerful that you could transform your organization? What if you could use cutting edge psychology to unlock people&#8217;s innate desire to innovate, experiment, and adapt? In Primed to Perform, Neel Doshi and Lindsay McGregor show you how to do just that. The result: higher sales, more loyal customers, and more passionate employees.  Primed to Perform explains the counter-intuitive science behind great cultures, building on over a century of academic thinking. It shares the simple, highly predictive new measurement tool-the Total Motivation (ToMo) Factor-that enables you to measure the strength of your culture, and track improvements over time. It explores the authors&#8217; original research into how Total Motivation leads to higher performance in iconic companies, from Apple to Starbucks to Southwest Airlines.<br />
                    Most importantly, it teaches you to build great cultures, using a systematic and sustainable approach.  High performing cultures cant be left to chance. Organizations must create systems that shape and maintain them. Whether you&#8217;re a five-person team or a startup, a school, a nonprofit or a mega-institution, Primed to Perform shows you how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/primed-to-perform-how-to-build-the-highest-performing-cultures-through-the-science-of-total-motivation-neel-doshi-lindsay-mcgregor-abridged/">Primed to Perform : How to Build the Highest Performing Cultures Through the Science of Total Motivation &#8211; Neel Doshi, Lindsay Mcgregor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wait : The useful art of procrastination &#8211; Frank Partnoy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wait-the-useful-art-of-procrastination-frank-partnoy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wait-the-useful-art-of-procrastination-frank-partnoy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Warren Buffett compares stock trading to great athletes: they excel not because of fast neurological responses, but because of their ability to delay as long as possible before reacting. Successful CEOs, fire fighters, and military officers all know how to manage delay to gather as much information as possible to get the results they need. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wait-the-useful-art-of-procrastination-frank-partnoy-abridged/">Wait : The useful art of procrastination &#8211; Frank Partnoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Warren Buffett compares stock trading to great athletes: they excel not because of fast neurological responses, but because of their ability to delay as long as possible before reacting. Successful CEOs, fire fighters, and military officers all know how to manage delay to gather as much information as possible to get the results they need.    </p>
<p>                    In Wait, Frank Partnoy argues that decisions of all kinds, whether &#8216;snap&#8217; or long-term, benefit from being made at the last possible moment. The art of knowing how long you can afford to delay before committing is at the heart of many a great decision, whether in a corporate takeover or a marriage proposal. Apologies are better received if they are not rushed and people who can defer gratification are happier and more successful than those who must have everything now. Partnoy demonstrates that the ability to wait is crucial to getting the right answer and that gut instincts are often wrong.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wait-the-useful-art-of-procrastination-frank-partnoy-abridged/">Wait : The useful art of procrastination &#8211; Frank Partnoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn or Die : Using Science to Build a Leading-Edge Learning Organization &#8211; Edward D. Hess (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To compete with today&#8217;s increasing globalization and rapidly evolving technologies, individuals and organizations must take their ability to learn-the foundation for continuous improvement, operational excellence, and innovation-to a much higher level. In Learn or Die, Edward D. Hess combines recent advances in neuroscience, psychology, behavioral economics, and education with key research on high-performance businesses to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/">Learn or Die : Using Science to Build a Leading-Edge Learning Organization &#8211; Edward D. Hess (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To compete with today&#8217;s increasing globalization and rapidly evolving technologies, individuals and organizations must take their ability to learn-the foundation for continuous improvement, operational excellence, and innovation-to a much higher level. In Learn or Die, Edward D. Hess combines recent advances in neuroscience, psychology, behavioral economics, and education with key research on high-performance businesses to create an actionable blueprint for becoming a leading-edge learning organization. Learn or Die examines the process of learning from an individual and an organizational standpoint. From an individual perspective, the book discusses the cognitive, emotional, motivational, attitudinal, and behavioral factors that promote better learning. Organizationally, Learn or Die focuses on the kinds of structures, culture, leadership, employee learning behaviors, and human resource policies that are necessary to create an environment that enables critical and innovative thinking, learning conversations, and collaboration.<br />
                    The volume also provides strategies to mitigate the reality that humans can be reflexive, lazy thinkers who seek confirmation of what they believe to be true and affirmation of their self-image. Exemplar learning organizations discussed include the secretive Bridgewater Associates, LP; Intuit, Inc.; United Parcel Service (UPS); W. L. Gore &#038; Associates; and IDEO.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/">Learn or Die : Using Science to Build a Leading-Edge Learning Organization &#8211; Edward D. Hess (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In private life, we try to induce or suppress love, envy, and anger through deep acting or &#8220;emotion work&#8221;, just as we manage our outer expressions of feeling through surface acting. In trying to bridge a gap between what we feel and what we &#8220;ought&#8221; to feel, we take guidance from &#8220;feeling rules&#8221; about what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In private life, we try to induce or suppress love, envy, and anger through deep acting or &#8220;emotion work&#8221;, just as we manage our outer expressions of feeling through surface acting. In trying to bridge a gap between what we feel and what we &#8220;ought&#8221; to feel, we take guidance from &#8220;feeling rules&#8221; about what is owing to others in a given situation. Based on our private mutual understandings of feeling rules, we make a &#8220;gift exchange&#8221; of acts of emotion management. We bow to each other not simply from the waist, but from the heart. But what occurs when emotion work, feeling rules, and the gift of exchange are introduced into the public world of work? In search of the answer, Arlie Russell Hochschild closely examines two groups of public-contact workers: flight attendants and bill collectors. The flight attendant&#8217;s job is to deliver a service and create further demand for it, to enhance the status of the customer and be &#8220;nicer than natural&#8221;. The bill collector&#8217;s job is to collect on the service, and if necessary, to deflate the status of the customer by being &#8220;nastier than natural.&#8221;<br />
                    Between these extremes, roughly one-third of American men and one-half of American women hold jobs that call for substantial emotional labor. In many of these jobs, they are trained to accept feeling rules and techniques of emotion management that serve the company&#8217;s commercial purpose. Just as we have seldom recognized or understood emotional labor, we have not appreciated its cost to those who do it for a living. Like a physical laborer who becomes estranged from what he or she makes, an emotional laborer, such as a flight attendant, can become estranged not only from her own expressions of feeling (her smile is not &#8220;her&#8221; smile), but also from what she actually feels (her managed friendliness). This estrangement, though a valuable defense against stress, is also an important occupational hazard, because it is through our feelings that we are connected with those around us. On the basis of this book, Hochschild was featured in Key Sociological Thinkers, edited by Rob Stones. This book was also the winner of the Charles Cooley Award in 1983, awarded by the American Sociological Association and received an honorable mention for the C. Wright Mills Award.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Bigger Prize : When No One Wins Unless Everyone Wins &#8211; Margaret Heffernan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-bigger-prize-when-no-one-wins-unless-everyone-wins-margaret-heffernan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-bigger-prize-when-no-one-wins-unless-everyone-wins-margaret-heffernan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the 100 best behavioural economic books of all time recommended by Jeff Bezos, Tim Ferriss, Satya Nadella, Brian Tracy and Erik Brynjolfsson. The Olympics. X-Factor. The Rich List. The Nobel Prize. Everywhere you look: competition &#8211; for fame, money, attention, status. Being top seems to be everything &#8211; but what is it costing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bigger-prize-when-no-one-wins-unless-everyone-wins-margaret-heffernan-abridged/">A Bigger Prize : When No One Wins Unless Everyone Wins &#8211; Margaret Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the 100 best behavioural economic books of all time recommended by Jeff Bezos, Tim Ferriss, Satya Nadella, Brian Tracy and Erik Brynjolfsson.    </p>
<p>                     The Olympics. X-Factor. The Rich List. The Nobel Prize. Everywhere you look: competition &#8211; for fame, money, attention, status. Being top seems to be everything &#8211; but what is it costing all of us?    </p>
<p>                     We depend on competition and expect it to identify the best, make complicated decisions easy and to motivate the lazy and inspire the dreamers. But, as Margaret Heffernan shows in this eye-opening look at competition, competition regularly produces just what we don&#8217;t want: rising levels of fraud, cheating, stress, inequality and political stalemate. Siblings won&#8217;t speak to each other. Children burn out at school. Doping proliferates among athletes. Auditors and fund managers go to jail for insider trading. Winners seem to take all while the desire to win consumes all, inciting panic and despair.    </p>
<p>                     We now know that competition often doesn&#8217;t work, that the best do not always rise to the top and the so-called efficiency of competition creates a great deal of waste. So what are our alternatives? What are the skills needed for creative collaboration and how do we hone them?    </p>
<p>                     Talking to scientists, musicians, athletes, entrepreneurs and executives, in the follow-up to her bestselling Wilful Blindness, Margaret Heffernan has discovered that, around the world, individuals and organizations are finding creative, cooperative ways to work that don&#8217;t pit people against each other but support them in their desire to work together. While the rest of the world remains mired in pitiless sniping, racing to the bottom, the future belongs to the people and companies who have learned that they are greater working together than against one another. Some call that soft but it&#8217;s harder than anything they&#8217;ve done before. They are the real winners, sharing a bigger prize.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bigger-prize-when-no-one-wins-unless-everyone-wins-margaret-heffernan-abridged/">A Bigger Prize : When No One Wins Unless Everyone Wins &#8211; Margaret Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Place To Work : The Art and Science of Creating an Extraordinary Workplace &#8211; Ron Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Malcolm Gladwell, Daniel Pink, and Freakonomics, comes a captivating and surprising journey through the science of workplace excellence. Why do successful companies reward failure? What can casinos teach us about building a happy workplace? How do you design an office that enhances both attention to detail and creativity? In The Best Place [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/">The Best Place To Work : The Art and Science of Creating an Extraordinary Workplace &#8211; Ron Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Malcolm Gladwell, Daniel Pink, and Freakonomics, comes a captivating and surprising journey through the science of workplace excellence.    </p>
<p>                     Why do successful companies reward failure?<br />
                     What can casinos teach us about building a happy workplace?<br />
                     How do you design an office that enhances both attention to detail and creativity?     </p>
<p>                     In The Best Place to Work, award-winning psychologist Ron Friedman, Ph.D. uses the latest research from the fields of motivation, creativity, behavioral economics, neuroscience, and management to reveal what really makes us successful at work. Combining powerful stories with cutting edge findings, Friedman shows leaders at every level how they can use scientifically-proven techniques to promote smarter thinking, greater innovation, and stronger performance.     </p>
<p>                     Among the many surprising insights, Friedman explains how learning to think like a hostage negotiator can help you diffuse a workplace argument, why placing a fish bowl near your desk can elevate your thinking, and how incorporating strategic distractions into your schedule can help you reach smarter decisions. Along the way, the book introduces the inventor who created the cubicle, the president who brought down the world&#8217;s most dangerous criminal, and the teenager who single-handedly transformed professional tennis&#8211;vivid stories that offer unexpected revelations on achieving workplace excellence.     </p>
<p>                     Brimming with counterintuitive insights and actionable recommendations, The Best Place to Work offers employees and executives alike game-changing advice for working smarter and turning any organization&#8211;regardless of its size, budgets, or ambitions&#8211;into an extraordinary workplace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/">The Best Place To Work : The Art and Science of Creating an Extraordinary Workplace &#8211; Ron Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Hard Feelings : Emotions at Work and How They Help Us Succeed &#8211; Liz Fosslien, Mollie West Duffy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-hard-feelings-emotions-at-work-and-how-they-help-us-succeed-liz-fosslien-mollie-west-duffy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-hard-feelings-emotions-at-work-and-how-they-help-us-succeed-liz-fosslien-mollie-west-duffy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How do you deal with your emotions at work? &#8216;Full of lively illustrations and practical examples to show how you can harness emotions to become more creative, collaborative and productive&#8217; Adam Grant, author of Originals ________________ We all know what it&#8217;s like to feel overwhelmed with emotions at work &#8211; everything from jealousy to insecurity, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-hard-feelings-emotions-at-work-and-how-they-help-us-succeed-liz-fosslien-mollie-west-duffy-abridged/">No Hard Feelings : Emotions at Work and How They Help Us Succeed &#8211; Liz Fosslien, Mollie West Duffy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do you deal with your emotions at work?     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Full of lively illustrations and practical examples to show how you can harness emotions to become more creative, collaborative and productive&#8217; Adam Grant, author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    ________________                           </p>
<p>                    We all know what it&#8217;s like to feel overwhelmed with emotions at work &#8211;  everything from jealousy to insecurity, anxiety to straight up panic &#8211; and there&#8217;s no field guide to coping with them well.     </p>
<p>                    But we also know that ignoring or suppressing what you feel hurts your health, happiness and productivity.     </p>
<p>                    This book will help you figure out how to express your emotions productively in order to be both happier and more effective at work. Drawing on behavioural economics and psychology, No Hard Feelings will show you how to bring your best self to work every day.    </p>
<p>                    ________________                           </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A must-read&#8217; Susan Cain, author of Quiet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-hard-feelings-emotions-at-work-and-how-they-help-us-succeed-liz-fosslien-mollie-west-duffy-abridged/">No Hard Feelings : Emotions at Work and How They Help Us Succeed &#8211; Liz Fosslien, Mollie West Duffy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joy, Inc : How We Built a Workplace People Love &#8211; Richard Sheridan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A guidebook for how leaders can motivate, engage, and recognize their people all the while growing the business profitably.&#8221; &#8211;Forbes.com Every year, thousands of visitors come from around the world to visit Menlo Innovations, a small software company in Ann Arbor, Michigan. They make the trek not to learn about technology but to witness a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/">Joy, Inc : How We Built a Workplace People Love &#8211; Richard Sheridan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A guidebook for how leaders can motivate, engage, and recognize their people all the while growing the business profitably.&#8221; &#8211;Forbes.com     </p>
<p>                    Every year, thousands of visitors come from around the world to visit Menlo Innovations, a small software company in Ann Arbor, Michigan. They make the trek not to learn about technology but to witness a radically different approach to company culture.     </p>
<p>                    CEO Rich Sheridan removed the fear and ambiguity that typically make a workplace miserable. With joy as the explicit goal, he and his team changed everything about how the company was run. The results blew away all expectations. Menlo has won numerous growth awards and was named an Inc. magazine &#8220;audacious small company.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Joy, Inc. offers an inside look at how Menlo created its culture, and shows how any organization can follow their methods for a more passionate team and sustainable, profitable results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/">Joy, Inc : How We Built a Workplace People Love &#8211; Richard Sheridan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Desktop Publishing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WE DESIGN TO ELICIT RESPONSES from people. We want them to buy something, read more, or take action of some kind. Designing without understanding what makes people act the way they do is like exploring a new city without a map: results will be haphazard, confusing, and inefficient. This book combines real science and research [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/">100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WE DESIGN TO ELICIT RESPONSES from people. We want them to buy something, read more, or take action of some kind. Designing without understanding what makes people act the way they do is like exploring a new city without a map: results will be haphazard, confusing, and inefficient. This book combines real science and research with practical examples to deliver a guide every designer needs. With this book you&#8217;ll design more intuitive and engaging apps, software, websites and products that match the way people think, decide and behave.    </p>
<p>                      INCREASE THE EFFECTIVENESS OF YOUR PRODUCTS.    </p>
<p>                      Apply psychology and behavioral science to your designs.    </p>
<p>                      Here are some of the questions this book will answer:    </p>
<p>                      * What grabs and holds attention.    </p>
<p>                      * What makes memories stick?    </p>
<p>                      * What is more important, peripheral or central vision?    </p>
<p>                      * Can you predict the types of errors people will make?    </p>
<p>                      * What is the limit to someone&#8217;s social circle?    </p>
<p>                      * What line length for text is best?    </p>
<p>                      * Are some fonts better than others?    </p>
<p>                      These are just a few of the questions that the book answers in its deep-dive exploration of what makes people tick.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/">100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meltdown : Why Our Systems Fail and What We Can Do About It &#8211; Chris Clearfield, Andras Tilcsik (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/meltdown-why-our-systems-fail-and-what-we-can-do-about-it-chris-clearfield-andras-tilcsik-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/meltdown-why-our-systems-fail-and-what-we-can-do-about-it-chris-clearfield-andras-tilcsik-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Financial Times&#8217; best business books of the year, 2018 &#8216;Endlessly fascinating, brimming with insight, and more fun than a book about failure has any right to be.&#8217; &#8211; Charles Duhigg, author of The Power of Habit What can we learn from our most disastrous failures? An accidental overdose in a state-of-the-art hospital. The Starbucks publicity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/meltdown-why-our-systems-fail-and-what-we-can-do-about-it-chris-clearfield-andras-tilcsik-abridged/">Meltdown : Why Our Systems Fail and What We Can Do About It &#8211; Chris Clearfield, Andras Tilcsik (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Financial Times&#8217; best business books of the year, 2018    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Endlessly fascinating, brimming with insight, and more fun than a book about failure has any right to be.&#8217; &#8211; Charles Duhigg, author of The Power of Habit     </p>
<p>                    What can we learn from our most disastrous failures?    </p>
<p>                    An accidental overdose in a state-of-the-art hospital.    </p>
<p>                    The Starbucks publicity stunt that spectacularly backfired.    </p>
<p>                    The mix-up at the 2017 Oscars ceremony.    </p>
<p>                    As technology rapidly advances, it brings with it an explosion of complexity that can trip us up. Meltdown uses real-life examples to reveal how errors in thinking, perception, and design lie behind both our everyday mistakes and our most terrifying disasters. It reveals how a five-minute exercise can prevent billion-dollar catastrophes, why teams with fewer experts are better at managing risk, and why diversity is one of our best safeguards against failure. This eye-opening book will change the way you see our complex world &#8211; and your place within it.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Essential reading.&#8217; &#8211; Martin Ford, bestselling author of Rise of the Robots</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/meltdown-why-our-systems-fail-and-what-we-can-do-about-it-chris-clearfield-andras-tilcsik-abridged/">Meltdown : Why Our Systems Fail and What We Can Do About It &#8211; Chris Clearfield, Andras Tilcsik (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Surprising Science of Meetings : How You Can Lead your Team to Peak Performance &#8211; Steven G. Rogelberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-surprising-science-of-meetings-how-you-can-lead-your-team-to-peak-performance-steven-g-rogelberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-surprising-science-of-meetings-how-you-can-lead-your-team-to-peak-performance-steven-g-rogelberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A recent estimate suggests that employees endure a staggering 55 million meetings a day in the United States. This tremendous time investment yields only modest returns. No organization made up of human beings is immune from the all-too-common meeting gripes: those that fail to engage, those that inadvertently encourage participants to tune out, and those [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-surprising-science-of-meetings-how-you-can-lead-your-team-to-peak-performance-steven-g-rogelberg-abridged/">The Surprising Science of Meetings : How You Can Lead your Team to Peak Performance &#8211; Steven G. Rogelberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A recent estimate suggests that employees endure a staggering 55 million meetings a day in the United States. This tremendous time investment yields only modest returns. No organization made up of human beings is immune from the all-too-common meeting gripes: those that fail to engage, those that inadvertently encourage participants to tune out, and those that blatantly disregard participants&#8217; time.     </p>
<p>                    Most companies and leaders view poor meetings as an inevitable cost of doing business. But managers can take heart: researchers now have a clear understanding of the key drivers that make meetings successful. In The Surprising Science of Meetings, Steven G. Rogelberg, researcher and consultant to some of the world&#8217;s most successful companies, draws from extensive research, analytics and data mining, and survey interviews with over 5,000 employees across a range of industries to share<br />
                    the proven practices and techniques that help managers and employees enhance the quality of their meetings. For those who lead and participate in meetings, Rogelberg provides immediate direction, guidance, and relief, offering a how-to guide to change your working life starting today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-surprising-science-of-meetings-how-you-can-lead-your-team-to-peak-performance-steven-g-rogelberg-abridged/">The Surprising Science of Meetings : How You Can Lead your Team to Peak Performance &#8211; Steven G. Rogelberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave New Work : Are You Ready to Reinvent Your Organization? &#8211; Aaron Dignan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s stopping you from doing the best work of your life? The way we work is broken. It takes forever to get anything done. Meetings and emails are incessant. Bureaucracy stifles talent and creativity. Is this really the best we can do? Aaron Dignan teaches companies how to eliminate red tape, tap into collective intelligence, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/">Brave New Work : Are You Ready to Reinvent Your Organization? &#8211; Aaron Dignan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s stopping you from doing the best work of your life?    </p>
<p>                    The way we work is broken. It takes forever to get anything done. Meetings and emails are incessant. Bureaucracy stifles talent and creativity.  Is this really the best we can do?    </p>
<p>                    Aaron Dignan teaches companies how to eliminate red tape, tap into collective intelligence, and rethink long-held traditions that no longer make sense. In Brave New Work, he shows you how to revolutionize the way you, your team and your company works forever.     </p>
<p>                    *         Have fewer but better meetings<br />
                    *         Create a culture of honesty, transparency and trust<br />
                    *         Cut down on rules to be more efficient<br />
                    *         Be more agile and adaptive<br />
                    *         Reignite passion and energy throughout your organisation    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Clear, powerful and urgent, it&#8217;s a must read for anyone who cares about where they work and how they work&#8221; &#8211; Seth Godin, author of This is Marketing and Purple Cow</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/">Brave New Work : Are You Ready to Reinvent Your Organization? &#8211; Aaron Dignan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Radical Collaboration : Five Essential Skills To Overcome Defensiveness And Build Successful Relationships &#8211; James W. Tamm, Ronald J. Luyet (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The second edition of the essential guide, updated with new research and observations to help twenty-first century organizations create models for effective collaboration. Collaborative skills have never been more important to a company&#8217;s success and these skills are essential for every worker today. Radical Collaboration is a how-to-manual for creating trusting, cooperative environments, and transforming [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/">Radical Collaboration : Five Essential Skills To Overcome Defensiveness And Build Successful Relationships &#8211; James W. Tamm, Ronald J. Luyet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The second edition of the essential guide, updated with new research and observations to help twenty-first century organizations create models for effective collaboration.    </p>
<p>                    Collaborative skills have never been more important to a company&#8217;s success and these skills are essential for every worker today. Radical Collaboration is a how-to-manual for creating trusting, cooperative environments, and transforming groups into motivated and empowered teams. James W. Tamm and Ronald J. Luyet provide tools that will help you increase your ability to work successfully with others, learn to be more aware of colleagues, and better problem-solve and negotiate.     </p>
<p>                    Radical Collaboration is an eye-opener for leaders, managers, HR professionals, agents, trainers, and consultants who are seeking constructive ways of getting the results they want.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/">Radical Collaboration : Five Essential Skills To Overcome Defensiveness And Build Successful Relationships &#8211; James W. Tamm, Ronald J. Luyet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good People, Bad Managers : How Work Culture Corrupts Good Intentions &#8211; Samuel A. Culbert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-people-bad-managers-how-work-culture-corrupts-good-intentions-samuel-a-culbert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-people-bad-managers-how-work-culture-corrupts-good-intentions-samuel-a-culbert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s worse than a bad manager who everybody knows is bad? A bad manager who is well-intentioned and considered to be good. Yet these well-intentioned bad managers make up the bulk of management today. How did that happen? How did so many of today&#8217;s managers end up with a self-preservation mindset that doesn&#8217;t always translate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-people-bad-managers-how-work-culture-corrupts-good-intentions-samuel-a-culbert-abridged/">Good People, Bad Managers : How Work Culture Corrupts Good Intentions &#8211; Samuel A. Culbert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s worse than a bad manager who everybody knows is bad? A bad manager who is well-intentioned and considered to be good. Yet these well-intentioned bad managers make up the bulk of management today. How did that happen? How did so many of today&#8217;s managers end up with a self-preservation mindset that doesn&#8217;t  always translate to a productive and mission-oriented environment? How did so many good people become wedded to a work culture that saps morale, well-being<br />
                    and performance at both the individual and organizational levels?     </p>
<p>                    an the well-intentioned doling it out realize&#8230; and even In Good People, Bad Managers: How Work Culture Corrupts Good Intentions, author Samuel A. Culbert sheds a light on the bad habits that are routinely followed by these well-intended managers. Managers need to understand the causes of their misguided practices. They need to become more aware of the damage they inflict, and the hollowness of the rationales they use to justify what they do. Company leaders, CEOs, and top-tier<br />
                    managers must become aware of how they have gone astray as a first step in implementing the truly beneficial management mentality that their companies, their managers and their employees require to succeed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-people-bad-managers-how-work-culture-corrupts-good-intentions-samuel-a-culbert-abridged/">Good People, Bad Managers : How Work Culture Corrupts Good Intentions &#8211; Samuel A. Culbert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Insight : How to succeed by seeing yourself clearly &#8211; Tasha Eurich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/insight-how-to-succeed-by-seeing-yourself-clearly-tasha-eurich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/insight-how-to-succeed-by-seeing-yourself-clearly-tasha-eurich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nominated as one of the 2019 Thinkers50 Radar group Research shows that self-awareness is the meta-skill of the 21st century &#8211; the foundation for high performance, smart choices, and lasting relationships. Unfortunately, we are remarkably poor judges of ourselves and how we come across, and it&#8217;s rare to get candid, objective feedback from colleagues, employees, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/insight-how-to-succeed-by-seeing-yourself-clearly-tasha-eurich-abridged/">Insight : How to succeed by seeing yourself clearly &#8211; Tasha Eurich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nominated as one of the 2019 Thinkers50 Radar group    </p>
<p>                    Research shows that self-awareness is the meta-skill of the 21st century &#8211; the foundation for high performance, smart choices, and lasting relationships. Unfortunately, we are remarkably poor judges of ourselves and how we come across, and it&#8217;s rare to get candid, objective feedback from colleagues, employees, and even friends and family. We can ALL learn to be more self-aware.    </p>
<p>                    Integrating hundreds of studies with her own research and work in the Fortune 500 world, organizational psychologist Dr Tasha Eurich shatters conventional assumptions about what it takes to truly know ourselves &#8211; like why introspection isn&#8217;t a bullet train to insight, how experience is the enemy of self-knowledge, and just how far others will go to avoid telling us the truth about ourselves. Through stories of people who&#8217;ve made dramatic self-awareness gains, she offers surprising secrets, techniques and strategies to help readers do the same &#8211; and therefore improve their work performance, career satisfaction, leadership potential, relationships, and more.    </p>
<p>                    At a time when self-awareness matters more than ever, Insight is the essential playbook for surviving and thriving in an unaware world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/insight-how-to-succeed-by-seeing-yourself-clearly-tasha-eurich-abridged/">Insight : How to succeed by seeing yourself clearly &#8211; Tasha Eurich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Payoff : The Hidden Logic That Shapes Our Motivations &#8211; Dr Dan Ariely (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/payoff-the-hidden-logic-that-shapes-our-motivations-dr-dan-ariely-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/payoff-the-hidden-logic-that-shapes-our-motivations-dr-dan-ariely-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bestselling author Dan Ariely reveals fascinating new insights into motivation&#8211;showing that the subject is far more complex than we ever imagined. Every day we work hard to motivate ourselves, the people we live with, the people who work for and do business with us. In this way, much of what we do can be defined [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/payoff-the-hidden-logic-that-shapes-our-motivations-dr-dan-ariely-abridged/">Payoff : The Hidden Logic That Shapes Our Motivations &#8211; Dr Dan Ariely (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bestselling author Dan Ariely reveals fascinating new insights into motivation&#8211;showing that the subject is far more complex than we ever imagined.     </p>
<p>                    Every day we work hard to motivate ourselves, the people we live with, the people who work for and do business with us. In this way, much of what we do can be defined as being &#8220;motivators.&#8221; From the boardroom to the living room, our role as motivators is complex, and the more we try to motivate partners and children, friends and coworkers, the clearer it becomes that the story of motivation is far more intricate and fascinating than we&#8217;ve assumed.     </p>
<p>                    Payoff investigates the true nature of motivation, our partial blindness to the way it works, and how we can bridge this gap. With studies that range from Intel to a kindergarten classroom, Ariely digs deep to find the root of motivation&#8211;how it works and how we can use this knowledge to approach important choices in our own lives. Along the way, he explores intriguing questions such as: Can giving employees bonuses harm productivity? Why is trust so crucial for successful motivation? What are our misconceptions about how to value our work? How does your sense of your mortality impact your motivation?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/payoff-the-hidden-logic-that-shapes-our-motivations-dr-dan-ariely-abridged/">Payoff : The Hidden Logic That Shapes Our Motivations &#8211; Dr Dan Ariely (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peak : How Great Companies Get Their Mojo from Maslow Revised and Updated &#8211; Chip Conley, Foreword byTony Hsieh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/peak-how-great-companies-get-their-mojo-from-maslow-revised-and-updated-chip-conley-foreword-by-tony-hsieh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/peak-how-great-companies-get-their-mojo-from-maslow-revised-and-updated-chip-conley-foreword-by-tony-hsieh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Proven principles for sustainable success, with new leadership insight PEAK is the popular, transformative guide to doing business better, written by a seasoned entrepreneur/CEO who has disrupted his favorite industry not once, but twice. Author Chip Conley, founder and former CEO of one of the world&#8217;s largest boutique hotel companies, turned to psychologist Abraham Maslow&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peak-how-great-companies-get-their-mojo-from-maslow-revised-and-updated-chip-conley-foreword-by-tony-hsieh-abridged/">Peak : How Great Companies Get Their Mojo from Maslow Revised and Updated &#8211; Chip Conley, Foreword byTony Hsieh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proven principles for sustainable success, with new leadership insight    </p>
<p>                     PEAK is the popular, transformative guide to doing business better, written by a seasoned entrepreneur/CEO who has disrupted his favorite industry not once, but twice. Author Chip Conley, founder and former CEO of one of the world&#8217;s largest boutique hotel companies, turned to psychologist Abraham Maslow&#8217;s Hierarchy of Needs at a time when his company was in dire need. And years later, when the young founders of Airbnb asked him to help turn their start-up home sharing company into a world-class hospitality giant, Conley once again used the principles he&#8217;d developed in PEAK. In the decade since this book&#8217;s first edition, Conley&#8217;s PEAK strategy has been developed on six continents in organizations in virtually every industry. The author&#8217;s foundational premise is that great leaders become amateur psychologists by understanding the unique needs of three key relationships-with employees, customers, and investors-and this message has resonated with every kind of leader and company including some of the world&#8217;s best-known, from Apple to Facebook. Avid users of PEAK have found that the principles create greater loyalty and differentiation with their key stakeholders. This new second edition includes in-depth examples of real-world PEAK companies, including the author&#8217;s own at Airbnb, and exclusive PEAK leadership practices that will take you-and your company&#8217;s performance-to new heights.    </p>
<p>                     Whether you&#8217;re at a startup or a Fortune 500 company, at a for-profit, nonprofit, or governmental organization, this book can help you and your people reach potential you never realized you had.    </p>
<p>                    Understand how Maslow&#8217;s hierarchy makes for winning business practices<br />
                    Learn how PEAK drove some of today&#8217;s top businesses to success<br />
                    Help employees reach their full potential-and beyond    </p>
<p>                    Transform the customer experience and keep investors happy    </p>
<p>                     The PEAK framework succeeds because it elevates the business from the inside out. These same principles apply in the boardroom, the breakroom, and your living room at home, and have proven to be the foundation of healthy, fulfilled lives. Even if you think you&#8217;re doing great, you could always be doing better-and PEAK gives you a roadmap to the next level.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peak-how-great-companies-get-their-mojo-from-maslow-revised-and-updated-chip-conley-foreword-by-tony-hsieh-abridged/">Peak : How Great Companies Get Their Mojo from Maslow Revised and Updated &#8211; Chip Conley, Foreword byTony Hsieh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Thinking Clearly: Better Thinking, Better Decisions &#8211; Rolf Dobelli, Translated byCaroline Waight (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-thinking-clearly-better-thinking-better-decisions-rolf-dobelli-translated-by-caroline-waight-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-thinking-clearly-better-thinking-better-decisions-rolf-dobelli-translated-by-caroline-waight-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SECRET TO PERFECT DECISION-MAKING &#8216;This book will change the way you think&#8217; Dan Goldstein, London Business School Have you ever&#8230; Invested time in something that, with hindsight, just wasn&#8217;t worth it? Overpaid in an Ebay auction? Continued doing something you knew was bad for you? Backed the wrong horse? THE ART OF THINKING CLEARLY [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-thinking-clearly-better-thinking-better-decisions-rolf-dobelli-translated-by-caroline-waight-abridged/">The Art of Thinking Clearly: Better Thinking, Better Decisions &#8211; Rolf Dobelli, Translated byCaroline Waight (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SECRET TO PERFECT DECISION-MAKING    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book will change the way you think&#8217; Dan Goldstein, London Business School    </p>
<p>                    Have you ever&#8230; Invested time in something that, with hindsight, just wasn&#8217;t worth it? Overpaid in an Ebay auction? Continued doing something you knew was bad for you? Backed the wrong horse?    </p>
<p>                    THE ART OF THINKING CLEARLY is essential reading for anyone with important decisions to make. It reveals, in 100 short chapters, the most common errors of judgement, and how to avoid them. Simple, clear and always surprising, this indispensable book will change the way you think and transform your decision-making &#8211; at work, at home, every day.    </p>
<p>                    SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER * GUARDIAN BESTSELLER * INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-thinking-clearly-better-thinking-better-decisions-rolf-dobelli-translated-by-caroline-waight-abridged/">The Art of Thinking Clearly: Better Thinking, Better Decisions &#8211; Rolf Dobelli, Translated byCaroline Waight (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sensemaking : What Makes Human Intelligence Essential in the Age of the Algorithm &#8211; Christian Madsbjerg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BUSINESS BOOK OF THE MONTH (APRIL 2017) Humans have become subservient to algorithms. Every day brings a new Moneyball fix &#8211; a maths whiz who will crack open an industry with clean fact-based analysis rather than human intuition and experience. As a result, we have stopped thinking. Machines do it for us. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/">Sensemaking : What Makes Human Intelligence Essential in the Age of the Algorithm &#8211; Christian Madsbjerg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BUSINESS BOOK OF THE MONTH (APRIL 2017)  Humans have become subservient to algorithms. Every day brings a new Moneyball fix &#8211; a maths whiz who will crack open an industry with clean fact-based analysis rather than human intuition and experience. As a result, we have stopped thinking. Machines do it for us. Christian Madsbjerg argues that our fixation with data often masks stunning deficiencies, and the risks for humankind are enormous. Blind devotion to number crunching imperils our businesses, our educations, our governments, and our life savings. Too many companies have lost touch with the humanity of their customers, while marginalising workers with arts-based skills. Contrary to popular thinking, Madsbjerg shows how many of today&#8217;s biggest success stories stem not from &#8216;quant&#8217; thinking but from deep, nuanced engagement with culture, language, and history. He calls his method sensemaking. In this landmark book, Madsbjerg lays out five principles for how business leaders, entrepreneurs, and individuals can use it to solve their thorniest problems.<br />
                    He profiles companies using sensemaking to connect with new customers, and takes readers inside the work process of sensemaking &#8216;connoisseurs&#8217; like investor George Soros, architect Bjarke Ingels, and others. Both practical and philosophical, Sensemaking is a powerful rejoinder to corporate groupthink and an indispensable resource for leaders and innovators who want to stand out from the pack.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/">Sensemaking : What Makes Human Intelligence Essential in the Age of the Algorithm &#8211; Christian Madsbjerg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fearless Organization : Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth &#8211; Amy C. Edmondson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fearless-organization-creating-psychological-safety-in-the-workplace-for-learning-innovation-and-growth-amy-c-edmondson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fearless-organization-creating-psychological-safety-in-the-workplace-for-learning-innovation-and-growth-amy-c-edmondson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Conquer the most essential adaptation to the knowledge economy The Fearless Organization: Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth offers practical guidance for teams and organizations who are serious about success in the modern economy. With so much riding on innovation, creativity, and spark, it is essential to attract and retain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fearless-organization-creating-psychological-safety-in-the-workplace-for-learning-innovation-and-growth-amy-c-edmondson-abridged/">The Fearless Organization : Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth &#8211; Amy C. Edmondson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Conquer the most essential adaptation to the knowledge economy    </p>
<p>                     The Fearless Organization: Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth offers practical guidance for teams and organizations who are serious about success in the modern economy. With so much riding on innovation, creativity, and spark, it is essential to attract and retain quality talent-but what good does this talent do if no one is able to speak their mind? The traditional culture of &#8220;fitting in&#8221; and &#8220;going along&#8221; spells doom in the knowledge economy. Success requires a continuous influx of new ideas, new challenges, and critical thought, and the interpersonal climate must not suppress, silence, ridicule or intimidate. Not every idea is good, and yes there are stupid questions, and yes dissent can slow things down, but talking through these things is an essential part of the creative process. People must be allowed to voice half-finished thoughts, ask questions from left field, and brainstorm out loud; it creates a culture in which a minor flub or momentary lapse is no big deal, and where actual mistakes are owned and corrected, and where the next left-field idea could be the next big thing.     </p>
<p>                     This book explores this culture of psychological safety, and provides a blueprint for bringing it to life. The road is sometimes bumpy, but succinct and informative scenario-based explanations provide a clear path forward to constant learning and healthy innovation.    </p>
<p>                    Explore the link between psychological safety and high performance<br />
                    Create a culture where it&#8217;s &#8220;safe&#8221; to express ideas, ask questions, and admit mistakes<br />
                    Nurture the level of engagement and candor required in today&#8217;s knowledge economy    </p>
<p>                    Follow a step-by-step framework for establishing psychological safety in your team or organization    </p>
<p>                     Shed the &#8220;yes-men&#8221; approach and step into real performance. Fertilize creativity, clarify goals, achieve accountability, redefine leadership, and much more. The Fearless Organization helps you bring about this most critical transformation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fearless-organization-creating-psychological-safety-in-the-workplace-for-learning-innovation-and-growth-amy-c-edmondson-abridged/">The Fearless Organization : Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth &#8211; Amy C. Edmondson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiness Advantage : The Seven Principles of Positive Psychology that Fuel Success and Performance at Work &#8211; Shawn Achor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiness-advantage-the-seven-principles-of-positive-psychology-that-fuel-success-and-performance-at-work-shawn-achor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiness-advantage-the-seven-principles-of-positive-psychology-that-fuel-success-and-performance-at-work-shawn-achor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most people want to be successful in life. And of course, everyone wants to be happy. When it comes to the pursuit of success and happiness, most people assume the same formula: if you work hard, you will become successful, and once you become successful, then you&#8217;ll be happy. The only problem is that a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-advantage-the-seven-principles-of-positive-psychology-that-fuel-success-and-performance-at-work-shawn-achor-abridged/">The Happiness Advantage : The Seven Principles of Positive Psychology that Fuel Success and Performance at Work &#8211; Shawn Achor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most people want to be successful in life. And of course, everyone wants to be happy. When it comes to the pursuit of success and happiness, most people assume the same formula: if you work hard, you will become successful, and once you become successful, then you&#8217;ll be happy. The only problem is that a decade of cutting-edge research in the field of positive psychology has proven that this formula is backwards. Success does not beget happiness.    </p>
<p>                    Based on the largest study ever conducted on happiness and human potential (a survey conducted by the author of more than 1,600 students), Harvard lecturer Shawn Achor shares seven core principles of positive psychology that each one of us can use to improve our performance, grow our careers, and gain a competitive edge at work. He reveals how happiness actually fuels success and performance, not the other way around. Why? Because when we are happier and more positive we are more engaged, creative, resilient to stress, and productive. The Happiness Advantage will appeal to anyone who wants practical advice on how to become happier and also more successful.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-advantage-the-seven-principles-of-positive-psychology-that-fuel-success-and-performance-at-work-shawn-achor-abridged/">The Happiness Advantage : The Seven Principles of Positive Psychology that Fuel Success and Performance at Work &#8211; Shawn Achor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Broadcasting Happinesss : The Science of Igniting and Sustaining Positive Change &#8211; Michelle Gielan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/broadcasting-happinesss-the-science-of-igniting-and-sustaining-positive-change-michelle-gielan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/broadcasting-happinesss-the-science-of-igniting-and-sustaining-positive-change-michelle-gielan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Broadcasting Happiness will &#8220;inspire you and change your life.&#8221; &#8211;Parade Magazine We are all broadcasters. As managers, colleagues, parents and friends, we are constantly transmitting information to the people around us, and the messages we choose to broadcast create success or hold us back. What&#8217;s your broadcast? New research from the fields of positive psychology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/broadcasting-happinesss-the-science-of-igniting-and-sustaining-positive-change-michelle-gielan-abridged/">Broadcasting Happinesss : The Science of Igniting and Sustaining Positive Change &#8211; Michelle Gielan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Broadcasting Happiness will &#8220;inspire you and change your life.&#8221; &#8211;Parade Magazine  We are all broadcasters. As managers, colleagues, parents and friends, we are constantly transmitting information to the people around us, and the messages we choose to broadcast create success or hold us back.  What&#8217;s your broadcast?  New research from the fields of positive psychology and neuroscience shows that small shifts in the way we communicate can create big ripple effects on business and educational outcomes, including 31 percent higher productivity, 25 percent better performance ratings, 37 percent higher sales, and 23 percent lower levels of stress.  In Broadcasting Happiness, Michelle Gielan, former national CBS News anchor turned positive psychology researcher, shows you how changing your broadcast changes your power by sharing jaw-dropping stories and incredible research.  Learn Michelle&#8217;s simple research-based communication habits that have been featured in her PBS program Inspire Happiness and Oprah&#8217;s 21 Days to Happiness class.<br />
                    Broadcasting Happiness will help you:  &#8211; Inoculate your brain against stress and negativity by fact-checking challenges &#8211; Drive success by leading a conversation or communication with positivity &#8211; Rewrite debilitating thought patterns and turn them into fuel for resilience and growth &#8211; Deal with negative people in a way that lessens their power &#8211; Share bad news more effectively to increase future social capital &#8211; Create and sustain a positive culture at work or home by creating contagious optimism &#8211; Help the people you care about most move from negative to positive in seconds  Broadcasting Happiness showcases how real individuals and organizations have used these techniques to achieve results that include increasing revenues by hundreds of millions of dollars, raising a school district&#8217;s graduation rate by 45 percent, and shifting family gatherings from toxic to thriving.  Changing your broadcast can change your life, your success, and the lives of others around you. Broadcasting Happiness will show you how!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/broadcasting-happinesss-the-science-of-igniting-and-sustaining-positive-change-michelle-gielan-abridged/">Broadcasting Happinesss : The Science of Igniting and Sustaining Positive Change &#8211; Michelle Gielan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Snakes in Suits : When Psychopaths Go to Work &#8211; Dr. Paul Babiak, Dr. Robert D. Hare (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/snakes-in-suits-when-psychopaths-go-to-work-dr-paul-babiak-dr-robert-d-hare-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/snakes-in-suits-when-psychopaths-go-to-work-dr-paul-babiak-dr-robert-d-hare-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Snakes in Suits&#8221; is a compelling, frightening, and scientifically sound look at exactly how psychopaths work in the corporate environment: what kind of companies attract them, how they negotiate the hiring process, and how they function day by day. You&#8217;ll learn how they apply their &#8220;instinctive&#8221; manipulation techniques-assessing potential targets, controlling influential victims, and abandoning [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/snakes-in-suits-when-psychopaths-go-to-work-dr-paul-babiak-dr-robert-d-hare-abridged/">Snakes in Suits : When Psychopaths Go to Work &#8211; Dr. Paul Babiak, Dr. Robert D. Hare (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Snakes in Suits&#8221; is a compelling, frightening, and scientifically sound look at exactly how psychopaths work in the corporate environment: what kind of companies attract them, how they negotiate the hiring process, and how they function day by day. You&#8217;ll learn how they apply their &#8220;instinctive&#8221; manipulation techniques-assessing potential targets, controlling influential victims, and abandoning those no longer useful-to business processes such as hiring, political command and control, and executive succession, all while hiding within the corporate culture. It&#8217;s a must read for anyone in the business world, because whatever level you&#8217;re at, you&#8217;ll learn the subtle warning signs of psychopathic behaviour and be able to protect yourself and your company-before it&#8217;s too late.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/snakes-in-suits-when-psychopaths-go-to-work-dr-paul-babiak-dr-robert-d-hare-abridged/">Snakes in Suits : When Psychopaths Go to Work &#8211; Dr. Paul Babiak, Dr. Robert D. Hare (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boost! : How the Psychology of Sports Can Enhance Your Performance in Management and Work &#8211; Michael Bar-Eli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/boost-how-the-psychology-of-sports-can-enhance-your-performance-in-management-and-work-michael-bar-eli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boost-how-the-psychology-of-sports-can-enhance-your-performance-in-management-and-work-michael-bar-eli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To perform better in any situation &#8211; in your career, hobbies, relationships, or in any facet of your life &#8211; it is critical to develop psychological skills, which, just like physical abilities, can be taught, learned, and practiced. Both as individuals and as groups, we can tone these psychological skills and use them to heighten [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boost-how-the-psychology-of-sports-can-enhance-your-performance-in-management-and-work-michael-bar-eli-abridged/">Boost! : How the Psychology of Sports Can Enhance Your Performance in Management and Work &#8211; Michael Bar-Eli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To perform better in any situation &#8211; in your career, hobbies, relationships, or in any facet of your life &#8211; it is critical to develop psychological skills, which, just like physical abilities, can be taught, learned, and practiced. Both as individuals and as groups, we can tone these<br />
                    psychological skills and use them to heighten awareness, foster talents and technical abilities, and reach peak performance. Mental preparedness and psychological awareness are the keys to thriving in any environment.     </p>
<p>                    Few understand the importance of psychological skills better than the internationally recognized professor Michael Bar-Eli. As both a sports and organizational psychologist for more than 35 years, Bar-Eli has not only researched the science of performance but has also worked directly with elite<br />
                    athletes, coaches, and teams to help them improve their success on the court or field. Boost! takes the lessons he&#8217;s learned from sports psychology and translates them for leaders and managers at any stage in their career. With prescriptive advice, Bar-Eli illustrates how anyone can apply these<br />
                    lessons to better support and inspire co-workers and employees and create a sustainable, successful working environment and business.     </p>
<p>                    Boost! breaks down the complex behavioral science of getting ahead. Through original scientific research, unique case studies, and anecdotes from the world of sports and beyond, Bar-Eli explains the psychological underpinnings of human behavior and how we can harness this knowledge to perform at our<br />
                    highest levels, succeeding in our careers and personal lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boost-how-the-psychology-of-sports-can-enhance-your-performance-in-management-and-work-michael-bar-eli-abridged/">Boost! : How the Psychology of Sports Can Enhance Your Performance in Management and Work &#8211; Michael Bar-Eli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Awakening Compassion at Work : The Quiet Power That Elevates People and Organizations (16pt Large Print Edition) &#8211; Monica C Worline, Jane E Dutton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Caring Is a Competitive Advantage Suffering in the workplace can rob our colleagues and coworkers of humanity, dignity, and motivation and is an unrecognized and costly drain on organizational potential. Marshaling evidence from two decades of field research, scholars and consultants Monica Worline and Jane Dutton show that alleviating such suffering confers measurable competitive advantages [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/">Awakening Compassion at Work : The Quiet Power That Elevates People and Organizations (16pt Large Print Edition) &#8211; Monica C Worline, Jane E Dutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Caring Is a Competitive Advantage Suffering in the workplace can rob our colleagues and coworkers of humanity, dignity, and motivation and is an unrecognized and costly drain on organizational potential. Marshaling evidence from two decades of field research, scholars and consultants Monica Worline and Jane Dutton show that alleviating such suffering confers measurable competitive advantages in areas like innovation, collaboration, service quality, and talent attraction and retention. They outline four steps for meeting suffering with compassion and show how to build a capacity for compassion into the structures and practices of an organization-because ultimately, as they write, Compassion is an irreplaceable dimension of excellence for any organization that wants to make the most of its human capabilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/">Awakening Compassion at Work : The Quiet Power That Elevates People and Organizations (16pt Large Print Edition) &#8211; Monica C Worline, Jane E Dutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Humans Are Underrated : What High Achievers Know that Brilliant Machines Never Will &#8211; Geoff Colvin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the dawning age of brilliant machines, what will people do better than computers? It&#8217;s easy to imagine a frightening future in which technology takes over the jobs that we now get paid to do, working more accurately and for barely any cost. Computers can already perform surgery, drive vehicles, write articles and do intricate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/">Humans Are Underrated : What High Achievers Know that Brilliant Machines Never Will &#8211; Geoff Colvin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the dawning age of brilliant machines, what will people do better than computers?    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s easy to imagine a frightening future in which technology takes over the jobs that we now get paid to do, working more accurately and for barely any cost. Computers can already perform surgery, drive vehicles, write articles and do intricate legal work, so what hope will there be for tomorrow&#8217;s workforce?    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on a wealth of research, Geoff Colvin uncovers the skills that will be in great demand as technology advances &#8211; and how they can be developed. In this new machine age, we shouldn&#8217;t try to beat computers at what they can do. We&#8217;ll lose that contest. Instead we must look to unlikely places, learn from the best, and cultivate the human abilities that make us unique.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/">Humans Are Underrated : What High Achievers Know that Brilliant Machines Never Will &#8211; Geoff Colvin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Too Fast to Think : How to Reclaim Your Creativity in a Hyper-connected Work Culture &#8211; Chris Lewis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/too-fast-to-think-how-to-reclaim-your-creativity-in-a-hyper-connected-work-culture-chris-lewis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/too-fast-to-think-how-to-reclaim-your-creativity-in-a-hyper-connected-work-culture-chris-lewis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our lives are getting faster and faster. We are engulfed in constant distraction from email, social media and our &#8216;always on&#8217; work culture. We are too busy, too overloaded with information and too focused on analytical left-brain thinking processes to be creative. Too Fast to Think exposes how our current work practices, media culture and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/too-fast-to-think-how-to-reclaim-your-creativity-in-a-hyper-connected-work-culture-chris-lewis-abridged/">Too Fast to Think : How to Reclaim Your Creativity in a Hyper-connected Work Culture &#8211; Chris Lewis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our lives are getting faster and faster. We are engulfed in constant distraction from email, social media and our &#8216;always on&#8217; work culture. We are too busy, too overloaded with information and too focused on analytical left-brain thinking processes to be creative. Too Fast to Think exposes how our current work practices, media culture and education systems are detrimental to innovation. The speed and noise of modern life is undermining the clarity and quiet that is essential to power individual thought. Our best ideas are often generated when we are free to think diffusely, in an uninterrupted environment, which is why moments of inspiration so often occur in places completely separate to our offices.     </p>
<p>                    To reclaim creativity, Too Fast to Think teaches you how to retrain your brain into allowing creative ideas to emerge, before they are shut down by interruption, distraction or the self-doubt of your over-rational brain. This is essential reading for anyone who wants to maximize their creative potential, as well as that of their team. Supported by cutting-edge research from the University of the Arts London and insightful interviews with business leaders, academics, artists, politicians and psychologists, Chris Lewis takes a holistic approach to explain the 8 crucial traits that are inherently linked to creation and innovation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/too-fast-to-think-how-to-reclaim-your-creativity-in-a-hyper-connected-work-culture-chris-lewis-abridged/">Too Fast to Think : How to Reclaim Your Creativity in a Hyper-connected Work Culture &#8211; Chris Lewis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Data : The Tiny Clues That Uncover Huge Trends &#8211; Martin Lindstrom Company (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller named one of the &#8220;Most Important Books of 2016&#8221; by Inc, and a Forbes 2016 &#8220;Must Read Business Book&#8221; &#8216;If you love &#8216;Bones&#8217; and &#8216;CSI&#8217;, this book is your kind of candy&#8217; Paco Underhill, author of Why We Buy &#8216;Martin&#8217;s best book to date. A personal, intuitive, powerful way to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/">Small Data : The Tiny Clues That Uncover Huge Trends &#8211; Martin Lindstrom Company (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller named one of the &#8220;Most Important Books of 2016&#8221; by Inc, and a Forbes 2016 &#8220;Must Read Business Book&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you love &#8216;Bones&#8217; and &#8216;CSI&#8217;, this book is your kind of candy&#8217; Paco Underhill, author of Why We Buy    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Martin&#8217;s best book to date. A personal, intuitive, powerful way to look at making an impact with your work&#8217; Seth Godin, author of Purple Cow    </p>
<p>                    Martin Lindstrom, one of Time Magazine&#8217;s 100 Most Influential People in The World and a modern-day Sherlock Holmes, harnesses the power of &#8220;small data&#8221; in his quest to discover the next big thing.    </p>
<p>                    In an era where many believe Big Data has rendered human perception and observation &#8216;old-school&#8217; or passe, Martin Lindstrom shows that mining and matching technological data with up-close psychological insight creates the ultimate snapshot of who we really are and what we really want. He works like a modern-day Sherlock Holmes, accumulating small clues &#8211; the progressively weaker handshakes of Millenials, a notable global decrease in the use of facial powder, a change in how younger consumers approach eating ice cream cones &#8211; to help solve a stunningly diverse array of challenges. In Switzerland, a stuffed teddy bear in a teenage girl&#8217;s bedroom helped revolutionise 1,000 stores &#8211; spread across twenty countries &#8211; for one of Europe&#8217;s largest fashion retailers. In Dubai, a distinctive bracelet strung with pearls helped Jenny Craig offset its declining membership in the United States and increase loyalty by 159% in only one year. In China, the look of a car dashboard led to the design of the iRobot, or Roomba, floor cleaner &#8211; a great success story.    </p>
<p>                    SMALL DATA combines armchair travel with forensic psychology in an interlocking series of international clue-gathering detective stories. It shows Lindstrom using his proprietary CLUES Framework &#8211; where big data is merely one part of the overall puzzle &#8211; to get radically close to consumers and come up with the counter-intuitive insights that have in some cases helped transform entire industries.     </p>
<p>                    SMALL DATA presents a rare behind-the-scenes look at what it takes to create global brands, and reveals surprising and counter-intuitive truths about what connects us all as humans.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/">Small Data : The Tiny Clues That Uncover Huge Trends &#8211; Martin Lindstrom Company (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enchantment : The Art of Changing Hearts, Minds, and Actions &#8211; Guy Kawasaki (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/enchantment-the-art-of-changing-hearts-minds-and-actions-guy-kawasaki-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/enchantment-the-art-of-changing-hearts-minds-and-actions-guy-kawasaki-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Enchantment, as defined by bestselling business guru Guy Kawasaki, is not about manipulating people. It transforms situations and relationships. It converts hostility into civility and civility into affinity. It changes skeptics and cynics into believers and the undecided into the loyal. Enchantment can happen during a retail transaction, a high-level corporate negotiation, or a Facebook [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enchantment-the-art-of-changing-hearts-minds-and-actions-guy-kawasaki-abridged/">Enchantment : The Art of Changing Hearts, Minds, and Actions &#8211; Guy Kawasaki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enchantment, as defined by bestselling business guru Guy Kawasaki, is not about manipulating people. It transforms situations and relationships. It converts hostility into civility and civility into affinity. It changes skeptics and cynics into believers and the undecided into the loyal.    </p>
<p>                    Enchantment can happen during a retail transaction, a high-level corporate negotiation, or a Facebook update. And when done right, it&#8217;s more powerful than traditional persuasion, influence, or marketing techniques.    </p>
<p>                    Kawasaki argues that in business and personal interactions, your goal is not merely to get what you want but to bring about a voluntary, enduring, and delightful change in other people. By enlisting their own goals and desires, by being likable and trustworthy, and by framing a cause that others can embrace, you can change hearts, minds, and actions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enchantment-the-art-of-changing-hearts-minds-and-actions-guy-kawasaki-abridged/">Enchantment : The Art of Changing Hearts, Minds, and Actions &#8211; Guy Kawasaki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
