<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought &amp; Practice Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/mind-body-spirit-thought-practice/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/mind-body-spirit-thought-practice/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought &amp; Practice Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/mind-body-spirit-thought-practice/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chicken Soup for the Soul Happily Ever After : Fun and Heartwarming Stories About Finding and Enjoying Your Mate &#8211; Amy Kaechele, Fred Stella, Compiled by JACK CANFIELD, Compiled by Mark Victor Hansen, Compiled by Amy Newmark</title>
		<link>/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-happily-ever-after-fun-and-heartwarming-stories-about-finding-and-enjoying-your-mate-amy-kaechele-fred-stella-compiled-by-jack-canfield-compiled-by-mark-vict/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-happily-ever-after-fun-and-heartwarming-stories-about-finding-and-enjoying-your-mate-amy-kaechele-fred-stella-compiled-by-jack-canfield-compiled-by-mark-vict/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dating and courtship, romance, love, and marriage are favorite Chicken Soup topics. Women, and even men, love to listen to true stories about how it happened for other people. This audiobook includes the 101 best stories on love and marriage chosen from a wide variety of past Chicken Soup books. These heartwarming stories will inspire [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-happily-ever-after-fun-and-heartwarming-stories-about-finding-and-enjoying-your-mate-amy-kaechele-fred-stella-compiled-by-jack-canfield-compiled-by-mark-vict/">Chicken Soup for the Soul Happily Ever After : Fun and Heartwarming Stories About Finding and Enjoying Your Mate &#8211; Amy Kaechele, Fred Stella, Compiled by JACK CANFIELD, Compiled by Mark Victor Hansen, Compiled by Amy Newmark</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dating and courtship, romance, love, and marriage are favorite Chicken Soup topics. Women, and even men, love to listen to true stories about how it happened for other people. This audiobook includes the 101 best stories on love and marriage chosen from a wide variety of past Chicken Soup books. These heartwarming stories will inspire and amuse listeners, whether they are just starting to date, are newly wed, or are veterans of a long marriage.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-happily-ever-after-fun-and-heartwarming-stories-about-finding-and-enjoying-your-mate-amy-kaechele-fred-stella-compiled-by-jack-canfield-compiled-by-mark-vict/">Chicken Soup for the Soul Happily Ever After : Fun and Heartwarming Stories About Finding and Enjoying Your Mate &#8211; Amy Kaechele, Fred Stella, Compiled by JACK CANFIELD, Compiled by Mark Victor Hansen, Compiled by Amy Newmark</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Master Key System (Unabridged Ed. Includes All 28 Parts) by Charles Haanel &#8211; Charles Haanel</title>
		<link>/the-master-key-system-unabridged-ed-includes-all-28-parts-by-charles-haanel-charles-haanel/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-master-key-system-unabridged-ed-includes-all-28-parts-by-charles-haanel-charles-haanel/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover for yourself within those pages the same secrets of wealth creation and personal improvement that are believed to have inspired Bill Gates to drop out of university and establish his financial empire. You are looking at a manual for your own success that has proven the test of time for close to a hundred [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-master-key-system-unabridged-ed-includes-all-28-parts-by-charles-haanel-charles-haanel/">The Master Key System (Unabridged Ed. Includes All 28 Parts) by Charles Haanel &#8211; Charles Haanel</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover for yourself within those pages the same secrets of wealth creation and personal improvement that are believed to have inspired Bill Gates to drop out of university and establish his financial empire. You are looking at a manual for your own success that has proven the test of time for close to a hundred years. So powerful are the teachings within this book that it mysteriously disappeared after it sold more than 200,000 copies. With its reemergence, it inspired another phenomena &#8211; The Secret. Somebody out there really didn¿t think people like you and me should be equipped with the power to achieve our full purpose and potential, but they failed. C¿mon, it is time you too started Keying and unleashing the power of the Law of Attraction into your life. Manifest your own dreams day after day with the proven principles of success outlined in the 28 lessons that form the Master Key System, because you know it is time to stop reacting and time to shape your own reality. The same gurus who are willing to charge you thousands of dollars for putting these secrets into their own words consider this work to be one of the finest programs in self-improvement, for the depth of its coverage. Save your money and learn from the master himself. It was written to be easy to follow, simple to understand, and readily applicable in every situation, so that you are both feeling and thinking good. Start your journey of self-mastery on the right foot by getting this edition. Someone thought we were crazy to publish another copy of the Master Key. We thought you should know why he changed his mind when he got his hands on this edition. Anyone who just wants to scan the book can find a copy of it online, but it is filled with typos and missing four vital chapters. All the other printed editions we bought fared no better and tried to compete on who could sell you this gem the cheapest, without regard to quality or completeness. You deserve the best edition possible for your money, one that is easy to use while studying, complete, accurate and beautifully designed. We¿ve produced a copy that you¿ll be proud to share with your friends as a gift, a copy that someone on their way to true success would own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-master-key-system-unabridged-ed-includes-all-28-parts-by-charles-haanel-charles-haanel/">The Master Key System (Unabridged Ed. Includes All 28 Parts) by Charles Haanel &#8211; Charles Haanel</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Do The Work : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Nicole LePera</title>
		<link>/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;If LePera&#8217;s Instagram feed is full of aha moments illuminating the inner workings of your psyche, the revelations in the book are more like a full firework display.&#8217; Red magazine &#8216;This book is a must-read for anyone on a path of personal growth.&#8217; GABBY BERNSTEIN, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/">How To Do The Work : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Nicole LePera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If LePera&#8217;s Instagram feed is full of aha moments illuminating the inner workings of your psyche, the revelations in the book are more like a full firework display.&#8217; Red magazine    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is a must-read for anyone on a path of personal growth.&#8217; GABBY BERNSTEIN, author of number one New York Times bestsellers Super Attractor and The Universe Has Your Back    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book I wish I had read in my twenties.&#8217; ELIZABETH DAY, author of How to Fail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;How to Do the Work will transform how you see yourself and your ability to change. I believe this book could change lives, if not the world.&#8217;  HOLLY BOURNE, bestselling author of How Do You Like Me Now?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Want more from life? Looking for answers? How to Do the Work will teach you how to find them within yourself. A masterpiece of empowerment &#8211; this book changed my life and, trust me, it&#8217;ll change yours too.&#8217; MEL ROBBINS, author of The 5 Second Rule    </p>
<p>                    As a clinical psychologist, Dr Nicole LePera found herself frustrated by the limitations of traditional psychotherapy. Wanting more for her patients &#8211; and for herself &#8211; she began a journey to develop a united philosophy of mental, physical and spiritual health that equips people with the tools necessary to heal themselves. After experiencing the life-changing results herself, she began to share what she&#8217;d learned with others &#8211; and The Holistic Psychologist was born.    </p>
<p>                    Now Dr LePera is ready to share her much-requested protocol with the world. In How to Do the Work, she offers both a manifesto for self-healing and an essential guide to creating a more vibrant, authentic, and joyful life. Drawing on the latest research from both scientific research and healing modalities, Dr LePera helps us recognise how adverse experiences and trauma in childhood live with us, keeping us stuck engaging in patterns of codependency, emotional immaturity, and trauma bonds. Unless addressed, these self-sabotaging behaviours can quickly become cyclical, leaving people feeling unhappy, unfulfilled, and unwell.    </p>
<p>                    In How to Do the Work, Dr LePera offers readers the support and tools that will allow them to break free from destructive behaviours to reclaim and recreate their lives. Nothing short of a paradigm shift, this is a celebration of empowerment that will forever change the way we approach mental wellness and self-care.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/">How To Do The Work : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Nicole LePera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon Hill&#8217;s Outwitting the Devil : The Secret to Freedom and Success &#8211; Dan John Miller, Phil Gigante, Napoleon Hill, Afterword by Michael Bernard Beckwith, Edited by Sharon Lechter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleon-hills-outwitting-the-devil-the-secret-to-freedom-and-success-dan-john-miller-phil-gigante-napoleon-hill-afterword-by-michael-bernard-beckwith-edited-by-sharon-lechter-abri/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleon-hills-outwitting-the-devil-the-secret-to-freedom-and-success-dan-john-miller-phil-gigante-napoleon-hill-afterword-by-michael-bernard-beckwith-edited-by-sharon-lechter-abri/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Napoleon Hill was one of America&#8217;s great, influential thinkers who continues to have an enormous impact today.&#8221; &#8211;Steve Forbes, editor-in-chief of Forbes magazine Bestselling author Napoleon Hill reveals the seven principles of good that allow us to triumph over obstacles&#8230;and find success. Using his legendary ability to get to the root of human potential, Napoleon [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-hills-outwitting-the-devil-the-secret-to-freedom-and-success-dan-john-miller-phil-gigante-napoleon-hill-afterword-by-michael-bernard-beckwith-edited-by-sharon-lechter-abri/">Napoleon Hill&#8217;s Outwitting the Devil : The Secret to Freedom and Success &#8211; Dan John Miller, Phil Gigante, Napoleon Hill, Afterword by Michael Bernard Beckwith, Edited by Sharon Lechter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Napoleon Hill was one of America&#8217;s great, influential thinkers who continues to have an enormous impact today.&#8221; &#8211;Steve Forbes, editor-in-chief of Forbes magazine    </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author Napoleon Hill reveals the seven principles of good that allow us to triumph over obstacles&#8230;and find success.    </p>
<p>                    Using his legendary ability to get to the root of human potential, Napoleon Hill digs deep to reveal how fear, procrastination, anger, and jealousy prevent us from realizing our personal goals. This long-suppressed parable, once considered too controversial to publish, was written by Hill in 1938 following the publication of his classic bestseller, Think and Grow Rich. Annotated and edited for a contemporary audience by Rich Dad, Poor Dad and Three Feet from Gold coauthor Sharon Lechter, this book is profound, powerful, resonant, and rich with insight.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-hills-outwitting-the-devil-the-secret-to-freedom-and-success-dan-john-miller-phil-gigante-napoleon-hill-afterword-by-michael-bernard-beckwith-edited-by-sharon-lechter-abri/">Napoleon Hill&#8217;s Outwitting the Devil : The Secret to Freedom and Success &#8211; Dan John Miller, Phil Gigante, Napoleon Hill, Afterword by Michael Bernard Beckwith, Edited by Sharon Lechter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Attractor : Methods for Manifesting a Life beyond Your Wildest Dreams &#8211; Gabrielle Bernstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-attractor-methods-for-manifesting-a-life-beyond-your-wildest-dreams-gabrielle-bernstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-attractor-methods-for-manifesting-a-life-beyond-your-wildest-dreams-gabrielle-bernstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! ** Ready to take the next step toward living in alignment with the Universe? The #1 New York Times best-selling author of The Universe Has Your Back shows you how. In Super Attractor, Gabrielle Bernstein lays out the essential steps for living in alignment with the Universe&#8211;more fully than you&#8217;ve [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-attractor-methods-for-manifesting-a-life-beyond-your-wildest-dreams-gabrielle-bernstein-abridged/">Super Attractor : Methods for Manifesting a Life beyond Your Wildest Dreams &#8211; Gabrielle Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! ** Ready to take the next step toward living in alignment with the Universe? The #1 New York Times best-selling author of The Universe Has Your Back shows you how.    </p>
<p>                    In Super Attractor, Gabrielle Bernstein lays out the essential steps for living in alignment with the Universe&#8211;more fully than you&#8217;ve ever done before. &#8220;I&#8217;ve always known that there is a nonphysical presence beyond my visible sight,&#8221; Gabby writes. &#8220;All my life I&#8217;ve intuitively tuned in to it and used it as a source for good. . . . What we call it is irrelevant. Connecting to it is imperative.&#8221; Super Attractor is a manifesto for making that connection and marrying your spiritual life with your day-to-day experience. In these pages, you&#8217;ll learn to:    </p>
<p>                    * Move beyond dabbling in your practice, when it&#8217;s convenient, to living a spiritual life all the time<br />
                    * Take practical steps to create a life filled with purpose, happiness, and freedom<br />
                    * Feel a sense of awe each day as you witness miracles unfold<br />
                    * Release the past and live without fear of the future<br />
                    * Tap into the infinite source of abundance, joy, and well-being that is your birthright<br />
                    * Bring more light to your own life and the world around you    </p>
<p>                    This book is a journey of remembering where your true power lies. You&#8217;ll learn how to co-create the life you want. You&#8217;ll accept that life can flow, that attracting is fun, and that you don&#8217;t have to work so hard to get what you want. Most important, you&#8217;ll feel good. And when you feel good, you&#8217;ll give off a presence of joy that can elevate everyone around you. After reading this book, you will know how to fulfill your function: to be a force of love in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-attractor-methods-for-manifesting-a-life-beyond-your-wildest-dreams-gabrielle-bernstein-abridged/">Super Attractor : Methods for Manifesting a Life beyond Your Wildest Dreams &#8211; Gabrielle Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everything is Figureoutable : The #1 New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Marie Forleo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everything-is-figureoutable-the-1-new-york-times-bestseller-marie-forleo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chakras, Auras & Spiritual Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everything-is-figureoutable-the-1-new-york-times-bestseller-marie-forleo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>***THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER*** &#8216;Fast-paced, generous, wise, raw, funny, practical and helpful&#8217; Glennon Doyle, author of Untamed &#8216;Millions of young women look to Marie Forleo as their inspiration for empowerment and achievement&#8217; Oprah Winfrey &#8216;Reading these pages I experienced the sensation of limitless possibility. This book will change lives&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert Do you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-is-figureoutable-the-1-new-york-times-bestseller-marie-forleo-abridged/">Everything is Figureoutable : The #1 New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Marie Forleo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>***THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER***    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fast-paced, generous, wise, raw, funny, practical and helpful&#8217; Glennon Doyle, author of Untamed    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Millions of young women look to Marie Forleo as their inspiration for empowerment and achievement&#8217; Oprah Winfrey    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Reading these pages I experienced the sensation of limitless possibility. This book will change lives&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert    </p>
<p>                     Do you ever have trouble finishing what you start? Do amazing ideas come to you all the time but after the initial excitement wanes you struggle to follow through? If you&#8217;re creative and ambitious, the answer is likely yes.    </p>
<p>                     The problem isn&#8217;t you. It&#8217;s not that you&#8217;re not hardworking, intelligent or deserving, but that you haven&#8217;t yet installed the one key belief that will change everything: Everything is figureoutable.     </p>
<p>                     Whether you want to leave a dead-end job, heal a relationship, grow a business, master your money, or just find two free hours in your day, Everything is Figureoutable will train your brain to think more positively and help you break down any dream into manageable steps.     </p>
<p>                     Inside you&#8217;ll learn:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; How to deal with criticism and imposter syndrome<br />
                     &#8211; Why it&#8217;s crucial that you strive for progress not perfection<br />
                     &#8211; How to bounce back from failure<br />
                     &#8211; How to overcome a lack of time and money     </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll also hear triumphant stories of everyday people using the everything is figureoutable philosophy to transform their life. Everything is figureoutable is more than just a fun phrase to say. It&#8217;s a practical, actionable discipline. And it&#8217;s about to make you unstoppable!    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Smart, funny, and as brilliant as it is straightforward. LOVED it!&#8217; Brene Brown    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book delivers a knockout punch to whatever is holding you back&#8217; Cheryl Strayed</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-is-figureoutable-the-1-new-york-times-bestseller-marie-forleo-abridged/">Everything is Figureoutable : The #1 New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Marie Forleo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happy Mind : A Simple Guide to Living a Happier Life Starting Today &#8211; Kevin Horsley, Louis Fourie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happy-mind-a-simple-guide-to-living-a-happier-life-starting-today-kevin-horsley-louis-fourie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happy-mind-a-simple-guide-to-living-a-happier-life-starting-today-kevin-horsley-louis-fourie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Happy Mind, Happy Life From the Wall Street Journal bestselling author of Unlimited Memory comes a new book on finding happiness in life using the power of your mind. The search for happiness is fundamental for all humans, and the answers lie within the depths of your mind. What is happiness? What causes it? How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happy-mind-a-simple-guide-to-living-a-happier-life-starting-today-kevin-horsley-louis-fourie-abridged/">The Happy Mind : A Simple Guide to Living a Happier Life Starting Today &#8211; Kevin Horsley, Louis Fourie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happy Mind, Happy Life    </p>
<p>                     From the Wall Street Journal bestselling author of Unlimited Memory comes a new book on finding happiness in life using the power of your mind.    </p>
<p>                     The search for happiness is fundamental for all humans, and the answers lie within the depths of your mind.    </p>
<p>                     What is happiness? What causes it? How do you hold onto it? What makes it go away?    </p>
<p>                     These questions have led to many philosophical debates over thousands of years. The philosophers of Greece were famous for their quest to define the pillars of &#8220;the good life.&#8221; Faith-based movements have painstakingly crafted dogmas and prescribed behaviors in pursuit of ultimate peace and joy. Academic studies have been concentrated on finding the answer to &#8220;the optimal life experience.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                     Governments have professed to craft policies to promote the overall well-being of their citizens. Every day, ordinary dinner table discussions are, at heart, a dialogue in search of a happy life.    </p>
<p>                     Happiness is Unique to You    </p>
<p>                     What makes one person happy may make another miserable. There is no one key to happiness for everyone. Instead, the answers lie within you.    </p>
<p>                     In The Happy Mind, you&#8217;ll learn to find your own personal answers to your most important questions. What makes you happy? What changes can you make to bring more happiness into your life? And how can you let go of old habits, beliefs, and situations that no longer fulfill you?    </p>
<p>                     The aim of this book is not to push a specific definition of happiness. Instead, you&#8217;ll discover valuable insights that will allow you to create lasting happiness instead of being driven by short-term pleasure-seeking.    </p>
<p>                     In this book you will learn:     </p>
<p>                       How people look for happiness in all the wrong places, and how you can avoid these &#8220;happiness traps&#8221; that keep you stuck and unfulfilled<br />
                     Why most people mistake pleasure for happiness, and how this simple mistake causes you to lose sight of what really matters to you<br />
                     The nine common qualities that super happy people share (and how you can apply them to brighten up your life)<br />
                     The key traits of unhappiness (and the most important behaviors you should avoid)<br />
                     Many easy-to-grasp suggestions that can be viewed daily to enhance your capacity to live a happy life.      </p>
<p>                     Give Yourself the Gift of The Happy Mind    </p>
<p>                     The Happy Mind is your roadmap to living a happy life, custom-designed just for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happy-mind-a-simple-guide-to-living-a-happier-life-starting-today-kevin-horsley-louis-fourie-abridged/">The Happy Mind : A Simple Guide to Living a Happier Life Starting Today &#8211; Kevin Horsley, Louis Fourie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>InGenius : A Crash Course on Creativity &#8211; Tina Seelig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ingenius-a-crash-course-on-creativity-tina-seelig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ingenius-a-crash-course-on-creativity-tina-seelig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is the ability to creatively tackle problems innate or can it be learned? Like most human traits, both answers are correct. Some people are inherently more innovative than others. But, just like maths, or writing, everyone can improve with practice. Tina Seelig, PhD teaches creativity every day in her courses on innovation at Stanford School [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ingenius-a-crash-course-on-creativity-tina-seelig-abridged/">InGenius : A Crash Course on Creativity &#8211; Tina Seelig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is the ability to creatively tackle problems innate or can it be  learned? Like most human traits, both answers are correct. Some people  are inherently more innovative than others. But, just like maths, or  writing, everyone can improve with practice. Tina Seelig, PhD teaches  creativity every day in her courses on innovation at Stanford School of  Engineering. After ten years of experience, she confidently asserts that  not only can creativity be taught but that there are a clear set of  tools, skills and approaches that can unlock anyone&#8217;s creative  potential.    </p>
<p>                     In InGenius, Seelig reminds us that creativity is not just  something that you think about &#8211; it is something that you do. It is as  natural as breathing, and just as necessary for leading a successful and  fulfilling life. Creative solutions are required because the status quo  is never good enough, and our goal should always be to push beyond the  limits of what seems possible. Great ideas are needed to solve all the  problems we face and to enrich our lives. Whether it is in the  conference room, classroom or kitchen, new ideas open up a world of  wonderful possibilities. With the tools presented in this remarkable book, we will learn how to pull out all stops to take on the  challenges, big and small, that come our way, and to see that every  word, every idea, and every moment provides an opportunity for  creativity that will enhance our lives.    </p>
<p>                    InGenius is filled with concepts, tools, techniques and  stories that reveal ways you can increase your creativity quotient, and  that of your groups and organizations. The first half of the book  focuses on the inside out &#8211; what you can personally do to increase your  own creative aptitude and attitude. The second half deals with the  outside in &#8211; how you can change the local and cultural environment to  increase the creativity quotient of your community.    </p>
<p>                     InGenius reveals one of the great truths about ideas: it costs nothing to generate amazing ideas, and yet the results have  the potential to be priceless.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ingenius-a-crash-course-on-creativity-tina-seelig-abridged/">InGenius : A Crash Course on Creativity &#8211; Tina Seelig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ikigai : The Japanese secret to a long and happy life &#8211; Hector Garcia, Francesc Miralles (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER We all have an ikigai. It&#8217;s the Japanese word for &#8216;a reason to live&#8217; or &#8216;a reason to jump out of bed in the morning&#8217;. It&#8217;s the place where your needs, desires, ambitions, and satisfaction meet. A place of balance. Small wonder that finding your ikigai is closely linked to living longer. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/">Ikigai : The Japanese secret to a long and happy life &#8211; Hector Garcia, Francesc Miralles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    We all have an ikigai.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s the Japanese word for &#8216;a reason to live&#8217; or &#8216;a reason to jump out of bed in the morning&#8217;.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s the place where your needs, desires, ambitions, and satisfaction meet. A place of balance. Small wonder that finding your ikigai is closely linked to living longer.    </p>
<p>                    Finding your ikigai is easier than you might think. This book will help you work out what your own ikigai really is, and equip you to change your life. You have a purpose in this world: your skills, your interests, your desires and your history have made you the perfect candidate for something. All you have to do is find it.    </p>
<p>                    Do that, and you can make every single day of your life joyful and meaningful.<br />
                    ______________________________<br />
                    &#8216;I read it and it&#8217;s bewitched me ever since. I&#8217;m spellbound.&#8217;<br />
                    Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A refreshingly simple recipe for happiness.&#8217; Stylist    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ikigai gently unlocks simple secrets we can all use to live long, meaningful, happy lives. Warm, patient, and kind, this book pulls you gently along your own journey rather than pushing you from behind.&#8217; Neil Pasricha, bestselling author of The Happiness Equation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/">Ikigai : The Japanese secret to a long and happy life &#8211; Hector Garcia, Francesc Miralles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Stay Sane &#8211; Philippa Perry, The School of Life (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-stay-sane-philippa-perry-the-school-of-life-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-stay-sane-philippa-perry-the-school-of-life-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There is no simple set of instructions that can guarantee sanity, but if you want to overcome emotional difficulties and become happier, psychotherapist Philippa Perry, author of The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read, argues that there are four cornerstones to sanity you can influence to bring about change. By developing your self-observation skills, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-stay-sane-philippa-perry-the-school-of-life-abridged/">How to Stay Sane &#8211; Philippa Perry, The School of Life (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is no simple set of instructions that can guarantee sanity, but if you want to overcome emotional difficulties and become happier, psychotherapist Philippa Perry, author of The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read, argues that there are four cornerstones to sanity you can influence to bring about change.     </p>
<p>                    By developing your self-observation skills, examining how you relate to others, breaking out of your comfort zone and exploring new ways of defining yourself, Philippa demonstrates that it is possible to become a little less tortured and a little more fulfilled. How to Stay Sane is at once a brilliant explanation of our minds and a profoundly useful guide to facing up to the many challenges life throws our way.    </p>
<p>                    Discover more inspirational guides from The School of Life series: How to Find Fulfilling Work, How to Worry Less About Money and How to Thrive in the Digital Age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-stay-sane-philippa-perry-the-school-of-life-abridged/">How to Stay Sane &#8211; Philippa Perry, The School of Life (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feng Shui]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Be more Zen in 2022 with this little book of 100 tips and activities to soothe the soul &#8216;Brings the spirit of Zen Buddhism to everyday life . . . 100 snack-size Zen activities you can do daily to add more calm to your life&#8217; Daily Telegraph _______ Zen is the perfect antidote to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/">Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Be more Zen in 2022 with this little book of 100 tips and activities to soothe the soul    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brings the spirit of Zen Buddhism to everyday life . . . 100 snack-size Zen activities you can do daily to add more calm to your life&#8217; Daily Telegraph<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    Zen is the perfect antidote to the stress and uncertainty of modern life . . .    </p>
<p>                    In clear, practical and easy to follow lessons &#8211; one a day for 100 days &#8211; renowned Buddhist monk Shunmyo Masuno draws on centuries of wisdom to show you how to apply the essence of Zen to modern life.    </p>
<p>                    You will learn how to exhale deeply to eliminate negative emotions, to arrange your house simply to clear your thinking, to line up your shoes at night to bring order to your mind, to plant a single flower and watch it grow, to worry less about what you cannot control, and so much more . . .    </p>
<p>                    You will even make time to think about nothing at all.    </p>
<p>                    Simplify your life with the art of Zen, and learn how to feel more relaxed, fulfilled, and with a renewed sense of peace.<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Full of the simplest yet richest rituals to adopt in order to live a long and happy life, this book of wisdom is a soothing balm of peace for anyone living in the busy modern world&#8217; Psychologies    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Does for mental clutter what Marie Kondo has done for household clutter&#8217; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This little treasure needs to be at every bedside&#8217; llan Lokos, author of Through the Flames, Patience, and Pocket Peace    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Zen: The Art of Simple Living makes the wisdom of the Buddha radically accessible&#8217; Dzogchen Ponlop Rinpoche, author of Emotional Rescue and Rebel Buddha</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/">Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership : Follow Them and People Will Follow You &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-21-irrefutable-laws-of-leadership-follow-them-and-people-will-follow-you-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-21-irrefutable-laws-of-leadership-follow-them-and-people-will-follow-you-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What would happen if a leadership expert were willing to distill everything he&#8217;s learned in his 30+ years of experience into a handful of life-changing principles just for you? It would change your life. Internationally-recognized leadership expert and bestselling author John C. Maxwell wrote his million-seller The 21 Laws of Leadership over ten years ago. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-21-irrefutable-laws-of-leadership-follow-them-and-people-will-follow-you-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership : Follow Them and People Will Follow You &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What would happen if a leadership expert were willing to distill everything he&#8217;s learned in his 30+ years of experience into a handful of life-changing principles just for you? It would change your life.    </p>
<p>                    Internationally-recognized leadership expert and bestselling author John C. Maxwell wrote his million-seller The 21 Laws of Leadership over ten years ago. Now, this expanded and updated edition of one of the most trusted and referenced leadership books features revised content that is fundamental to any leader.    </p>
<p>                    Maxwell provides new learnings that makes his original bestseller bigger and better including:    </p>
<p>                    Sharpening and updating every Law of Leadership<br />
                    Seventeen new leadership stories<br />
                    Two new Laws of Leadership<br />
                    New evaluation tool revealing your leadership strengths and weaknesses<br />
                    New application exercises in every chapter that help you grow    </p>
<p>                    The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership features insights learned from Maxwell&#8217;s 30-plus years of leadership successes and mistakes with observations from the worlds of business, politics, sports, religion, and military conflict.    </p>
<p>                    The result is a revealing study of leadership delivered as only a communicator like Maxwell can. Follow these laws of leadership and people will follow you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-21-irrefutable-laws-of-leadership-follow-them-and-people-will-follow-you-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership : Follow Them and People Will Follow You &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Greatest Salesman in the World &#8211; Og Mandino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Christian Testimony & Popular Inspirational Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The runaway bestseller with more than four million copies in print! You too can change your life with the priceless wisdom of ten ancient scrolls handed down for thousands of years. &#8220;Every sales manager should read The Greatest Salesman in the World. It is a book to keep at the bedside, or on the living [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/">The Greatest Salesman in the World &#8211; Og Mandino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The runaway bestseller with more than four million copies in print! You too can change your life with the priceless wisdom of ten ancient scrolls handed down for thousands of years.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every sales manager should read The Greatest Salesman in the World. It is a book to keep at the bedside, or on the living room table&#8211;a book to dip into as needed, to browse in now and then, to enjoy in small stimulating portions. It is a book for the hours and for the years, a book to turn to over and over again, as to a friend, a book of moral, spiritual and ethical guidance, an unfailing source of comfort and inspiration.&#8221;&#8211;Lester J. Bradshaw, Jr., Former Dean, Dale Carnegie Institute of Effective Speaking &#038; Human Relations     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I have read almost every book that has ever been written on salesmanship, but I think Og Mandino has captured all of them in The Greatest Salesman in the World. No one who follows these principles will ever fail as a salesman, and no one will ever be truly great without them; but, the author has done more than present the principles&#8211;he has woven them into the fabric of one of the most fascinating stories I have ever read.&#8221;&#8211;Paul J. Meyer, President of Success Motivation Institute, Inc.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I was overwhelmed by The Greatest Salesman in the World. It is, without doubt, the greatest and the most touching story I have ever read. It is so good that there are two musts that I would attach to it: First, you must not lay it down until you have finished it; and secondly, every individual who sells anything, and that includes us all, must read it.&#8221;&#8211;Robert B. Hensley, President, Life Insurance Co. of Kentucky</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/">The Greatest Salesman in the World &#8211; Og Mandino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind. In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind.    </p>
<p>                    In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and how it evolved. With deft use of examples of humor and wordplay, Steven Pinker weaves our vast knowledge of language into a compelling story: language is a human instinct, wired into our brains by evolution. The Language Instinct received the William James Book Prize from the American Psychological Association and the Public Interest Award from the Linguistics Society of America. This edition includes an update on advances in the science of language since The Language Instinct was first published.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Return to Love : Reflections on the Principles of &#8220;a Course in Miracles&#8221; &#8211; Marianne Williamson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-return-to-love-reflections-on-the-principles-of-a-course-in-miracles-marianne-williamson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chakras, Auras & Spiritual Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stationery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-return-to-love-reflections-on-the-principles-of-a-course-in-miracles-marianne-williamson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Back by popular demand &#8212; and newly updated by the author &#8212; the mega-bestselling spiritual guide in which Marianne Williamson shares her reflections on A Course in Miracles and her insights on the application of love in the search for inner peace. Williamson reveals how we each can become a miracle worker by accepting God [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-return-to-love-reflections-on-the-principles-of-a-course-in-miracles-marianne-williamson-abridged/">A Return to Love : Reflections on the Principles of &#8220;a Course in Miracles&#8221; &#8211; Marianne Williamson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Back by popular demand &#8212; and newly updated by the author &#8212; the mega-bestselling spiritual guide in which Marianne Williamson shares her reflections on A Course in Miracles and her insights on the application of love in the search for inner peace.    </p>
<p>                    Williamson reveals how we each can become a miracle worker by accepting God and by the expression of love in our daily lives. Whether psychic pain is in the area of relationships, career, or health, she shows us how love is a potent force, the key to inner peace, and how by practicing love we can make our own lives more fulfilling while creating a more peaceful and loving world for our children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-return-to-love-reflections-on-the-principles-of-a-course-in-miracles-marianne-williamson-abridged/">A Return to Love : Reflections on the Principles of &#8220;a Course in Miracles&#8221; &#8211; Marianne Williamson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unplug : A Simple Guide to Meditation for Busy Sceptics and Modern Soul Seekers &#8211; Suze Yalof Schwartz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unplug is the book I wish I had when I first started meditating. Simple, smart, and inspirational, it provides concrete tools you can use to live a more fulfilling, happier, and yes, more productive life&#8217; Arianna Huffington THE MODERN GUIDE TO MEDITATION FOR BUSY PEOPLE Unplug is the modern, minimalist guide to meditation for busy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/">Unplug : A Simple Guide to Meditation for Busy Sceptics and Modern Soul Seekers &#8211; Suze Yalof Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unplug is the book I wish I had when I first started meditating. Simple, smart, and inspirational, it provides concrete tools you can use to live a more fulfilling, happier, and yes, more productive life&#8217;  Arianna Huffington    </p>
<p>                    THE MODERN GUIDE TO MEDITATION FOR BUSY PEOPLE    </p>
<p>                    Unplug is the modern, minimalist guide to meditation for busy people. Whether you&#8217;re a Fortune 500 CEO or someone bogged down with a never ending to-do list, Suze Yalof-Schwartz shows that you can get more done &#8211; and do it better &#8211; by consciously unplugging for just a few minutes each day.    </p>
<p>                    This revolutionary book brilliantly simplifies the art of meditation and reveals the life-changing benefits you will experience, from improved memory and a more positive outlook to a reduction in anxiety and stress.    </p>
<p>                    Through easy techniques and tips for incorporating meditation into your daily life, Unplug shows you that everyone can meditate, even if &#8211; especially if &#8211; you believe you think too much, have no time, can&#8217;t sit still or that it&#8217;s just &#8216;not you&#8217;.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/">Unplug : A Simple Guide to Meditation for Busy Sceptics and Modern Soul Seekers &#8211; Suze Yalof Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Name of God is Mercy &#8211; Pope Francis, Translated by Oonagh Stransky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-name-of-god-is-mercy-pope-francis-translated-by-oonagh-stransky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Leaders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Roman Catholicism, Roman Catholic Church]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-name-of-god-is-mercy-pope-francis-translated-by-oonagh-stransky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Name of God is Mercy, Pope Francis&#8217; exploration on the universal theme of mercy, is a spiritual inspiration to both followers of Christianity and non-Christians around the world. Drawing on his own experience as a priest and shepherd, Pope Francis discusses mercy, a subject of central importance in his religious teaching and testimony, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-name-of-god-is-mercy-pope-francis-translated-by-oonagh-stransky-abridged/">The Name of God is Mercy &#8211; Pope Francis, Translated by Oonagh Stransky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Name of God is Mercy, Pope Francis&#8217; exploration on the universal theme of mercy, is a spiritual inspiration to both followers of Christianity and non-Christians around the world.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own experience as a priest and shepherd, Pope Francis discusses mercy, a subject of central importance in his religious teaching and testimony, and in addition sums up other ideas &#8211; reconciliation, the closeness of God &#8211; that comprise the heart of his papacy. Written in conversation with Vatican expert and La Stampa journalist Andrea Tornielli, The Name of God is Mercy is directed at everyone, inside or outside of the Catholic Church, seeking meaning in life, a road to peace and reconciliation, or the healing of physical or spiritual wounds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-name-of-god-is-mercy-pope-francis-translated-by-oonagh-stransky-abridged/">The Name of God is Mercy &#8211; Pope Francis, Translated by Oonagh Stransky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Revolutionise your life one day at a time with this empowering handbook designed for men and women which provides simple strategies for each element of your day. Marcus Aubrey, author of the book is CEO of Onnit, a human performance company that he has built into one of the fastest growing companies in the world. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/">Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Revolutionise your life one day at a time with this empowering handbook designed for men and women which provides simple strategies for each element of your day. Marcus Aubrey, author of the book is CEO of Onnit, a human performance company that he has built into one of the fastest growing companies in the world.    </p>
<p>                              How can we get the most out of our body and mind on a daily basis? Want to change your life for the better?    </p>
<p>                              Aubrey Marcus answers these questions in this handbook that guides the reader to optimise each moment of the day. With small, actionable changes implemented throughout the course of one day we can feel better, perform more efficiently and live happier. And these habits turn into weekly routines, ultimately becoming part of a lifelong healthy choice.    </p>
<p>                              From workouts and diet to inbox triage, mindfulness, shower temperature and sex this groundbreaking manual provides strategies for each element of your day. Drawing on the latest studies and traditional practices from around the world, this book delivers cutting-edge life hacks, nutritional expertise, brain upgrades and fitness regimes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/">Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Code of the Extraordinary Mind : 10 Unconventional Laws to Redefine Your Life and Succeed on Your Own Terms &#8211; Vishen Lakhiani (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-code-of-the-extraordinary-mind-10-unconventional-laws-to-redefine-your-life-and-succeed-on-your-own-terms-vishen-lakhiani-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-code-of-the-extraordinary-mind-10-unconventional-laws-to-redefine-your-life-and-succeed-on-your-own-terms-vishen-lakhiani-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; What if everything we think we know about how the world works&#8211;our ideas of love, education, spirituality, work, happiness, and love&#8211;are based on Brules (bullsh*t rules) that get passed from generation to generation and are long past their expiration date? This book teaches you to think like some of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-of-the-extraordinary-mind-10-unconventional-laws-to-redefine-your-life-and-succeed-on-your-own-terms-vishen-lakhiani-abridged/">The Code of the Extraordinary Mind : 10 Unconventional Laws to Redefine Your Life and Succeed on Your Own Terms &#8211; Vishen Lakhiani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; What if everything we think we know about how the world works&#8211;our ideas of love, education, spirituality, work, happiness, and love&#8211;are based on Brules (bullsh*t rules) that get passed from generation to generation and are long past their expiration date?     </p>
<p>                    This book teaches you to think like some of the greatest non-conformist minds of our era, to question, challenge, hack, and create new rules for YOUR life so you can define success on your own terms.     </p>
<p>                    The Code of the Extraordinary Mind is a blueprint of laws to break us free from the shackles of an ordinary life. It makes a case that everything we know about the world is shaped by conditioning and habit. And thus, most people live their lives based on limiting rules and outdated beliefs about pretty much everything&#8211;love, work, money, parenting, sex, health, and more&#8211;which they inherit and pass on from generation to generation.     </p>
<p>                    But what if you could remove these outdated ideas and start anew? What would your life look like if you could forget the rules of the past, and redefine what happiness, purpose, and success mean for you?     </p>
<p>                    Not Just a Book, but a Movement<br />
                    Blending computational thinking, integral theory, modern spirituality, evolutionary biology, and humor, personal growth entrepreneur Vishen Lakhiani provides a revolutionary 10-point framework for understanding and enhancing the human self. You will learn about bending reality. You will learn how to apply unique models like consciousness engineering to help you learn and grow at speeds like never before.You will learn to make a dent in the universe and discover your quest. This framework is based on Lakhiani&#8217;s personal experiences, the 5 million people he&#8217;s reached through Mindvalley, and 200 hours of interviews and questions posed to incredible minds, including Elon Musk, Richard Branson, Peter Diamandis, Ken Wilber, Dean Kamen, Arianna Huffington, Michael Beckwith, and other legendary leaders.     </p>
<p>                    In a unique fusion of cutting-edge ideas, personal stories, irreverence, and a brilliant teaching style, Lakhiani reveals the 10 powerful laws that form a step-by-step process that you can apply to life to shed years of struggle and elevate yourself to exceptional new heights.     </p>
<p>                    The 10 Laws to an Extraordinary Life<br />
                    This book challenges conventional ideas of relationships, goal-setting, mindfulness, happiness, and meaning. In a unique fusion of cutting-edge ideas, personal stories, and humorous irreverence, and not to mention, humor and napkin diagrams,  this framework combines computational thinking with personal growth to provide a powerful framework for re-coding yourself&#8211;and replacing old, limiting models that hold you back with new, empowering beliefs and behaviors that set you on the path toward an extraordinary life. A life of more happiness and achievement than you might have dared to dream possible.     </p>
<p>                    Once you discover the code, you will question your limits and realize that there are none. Step into a new understanding of the world around you and your place in it, and find yourself operating at a new, extraordinary level in every way&#8230;happiness, purpose, fulfilment, and love.     </p>
<p>                    This Book Is a Living, Breathing Manifesto That Goes Beyond a Traditional Publication<br />
                    For those who want more, The Code of the Extraordinary Mind connects to a full on immersive experience including ways for you to dive into particular chapters to unlock additional videos or training and connect with each other and the author to learn via peer-to-peer learning networks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-of-the-extraordinary-mind-10-unconventional-laws-to-redefine-your-life-and-succeed-on-your-own-terms-vishen-lakhiani-abridged/">The Code of the Extraordinary Mind : 10 Unconventional Laws to Redefine Your Life and Succeed on Your Own Terms &#8211; Vishen Lakhiani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Loving What Is : Four Questions That Can Change Your Life &#8211; Byron Katie, Stephen Mitchell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/loving-what-is-four-questions-that-can-change-your-life-byron-katie-stephen-mitchell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/loving-what-is-four-questions-that-can-change-your-life-byron-katie-stephen-mitchell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bryon Katie found herself at a complete dead end in her life, she felt increasingly depressed and over a ten-year period had sunk into an existence of depression, despair and rage. Then one morning she woke up in a state of absolute joy, filled with the freedom of knowing her suffering had ended. Determined to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/loving-what-is-four-questions-that-can-change-your-life-byron-katie-stephen-mitchell-abridged/">Loving What Is : Four Questions That Can Change Your Life &#8211; Byron Katie, Stephen Mitchell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bryon Katie found herself at a complete dead end in her life, she felt increasingly depressed and over a ten-year period had sunk into an existence of depression, despair and rage. Then one morning she woke up in a state of absolute joy, filled with the freedom of knowing her suffering had ended.     </p>
<p>                    Determined to give people a way to discover for themselves what she had experienced, Katie has developed a simple method of self-enquiry that she calls The Work, four simple questions that allow you to see the problems that are troubling you in a whole new light. The Work is a life-transforming system for discarding the stories we tell ourselves, which are the source of our suffering, and replacing them with the truth and a life of joy and peace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/loving-what-is-four-questions-that-can-change-your-life-byron-katie-stephen-mitchell-abridged/">Loving What Is : Four Questions That Can Change Your Life &#8211; Byron Katie, Stephen Mitchell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crafts & Hobbies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge &#8211; over one million copies sold** Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge  &#8211; over one million copies sold**    </p>
<p>                    Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness    </p>
<p>                    Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. In The Little Book of Lykke, he reveals what he has found.    </p>
<p>                    This captivating read features case studies from Bhutan to Australia, South Korea to Canada, France to Denmark, taking the reader on a happiness treasure hunt. Written in the same warm tone as Meik&#8217;s phenomenal bestseller The Little Book of Hygge, this easy-to-understand book will change the way you think about how you relate to your neighbours, the rituals around cooking and eating dinner, and when to book your next holiday &#8211; and is guaranteed to put a smile on your face.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is a happy book about happiness, written with a twinkle and packaged with Danish style&#8217; (John Helliwell, Economist and Editor of the World Happiness Report)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Thinking : Upgrade Your Reasoning and Make Better Decisions with Mental Models &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Lauren McCann (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An invaluable resource for making sense of the world, making good decisions, and placing smart bets. A fast-paced and fun read jam-packed with useful information on every page.&#8217; Annie Duke, author of Thinking in Bets ________________ Turn yourself into a superthinker and make the right decisions every time. You want to make better decisions. You [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/">Super Thinking : Upgrade Your Reasoning and Make Better Decisions with Mental Models &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Lauren McCann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An invaluable resource for making sense of the world, making good decisions, and placing smart bets. A fast-paced and fun read jam-packed with useful information on every page.&#8217; Annie Duke, author of Thinking in Bets<br />
                     ________________                           </p>
<p>                     Turn yourself into a superthinker and make the right decisions every time.    </p>
<p>                     You want to make better decisions. You want to be right more of the time professionally and personally. However, being more right consistently is a hard problem because the world is such a complex, evolving place. How do you navigate this complexity?    </p>
<p>                     Mental models are decision-making tools that guide our perception of the world and our behaviour in it. They help us understand life, make decisions and solve problems. The best models help us make intelligent investments, develop ground-breaking technologies and even travel to outer space.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Note your frame of reference before debating someone with different political views. If you understand how your perspective contrasts with someone else&#8217;s you can prevent the conversation from getting hostile.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Apply the sunk cost fallacy to the end of a doomed project. Just because you&#8217;ve put a lot of hours into it doesn&#8217;t mean that you have to keep going.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Before blaming someone, consider Hanlon&#8217;s Razor, &#8216;Never attribute to malice that which is adequately explained by carelessness&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Try to solve mysteries with Occam&#8217;s Razor, &#8216;Among competing hypotheses, the one with the fewest assumptions should be selected&#8217;. When you hear hoof beats, think of horses not zebras.    </p>
<p>                     Building on our knowledge of well-known models such as the Bandwagon Effect or Paradigm Shift and introducing us to the lesser known like the Eisenhower Matrix or the Boiling Frog Symbol, this indispensable book distils the most effective mental models into a single, digestible volume. It will make even the most complex models accessible and engaging to enable you to make better, more informed decisions in every part of your life.<br />
                     ________________    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Internalizing these mental models will help you understand the world around you. Once you can spot them, you can change your own behavior to avoid common traps, adjust how you interact with people to get better results, and maybe even articulate new mental models of the world that have yet to be discovered.&#8217; Brian Armstrong, co-founder and CEO, Coinbase    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;You can&#8217;t really know anything if you just remember isolated facts. If the facts don&#8217;t hang together on a latticework of theory, you don&#8217;t have them in a usable form. You&#8217;ve got to have models in your head.&#8217; Charlie Munger, vice chairman, Berkshire Hathaway</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/">Super Thinking : Upgrade Your Reasoning and Make Better Decisions with Mental Models &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Lauren McCann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>As a Man Thinketh &#8211; James Allen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/as-a-man-thinketh-james-allen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/as-a-man-thinketh-james-allen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Allen combines personal experience with meditation to probe the power of thought and the processes by which man perceives truth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/as-a-man-thinketh-james-allen-abridged/">As a Man Thinketh &#8211; James Allen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Allen combines personal experience with meditation to probe the power of thought and the processes by which man perceives truth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/as-a-man-thinketh-james-allen-abridged/">As a Man Thinketh &#8211; James Allen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Free-Time Formula : Finding Happiness, Focus, and Productivity No Matter How Busy You Are &#8211; Jeff Sanders (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-free-time-formula-finding-happiness-focus-and-productivity-no-matter-how-busy-you-are-jeff-sanders-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-free-time-formula-finding-happiness-focus-and-productivity-no-matter-how-busy-you-are-jeff-sanders-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Find the time, clarity, and mental space to achieve your goals The Free-Time Formula helps you slow down time and get the important things done. We&#8217;re all overworked, stressed, and always being asked to do more, and do it better; the days aren&#8217;t getting any longer, so something has to give-don&#8217;t let it be your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-free-time-formula-finding-happiness-focus-and-productivity-no-matter-how-busy-you-are-jeff-sanders-abridged/">The Free-Time Formula : Finding Happiness, Focus, and Productivity No Matter How Busy You Are &#8211; Jeff Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Find the time, clarity, and mental space to achieve your goals The Free-Time Formula helps you slow down time and get the important things done. We&#8217;re all overworked, stressed, and always being asked to do more, and do it better; the days aren&#8217;t getting any longer, so something has to give-don&#8217;t let it be your sanity. This book provides a real-world framework for more effective time management that helps you prioritize, focus, clarify, and go. You&#8217;ll begin with a time audit to assess your current stress, strategies, and output-and the results may shock you. From there, you&#8217;ll work step-by-step toward a new daily routine that will help you become the focused, efficient achiever you&#8217;ve been trying to be for so long. It&#8217;s not about cramming more into your precious 24 hours, it&#8217;s about figuring out what really matters to you, and getting the most important things done first. Every day. Never miss another big deadline, never flake on an important meeting, never be late to an appointment again. It is possible with great planning, and this book is your personal guide.     </p>
<p>                    Focused on action, not filler, this book is an excellent resource for those who want to achieve more, but do less. With a few simple changes, you&#8217;ll find the time you&#8217;ve been missing and put it to more productive use.     </p>
<p>                    Define and prioritize your personal and professional goals and responsibilities<br />
                    Cut the distractions and clarify your daily objectives<br />
                    Adapt your workplace tools and environment to facilitate actual work<br />
                    Periodically self-assess, course-correct when needed, and plan for the future    </p>
<p>                     Rather than rush through another day leaving things un-done and roses un-sniffed, take a beat and a breath, and take back your day with The Free-Time Formula.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-free-time-formula-finding-happiness-focus-and-productivity-no-matter-how-busy-you-are-jeff-sanders-abridged/">The Free-Time Formula : Finding Happiness, Focus, and Productivity No Matter How Busy You Are &#8211; Jeff Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Change Your Thoughts &#8211; Change Your Life : Living the Wisdom of the Tao &#8211; Dr. Wayne W. Dyer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/change-your-thoughts-change-your-life-living-the-wisdom-of-the-tao-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chakras, Auras & Spiritual Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taoism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/change-your-thoughts-change-your-life-living-the-wisdom-of-the-tao-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Five hundred years before the birth of Jesus, a God-realized being named Lao-tzu in ancient China dictated 81 verses, which are regarded by many as the ultimate commentary on the nature of our existence. The classic text of these 81 verses, called the Tao Te Ching or the Great Way, offers advice and guidance that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/change-your-thoughts-change-your-life-living-the-wisdom-of-the-tao-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/">Change Your Thoughts &#8211; Change Your Life : Living the Wisdom of the Tao &#8211; Dr. Wayne W. Dyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Five hundred years before the birth of Jesus, a God-realized being named Lao-tzu in ancient China dictated 81 verses, which are regarded by many as the ultimate commentary on the nature of our existence. The classic text of these 81 verses, called the Tao Te Ching or the Great Way, offers advice and guidance that is balanced, moral, spiritual, and always concerned with working for the good. In this book, Dr. Wayne W. Dyer has reviewed hundreds of translations of the Tao Te Ching and has written 81 distinct essays on how to apply the ancient wisdom of Lao-tzu to today&#8217;s modern world. This work contains the entire 81 verses of the Tao, compiled from Wayne&#8217;s researching of 10 of the most well-respected translations of text that have survived for more than 25 centuries. Each chapter is designed for actually living the Tao or the Great Way today. Some of the chapter titles are &#8216;Living with Flexibility,&#8217; &#8216;Living Without Enemies,&#8217; and &#8216;Living by Letting Go.&#8217; Each of the 81 brief chapters focuses on living the Tao and concludes with a section called &#8216;Doing the Tao Now.&#8217;<br />
                    Wayne spent one entire year reading, researching, and meditating on Lao-tzu&#8217;s messages, practicing them each day and ultimately writing down these essays as he felt Lao-tzu wanted you to know them. This is a work to be read slowly, one essay a day. As Wayne says, &#8216;This is a book that will forever change the way you look at your life, and the result will be that you&#8217;ll live in a new world aligned with nature. Writing this book changed me forever, too. I now live in accord with the natural world and feel the greatest sense of peace I&#8217;ve ever experienced. I&#8217;m so proud to present this interpretation of the Tao Te Ching, and offer the same opportunity for change that it has brought me.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/change-your-thoughts-change-your-life-living-the-wisdom-of-the-tao-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/">Change Your Thoughts &#8211; Change Your Life : Living the Wisdom of the Tao &#8211; Dr. Wayne W. Dyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Keep Going : 10 Ways to Stay Creative in Good Times and Bad &#8211; Austin Kleon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/keep-going-10-ways-to-stay-creative-in-good-times-and-bad-austin-kleon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/keep-going-10-ways-to-stay-creative-in-good-times-and-bad-austin-kleon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The world is crazy. Creative work is hard. And nothing is getting any easier! In his previous books &#8211; Steal Like an Artistand Show Your Work!, New York Times bestsellers with over a million copies in print combined &#8211; Austin Kleon gave readers the key to unlock their creativity and then showed them how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/keep-going-10-ways-to-stay-creative-in-good-times-and-bad-austin-kleon-abridged/">Keep Going : 10 Ways to Stay Creative in Good Times and Bad &#8211; Austin Kleon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world is crazy. Creative work is hard. And nothing is getting any easier!    </p>
<p>                    In his previous books &#8211; Steal Like an Artistand Show Your Work!, New York Times bestsellers with over a million copies in print combined &#8211; Austin Kleon gave readers the key to unlock their creativity and then showed them how to share it. Now he completes his trilogy with his most inspiring work yet.    </p>
<p>                    Keep Going gives the reader life-changing, illustrated advice and encouragement on how to stay creative, focused, and true to yourself in the face of personal burnout or external distractions. Here is how to Build a Bliss Station &#8211; a place or fixed period where you can disconnect from the world. How to see that Every Day Is Groundhog Day &#8211; yesterday&#8217;s over, tomorrow may never come, so just do what you can do today. How to Forget the Noun, Do the Verb &#8211; stop worrying about being a &#8220;painter&#8221; and just paint.    </p>
<p>                    Keep working. Keep playing. Keep searching. Keep giving. Keep living. Keep Going. It&#8217;s exactly the message all of us need, at exactly the right time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/keep-going-10-ways-to-stay-creative-in-good-times-and-bad-austin-kleon-abridged/">Keep Going : 10 Ways to Stay Creative in Good Times and Bad &#8211; Austin Kleon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the revolutionary science behind the power of thought, this book will forever change how you think about your own thinking. This new updated and expanded 10th anniversary edition of The Biology of Belief contains stunning new scientific discoveries about the biochemical effects of the brain&#8217;s functioning that show all the cells of your body [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/">The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the revolutionary science behind the power of thought, this book will forever change how you think about your own thinking.    </p>
<p>                    This new updated and expanded 10th anniversary edition of The Biology of Belief contains stunning new scientific discoveries about the biochemical effects of the brain&#8217;s functioning that show all the cells of your body are affected by your thoughts. Bruce H. Lipton PhD, a renowned cell biologist, describes the precise molecular pathways through which this occurs. Using simple language, illustrations, humour and everyday examples, he demonstrates how the new science of epigenetics is revolutionizing our understanding of the link between mind and matter, and the profound effects it has on our personal lives and the collective life of our species.    </p>
<p>                    It has been 10 years since the publication of The Biology of Belief, Bruce Lipton&#8217;s seminal book on the relationship between mind and body that changed the way we think about our lives, our health and our planet. During that time, research in this field has grown exponentially &#8211; Lipton&#8217;s ground-breaking experiments have now been endorsed by more than a decade of rigorous scientific study.    </p>
<p>                    In this greatly expanded edition, Lipton explores his own experiments and those of other leading-edge scientists that have unravelled in ever greater detail how truly connected the mind, body and spirit are. It is now widely recognized that genes and DNA do not control our biology. Instead, they are controlled by signals from outside the cell, including energetic messages emanating from our thoughts.    </p>
<p>                    This profoundly hopeful synthesis of the latest and best research in cell biology and quantum physics puts the power to create a healthy, joyous life back in our own hands. When we transform our conscious and subconscious thoughts, we transform our lives, and in the process help humanity evolve to a new level of understanding and peace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/">The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Success Principles : How to Get from Where You Are to Where You Want to Be &#8211; Jack Canfield, Janet Switzer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-success-principles-how-to-get-from-where-you-are-to-where-you-want-to-be-jack-canfield-janet-switzer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-success-principles-how-to-get-from-where-you-are-to-where-you-want-to-be-jack-canfield-janet-switzer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In celebration of its 10th anniversary, a revised and updated edition of Jack Canfield&#8217;s classic bestseller with a brand new foreword and an afterword for succeeding in the digital age. Since its publication a decade ago, Jack Canfield&#8217;s practical and inspiring guide has helped thousands of people transform themselves for success. Now, he has revised [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-success-principles-how-to-get-from-where-you-are-to-where-you-want-to-be-jack-canfield-janet-switzer-abridged/">The Success Principles : How to Get from Where You Are to Where You Want to Be &#8211; Jack Canfield, Janet Switzer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In celebration of its 10th anniversary, a revised and updated edition of Jack Canfield&#8217;s classic bestseller with a brand new foreword and an afterword for succeeding in the digital age.    </p>
<p>                    Since its publication a decade ago, Jack Canfield&#8217;s practical and inspiring guide has helped thousands of people transform themselves for success. Now, he has revised and updated his essential guidebook to reflect our changing times.    </p>
<p>                    In The Success Principles, the cocreator of the phenomenal bestselling Chicken Soup for the Soul series, helps you get from where you are to where you want to be, teaching you how to increase your confidence, tackle daily challenges, live with passion and purpose, and realize all your ambitions. Filled with memorable and inspiring stories of CEO&#8217;s, world-class athletes, celebrities, and everyday people, it spells out the 64 timeless principles used by successful men and women throughout history&#8211;proven principles and strategies that can be adapted for your own life, whether you want to be the best salesperson in your company, become a leading architect, score top grades in school, lose weight, buy your dream home, make millions, or just get back in the job market.    </p>
<p>                    Taken together and practiced every day, these principles will change your life beyond your wildest dreams.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-success-principles-how-to-get-from-where-you-are-to-where-you-want-to-be-jack-canfield-janet-switzer-abridged/">The Success Principles : How to Get from Where You Are to Where You Want to Be &#8211; Jack Canfield, Janet Switzer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metahuman : Unleashing your infinite potential &#8211; Dr Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/metahuman-unleashing-your-infinite-potential-dr-deepak-chopra-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spiritualism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/metahuman-unleashing-your-infinite-potential-dr-deepak-chopra-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to venture beyond daily living and experience heightened states of awareness? In this highly anticipated new book, integrative medicine pioneer and New York Times bestselling author Deepak Chopra states that a higher state of consciousness is available here and now, for us all. Chopra unlocks the secrets to moving beyond our present [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/metahuman-unleashing-your-infinite-potential-dr-deepak-chopra-abridged/">Metahuman : Unleashing your infinite potential &#8211; Dr Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to venture beyond daily living and experience heightened states of awareness?     </p>
<p>                    In this highly anticipated new book, integrative medicine pioneer and New York Times bestselling author Deepak Chopra states that a higher state of consciousness is available here and now, for us all. Chopra unlocks the secrets to moving beyond our present limitations of the mind to access a field of infinite possibilities and reach our full potential. How do you achieve this? By becoming metahuman.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing from the latest research on neuroscience, artificial intelligence and biometrics, Chopra offers a practical 31 day guide to help us &#8216;wake up&#8217; at the deepest level in order to liberate ourselves from the conditioning and constructs that underlie anxiety, tension and ego driven demands. Only then does your infinite potential become your personal reality.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Grasping this revolutionary idea will effectively remove the limiting belief systems and negativity that may be holding us back from achieving our maximum human potential. Highly recommended!&#8221; Dr Rudolph E. Tanzi    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Metahuman helps us harvest peak experiences so we can see our Truth and mold the universe&#8217;s chaos into a form that brings light to the world&#8217; Dr Mehmet Oz</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/metahuman-unleashing-your-infinite-potential-dr-deepak-chopra-abridged/">Metahuman : Unleashing your infinite potential &#8211; Dr Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>LIFE-CHANGING&#8217; CAROLINE HINNES Learn to harness the strength of mindfulness and positivity to change your life with Eckhart Tolle THE BOOK THAT INSPIRED THE CHART-TOPPING PODCAST OPRAH &#038; ECKHART TOLLE: A NEW EARTH ____________ Are you ready to change your life? In Eckhart Tolle&#8217;s ground-breaking book, he gives you the spiritual framework to: &#8211; Understand [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/">A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LIFE-CHANGING&#8217; CAROLINE HINNES    </p>
<p>                    Learn to harness the strength of mindfulness and positivity to change your life with Eckhart Tolle    </p>
<p>                    THE BOOK THAT INSPIRED THE CHART-TOPPING PODCAST OPRAH &#038; ECKHART TOLLE: A NEW EARTH<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    Are you ready to change your life?    </p>
<p>                    In Eckhart Tolle&#8217;s ground-breaking book, he gives you the spiritual framework to:<br />
                    &#8211; Understand yourself better<br />
                    &#8211; Manage, manifest and achieve your goals<br />
                    &#8211; Reach your full potential<br />
                    &#8211; Channel conflict into something positive<br />
                    &#8211; Change negative habits<br />
                    &#8211; Live in the moment    </p>
<p>                    Open your mind and follow Tolle&#8217;s guidance to happiness and health in the modern world.<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wake up call for the entire planet. A New Earth helps us to stop creating our own suffering and obsessing over the past and what the future might be and to put ourselves in the now&#8217; Oprah Winfrey    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My No. 1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans, Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;m gonna have to listen to [this podcast] several times! Too good!&#8217; Fearne Cotton on the &#8216;Oprah and Eckhart Tolle: A New Earth&#8217; podcast    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book changed my life. It&#8217;s a brilliant and very practical spiritual guide that teaches the way to inner peace: how to live in the moment and get beyond the ego&#8217; Santa Montefiore, bestselling author of The Secret Hours</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/">A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thoughts Without A Thinker : Psychotherapy from a Buddhist Perspective &#8211; Mark Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The line between psychology and spirituality has blurred, as clinicians, their patients, and religious seekers explore new perspectives on the self. A landmark contribution to the field of psychoanalysis, Thoughts Without a Thinker describes the unique psychological contributions offered by the teachings of Buddhism. Drawing upon his own experiences as a psychotherapist and meditator, New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/">Thoughts Without A Thinker : Psychotherapy from a Buddhist Perspective &#8211; Mark Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The line between psychology and spirituality has blurred, as clinicians, their patients, and religious seekers explore new perspectives on the self. A landmark contribution to the field of psychoanalysis,  Thoughts Without a Thinker  describes the unique psychological contributions offered by the teachings of Buddhism. Drawing upon his own experiences as a psychotherapist and meditator, New York-based psychiatrist Mark Epstein lays out the path to meditation-inspired healing, and offers a revolutionary new understanding of what constitutes a healthy emotional life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/">Thoughts Without A Thinker : Psychotherapy from a Buddhist Perspective &#8211; Mark Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book of Joy. The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Dalai Lama, Desmond Tutu (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-book-of-joy-the-sunday-times-bestseller-dalai-lama-desmond-tutu-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Leaders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tibetan Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-of-joy-the-sunday-times-bestseller-dalai-lama-desmond-tutu-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two spiritual giants. Seven days. One timeless question. &#8216;The ultimate source of happiness is within us.&#8217; DALAI LAMA &#8216;We grow in kindness when our kindness is tested.&#8217; DESMOND TUTU Archbishop Desmond Tutu and the Dalai Lama have been friends for many, many years. Between them, they have endured exile, violence and oppression. And in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-joy-the-sunday-times-bestseller-dalai-lama-desmond-tutu-abridged/">The Book of Joy. The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Dalai Lama, Desmond Tutu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two spiritual giants. Seven days. One timeless question.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The ultimate source of happiness is within us.&#8217; DALAI LAMA    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We grow in kindness when our kindness is tested.&#8217; DESMOND TUTU    </p>
<p>                    Archbishop Desmond Tutu and the Dalai Lama have been friends for many, many years. Between them, they have endured exile, violence and oppression. And in the face of these hardships, they have continued to radiate compassion, humour and above all, joy.    </p>
<p>                    To celebrate His Holiness&#8217;s eightieth birthday, Archbishop Tutu travelled to the Dalai Lama&#8217;s home in Dharamsala. The two men spent a week discussing a single burning question: how do we find joy in the face of suffering?    </p>
<p>                    This book is a gift from two of the most important spiritual figures of our time. Full of love, warmth and hope, The Book of Joy offers us the chance to experience their journey from first embrace to final goodbye.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-joy-the-sunday-times-bestseller-dalai-lama-desmond-tutu-abridged/">The Book of Joy. The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Dalai Lama, Desmond Tutu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Men]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone needs to love and be loved-even men. But to know love, men must be able to look at the ways that patriarchal culture keeps them from knowing themselves, from being in touch with their feelings, from loving. In The Will to Change, bell hooks gets to the heart of the matter and shows men [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/">The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone needs to love and be loved-even men. But to know love, men must be able to look at the ways that patriarchal culture keeps them from knowing themselves, from being in touch with their feelings, from loving.    </p>
<p>                    In The Will to Change, bell hooks gets to the heart of the matter and shows men how to express the emotions that are a fundamental part of who they are-whatever their age, marital status, ethnicity, or sexual orientation. But toxic masculinity punishes those fundamental emotions, and it&#8217;s so deeply ingrained in our society that it&#8217;s hard for men to not comply-but hooks wants to help change that.    </p>
<p>                    With trademark candor and fierce intelligence, hooks addresses the most common concerns of men, such as fear of intimacy and loss of their patriarchal place in society, in new and challenging ways. She believes men can find the way to spiritual unity by getting back in touch with the emotionally open part of themselves-and lay claim to the rich and rewarding inner lives that have historically been the exclusive province of women. A brave and astonishing work, The Will to Change is designed to help men reclaim the best part of themselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/">The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Surrender Experiment : My Journey into Life&#8217;s Perfection &#8211; Michael A. Singer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-surrender-experiment-my-journey-into-lifes-perfection-michael-a-singer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-surrender-experiment-my-journey-into-lifes-perfection-michael-a-singer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael A. Singer, author of The Untethered Soul, tells the extraordinary story of what happened when, after a deep spiritual awakening, he decided to let go of his personal preferences and simply let life call the shots. As Singer takes you on this great experiment and journey into life&#8217;s perfection, the events that transpire will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-surrender-experiment-my-journey-into-lifes-perfection-michael-a-singer-abridged/">The Surrender Experiment : My Journey into Life&#8217;s Perfection &#8211; Michael A. Singer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael A. Singer, author of The Untethered Soul, tells the extraordinary story of what happened when, after a deep spiritual awakening, he decided to let go of his personal preferences and simply let life call the shots. As Singer takes you on this great experiment and journey into life&#8217;s perfection, the events that transpire will both challenge your deepest assumptions about life and inspire you to look at your own life in a radically different way.    </p>
<p>                    Spirituality is meant to bring about harmony and peace. But the diversity of our philosophies, beliefs, concepts, and views about the soul often leads to confusion. To reconcile the noise that clouds spirituality, Michael Singer combines accounts of his own life journey to enlightenment &#8211; from his years as a hippie-loner to his success as a computer program engineer to his work in spiritual and humanitarian efforts &#8211; with lessons on how to put aside conflicting beliefs, let go of worries, and transform misdirected desires. Singer provides a road map to a new way of living not in the moment, but to exist in a state of perpetual happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-surrender-experiment-my-journey-into-lifes-perfection-michael-a-singer-abridged/">The Surrender Experiment : My Journey into Life&#8217;s Perfection &#8211; Michael A. Singer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics & Communications Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phones: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as you idly scroll through your social media timeline? In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the  last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as  you idly scroll through your social media timeline?     </p>
<p>                     In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone is here to help.     </p>
<p>                     How to Break Up With Your Phone  is a smart, practical and useful plan to help you conquer your mobile  phone addiction in just 30 days &#8211; and take back your life in the  process.     </p>
<p>                    Recent studies have shown that spending extended time  on our phones affects our ability to form new memories, think deeply,  focus and absorb information, and the hormones triggered every time we  hear our phones buzz both add to our stress levels and are the hallmark  signs of addiction. In How to Break Up with Your Phone,  award-winning science journalist Catherine Price explores the effects  that our constant connectivity is having on our brains, bodies,  relationships, and society at large and asks, how much time do you really want to spend on your phone?     </p>
<p>                    Over  the course of 30 days, Catherine will guide you through an  easy-to-follow plan that enables you to identify your goals, priorities  and bad habits, tidy your apps, prune your email, and take time away.  Lastly, you will create a new, healthier relationship with your phone  and establish habits and routines to ensure this new relationship  sticks.     </p>
<p>                    You don&#8217;t have to give up your phone forever; instead  you will be more mindful not only of how you use your phone, but also  about how you choose to spend the precious moments of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Science of Getting Rich : Attracting Financial Success through Creative Thought &#8211; Wallace D. Wattles (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-science-of-getting-rich-attracting-financial-success-through-creative-thought-wallace-d-wattles-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-science-of-getting-rich-attracting-financial-success-through-creative-thought-wallace-d-wattles-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his bestselling book, Wallace D. Wattles explains that &#8220;universal mind&#8221; underlies and permeates all creation. Through the process of visualization we can engage the law of attraction&#8211;impressing our thoughts upon &#8220;formless substance&#8221; and bringing the desired object or circumstances into material form. The author emphasizes the critical importance of attitude: only by aligning ourselves [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-getting-rich-attracting-financial-success-through-creative-thought-wallace-d-wattles-abridged/">The Science of Getting Rich : Attracting Financial Success through Creative Thought &#8211; Wallace D. Wattles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his bestselling book, Wallace D. Wattles explains that &#8220;universal mind&#8221; underlies and permeates all creation. Through the process of visualization we can engage the law of attraction&#8211;impressing our thoughts upon &#8220;formless substance&#8221; and bringing the desired object or circumstances into material form. The author emphasizes the critical importance of attitude: only by aligning ourselves with the positive forces of natural law can we gain unlimited access to the creative mind and its abundant rewards. The Science of Getting Richholds the secret to how economic and emotional security can be achieved in a practical, imaginative, and noncompetitive way, while maintaining a loving and harmonious relationship with all of life. By living in accordance with the positive principles outlined in this book, we can find our rightful place in the cosmic scheme and create for ourselves an environment in which to grow in wealth, wisdom, and happiness. Rhonda Byrne, in her book and DVD, The Secret, tells how a 100-year-old book entered her life and changed it forever. Here is that book. Written in 1910, The Science of Getting Richinspired Byrne to create her bestselling DVD, and subsequently, to write her book. She has said that it &#8220;gave me a glimpse of The Secret. It was like a flame inside of my heart. And with every day since, it&#8217;s just become a raging fire of wanting to share all of this with the world.&#8221; &#8220;There is a science of getting rich. It is an exact science, like algebra or arithmetic. There are certain laws which govern the process of acquiring riches. Once a person learns and obeys these laws, he will get rich with mathematical certainty.&#8221; &#8211;Wallace D. Wattles, The Science of Getting Rich</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-getting-rich-attracting-financial-success-through-creative-thought-wallace-d-wattles-abridged/">The Science of Getting Rich : Attracting Financial Success through Creative Thought &#8211; Wallace D. Wattles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who Will Cry When You Die? &#8211; Robin S. Sharma (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-will-cry-when-you-die-robin-s-sharma-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-will-cry-when-you-die-robin-s-sharma-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;When you were born, you cried while the world rejoiced. Live your life in such a way that when you die, the world cries while you rejoice.&#8221;&#8211; Ancient Sanskrit saying Does the gem of wisdom quoted above strike a chord deep within you? Do you feel that life is slipping by so fast that you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-will-cry-when-you-die-robin-s-sharma-abridged/">Who Will Cry When You Die? &#8211; Robin S. Sharma (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;When you were born, you cried while the world rejoiced. Live your life in such a way that when you die, the world cries while you rejoice.&#8221;&#8211; Ancient Sanskrit saying    </p>
<p>                    Does the gem of wisdom quoted above strike a chord deep within you? Do you feel that life is slipping by so fast that you just might never get the chance to live with the meaning, happiness and joy you know you deserve? If so, then this very special book by leadership guru Robin S. Sharma, the author whose Monk Who Sold His Ferrari series has transformed the lives of thousands, will be the guiding light that leads you to a brilliant new way of living. In this easy-to-read yet wisdom-rich manual, Robin S. Sharma offers 101 simple solutions to life&#8217;s most complex problems, ranging from a little-known method for beating stress and worry to a powerful way to enjoy the journey while you create a legacy that lasts. Other lessons include &#8220;Honor Your Past,&#8221; &#8220;Start Your Day Well,&#8221; &#8220;See Troubles as Blessings&#8221; and &#8220;Discover Your Calling.&#8221; If you are finally ready to move beyond a life spent chasing success to one of deep significance, this is the ideal book for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-will-cry-when-you-die-robin-s-sharma-abridged/">Who Will Cry When You Die? &#8211; Robin S. Sharma (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gifts Of Imperfection &#8211; Brené Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gifts-of-imperfection-brene-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gifts-of-imperfection-brene-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Brené Brown&#8217;s game-changing New York Times bestseller, The Gifts of Imperfection, has sold more than 2 million copies in more than 30 different languages and is celebrating its 10th Anniversary in print. Forbes magazine named Gifts one of the Five Books That Will Actually Change Your Outlook On Life. Through this self-help classic we find [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gifts-of-imperfection-brene-brown-abridged/">The Gifts Of Imperfection &#8211; Brené Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brené Brown&#8217;s game-changing New York Times bestseller, The Gifts of Imperfection, has sold more than 2 million copies in more than 30 different languages and is celebrating its 10th Anniversary in print. Forbes magazine named Gifts one of the Five Books That Will Actually Change Your Outlook On Life. Through this self-help classic we find courage to overcome paralyzing fear and self-consciousness, strengthening our connection to the world and helping us to believe we are worthy of self-discovery, personal growth, and boundless love.     </p>
<p>                    A motivational and inspiring guide to wholehearted living, rather than just the average self-help book, with this groundbreaking work Brené Brown, Ph.D., bolsters the self-esteem and personal development process through her characteristic heartfelt, honest storytelling. With original research and plenty of encouragement, she explores the psychology of releasing our definitions of an &#8220;imperfect&#8221; life and embracing living authentically. Brown&#8217;s &#8220;ten guideposts&#8221; are benchmarks for authenticity that can help anyone establish a practice for a life of honest beauty&#8211;a perfectly imperfect life.     </p>
<p>                     Now more than ever, we all need to cultivate feelings of self-worth, as well as acceptance and love for ourselves. In a world where insults, criticisms, and fears are spread too generously alongside messages of unrealistic beauty, attainment, and expectation, we look for ways to &#8220;dig deep&#8221; and find truth and gratitude in our lives. A new way forward means we can&#8217;t hold on too tightly to our own self-defeating thoughts or the displaced pain in our world. Instead, we can embrace the imperfection.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gifts-of-imperfection-brene-brown-abridged/">The Gifts Of Imperfection &#8211; Brené Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happiness : A Guide to Developing Life&#8217;s Most Important Skill &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Although we are materially better off than ever before, surveys show that we are depressed and listless. In his revolutionary book, Buddhist monk Matthieu Ricard shows that happiness is not just an emotion, but a skill that can be developed. Free of jargon, Happiness contains simple exercises that will train the mind to recognize and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Happiness : A Guide to Developing Life&#8217;s Most Important Skill &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although we are materially better off than ever before, surveys show that we are depressed and listless. In his revolutionary book, Buddhist monk Matthieu Ricard shows that happiness is not just an emotion, but a skill that can be developed. Free of jargon, Happiness contains simple exercises that will train the mind to recognize and pursue happiness by concentrating on the fundamental things in life, and in doing so change the way we view the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Happiness : A Guide to Developing Life&#8217;s Most Important Skill &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Willpower : The Secret Principle to Achieving Success in Life, Love, and Happiness &#8211; Alex Loyd (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-willpower-the-secret-principle-to-achieving-success-in-life-love-and-happiness-alex-loyd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-willpower-the-secret-principle-to-achieving-success-in-life-love-and-happiness-alex-loyd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new book from the bestselling author of The Healing Code about how to go from stress to success in 40 days. The revolutionary new science of Practical Spirituality designed to replace stress with well being and success, quickly and for the long term. Did you know that most self-help programmes have a 97% failure [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-willpower-the-secret-principle-to-achieving-success-in-life-love-and-happiness-alex-loyd-abridged/">Beyond Willpower : The Secret Principle to Achieving Success in Life, Love, and Happiness &#8211; Alex Loyd (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new book from the bestselling author of The Healing Code about how to go from stress to success in 40 days.     </p>
<p>                    The revolutionary new science of Practical Spirituality designed to replace stress with well being and success, quickly and for the long term.    </p>
<p>                    Did you know that most self-help programmes have a 97% failure rate? The truth is that the standard self-help mantra of  tapping into your willpower and using the power of positive thinking is actually a blueprint for failure.  In Beyond Willpower, bestselling author and psychological counsellor Alex Loyd, reveals the definitive step-by-step programme to help you finally achieve the life you want and the success you deserve.    </p>
<p>                      Science has proven that stress is the primary source of virtually any problem &#8211;  physical, spiritual, emotional, and even circumstantial.  Loyd believes that we need to understand how love works in our bodies to combat stress. By harnessing love&#8217;s power and learning to love in the present moment, you can define your life goals and live mindfully in a state of peace.<br />
                      Beyond Willpower offers a revolutionary 40-day holistic guide based on more than 25 years of clinical experience and rooted in science, ancient wisdom, and proven therapeutic techniques to remove personal obstacles that sabotage success. Using the programme you will define your goal, be it wealth, career satisfactions, healing of health issues, or resolution of relationship problems and follow the step-by step process for achieving this goal quickly and for the long term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-willpower-the-secret-principle-to-achieving-success-in-life-love-and-happiness-alex-loyd-abridged/">Beyond Willpower : The Secret Principle to Achieving Success in Life, Love, and Happiness &#8211; Alex Loyd (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Time and How to Spend It : The 7 Rules for Richer, Happier Days &#8211; James Wallman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/time-and-how-to-spend-it-the-7-rules-for-richer-happier-days-james-wallman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/time-and-how-to-spend-it-the-7-rules-for-richer-happier-days-james-wallman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times Book of the Year &#8216;Genius &#8230; I couldn&#8217;t put it down, I read it from cover to cover&#8217; CHRIS EVANS If the most precious thing we have is time, the most highly prized expertise should be knowing how to spend it well. Yet, busier than ever, do we really understand which experiences [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-and-how-to-spend-it-the-7-rules-for-richer-happier-days-james-wallman-abridged/">Time and How to Spend It : The 7 Rules for Richer, Happier Days &#8211; James Wallman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Genius &#8230; I couldn&#8217;t put it down, I read it from cover to cover&#8217;<br />
                    CHRIS EVANS    </p>
<p>                    If the most precious thing we have is time, the most highly prized expertise should be knowing how to spend it well. Yet, busier than ever, do we really understand which experiences bring us joy and success, and which don&#8217;t?    </p>
<p>                    After all, we&#8217;ve learned how to spot the difference between junk foods and superfoods. When you discover the equivalent rules for time, it&#8217;ll change how you live your life.    </p>
<p>                    In his first book since the era-defining Stuffocation, cultural commentator and bestselling author James Wallman investigates the persistent problem of wasted, unfulfilling time, and finds a powerful answer &#8211; a revolutionary approach to life based on the latest scientific discoveries. At its heart is the inspiring revelation that, when you play by the new rules, you can actively choose better experiences.    </p>
<p>                    Bursting with original stories, fresh takes on tales you thought you knew, and insights from psychology, economics, and culture, Time and How to Spend It reveals a seven-point checklist that&#8217;ll help you avoid empty experiences, and fill your free hours with exciting and enriching ones instead.    </p>
<p>                    This life-enhancing book will show you how to be the hero or heroine of your own story. You&#8217;ll learn how to avoid WMDs (weapons of mass distraction), and discover the roads that lead to flow. You&#8217;ll get more out of every minute and every day; your weekends will fizz and your holidays will be deeply nourishing. You&#8217;ll not only be living the good life, but building a truly great life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-and-how-to-spend-it-the-7-rules-for-richer-happier-days-james-wallman-abridged/">Time and How to Spend It : The 7 Rules for Richer, Happier Days &#8211; James Wallman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Real Love : The Art of Mindful Connection &#8211; Sharon Salzberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/real-love-the-art-of-mindful-connection-sharon-salzberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/real-love-the-art-of-mindful-connection-sharon-salzberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Real Love, one of the world&#8217;s leading authorities on love tells us how to find it, how to nurture it, how to honor it-and most of all how to rethink it &#8230; This book has the power to set your heart at peace.&#8217; -Susan Cain, author of Quiet What is love? Sharon Salzberg believes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/real-love-the-art-of-mindful-connection-sharon-salzberg-abridged/">Real Love : The Art of Mindful Connection &#8211; Sharon Salzberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Real Love, one of the world&#8217;s leading authorities on love tells us how to find it, how to nurture it, how to honor it-and most of all how to rethink it &#8230; This book has the power to set your heart at peace.&#8217; -Susan Cain, author of Quiet    </p>
<p>                    What is love? Sharon Salzberg believes that love is a powerful healing force for us all, and that modern associations with romance and adoration are limiting. By redefining love, she helps us to recognize our desire for happiness and enhance our connections with each other.     </p>
<p>                    Real Love is a creative toolkit of mindfulness exercises and meditation techniques that can help you to truly engage with your present experience and create deeper love relationships &#8211; with yourself, your partner, friends and family, and with life itself. The book encourages us to strip away layers of negative habits and obstacles and to improve deeper connections, helping us to experience authentic love based on direct experience, rather than preconceptions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/real-love-the-art-of-mindful-connection-sharon-salzberg-abridged/">Real Love : The Art of Mindful Connection &#8211; Sharon Salzberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presence : Bringing Your Boldest Self to Your Biggest Challenges &#8211; Amy Cuddy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/presence-bringing-your-boldest-self-to-your-biggest-challenges-amy-cuddy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/presence-bringing-your-boldest-self-to-your-biggest-challenges-amy-cuddy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Cuddy shows how your body language influences others and even changes the way you see yourself. Social scientists have shown that we make sweeping inferences and judgements based on body language, judgements that can predict meaningful life outcomes like who we hire, who we promote, who we ask out on a date, who we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presence-bringing-your-boldest-self-to-your-biggest-challenges-amy-cuddy-abridged/">Presence : Bringing Your Boldest Self to Your Biggest Challenges &#8211; Amy Cuddy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amy Cuddy shows how your body language influences others and even changes the way you see yourself. Social scientists have shown that we make sweeping inferences and judgements based on body language, judgements that can predict meaningful life outcomes like who we hire, who we promote, who we ask out on a date, who we invest in and who we trust. In PRESENCE, Amy Cuddy reveals that we have the power not only to affect how others see us but also to change how we see ourselves and even the ability to alter our own chemistry, simply by changing body positions. Cuddy&#8217;s research shows how faking body postures that convey competence and power (power posing) even for as little as two minutes changes our cortisone and testosterone levels, increases our appetite for risk, helps us perform better in job interviews and configures our brains to cope in stressful situations. If you act powerfully, you will begin to think powerfully.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presence-bringing-your-boldest-self-to-your-biggest-challenges-amy-cuddy-abridged/">Presence : Bringing Your Boldest Self to Your Biggest Challenges &#8211; Amy Cuddy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everyday Ubuntu : Living better together, the African way &#8211; Nompumelelo Mungi Ngomane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book will open your eyes, mind and heart to a way of being in the world that will make our world a better and more caring one.&#8217; ARCHBISHOP DESMOND TUTU, author of The Book of Joy Ubuntu is an ancient Southern African philosophy about how to live life well, together. It is a belief [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/">Everyday Ubuntu : Living better together, the African way &#8211; Nompumelelo Mungi Ngomane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book will open  your eyes, mind and heart to a way of being in the world that will make  our world a better and more caring one.&#8217; ARCHBISHOP DESMOND TUTU, author of The Book of Joy    </p>
<p>                    Ubuntu is an ancient Southern African philosophy about how to live life well, together. It is a belief in a universal human bond, which says: I am only because you are.     </p>
<p>                    It means that if you can see everyone as fully human, connected to  you by their humanity, you will never be able to treat others as  disposable or without worth. By embracing the philosophy of ubuntu  it&#8217;s possible to  overcome division and be stronger together in a world  where the wise build bridges and the foolish build walls.    </p>
<p>                    These  14 beautifully illustrated lessons from the Rainbow Nation are an  essential toolkit to helping us all to live better, together. In  stories, practical lessons and applications that recognise our common  humanity, our connectedness and interdependence, Everyday Ubuntu helps us to make sense of the world and our place in it.    </p>
<p>                    Exploring  ideas of kindness and forgiveness, tolerance and the power of  listening, this definitive guide offers practical tips on how we can all  benefit from embracing others and living a more fulfilling life as part  of the large family to which we all belong.<br />
                    __________    </p>
<p>                    What readers are saying about Everyday Ubuntu:    </p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;A concept we should all live by.&#8217;<br />
                    ***** &#8216;Lots of little gems to help with everyday life.&#8217;<br />
                    ***** &#8216;Must read&#8230; Very inspiring and thought-provoking.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/">Everyday Ubuntu : Living better together, the African way &#8211; Nompumelelo Mungi Ngomane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Move, Big Change : Using Microresolutions to Transform Your Life Permanently &#8211; Caroline L. Arnold (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-move-big-change-using-microresolutions-to-transform-your-life-permanently-caroline-l-arnold-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-move-big-change-using-microresolutions-to-transform-your-life-permanently-caroline-l-arnold-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Small, but smart: a Wall Street guru&#8217;s secrets to making change that sticks. &#8216;A rare self-improvement book that actually works&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Give and Take Every year, we&#8217;re determined to achieve our goals: to lose weight, save money or get a promotion. But how often do we follow them through? Science &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-move-big-change-using-microresolutions-to-transform-your-life-permanently-caroline-l-arnold-abridged/">Small Move, Big Change : Using Microresolutions to Transform Your Life Permanently &#8211; Caroline L. Arnold (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Small, but smart: a Wall Street guru&#8217;s secrets to making change that sticks.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A rare self-improvement book that actually works&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Give and Take    </p>
<p>                    Every year, we&#8217;re determined to achieve our goals: to lose weight, save money or get a promotion. But how often do we follow them through? Science &#8211; and real life &#8211; shows that this &#8216;big push&#8217; strategy is ultimately designed to fail, with our limited willpower struggling against entrenched routines and autopilot behaviours.    </p>
<p>                    In Small Move, Big Change, Wall Street technology guru, Caroline Arnold, introduces micro-resolutions: simple and deceptively effective, they reward us with instant results that have huge, lasting effects that can help you revolutionise your:    </p>
<p>                    *         Sleep<br />
                    *         Fitness<br />
                    *         Relationships<br />
                    *         Organisation<br />
                    *         Budgeting    </p>
<p>                    Packed full of real-world examples, this practical guide will help you spot the small moves that will bring the biggest change to your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-move-big-change-using-microresolutions-to-transform-your-life-permanently-caroline-l-arnold-abridged/">Small Move, Big Change : Using Microresolutions to Transform Your Life Permanently &#8211; Caroline L. Arnold (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting COMFY : Your Morning Guide to Daily Happiness &#8211; Jordan Gross (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-comfy-your-morning-guide-to-daily-happiness-jordan-gross-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-comfy-your-morning-guide-to-daily-happiness-jordan-gross-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Want to start getting a little bit better every single day, right when you wake up? Get COMFY in the morning! Get COMFY in your own skin! Get COMFY with the rest of your life! In a society based on constant external pressure to succeed, Getting COMFY is an internal method that thwarts this pressure [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-comfy-your-morning-guide-to-daily-happiness-jordan-gross-abridged/">Getting COMFY : Your Morning Guide to Daily Happiness &#8211; Jordan Gross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Want to start getting a little bit better every single day, right when you wake up?      </p>
<p>                    Get COMFY in the morning!     </p>
<p>                    Get COMFY in your own skin!     </p>
<p>                    Get COMFY with the rest of your life!     </p>
<p>                    In a society based on constant external pressure to succeed, Getting COMFY is an internal method that thwarts this pressure right when you wake up. It is a 5-step voyage that soothes the mind and energizes the body as you approach the rest of the day. We may have un-COMFY feelings with our bodies, our jobs, or our schoolwork. This has happened to me too. But the way we respond to these situations is what we can control, what ultimately leads us to the people we strive to be, and what leads us to Getting COMFY!     </p>
<p>                    Getting COMFY will:     </p>
<p>                    -Provide a variety of stories to grab your attention<br />
                    -Delve deep into my life and the lives of a few others to share how we have been impacted by the Getting COMFY mindset<br />
                    -Be short and to the point so you&#8217;re not intimidated by a 300-page novel<br />
                    -Offer lists and examples of ideas and recommendations to implement into your routines, starting now<br />
                    -Create challenges for you to attempt and share with friends     </p>
<p>                    Getting COMFY is all about you. So get up, get ready, and Get COMFY!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-comfy-your-morning-guide-to-daily-happiness-jordan-gross-abridged/">Getting COMFY : Your Morning Guide to Daily Happiness &#8211; Jordan Gross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Make a new start in 2022 with positive daily habits for a healthy mind, from the incredible No. 1 New York Times bestseller THE INCREDIBLE NO. 1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;SUPERB, SMART, AND SUCCINCT&#8217; FORBES ______ Struggling to find structure? Finding yourself lacking motivation? Start by making your bed. Maintaining routine and structure is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Make a new start in 2022 with positive daily habits for a healthy mind, from the incredible No. 1 New York Times bestseller    </p>
<p>                    THE INCREDIBLE NO. 1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;SUPERB, SMART, AND SUCCINCT&#8217; FORBES<br />
                    ______    </p>
<p>                    Struggling to find structure? Finding yourself lacking motivation?    </p>
<p>                    Start by making your bed.    </p>
<p>                    Maintaining routine and structure is more important than ever in the age of home working, flexi-time and the general chaos of life.    </p>
<p>                    In Make Your Bed, Admiral William H. McRaven shares 10 life lessons he learned during his Navy Seal training that helped him overcome challenges not only in his long Naval career, but also throughout his life.    </p>
<p>                    He will teach you how to . . .<br />
                    * Master the essential daily habits for staying grounded<br />
                    * Learn how to keep your mind calm and ready for the day ahead<br />
                    * Find solace and companionship in the people around you<br />
                    * Cope with setbacks and keep moving forward<br />
                    * Stray beyond your comfort zone and take risks    </p>
<p>                    Written with great humility and optimism, this timeless book provides simple and universal wisdom, practical advice, and words of encouragement that will inspire every reader.<br />
                    ______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book to inspire your children and grandchildren to become everything that they can&#8217; The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You&#8217;ll See It When You Believe It &#8211; Dr Wayne W Dyer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/youll-see-it-when-you-believe-it-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/youll-see-it-when-you-believe-it-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our thoughts are a magic part of us, and they carry us to places that have no boundaries, and no limitations&#8217; In this bestselling thought-provoking book, Dr. Wayne Dyer stretches beyond self-help to self-realisation. To do so, he embarks on a journey to activate our minds and shows us how to transform our lives by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youll-see-it-when-you-believe-it-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/">You&#8217;ll See It When You Believe It &#8211; Dr Wayne W Dyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our thoughts are a magic part of us, and they carry us to places that have no boundaries, and no limitations&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    In this bestselling thought-provoking book, Dr. Wayne Dyer stretches beyond self-help to self-realisation. To do so, he embarks on a journey to activate our minds and shows us how to transform our lives by using our thoughts constructively: in other words, how to focus on a belief and see it.     </p>
<p>                    Using anecdotes and examples, writing with wit and compassion, and drawing on his own amazing life story, Dr. Dyer has, once again, written an inspirational self-help book that explores how to achieve personal transformation through the visualisation of thought- and teaches us that believing is seeing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youll-see-it-when-you-believe-it-dr-wayne-w-dyer-abridged/">You&#8217;ll See It When You Believe It &#8211; Dr Wayne W Dyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Welcoming the Unwelcome : Wholehearted Living in a Brokenhearted World &#8211; Pema Chodron (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/welcoming-the-unwelcome-wholehearted-living-in-a-brokenhearted-world-pema-chodron-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tibetan Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/welcoming-the-unwelcome-wholehearted-living-in-a-brokenhearted-world-pema-chodron-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of When Things Fall Apart, an open-hearted call for human connection, compassion, and learning to love the world just as it is during these most challenging times. In her first new book of spiritual teachings in over seven years, Pema Chödrön offers a combination of wisdom, heartfelt reflections, and the signature [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/welcoming-the-unwelcome-wholehearted-living-in-a-brokenhearted-world-pema-chodron-abridged/">Welcoming the Unwelcome : Wholehearted Living in a Brokenhearted World &#8211; Pema Chodron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of When Things Fall Apart, an open-hearted call for human connection, compassion, and learning to love the world just as it is during these most challenging times.      </p>
<p>                     In her first new book of spiritual teachings in over seven years, Pema Chödrön offers a combination of wisdom, heartfelt reflections, and the signature mix of humor and insight that have made her a beloved figure to turn to during times of change. In an increasingly polarized world, Pema shows us how to strengthen our abilities to find common ground, even when we disagree, and influence our environment in positive ways. Sharing never-before told personal stories from her remarkable life, simple and powerful everyday practices, and directly relatable advice, Pema encourages us all to become triumphant bodhisattvas&#8211;compassionate beings&#8211;in times of hardship.     </p>
<p>                     Welcoming the Unwelcome includes teachings on the true meaning of karma, recognizing the basic goodness in ourselves and the people we share our lives with&#8211;even the most challenging ones, transforming adversity into opportunities for growth, and freeing ourselves from the empty and illusory labels that separate us. Pema also provides step-by-step guides to a basic sitting meditation and a compassion meditation that anyone can use to bring light to the darkness we face, wherever and whatever it may be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/welcoming-the-unwelcome-wholehearted-living-in-a-brokenhearted-world-pema-chodron-abridged/">Welcoming the Unwelcome : Wholehearted Living in a Brokenhearted World &#8211; Pema Chodron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax    </p>
<p>                    Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world has become a word-of-mouth bestseller and global phenomenon. It reveals a set of simple yet powerful practices that you can incorporate into daily life to break the cycle of anxiety, stress unhappiness and exhaustion. It promotes the kind of happiness that gets into your bones and allows you to meet the worst that life throws at you with new courage.     </p>
<p>                    Mindfulness is based on mindfulness-based cognitive therapy (MBCT). Co-developed by Professor Mark Williams of Oxford University, MBCT is recommended by the UK&#8217;s National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and is as effective as drugs for preventing depression. But, equally, it works for the rest of us who aren&#8217;t depressed but who are struggling to keep up with the relentless demands of the modern world.     </p>
<p>                    By investing just a few minutes each day, this classic guide to mindfulness will put you back in control of your life once again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seven Spiritual Laws of Success : A Pocketbook Guide to Fulfilling Your Dreams &#8211; Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seven-spiritual-laws-of-success-a-pocketbook-guide-to-fulfilling-your-dreams-deepak-chopra-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seven-spiritual-laws-of-success-a-pocketbook-guide-to-fulfilling-your-dreams-deepak-chopra-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is a book you will cherish for a lifetime, for within its pages are the secrets to making all your dreams come true. Based on natural laws that govern all of creation, this book shatters the myth that success is the result of hard work, exacting plans, or driving ambition. Instead, Deepak Chopra offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seven-spiritual-laws-of-success-a-pocketbook-guide-to-fulfilling-your-dreams-deepak-chopra-abridged/">The Seven Spiritual Laws of Success : A Pocketbook Guide to Fulfilling Your Dreams &#8211; Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a book you will cherish for a lifetime, for within its pages are the secrets to making all your dreams come true.     </p>
<p>                    Based on natural laws that govern all of creation, this book shatters the myth that success is the result of hard work, exacting plans, or driving ambition. Instead, Deepak Chopra offers a life-altering perspective on the attainment of success: When we understand our true nature and learn to live in harmony with natural law, a sense of well-being, good health, fulfilling relationships, and material abundance spring forth easily and effortlessly.     </p>
<p>                     Filled with timeless wisdom and practical steps you can apply right away, this pocketbook edition of Chopra&#8217;s classic bestselling book makes it easy for you to read and refer to again and again. Carry it with you in your purse or your pocket, and in less than one hour, learn the seven powerful principles that can easily be applied to create success in all areas of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seven-spiritual-laws-of-success-a-pocketbook-guide-to-fulfilling-your-dreams-deepak-chopra-abridged/">The Seven Spiritual Laws of Success : A Pocketbook Guide to Fulfilling Your Dreams &#8211; Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened by the traces of memory inside the connections between our neurons. We are memory. We are nostalgia. We are longing for a future that will not come&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Time is a mystery that does not cease to puzzle us. Philosophers, artists and poets have long explored its meaning while scientists have found that its structure is different from the simple intuition we have of it. From Boltzmann to quantum theory, from Einstein to loop quantum gravity, our understanding of time has been undergoing radical transformations. Time flows at a different speed in different places, the past and the future differ far less than we might think, and the very notion of the present evaporates in the vast universe.    </p>
<p>                    With his extraordinary charm and sense of wonder, bringing together science, philosophy and art, Carlo Rovelli unravels this mystery. Enlightening and consoling, The Order of Time shows that to understand ourselves we need to reflect on time &#8212; and to understand time we need to reflect on ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Women Food and God : An Unexpected Path to Almost Everything &#8211; Geneen Roth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/women-food-and-god-an-unexpected-path-to-almost-everything-geneen-roth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/women-food-and-god-an-unexpected-path-to-almost-everything-geneen-roth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Millions of us are locked into an unwinnable weight game, as our self-worth is shredded with every diet failure. Combine the utter inefficacy of dieting with the lack of spiritual nourishment and we have generations of mad, ravenous self-loathing women. So says Geneen Roth, in her life-changing new book, Women, Food and God. Since her [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-food-and-god-an-unexpected-path-to-almost-everything-geneen-roth-abridged/">Women Food and God : An Unexpected Path to Almost Everything &#8211; Geneen Roth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Millions of us are locked into an unwinnable weight game, as our self-worth is shredded with every diet failure. Combine the utter inefficacy of dieting with the lack of spiritual nourishment and we have generations of mad, ravenous self-loathing women. So says Geneen Roth, in her life-changing new book, Women, Food and God. Since her 1991 bestseller, When Food Is Love, was published, Roth has taken the sum total of her experience and combined it with spirituality and psychology to explain women&#8217;s true hunger. Roth&#8217;s approach to eating is that it is the same as any addiction &#8211; an activity to avoid feeling emotions. From the first page, readers will be struck by the author&#8217;s intelligence, humour and sensitivity, as she traces the path of overeating from its subtle beginnings through to its logical end. Whether the drug is booze or brownies, the problem is the same: opting out of life. She powerfully urges readers to pay attention to what they truly need &#8211; which cannot be found in a supermarket.<br />
                    She provides seven basic guidelines for eating (the most important is to never diet) and shares reassuring, practical advice that has helped thousands of women who have attended her highly successful seminars. Truly a thinking woman&#8217;s guide to eating &#8211; and an anti-diet book &#8211; women everywhere will find insights and revelations on every page.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-food-and-god-an-unexpected-path-to-almost-everything-geneen-roth-abridged/">Women Food and God : An Unexpected Path to Almost Everything &#8211; Geneen Roth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Activate Your Brain : How Understanding Your Brain Can Improve Your Work &#8211; and Your Life &#8211; Scott G Halford (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/activate-your-brain-how-understanding-your-brain-can-improve-your-work-and-your-life-scott-g-halford-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/activate-your-brain-how-understanding-your-brain-can-improve-your-work-and-your-life-scott-g-halford-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Wall Street Journal bestselling ebook! Axiom Business Book Bronze Award Winner Push your brain to full power, for success at the office and at home Would you like more control over your life and your work? Would you like greater stamina as you carry out</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/activate-your-brain-how-understanding-your-brain-can-improve-your-work-and-your-life-scott-g-halford-abridged/">Activate Your Brain : How Understanding Your Brain Can Improve Your Work &#8211; and Your Life &#8211; Scott G Halford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Wall Street Journal bestselling ebook! Axiom Business Book Bronze Award Winner Push your brain to full power, for success at the office and at home Would you like more control over your life and your work? Would you like greater stamina as you carry out</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/activate-your-brain-how-understanding-your-brain-can-improve-your-work-and-your-life-scott-g-halford-abridged/">Activate Your Brain : How Understanding Your Brain Can Improve Your Work &#8211; and Your Life &#8211; Scott G Halford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret &#8211; Rhonda Byrne (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2006, a groundbreaking feature-length film revealed the great mystery of the universe &#8211; The Secret. Later that year, Rhonda Byrne followed with a book that became a worldwide bestseller. Fragments of a Great Secret have been found in the oral traditions, in literature, in religions and philosophies throughout the centuries. For the first time, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/">The Secret &#8211; Rhonda Byrne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2006, a groundbreaking feature-length film revealed the great mystery of the universe &#8211; The Secret. Later that year, Rhonda Byrne followed with a book that became a worldwide bestseller.     </p>
<p>                    Fragments of a Great Secret have been found in the oral traditions, in literature, in religions and philosophies throughout the centuries. For the first time, all the pieces of The Secret come together in an incredible revelation that will be life-transforming for all who experience it.    </p>
<p>                    In this book, you&#8217;ll learn how to use The Secret in every aspect of your life &#8211; money, health, relationships, happiness, and in every interaction you have in the world. You&#8217;ll begin to understand the hidden, untapped power that&#8217;s within you, and this revelation can bring joy to every aspect of your life.    </p>
<p>                    The Secret contains wisdom from modern-day teachers &#8211; men and women who have used it to achieve health, wealth and happiness. By applying the knowledge of The Secret, they bring to light compelling stories of eradicating obstacles, and achieving what many would regard as impossible.    </p>
<p>                    Discover the book which has been changing millions of lives around the world. No matter who you are, where you are right now, no matter what you want &#8211; when you realise The Secret you can have anything.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/">The Secret &#8211; Rhonda Byrne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Woo-Woo Works : The Surprising Science Behind Meditation, Reiki, Crystals, and Other Alternative Practices &#8211; Dr David R. Hamilton, PhD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-woo-woo-works-the-surprising-science-behind-meditation-reiki-crystals-and-other-alternative-practices-dr-david-r-hamilton-phd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-woo-woo-works-the-surprising-science-behind-meditation-reiki-crystals-and-other-alternative-practices-dr-david-r-hamilton-phd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why should we meditate? How can crystals heal the mind and body? Why is visualization so powerful &#8211; and so effective? Alternative therapies, healing modalities, and spiritual practices are often referred to as &#8216;woo-woo,&#8217; &#8211; but many of these approaches are actually supported by compelling scientific evidence. In this dynamic and thought-provoking book, David R. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-woo-woo-works-the-surprising-science-behind-meditation-reiki-crystals-and-other-alternative-practices-dr-david-r-hamilton-phd-abridged/">Why Woo-Woo Works : The Surprising Science Behind Meditation, Reiki, Crystals, and Other Alternative Practices &#8211; Dr David R. Hamilton, PhD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why should we meditate? How can crystals heal the mind and body? Why is visualization so powerful &#8211; and so effective?     </p>
<p>                    Alternative therapies, healing modalities, and spiritual practices are often referred to as &#8216;woo-woo,&#8217; &#8211; but many of these approaches are actually supported by compelling scientific evidence.    </p>
<p>                    In this dynamic and thought-provoking book, David R. Hamilton PhD dives deeper into the true nature of consciousness and presents the cutting-edge research behind energy healing, crystals, meditation, and more.    </p>
<p>                    You&#8217;ll discover:<br />
                    *      The science behind some of today&#8217;s most popular alternative practices<br />
                    *      How your thoughts, emotions, and beliefs have healing power<br />
                    *      The benefits of nature and a holistic approach to healing<br />
                    *      A fascinating link between consciousness and human connection<br />
                    *      The relationship between suppressed emotions and disease    </p>
<p>                    The ideas behind some of these holistic therapies have been around for millennia &#8211; but now we have scientific evidence demonstrating how they can contribute to physical, emotional, and energetic healing too.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s time to embrace the truth: That woo-woo really does work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-woo-woo-works-the-surprising-science-behind-meditation-reiki-crystals-and-other-alternative-practices-dr-david-r-hamilton-phd-abridged/">Why Woo-Woo Works : The Surprising Science Behind Meditation, Reiki, Crystals, and Other Alternative Practices &#8211; Dr David R. Hamilton, PhD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What We Say Matters : Practicing Nonviolent Communication &#8211; Ike Lasater, Judith Hanson Lasater (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-we-say-matters-practicing-nonviolent-communication-ike-lasater-judith-hanson-lasater-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chakras, Auras & Spiritual Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-we-say-matters-practicing-nonviolent-communication-ike-lasater-judith-hanson-lasater-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Drawing from Buddhist and yogic precepts, this practical guide offers tools for becoming a better, more compassionate communicator at home, at work, and in the world Have you ever tried to tell someone what you want only to feel misunderstood and frustrated? Or hesitated to ask for what you needed because you didn&#8217;t want to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-we-say-matters-practicing-nonviolent-communication-ike-lasater-judith-hanson-lasater-abridged/">What We Say Matters : Practicing Nonviolent Communication &#8211; Ike Lasater, Judith Hanson Lasater (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Drawing from Buddhist and yogic precepts, this practical guide offers tools for becoming a better, more compassionate communicator at home, at work, and in the world     </p>
<p>                     Have you ever tried to tell someone what you want only to feel misunderstood and frustrated? Or hesitated to ask for what you needed because you didn&#8217;t want to burden the other person? Or been stuck in blame or anger that wouldn&#8217;t go away?     </p>
<p>                     Judith and Ike Lasater, long-term students of yoga and Buddhism, experienced dilemmas like these, too. Even though they had studied the yoga principle of satya (truth) and the Buddhist precept of right speech, it was not until they began practicing Marshall Rosenberg&#8217;s techniques of Nonviolent Communication (NVC) that they understood how to live satya and right speech.     </p>
<p>                     In What We Say Matters, Judith and Ike describe their journey through NVC and how speech becomes a spiritual practice based on giving and receiving with compassion&#8211;everywhere, all the time&#8211;whether at home, at work, or in the world. Their writing is deeply personal, punctuated by their recounts of trial and error, success and failure, laughter and challenge&#8211;even in writing this book! They guide you through an introduction to NVC with clear explanations, poignant examples, suggested exercises, and helpful resources. With practice, you&#8217;ll learn new ways to:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Extend empathy to yourself and others<br />
                    &#8211; Distinguish between feelings and needs<br />
                    &#8211; Make requests rather than demands<br />
                    &#8211; Choose connection over conflict<br />
                    &#8211; Create mutually satisfying outcomes</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-we-say-matters-practicing-nonviolent-communication-ike-lasater-judith-hanson-lasater-abridged/">What We Say Matters : Practicing Nonviolent Communication &#8211; Ike Lasater, Judith Hanson Lasater (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rising Strong &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rising-strong-brene-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rising-strong-brene-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to Brene Brown I learned how to be vulnerable&#8230; a life changer&#8217; Miranda Hart The physics of vulnerability is simple: If we are brave enough often enough, we will fall. This is a book about what it takes to get back up and how owning our stories of disappointment, failure, and heartbreak gives us [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rising-strong-brene-brown-abridged/">Rising Strong &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to Brene Brown I learned how to be vulnerable&#8230; a life changer&#8217; Miranda Hart    </p>
<p>                    The physics of vulnerability is simple: If we are brave enough often enough, we will fall. This is a book about what it takes to get back up and how owning our stories of disappointment, failure, and heartbreak gives us the power to write a daring new ending. Struggle can be our greatest call to courage and Rising Strong, our clearest path to deeper meaning, wisdom and hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rising-strong-brene-brown-abridged/">Rising Strong &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hallelujah Anyway : Rediscovering Mercy &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hallelujah-anyway-rediscovering-mercy-anne-lamott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hallelujah-anyway-rediscovering-mercy-anne-lamott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Anne Lamott is my Oprah.&#8221; -Chicago Tribune The New York Times bestseller from the author of Dusk, Night, Dawn, Almost Everything and Bird by Bird, a powerful exploration of mercy and how we can embrace it. &#8220;Mercy is radical kindness,&#8221; Anne Lamott writes in her enthralling and heartening book, Hallelujah Anyway. It&#8217;s the permission you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hallelujah-anyway-rediscovering-mercy-anne-lamott-abridged/">Hallelujah Anyway : Rediscovering Mercy &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Anne Lamott is my Oprah.&#8221; -Chicago Tribune    </p>
<p>                    The New York Times bestseller from the author of Dusk, Night, Dawn, Almost Everything and Bird by Bird, a powerful exploration of mercy and how we can embrace it.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Mercy is radical kindness,&#8221; Anne Lamott writes in her enthralling and heartening book, Hallelujah Anyway. It&#8217;s the permission you give others-and yourself-to forgive a debt, to absolve the unabsolvable, to let go of the judgment and pain that make life so difficult.    </p>
<p>                    In Hallelujah Anyway: Rediscovering Mercy Lamott ventures to explore where to find meaning in life. We should begin, she suggests, by &#8220;facing a great big mess, especially the great big mess of ourselves.&#8221; It&#8217;s up to each of us to recognize the presence and importance of mercy everywhere-&#8220;within us and outside us, all around us&#8221;-and to use it to forge a deeper understanding of ourselves and more honest connections with each other. While that can be difficult to do, Lamott argues that it&#8217;s crucial, as &#8220;kindness towards others, beginning with myself, buys us a shot at a warm and generous heart, the greatest prize of all.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Full of Lamott&#8217;s trademark honesty, humor and forthrightness, Hallelujah Anyway is profound and caring, funny and wise-a hopeful book of hands-on spirituality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hallelujah-anyway-rediscovering-mercy-anne-lamott-abridged/">Hallelujah Anyway : Rediscovering Mercy &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eight Dates : To keep your relationship happy, thriving and lasting &#8211; Dr John Gottman, Dr Julie Gottman, Rachel Abrams, Doug Abrams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eight-dates-to-keep-your-relationship-happy-thriving-and-lasting-dr-john-gottman-dr-julie-gottman-rachel-abrams-doug-abrams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eight-dates-to-keep-your-relationship-happy-thriving-and-lasting-dr-john-gottman-dr-julie-gottman-rachel-abrams-doug-abrams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What really makes a relationship work? How can we stay interested in our partner for ever? How can we be happier in our marriage? Doctors John and Julie Gottman have spent over three decades studying the habits of 3000 couples. Within 10 minutes of meeting a couple, they can predict who will stay happily together [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eight-dates-to-keep-your-relationship-happy-thriving-and-lasting-dr-john-gottman-dr-julie-gottman-rachel-abrams-doug-abrams-abridged/">Eight Dates : To keep your relationship happy, thriving and lasting &#8211; Dr John Gottman, Dr Julie Gottman, Rachel Abrams, Doug Abrams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What really makes a relationship work? How can we stay interested in our partner for ever? How can we be happier in our marriage?     </p>
<p>                    Doctors John and Julie Gottman have spent over three decades studying the habits of 3000 couples. Within 10 minutes of meeting a couple, they can predict who will stay happily together or who will split up, with 94% accuracy. Based on their findings on the ingredients to a happy, lasting love life, they have now created an easy series of eight dates, spanning:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; commitment &#038; trust<br />
                    &#8211; conflict resolution<br />
                    &#8211; intimacy &#038; sex<br />
                    &#8211; fun &#038; adventure<br />
                    &#8211; work &#038; money<br />
                    &#8211; family values<br />
                    &#8211; growth &#038; spirituality<br />
                    &#8211; goals &#038; aspirations    </p>
<p>                    Eight Dates draws on rigorous scientific and psychological research about how we fall in love using case studies of real-life couples whose relationships have improved after committing time to each other and following the dates. Full of innovative exercises and conversation starters to explore ways to deepen each aspect of the relationship, Eight Dates is an essential resource that makes a relationship fulfilling.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Can a marriage really be understood? Yes it can. Gottman shows us how&#8217; Malcolm Gladwell, author of Blink</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eight-dates-to-keep-your-relationship-happy-thriving-and-lasting-dr-john-gottman-dr-julie-gottman-rachel-abrams-doug-abrams-abridged/">Eight Dates : To keep your relationship happy, thriving and lasting &#8211; Dr John Gottman, Dr Julie Gottman, Rachel Abrams, Doug Abrams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness : Meditation in the 21st century &#8211; Gelong Thubten (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-monks-guide-to-happiness-meditation-in-the-21st-century-gelong-thubten-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-monks-guide-to-happiness-meditation-in-the-21st-century-gelong-thubten-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller FEATURED ON THE DELICIOUSLY ELLA PODCAST We&#8217;re all on a search for happiness, but we&#8217;re looking in the wrong places. Everyone looks externally to find contentment, we think material possessions will unlock our happiness. A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness explains how and why we need to look within, and connect to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-monks-guide-to-happiness-meditation-in-the-21st-century-gelong-thubten-abridged/">A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness : Meditation in the 21st century &#8211; Gelong Thubten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller    </p>
<p>                    FEATURED ON THE DELICIOUSLY ELLA PODCAST    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;re all on a search for happiness, but we&#8217;re looking in the wrong places.    </p>
<p>                    Everyone looks externally to find contentment, we think material possessions will unlock our happiness. A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness explains how and why we need to look within, and connect to our true essence, in order to find peace. Everyone has the potential to be happy, after all, we&#8217;re all &#8216;hardwired&#8217; for happiness.    </p>
<p>                    But how do we get there? By meditating. Not just in the morning, but throughout the day by introducing micro moments so we never drop the mindfulness ball, even when we&#8217;re busy. Meditation is more than just a stress-reduction tool or a relaxation therapy, it is the key to finding long-lasting happiness.    </p>
<p>                    Gelong Thubten, a Buddhist monk who has worked with everyone from Silicon Valley entrepreneurs to Ruby Wax and Benedict Cumberbatch, explores the theme of happiness in his debut book and explains how to bring meditation into our busy 21st century lives with simple exercises.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thubten is a very generous and kind monk who writes with the lived honesty and humour of someone who has experienced the wisdom he shares. His writing is full of inspiration but also the pragmatism needed to form a sustainable practice. His book clearly illustrates why we all need meditation and mindfulness in our lives.&#8217; &#8211; Benedict Cumberbatch</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-monks-guide-to-happiness-meditation-in-the-21st-century-gelong-thubten-abridged/">A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness : Meditation in the 21st century &#8211; Gelong Thubten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altruism : The Science and Psychology of Kindness &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The concern for the well-being of others could be the saving grace of the 21st century. Matthieu Ricard&#8217;s Altruism, an erudite, brilliantly ranging synthesis of philosophy, psychology and ages old wisdom, is a radical call to kindness, which has the potential as a new global movement to answer the biggest problems of our time: the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Altruism : The Science and Psychology of Kindness &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The concern for the well-being of others could be the saving grace of the 21st century. Matthieu Ricard&#8217;s Altruism, an erudite, brilliantly ranging synthesis of philosophy, psychology and ages old wisdom, is a radical call to kindness, which has the potential as a new global movement to answer the biggest problems of our time: the economy in the short term, life satisfaction in the mid-term, and the environment in the long term. As the faultlines of inequality and nationalism leave us ever more divided, Ricard challenges us to be better people &#8211; and in the process, make the world a better place.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Altruism : The Science and Psychology of Kindness &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
