<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Industrial Relations Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/industrial-relations/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/industrial-relations/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Industrial Relations Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/industrial-relations/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN* A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood<br />
                    &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson<br />
                    &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson    </p>
<p>                    *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN*    </p>
<p>                    A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey that helped change the world.    </p>
<p>                    Hollywood was talking as never before. Kantor and Twohey outmanoeuvred Harvey Weinstein, his team of defenders and private investigators, convincing some of the most famous women in the world &#8211; and some unknown ones &#8211; to go on the record. Three years later, it helped lead to his conviction.    </p>
<p>                    This is how they did it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dangerously Sleepy : Overworked Americans and the Cult of Manly Wakefulness &#8211; Alan Derickson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Workers in the United States are losing sleep. In the global economy a growing number of employees hold jobs-often more than one at once-with unpredictable hours. Even before the rise of the twenty-four-hour workplace, the relationship between sleep and industry was problematic: sleep is frequently cast as an enemy or a weakness, while constant productivity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/">Dangerously Sleepy : Overworked Americans and the Cult of Manly Wakefulness &#8211; Alan Derickson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Workers in the United States are losing sleep. In the global economy a growing number of employees hold jobs-often more than one at once-with unpredictable hours. Even before the rise of the twenty-four-hour workplace, the relationship between sleep and industry was problematic: sleep is frequently cast as an enemy or a weakness, while constant productivity and flexibility are glorified at the expense of health and safety.    </p>
<p>                    Dangerously Sleepy is the first book to track the longtime association of overwork and sleep deprivation from the nineteenth century to the present. Health and labor historian Alan Derickson charts the cultural and political forces behind the overvaluation-and masculinization-of wakefulness in the United States. Since the nineteenth century, men at all levels of society have toiled around the clock by necessity: steel workers coped with rotating shifts, Pullman porters grappled with ever-changing timetables and unrelenting on-call status, and long-haul truckers dealt with chaotic life on the road. But the dangerous realities of exhaustion were minimized and even glamorized when the entrepreneurial drive of public figures such as Thomas Edison and Donald Trump encouraged American men to deny biological need in the name of success. For workers, resisting sleep became a challenge of masculine strength.    </p>
<p>                    This lucid history of the wakeful work ethic suggests that for millions of American men and women, untenable work schedules have been the main factor leading to sleep loss, newer ailments such as shift work sleep disorder, and related morbidity and mortality. Dangerously Sleepy places these public health problems in historical context.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/">Dangerously Sleepy : Overworked Americans and the Cult of Manly Wakefulness &#8211; Alan Derickson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The shift toward automation is about to create a tsunami of unemployment. Not in the distant future&#8211;now. One recent estimate predicts 13 million American workers will lose their jobs within the next seven years-jobs that won&#8217;t be replaced. In a future marked by restlessness and chronic unemployment, what will happen to American society? In The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/">The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The shift toward automation is about to create a tsunami of unemployment. Not in the distant future&#8211;now. One recent estimate predicts 13 million American workers will lose their jobs within the next seven years-jobs that won&#8217;t be replaced. In a future marked by restlessness and chronic unemployment, what will happen to American society?    </p>
<p>                    In The War on Normal People, Andrew Yang paints a dire portrait of the American economy. Rapidly advancing technologies like artificial intelligence, robotics and automation software are making millions of Americans&#8217; livelihoods irrelevant. The consequences are these trends are already being felt across our communities in the form of political unrest, drug use, and other social ills. The future looks dire-but is it unavoidable?    </p>
<p>                    In The War on Normal People, Yang imagines a different future &#8212; one in which having a job is distinct from the capacity to prosper and seek fulfillment. At this vision&#8217;s core is Universal Basic Income, the concept of providing all citizens with a guaranteed income-and one that is rapidly gaining popularity among forward-thinking politicians and economists. Yang proposes that UBI is an essential step toward a new, more durable kind of economy, one he calls &#8220;human capitalism.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/">The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job? That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves. The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job?     </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves.     </p>
<p>                    The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even many full-time and professional jobs are experiencing this precarious shift. Within a decade, a near-majority of the 145 million employed Americans will be impacted. Add to that the steamroller of automation, robots and artificial intelligence already replacing millions of workers and projected to obsolesce millions more, and the jobs picture starts looking grim.     </p>
<p>                    Now a weird yet historic mash-up of Silicon Valley technology and Wall Street greed is thrusting upon us the latest economic fraud: the so-called sharing economy, with companies like Uber, Airbnb and TaskRabbit allegedly liberating workers to become independent and their own CEOs, hiring themselves out for ever-smaller jobs and wages while the companies profit.     </p>
<p>                    But this share the crumbs economy is just the tip of a looming iceberg that the middle class is drifting toward. Raw Deal: How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers, by veteran journalist Steven Hill, is an exposé that challenges conventional thinking, and the hype celebrating this new economy, by showing why the vision of the techno sapien leaders and their Ayn Rand libertarianism is a dead end.     </p>
<p>                    In Raw Deal, Steven Hill proposes pragmatic policy solutions to transform the US economy and its safety net and social contract, launching a new kind of deal to restore power back into the hands of American workers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brotopia &#8211; Interviewee Emily Chang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brotopia-interviewee-emily-chang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brotopia-interviewee-emily-chang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Instant National Bestseller A PBS NewsHour-New York Times Book Club Pick! Excellent. &#8211;San Francisco Chronicle Brotopia is more than a business book. Silicon Valley holds extraordinary power over our present lives as well as whatever utopia (or nightmare) might come next. &#8211;New York Times Silicon Valley is a modern utopia where anyone can change the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brotopia-interviewee-emily-chang-abridged/">Brotopia &#8211; Interviewee Emily Chang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Instant National Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    A PBS NewsHour-New York Times Book Club Pick!     </p>
<p>                    Excellent. &#8211;San Francisco Chronicle     </p>
<p>                    Brotopia is more than a business book. Silicon Valley holds extraordinary power over our present lives as well as whatever utopia (or nightmare) might come next. &#8211;New York Times     </p>
<p>                    Silicon Valley is a modern utopia where anyone can change the world. Unless you&#8217;re a woman.     </p>
<p>                    For women in tech, Silicon Valley is not a fantasyland of unicorns, virtual reality rainbows, and 3D-printed lollipops, where millions of dollars grow on trees. It&#8217;s a Brotopia, where men hold all the cards and make all the rules. Vastly outnumbered, women face toxic workplaces rife with discrimination and sexual harassment, where investors take meetings in hot tubs and network at sex parties.     </p>
<p>                    In this powerful exposé, Bloomberg TV journalist Emily Chang reveals how Silicon Valley got so sexist despite its utopian ideals, why bro culture endures despite decades of companies claiming the moral high ground (Don&#8217;t Be Evil! Connect the World!)&#8211;and how women are finally starting to speak out and fight back.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on her deep network of Silicon Valley insiders, Chang opens the boardroom doors of male-dominated venture capital firms like Kleiner Perkins, the subject of Ellen Pao&#8217;s high-profile gender discrimination lawsuit, and Sequoia, where a partner once famously said they won&#8217;t lower their standards just to hire women. Interviews with Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg, YouTube CEO Susan Wojcicki, and former Yahoo! CEO Marissa Mayer&#8211;who got their start at Google, where just one in five engineers is a woman&#8211;reveal just how hard it is to crack the Silicon Ceiling. And Chang shows how women such as former Uber engineer Susan Fowler, entrepreneur Niniane Wang, and game developer Brianna Wu, have risked their careers and sometimes their lives to pave a way for other women.     </p>
<p>                    Silicon Valley&#8217;s aggressive, misogynistic, work-at-all costs culture has shut women out of the greatest wealth creation in the history of the world. It&#8217;s time to break up the boys&#8217; club. Emily Chang shows us how to fix this toxic culture&#8211;to bring down Brotopia, once and for all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brotopia-interviewee-emily-chang-abridged/">Brotopia &#8211; Interviewee Emily Chang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations & Safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers. Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell    </p>
<p>                    Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers.    </p>
<p>                    Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into the hands of the &#8216;managers&#8217;. Burnham explains how Capitalism had virtually lost its control, and would be displaced not by labour, nor by socialism, but by the rule of administartors in business and in government.    </p>
<p>                    This revolution, he posited, is as broad as the world and as comprehensive as human society, asking &#8220;Why is &#8216;totalitarianism&#8217; not the issue?&#8221; &#8220;Can civilization be destroyed?&#8221; And &#8220;Why is the New Deal something bigger than Roosevelt can handle?&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    In a volume extraordinary for its dispassionate handling of those and other fundamental questions, James Burnham explores fully the implications of the managerial revolution.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
