<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Human Geography Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/human-geography/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/human-geography/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Human Geography Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/human-geography/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Happy City : Transforming Our Lives Through Urban Design &#8211; Charles Montgomery (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[City & Town Planning - Architectural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban & Municipal Planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Happy City is the story of how the solutions to this century&#8217;s problems lie in unlocking the secrets to great city living This is going to be the century of the city. But what actually makes a good city? Why are some cities a joy to live in? As Charles Montgomery reveals, it&#8217;s not how [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/">Happy City : Transforming Our Lives Through Urban Design &#8211; Charles Montgomery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happy City is the story of how the solutions to this century&#8217;s problems lie in unlocking the secrets to great city living    </p>
<p>                    This is going to be the century of the city. But what actually makes a good city? Why are some cities a joy to live in?    </p>
<p>                    As Charles Montgomery reveals, it&#8217;s not how much money your neighbours earn, or how pleasant the climate is that makes the most difference. Journeying to dozens of cities &#8211; from Atlanta to Bogota to Vancouver &#8211; he talks to the new champions of the happy city to explore the urban innovations already transforming people&#8217;s lives. He meets the visionary Colombian mayor who turned some of the world&#8217;s most dangerous roads into an urban cycling haven; the Danish architect who brought the lessons of medieval Tuscan towns to modern-day Copenhagen; and the New York City transport commissioner who turned the gridlock of Times Square into a place to lounge in the sun.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the lessons from their stories, from brain science, and from the fascinating realm of urban experimentation, Happy City offers solutions we can all use to improve our livesandshows that simple changes can make all the difference.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Do we live in neighbourhoods that make us happy? Montgomery encourages us to ask without embarrassment, and to think intelligently about the answer&#8217; The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Excellent . . . Montgomery believes in the importance of smart town planning and Happy City is a compendium of its major ideas&#8217; Will Dean, Independent    </p>
<p>                    Charles Montgomery is a journalist and urban experimentalist from Vancouver, Canada. His writings on urban planning, psychology, culture, and history have appeared in magazines and journals on three continents. He is the author of one previous book, and was an original member of the BMW Guggenheim Lab.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/">Happy City : Transforming Our Lives Through Urban Design &#8211; Charles Montgomery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geographical Discovery & Exploration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geology & The Lithosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Geography & Topography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** Winner of Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books 2015 ** We live in epoch-making times. The changes we humans have made in recent decades have altered our world beyond anything it has experienced in its 4.6 billion-year history. As a result, our planet is said to be crossing into the Anthropocene &#8211; the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/">Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** Winner of Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books 2015 **    </p>
<p>                    We live in epoch-making times. The changes we humans have made in recent decades have altered our world beyond anything it has experienced in its 4.6 billion-year history. As a result, our planet is said to be crossing into the Anthropocene &#8211; the Age of Humans.     </p>
<p>                     Gaia Vince decided to travel the world at the start of this new age to see what life is really like for the people on the frontline of the planet we&#8217;ve made.  From artificial glaciers in the Himalayas to painted mountains in Peru, electrified reefs in the Maldives to garbage islands in the Caribbean, Gaia found people doing the most extraordinary things to solve the problems that we ourselves have created.    </p>
<p>                     These stories show what the Anthropocene means for all of us &#8211; and they illuminate how we might engineer Earth for our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/">Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he tries to understand so-called European socialism firsthand. Though he first tries France (which has become a rhetorical stand-in for the continent as a whole in many Americans&#8217; minds), he eventually ventures into Germany to see what some call the &#8220;boring&#8221; Europe. There he finds the true &#8220;other&#8221; an economic model with more bottom-up worker control than that of any other country in the world and argues that, while we have to take Germany&#8217;s problems seriously, we also have to look seriously at how much it has achieved. Social democracy may let us live nicer lives; it also may be the only way to be globally competitive. This wry, timely book helps us understand why the European model, contrary to popular neoliberal wisdom, may thrive well into the twenty-first century without compromising its citizens&#8217; ease of living and be the best example for the United States to follow.    </p>
<p>                    Germany is more generous than the U.S.:    </p>
<p>                    The average number of paid vacation days in the U.S. is 13, versus Germany&#8217;s 35<br />
                    New mothers in the U.S. get three months of unpaid job-protected leave and only if they work for a company of 50 or more employees, while Germany mandates four months&#8217; paid leave and will pay parents 67% of their salary to stay home for up to 14 months to care for a newborn.<br />
                    U.S. life expectancy is 50th in the world, compared to Germany&#8217;s 32nd.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
