<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Drought &amp; Water Supply Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/drought-water-supply/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/drought-water-supply/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Drought &amp; Water Supply Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/drought-water-supply/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Let There Be Water : Israel&#8217;s Solution for a Water-Starved World &#8211; Siegel, Seth M. (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drought & Water Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hydrology & The Hydrosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Irrigation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Supply & Treatment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With hardly a day without a water-crisis story somewhere, Let There Be Water offers prescriptions on how countries, cities, and businesses can avoid the worst of it. With sixty percent of the country in a desert and despite a rapidly growing population, Israel has been jumping ahead of the water-innovation curve for decades. Beyond securing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/">Let There Be Water : Israel&#8217;s Solution for a Water-Starved World &#8211; Siegel, Seth M. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With hardly a day without a water-crisis story somewhere, Let There Be Water offers prescriptions on how countries, cities, and businesses can avoid the worst of it. With sixty percent of the country in a desert and despite a rapidly growing population, Israel has been jumping ahead of the water-innovation curve for decades. Beyond securing its own water supply, Israel has also created a high-export industry in water technology, a timely example of how countries can build their economies while making the world better. Built on meticulous research and hundreds of interviews with both world leaders and experts in the field, Let There Be Water tells the inspiring story of how this all came to be. The author is now widely considered to be one of the nation&#8217;s go-to authorities on water and has in the last year alone, spoken to more than 160 different organisations, civic groups, and universities all across the country.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/">Let There Be Water : Israel&#8217;s Solution for a Water-Starved World &#8211; Siegel, Seth M. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drought & Water Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An inspiring personal story of redemption, second chances, and the transformative power within us all, from the founder and CEO of the nonprofit charity: water. At 28 years old, Scott Harrison had it all. A top nightclub promoter in New York City, his life was an endless cycle of drugs, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/">Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An inspiring personal story of redemption, second chances, and the transformative power within us all, from the founder and CEO of the nonprofit charity: water.    </p>
<p>                    At 28 years old, Scott Harrison had it all. A top nightclub promoter in New York City, his life was an endless cycle of drugs, booze, models&#8211;repeat. But 10 years in, desperately unhappy and morally bankrupt, he asked himself, What would the exact opposite of my life look like? Walking away from everything, Harrison spent the next 16 months on a hospital ship in West Africa and discovered his true calling. In 2006, with no money and less than no experience, Harrison founded charity: water. Today, his organization has raised over $400 million to bring clean drinking water to more than 10 million people around the globe.     </p>
<p>                    In Thirst, Harrison recounts the twists and turns that built charity: water into one of the most trusted and admired nonprofits in the world. Renowned for its 100% donation model, bold storytelling, imaginative branding, and radical commitment to transparency, charity: water has disrupted how social entrepreneurs work while inspiring millions of people to join its mission of bringing clean water to everyone on the planet within our lifetime.     </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of such bestselling books as Shoe Dog and Mountains Beyond Mountains, Thirst is a riveting account of how to build a better charity, a better business, a better life&#8211;and a gritty tale that proves it&#8217;s never too late to make a change.     </p>
<p>                    100% of the author&#8217;s net proceeds from Thirst will go to fund charity: water projects around the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/">Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
