<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sociology: Sport &amp; Leisure Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sociology-sport-leisure/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sociology-sport-leisure/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sociology: Sport &amp; Leisure Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sociology-sport-leisure/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>This Is Your Brain on Sports : The Science of Underdogs, the Value of Rivalry, and What We Can Learn from the T-Shirt Cannon &#8211; L. Jon Wertheim, Sam Sommers (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-your-brain-on-sports-the-science-of-underdogs-the-value-of-rivalry-and-what-we-can-learn-from-the-t-shirt-cannon-l-jon-wertheim-sam-sommers-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sport & Leisure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-your-brain-on-sports-the-science-of-underdogs-the-value-of-rivalry-and-what-we-can-learn-from-the-t-shirt-cannon-l-jon-wertheim-sam-sommers-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is Your Brain on Sports is the book for sports fans searching for a deeper understanding of the games they watch and the people who play them. Sports Illustrated executive editor and bestselling author L. Jon Wertheim teams up with Tufts psychologist Sam Sommers to take readers on a wild ride into the inner [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-sports-the-science-of-underdogs-the-value-of-rivalry-and-what-we-can-learn-from-the-t-shirt-cannon-l-jon-wertheim-sam-sommers-abridged/">This Is Your Brain on Sports : The Science of Underdogs, the Value of Rivalry, and What We Can Learn from the T-Shirt Cannon &#8211; L. Jon Wertheim, Sam Sommers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is Your Brain on Sports is the book for sports fans searching for a deeper understanding of the games they watch and the people who play them. Sports Illustrated executive editor and bestselling author L. Jon Wertheim teams up with Tufts psychologist Sam Sommers to take readers on a wild ride into the inner world of sports. Through the prism of behavioral economics, neuroscience, and psychology, they reveal the hidden influences and surprising cues that inspire and derail us&#8211;on the field and in the stands&#8211;and by extension, in corporate board rooms, office settings, and our daily lives.     </p>
<p>                     In this irresistible narrative romp, Wertheim and Sommers usher us from professional football to the NBA to Grand Slam tennis, from the psychology of athletes self-handicapping their performance in the boxing ring or the World Series, to an explanation of why even the glimpse of a finish line can lift us beyond ordinary physical limits. They explore why Tom Brady and other starting NFL quarterbacks all seem to look like fashion models; why fans of teams like the Cubs, Mets, and any franchise from Cleveland love rooting for a loser; why the best players make the worst coaches; why hockey goons (and fans) would rather fight at home than on the road; and why the arena t-shirt cannon has something to teach us about human nature.     </p>
<p>                     In short, this book is an entertaining and thought-provoking journey into how psychology and behavioral science collide with the universe of wins-and-losses, coaching changes, underdogs, and rivalry games.     </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Boston Globe, Best Books of 2016, Sports</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-sports-the-science-of-underdogs-the-value-of-rivalry-and-what-we-can-learn-from-the-t-shirt-cannon-l-jon-wertheim-sam-sommers-abridged/">This Is Your Brain on Sports : The Science of Underdogs, the Value of Rivalry, and What We Can Learn from the T-Shirt Cannon &#8211; L. Jon Wertheim, Sam Sommers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Professor in the Cage : Why Men Fight and Why We Like to Watch &#8211; Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-professor-in-the-cage-why-men-fight-and-why-we-like-to-watch-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Combat Sports & Self-defence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sport & Leisure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-professor-in-the-cage-why-men-fight-and-why-we-like-to-watch-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An English professor starts training in mixed martial arts, exploring the science and history behind the violence of men When a mixed martial arts (MMA) gym opens across the street from his office, Jonathan Gottschall sees a challenge. Pushing forty, out of shape, and disenchanted with his job as an adjunct English professor, he works [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-professor-in-the-cage-why-men-fight-and-why-we-like-to-watch-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Professor in the Cage : Why Men Fight and Why We Like to Watch &#8211; Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An English professor starts training in mixed martial arts, exploring the science and history behind the violence of men    </p>
<p>                     When a mixed martial arts (MMA) gym opens across the street from his office, Jonathan Gottschall sees a challenge. Pushing forty, out of shape, and disenchanted with his job as an adjunct English professor, he works up his nerve and finds himself training for an all-out cage fight. He sees it not just as a personal test, but also as an opportunity to answer questions that have intrigued him for years: Why do men fight? And why do so many seemingly decent people love to watch?    </p>
<p>                     In The Professor in the Cage, Gottschall&#8217;s unlikely journey from the college classroom to the fighting cage drives an important new investigation into the science and history of violence. The surging popularity of MMA-a full-contact sport in which fighters punch, choke, and kick each other into submission-is just one example of our species&#8217; insatiable interest both in violence and in the rituals that keep violence in check. From duels to football to the roughhousing of children, humans are masters of what Gottschall calls the monkey dance: a dizzying variety of rule-bound contests that establish hierarchies while minimizing risk and social disorder. Gottschall&#8217;s unsparing odyssey-through extremes of pain, occasional humiliation, his wife&#8217;s incredulity, and ultimately his own cage fight-opens his, and our, eyes to the uncomfortable truth that, as brutal as these contests can be, the world would be a much more chaotic and dangerous place without them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-professor-in-the-cage-why-men-fight-and-why-we-like-to-watch-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Professor in the Cage : Why Men Fight and Why We Like to Watch &#8211; Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
