<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Atomic &amp; Molecular Physics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/atomic-molecular-physics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/atomic-molecular-physics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Atomic &amp; Molecular Physics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/atomic-molecular-physics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Short History of Nearly Everything &#8211; Bill Bryson</title>
		<link>/a-short-history-of-nearly-everything-bill-bryson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atomic & Molecular Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geology & The Lithosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space & Time]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-short-history-of-nearly-everything-bill-bryson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bill Bryson describes himself as a reluctant traveller: but even when he stays safely in his own study at home, he can&#8217;t contain his curiosity about the world around him. A Short History of Nearly Everything is his quest to find out everything that has happened from the Big Bang to the rise of civilization [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-nearly-everything-bill-bryson/">A Short History of Nearly Everything &#8211; Bill Bryson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bill Bryson describes himself as a reluctant traveller: but even when he stays safely in his own study at home, he can&#8217;t contain his curiosity about the world around him. A Short History of Nearly Everything is his quest to find out everything that has happened from the Big Bang to the rise of civilization &#8211; how we got from there, being nothing at all, to here, being us. </p>
<p>                    Bill Bryson&#8217;s challenge is to take subjects that normally bore the pants off most of us, like geology, chemistry and particle physics, and see if there isn&#8217;t some way to render them comprehensible to people who have never thought they could be interested in science. It&#8217;s not so much about what we know, as about how we know what we know. How do we know what is in the centre of the Earth, or what a black hole is, or where the continents were 600 million years ago? How did anyone ever figure these things out?</p>
<p>                    On his travels through time and space, he encounters a splendid collection of astonishingly eccentric, competitive, obsessive and foolish scientists, like the painfully shy Henry Cavendish who worked out many conundrums like how much the Earth weighed, but never bothered to tell anybody about many of his findings. In the company of such extraordinary people, Bill Bryson takes us with him on the ultimate eye-opening journey, and reveals the world in a way most of us have never seen it before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-nearly-everything-bill-bryson/">A Short History of Nearly Everything &#8211; Bill Bryson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Particle at the End of the Universe : Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atomic & Molecular Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Particle & High-energy Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research Methods: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books A Best Science Book of the Year for the Guardian, Financial Times, and New Scientist It was the universe&#8217;s most elusive particle, the linchpin for everything scientists dreamed up to explain how physics works. It had to be found. But projects as big as CERN&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Particle at the End of the Universe : Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books    </p>
<p>                    A Best Science Book of the Year for the Guardian, Financial Times, and New Scientist    </p>
<p>                    It was the universe&#8217;s most elusive particle, the linchpin for everything scientists dreamed up to explain how physics works. It had to be found. But projects as big as CERN&#8217;s Large Hadron Collider don&#8217;t happen without incredible risks &#8211; or occasional skulduggery. In the definitive account of the greatest science story of our time, acclaimed physicist Sean Carroll reveals the insights, rivalry, and wonder that fuelled the Higgs discovery, and takes us on a riveting and irresistible ride to the very edge of physics today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Particle at the End of the Universe : Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Intelligence : How a New Understanding of the Brain Will Lead to the Creation of Truly Intelligent Machines &#8211; Hawkins, Jeff, Sandra Blakeslee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-intelligence-how-a-new-understanding-of-the-brain-will-lead-to-the-creation-of-truly-intelligent-machines-hawkins-jeff-sandra-blakeslee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atomic & Molecular Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-intelligence-how-a-new-understanding-of-the-brain-will-lead-to-the-creation-of-truly-intelligent-machines-hawkins-jeff-sandra-blakeslee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the inventor of the PalmPilot comes a new and compelling theory of intelligence, brain function, and the future of intelligent machines Jeff Hawkins, the man who created the PalmPilot, Treo smart phone, and other handheld devices, has reshaped our relationship to computers. Now he stands ready to revolutionize both neuroscience and computing in one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-intelligence-how-a-new-understanding-of-the-brain-will-lead-to-the-creation-of-truly-intelligent-machines-hawkins-jeff-sandra-blakeslee-abridged/">On Intelligence : How a New Understanding of the Brain Will Lead to the Creation of Truly Intelligent Machines &#8211; Hawkins, Jeff, Sandra Blakeslee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the inventor of the PalmPilot comes a new and compelling theory of intelligence, brain function, and the future of intelligent machines     </p>
<p>                    Jeff Hawkins, the man who created the PalmPilot, Treo smart phone, and other handheld devices, has reshaped our relationship to computers. Now he stands ready to revolutionize both neuroscience and computing in one stroke, with a new understanding of intelligence itself.     </p>
<p>                    Hawkins develops a powerful theory of how the human brain works, explaining why computers are not intelligent and how, based on this new theory, we can finally build intelligent machines.     </p>
<p>                    The brain is not a computer, but a memory system that stores experiences in a way that reflects the true structure of the world, remembering sequences of events and their nested relationships and making predictions based on those memories. It is this memory-prediction system that forms the basis of intelligence, perception, creativity, and even consciousness.     </p>
<p>                    In an engaging style that will captivate audiences from the merely curious to the professional scientist, Hawkins shows how a clear understanding of how the brain works will make it possible for us to build intelligent machines, in silicon, that will exceed our human ability in surprising ways.     </p>
<p>                    Written with acclaimed science writer Sandra Blakeslee, On Intelligence promises to completely transfigure the possibilities of the technology age. It is a landmark book in its scope and clarity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-intelligence-how-a-new-understanding-of-the-brain-will-lead-to-the-creation-of-truly-intelligent-machines-hawkins-jeff-sandra-blakeslee-abridged/">On Intelligence : How a New Understanding of the Brain Will Lead to the Creation of Truly Intelligent Machines &#8211; Hawkins, Jeff, Sandra Blakeslee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
