<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Health &amp; Wholefood Cookery Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/health-wholefood-cookery/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/health-wholefood-cookery/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Health &amp; Wholefood Cookery Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/health-wholefood-cookery/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible. The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi    </p>
<p>                    Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic meal centred on a large cut of meat with few vegetables. On the &#8216;second plate&#8217;, championed by the farm-to-table movement, meat is free-range and vegetables are locally sourced. It&#8217;s better-tasting, and better for the planet, but the second plate&#8217;s architecture is identical to that of the first. It, too, disrupts ecological balances, causing soil depletion and nutrient loss &#8211; it just isn&#8217;t a sustainable way to farm or eat.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;third plate&#8217; offers a solution: an integrated system of vegetable, cereal and livestock production that is fully supported &#8211; in fact, dictated &#8211; by what we choose to cook for dinner. The Third Plate is where good farming and good food intersect.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wild Diet : Go Beyond Paleo to Burn Fat and Drop Up to 20 Pounds in 40 Days &#8211; Abel James (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Abel James, the ABC star and creator of the #1 Fat-Burning Man Show, shares his revolutionary weight-loss program in The Wild Diet &#8211; now a New York Times Bestseller! Can you really lose 20 pounds in 40 days while enjoying real butter, juicy burgers, chicken parmesan, chocolate, and even cheesecake? The answer might surprise you. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/">The Wild Diet : Go Beyond Paleo to Burn Fat and Drop Up to 20 Pounds in 40 Days &#8211; Abel James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Abel James, the ABC star and creator of the #1 Fat-Burning Man Show, shares his revolutionary weight-loss program in The Wild Diet &#8211; now a New York Times Bestseller!      </p>
<p>                    Can you really lose 20 pounds in 40 days while enjoying real butter, juicy burgers, chicken parmesan, chocolate, and even cheesecake?     </p>
<p>                    The answer might surprise you.     </p>
<p>                    By focusing on simple, fresh ingredients and nutrient-dense meals, The Wild Diet programs your body to burn fat as its main fuel source. Eating Wild, thousands of people across the world have dropped 20, 60, or even more than 100+ pounds without hunger&#8230; and often with minimal exercise.     </p>
<p>                    In The Wild Diet, you&#8217;ll find that we are not meant to starve ourselves, count calories, or avoid delicious food. We&#8217;re wired to eat luxuriously and live well without getting fat.     </p>
<p>                    If you think that you&#8217;re stuck with the genes you inherited and there&#8217;s nothing you can do about it, read closely. The Wild Diet paints a different picture, one in which we have the power to influence our genetic expression by taking control of the quality of food we eat, the way we move, and the environment around us.     </p>
<p>                    We once had access to an immense variety of fresh seasonal foods from small, local sources. Now we have access to few varieties of processed foods from a massive industrial system often thousands of miles from where we live. The secret to great health simply getting back to our wild roots and enjoying real, Wild foods grown on a farm and not in a factory.     </p>
<p>                    By prioritizing foods found in the natural world, rich in fiber and nutrients, your body will burn fat instead of sugar for energy. When you reduce your consumption of processed grains, sugars and other simple carbohydrates in favor of healthy plants and animals, you will be shocked by how quickly you can reverse the damage of decades of poor eating.     </p>
<p>                    The Wild Diet proves that it&#8217;s possible to get in best shape of your life while eating delicious foods like chicken parmesan, bacon cheeseburgers, and even chocolate pudding. If you want to know how to burn more fat by indulging in incredible meals and exercising less, it&#8217;s time to treat yourself to The Wild Diet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/">The Wild Diet : Go Beyond Paleo to Burn Fat and Drop Up to 20 Pounds in 40 Days &#8211; Abel James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report, Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report,  Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by Medicare when offered virtually at home.     </p>
<p>                     Dean Ornish, M.D., has directed revolutionary research proving, for the first time, that lifestyle changes can often reverse&#8211;undo!&#8211;the progression of many of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level.     </p>
<p>                     Medicare and many insurance companies now cover Dr. Ornish&#8217;s lifestyle medicine program for reversing chronic disease because it consistently achieves bigger changes in lifestyle, better clinical outcomes, larger cost savings, and greater adherence than have ever been reported&#8211;based on forty years of research published in the leading peer-reviewed medical and scientific journals.     </p>
<p>                     Now, in this landmark book, he and Anne Ornish present a simple yet powerful new unifying theory explaining why these same lifestyle changes can reverse so many different chronic diseases and how quickly these benefits occur. They describe what it is, why it works, and how you can do it:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Eat well a whole foods, plant-based diet naturally low in fat and sugar and high in flavor. The &#8220;Ornish diet&#8221; has been rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report for eleven years since 2011.<br />
                     &#8211; Move more moderate exercise such as walking<br />
                     &#8211; Stress less including meditation and gentle yoga practices<br />
                     &#8211; Love more how love and intimacy transform loneliness into healing     </p>
<p>                    With seventy recipes, easy-to-follow meal plans, tips for stocking your kitchen and eating out, recommended exercises, stress-reduction advice, and inspiring patient stories of life-transforming benefits&#8211;for example, several people improved so much after only nine weeks they were able to avoid a heart transplant&#8211;Undo It! empowers readers with new hope and new choices.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Undo It!     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Ornishes&#8217; work is elegant and simple and deserving of a Nobel Prize, since it can change the world!&#8221;&#8211;Richard Carmona, M.D., MPH, FACS, seventeenth Surgeon General of the United States     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;If you want to see what medicine will be like ten years from now, read this book today.&#8221;&#8211;Rita F. Redberg, M.D., editor in chief, JAMA Internal Medicine     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This is one of the most important books on health ever written.&#8221;&#8211;John Mackey, CEO, Whole Foods Market</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genius Foods : Become Smarter, Happier, and More Productive, While Protecting Your Brain Health for Life &#8211; Max Lugavere (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller Discover the critical link between your brain and the food you eat and change the way your brain ages, in this cutting-edge, practical guide to eliminating brain fog, optimizing brain health, and achieving peak mental performance from media personality and leading voice in health Max Lugavere. After his mother was diagnosed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/">Genius Foods : Become Smarter, Happier, and More Productive, While Protecting Your Brain Health for Life &#8211; Max Lugavere (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Discover the critical link between your brain and the food you eat and change the way your brain ages, in this cutting-edge, practical guide to eliminating brain fog, optimizing brain health, and achieving peak mental performance from media personality and leading voice in health Max Lugavere.     </p>
<p>                    After his mother was diagnosed with a mysterious form of dementia, Max Lugavere put his successful media career on hold to learn everything he could about brain health and performance. For the better half of a decade, he consumed the most up-to-date scientific research, talked to dozens of leading scientists and clinicians around the world, and visited the country&#8217;s best neurology departments-all in the hopes of understanding his mother&#8217;s condition.     </p>
<p>                    Now, in Genius Foods, Lugavere presents a comprehensive guide to brain optimization. He uncovers the stunning link between our dietary and lifestyle choices and our brain functions, revealing how the foods you eat directly affect your ability to focus, learn, remember, create, analyze new ideas, and maintain a balanced mood.     </p>
<p>                    Weaving together pioneering research on dementia prevention, cognitive optimization, and nutritional psychiatry, Lugavere distills groundbreaking science into actionable lifestyle changes. He shares invaluable insights into how to improve your brain power, including     </p>
<p>                    the nutrients that can boost your memory and improve mental clarity (and where to find them);<br />
                    the foods and tactics that can energize and rejuvenate your brain, no matter your age;<br />
                    a brain-boosting fat-loss method so powerful it has been called &#8220;biochemical liposuction&#8221;; and<br />
                    the foods that can improve your happiness, both now and for the long term.    </p>
<p>                    With Genius Foods, Lugavere offers a cutting-edge yet practical road map to eliminating brain fog and optimizing the brain&#8217;s health and performance today-and decades into the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/">Genius Foods : Become Smarter, Happier, and More Productive, While Protecting Your Brain Health for Life &#8211; Max Lugavere (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Blue Zones Kitchen : 100 Recipes to Live to 100 &#8211; DAN BUETTNER (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-blue-zones-kitchen-100-recipes-to-live-to-100-dan-buettner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-blue-zones-kitchen-100-recipes-to-live-to-100-dan-buettner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Best-selling author Dan Buettner debuts his first cookbook, filled with 100 longevity recipes inspired by the Blue Zones locations around the world, where people live the longest. Building on decades of research, longevity guru Dan Buettner has gathered 100 recipes inspired by the Blue Zones, home to the healthiest and happiest communities in the world. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blue-zones-kitchen-100-recipes-to-live-to-100-dan-buettner-abridged/">The Blue Zones Kitchen : 100 Recipes to Live to 100 &#8211; DAN BUETTNER (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Best-selling author Dan Buettner debuts his first cookbook, filled with 100 longevity recipes inspired by the Blue Zones locations around the world, where people live the longest.    </p>
<p>                     Building on decades of research, longevity guru Dan Buettner has gathered 100 recipes inspired by the Blue Zones, home to the healthiest and happiest communities in the world. Each dish&#8211;for example, Sardinian Herbed Lentil Minestrone; Costa Rican Hearts of Palm Ceviche; Cornmeal Waffles from Loma Linda, California; and Okinawan Sweet Potatoes&#8211;uses ingredients and cooking methods proven to increase longevity, wellness, and mental health. Complemented by mouthwatering photography, the recipes also include lifestyle tips (including the best times to eat dinner and proper portion sizes), all gleaned from countries as far away as Japan and as near as Blue Zones project cities in Texas. Innovative, easy to follow, and delicious, these healthy living recipes make the Blue Zones lifestyle even more attainable, thereby improving your health, extending your life, and filling your kitchen with happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blue-zones-kitchen-100-recipes-to-live-to-100-dan-buettner-abridged/">The Blue Zones Kitchen : 100 Recipes to Live to 100 &#8211; DAN BUETTNER (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book. Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book.     </p>
<p>                    Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. Why suffer from disease and ill health when the right food is proven to keep you healthy, and without the side effects of drugs? We can avoid heart disease, cancer and our other biggest killers if we use food as medicine, and the How Not To Die Cookbook offers a sustainable and delicious guide to preparing and eating the foods that will prevent and reverse fatal diseases.    </p>
<p>                    Featuring over 100 easy-to-follow, beautifully photographed plant-based recipes, with plenty of recipes suitable for vegetarians and vegans, the How Not To Die Cookbook merges cutting-edge science with everyday ingredients from the supermarket to help you and your family eat your way to better health and a longer life.    </p>
<p>                    All recipes in this cookbook have been fully anglicized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dreams & Their Interpretation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now! __________________________________________________________________________________ FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now!<br />
                    __________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver    </p>
<p>                    Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in his Sunday Times bestselling book, The 4 Pillar Plan, BBC One&#8217;s Dr Rangan Chatterjee creates an easily accessible plan for taking control of your health and your life.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Chatterjee believes that everyday health revolves around the following four pillars: relaxation, food, movement and sleep. By making small, achievable changes in each of these key areas you can create and maintain good health &#8211; and avoid illness. Top tips in each area include:     </p>
<p>                    * an electronic &#8216;sabbath&#8217; once a week<br />
                     * 12 hours every day without food<br />
                     * exposure to sunlight first thing each morning<br />
                     * walking at least 10,000 steps a day    </p>
<p>                    Based on cutting edge research and his own two decades&#8217; worth of experience as a doctor, this book contains fascinating case studies from real patients and is an inspiring and easy-to-follow guide to better health and happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health    </p>
<p>                    Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, bacteria and human cells have co-existed in a relationship that has ensured the health and equilibrium of our body. But now, much like the natural world outside of us, our internal environment is being irrevocably destroyed. The culprit: some of our most revered medical advances &#8211; antibiotics &#8211; which appear to be linked to the epidemics of asthma, eczema, obesity, certain forms of cancer, and other diseases plaguing modern society.    </p>
<p>                    In a book that stands as the Silent Spring of its day, Blaser sounds a provocative alarm that we ignore at our peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It Starts With Food &#8211; Revised Edition : Discover the Whole30 and Change Your Life in Unexpected Ways &#8211; Dallas Hartwig, Melissa Hartwig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/it-starts-with-food-revised-edition-discover-the-whole30-and-change-your-life-in-unexpected-ways-dallas-hartwig-melissa-hartwig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/it-starts-with-food-revised-edition-discover-the-whole30-and-change-your-life-in-unexpected-ways-dallas-hartwig-melissa-hartwig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Food can change your life in unexpected ways. It Starts With Food will show you how by outlining a clear, balanced, sustainable plan to change the way you eat forever &#8211; and transform your life in unexpected ways. Your success story begins with The Whole30,&#8217; Dallas and Melissa Hartwig&#8217;s powerful 30-day nutritional reset. Since 2009, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-starts-with-food-revised-edition-discover-the-whole30-and-change-your-life-in-unexpected-ways-dallas-hartwig-melissa-hartwig-abridged/">It Starts With Food &#8211; Revised Edition : Discover the Whole30 and Change Your Life in Unexpected Ways &#8211; Dallas Hartwig, Melissa Hartwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Food can change your life in unexpected ways. It Starts With Food will show you how by outlining a clear, balanced, sustainable plan to change the way you eat forever &#8211; and transform your life in unexpected ways. Your success story begins with The Whole30,&#8217; Dallas and Melissa Hartwig&#8217;s powerful 30-day nutritional reset. Since 2009, their underground Whole30 program has quietly led tens of thousands of people to weight loss, improved quality of life and a healthier relationship with food.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-starts-with-food-revised-edition-discover-the-whole30-and-change-your-life-in-unexpected-ways-dallas-hartwig-melissa-hartwig-abridged/">It Starts With Food &#8211; Revised Edition : Discover the Whole30 and Change Your Life in Unexpected Ways &#8211; Dallas Hartwig, Melissa Hartwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle, from the bestselling author of How Not to Die. Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle,  from the bestselling author of How Not to Die.    </p>
<p>                    Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any happier or healthier. As obesity rates and associated disease and impairments continue to rise, it&#8217;s time for a different approach.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet is a treasure trove of buried data and cutting-edge dietary research that Dr Michael Greger has translated into accessible, actionable advice with exciting tools and tricks that will help you to safely lose weight and eliminate unwanted body fat &#8211; for good.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Greger, renowned nutrition expert, physician, and founder of the NutritionFacts website, explores the many causes of obesity &#8211; from our genes to the portions on our plate to other environmental factors &#8211; and the many consequences, from diabetes to cancer to mental health issues. From there, Dr Greger breaks down a variety of approaches to weight loss, honing in on the optimal criteria that enable success, including: a diet high in fibre and water, a diet low in fat, salt, and sugar, and diet full of anti-inflammatory foods.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet then goes beyond food to explore the many other weight-loss accelerators available to us in our body&#8217;s systems, revealing how plant-based meals can be eaten at specific times to maximize our bodies&#8217; natural fat-burning activities. Dr Greger provides a clear plan not only for the ultimate weight loss diet, but also the approach we must take to unlock its greatest efficacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
