<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Travel Writing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/travel-writing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/travel-writing/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Travel Writing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/travel-writing/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck and Capa&#8217;s account of their journey through Cold War Russia is a classic piece of reportage and travel writing. A Penguin Classic Just after the Iron Curtain fell on Eastern Europe, Pulitzer Prize-winning author John Steinbeck and acclaimed war photographer Robert Capa ventured into the Soviet Union to report for the New York Herald [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/">A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck and Capa&#8217;s account of their journey through Cold War Russia is a classic piece of reportage and travel writing. </p>
<p>                    A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    Just after the Iron Curtain fell on Eastern Europe, Pulitzer Prize-winning author John Steinbeck and acclaimed war photographer Robert Capa ventured into the Soviet Union to report for the New York Herald Tribune. This rare opportunity took the famous travelers not only to Moscow and Stalingrad &#8211; now Volgograd &#8211; but through the countryside of the Ukraine and the Caucasus. Hailed by the New York Times as superb when it first appeared in 1948, A Russian Journal is the distillation of their journey and remains a remarkable memoir and unique historical document.</p>
<p>                    What they saw and movingly recorded in words and on film was what Steinbeck called the great other side there &#8230; the private life of the Russian people. Unlike other Western reporting about Russia at the time, A Russian Journal is free of ideological obsessions. Rather, Steinbeck and Capa recorded the grim realities of factory workers, government clerks, and peasants, as they emerged from the rubble of World War II&#8211;represented here in Capa&#8217;s stirring photographs alongside Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful prose. Through it all, we are given intimate glimpses of two artists at the height of their powers, answering their need to document human struggle. This edition features an introduction by Steinbeck scholar Susan Shillinglaw.</p>
<p>                     For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/">A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Into Thin Air : A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster &#8211; Jon Krakauer</title>
		<link>/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Climbing & Mountaineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; A harrowing tale of the perils of high-altitude climbing, a story of bad luck and worse judgment and of heartbreaking heroism. &#8211;PEOPLE A bank of clouds was assembling on the not-so-distant horizon, but journalist-mountaineer Jon Krakauer, standing on the summit of Mt. Everest, saw nothing that suggested that a murderous storm [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/">Into Thin Air : A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster &#8211; Jon Krakauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; A harrowing tale of the perils of high-altitude climbing, a story of bad luck and worse judgment and of heartbreaking heroism. &#8211;PEOPLE  </p>
<p>                    A bank of clouds was assembling on the not-so-distant horizon, but journalist-mountaineer Jon Krakauer, standing on the summit of Mt. Everest, saw nothing that suggested that a murderous storm was bearing down. He was wrong. The storm, which claimed five lives and left countless more&#8211;including Krakauer&#8217;s&#8211;in guilt-ridden disarray, would also provide the impetus for Into Thin Air, Krakauer&#8217;s epic account of the May 1996 disaster. </p>
<p>                    By writing Into Thin Air, Krakauer may have hoped to exorcise some of his own demons and lay to rest some of the painful questions that still surround the event. He takes great pains to provide a balanced picture of the people and events he witnessed and gives due credit to the tireless and dedicated Sherpas. He also avoids blasting easy targets such as Sandy Pittman, the wealthy socialite who brought an espresso maker along on the expedition. Krakauer&#8217;s highly personal inquiry into the catastrophe provides a great deal of insight into what went wrong. But for Krakauer himself, further interviews and investigations only lead him to the conclusion that his perceived failures were directly responsible for a fellow climber&#8217;s death. Clearly, Krakauer remains haunted by the disaster, and although he relates a number of incidents in which he acted selflessly and even heroically, he seems unable to view those instances objectively. In the end, despite his evenhanded and even generous assessment of others&#8217; actions, he reserves a full measure of vitriol for himself. </p>
<p>                    This updated trade paperback edition of Into Thin Air includes an extensive new postscript that sheds fascinating light on the acrimonious debate that flared between Krakauer and Everest guide Anatoli Boukreev in the wake of the tragedy. I have no doubt that Boukreev&#8217;s intentions were good on summit day, writes Krakauer in the postscript, dated August 1999. What disturbs me, though, was Boukreev&#8217;s refusal to acknowledge the possibility that he made even a single poor decision. Never did he indicate that perhaps it wasn&#8217;t the best choice to climb without gas or go down ahead of his clients. As usual, Krakauer supports his points with dogged research and a good dose of humility. But rather than continue the heated discourse that has raged since Into Thin Air&#8217;s denouncement of guide Boukreev, Krakauer&#8217;s tone is conciliatory; he points most of his criticism at G. Weston De Walt, who coauthored The Climb, Boukreev&#8217;s version of events. And in a touching conclusion, Krakauer recounts his last conversation with the late Boukreev, in which the two weathered climbers agreed to disagree about certain points. Krakauer had great hopes to patch things up with Boukreev, but the Russian later died in an avalanche on another Himalayan peak, Annapurna I. </p>
<p>                    In 1999, Krakauer received an Academy Award in Literature from the American Academy of Arts and Letters&#8211;a prestigious prize intended to honor writers of exceptional accomplishment. According to the Academy&#8217;s citation, Krakauer combines the tenacity and courage of the finest tradition of investigative journalism with the stylish subtlety and profound insight of the born writer. His account of an ascent of Mount Everest has led to a general reevaluation of climbing and of the commercialization of what was once a romantic, solitary sport; while his account of the life and death of Christopher McCandless, who died of starvation after challenging the Alaskan wilderness, delves even more deeply and disturbingly into the fascination of nature and the devastating effects of its lure on a young and curious mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/">Into Thin Air : A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster &#8211; Jon Krakauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Travels with Charley in Search of America &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/travels-with-charley-in-search-of-america-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/travels-with-charley-in-search-of-america-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An intimate journey across America, as told by one of its most beloved writers To hear the speech of the real America, to smell the grass and the trees, to see the colors and the light-these were John Steinbeck&#8217;s goals as he set out, at the age of fifty-eight, to rediscover the country he had [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travels-with-charley-in-search-of-america-john-steinbeck/">Travels with Charley in Search of America &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An intimate journey across America, as told by one of its most beloved writers    </p>
<p>                     To hear the speech of the real America, to smell the grass and the trees, to see the colors and the light-these were John Steinbeck&#8217;s goals as he set out, at the age of fifty-eight, to rediscover the country he had been writing about for so many years.    </p>
<p>                     With Charley, his French poodle, Steinbeck drives the interstates and the country roads, dines with truckers, encounters bears at Yellowstone and old friends in San Francisco. Along the way he reflects on the American character, racial hostility, the particular form of American loneliness he finds almost everywhere, and  the unexpected kindness of strangers.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travels-with-charley-in-search-of-america-john-steinbeck/">Travels with Charley in Search of America &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic In the two years after the 1939 publication of Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful The Grapes of Wrath, Steinbeck and his novel increasingly became the center of intense controversy and censorship. In search of a respite from the national stage, Steinbeck and his close friend, biologist Ed Ricketts, embarked on a month long marine specimen-collecting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/">The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic     </p>
<p>                    In the two years after the 1939 publication of Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful The Grapes of Wrath, Steinbeck and his novel increasingly became the center of intense controversy and censorship. In search of a respite from the national stage, Steinbeck and his close friend, biologist Ed Ricketts, embarked on a month long marine specimen-collecting expedition in the Gulf of California, which resulted in their collaboration on the Sea of Cortez. In 1951, after Ricketts&#8217; death, Steinbeck reissued his narrative portion of the work in memory of his friend and the inspiration for Cannery Row&#8217;s &#8220;Doc&#8221;. This exciting day-by-day account of their journey together is a rare blend of science, philosophy, and high-spirited adventure. This edition features an introduction by Richard Astro.     </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/">The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel With Children / Family Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* NOW WITH A NEW CHAPTER * &#8216;A hugely enjoyable romp through the pleasures and pitfalls of setting up home in a foreign land.&#8217;- Guardian Given the opportunity of a new life in rural Jutland, Helen Russell discovered a startling statistic: Denmark, land of long dark winters, cured herring, Lego and pastries, was the happiest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/">The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* NOW WITH A NEW CHAPTER *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A hugely enjoyable romp through the pleasures and pitfalls of setting up home in a foreign land.&#8217;- Guardian    </p>
<p>                    Given the opportunity of a new life in rural Jutland, Helen Russell discovered a startling statistic: Denmark, land of long dark winters, cured herring, Lego and pastries, was the happiest place on earth.    </p>
<p>                    Keen to know their secrets, Helen gave herself a year to uncover the formula for Danish happiness.    </p>
<p>                    From childcare, education, food and interior design to SAD and taxes, The Year of Living Danishly records a funny, poignant journey, showing us what the Danes get right, what they get wrong, and how we might all live a little more Danishly ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    In this new edition, six years on Helen reveals how her life and family have changed, and explores how Denmark, too &#8211; or. her understanding of it &#8211; has shifted. It&#8217;s a messy and flawed place, she concludes &#8211; but can still be a model for a better way of living.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/">The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Colour : Travels Through the Paintbox &#8211; Victoria Finlay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paintings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A rare and wonderful book&#8230; I could not be more enthusiastic.&#8217; Simon Winchester &#8216;A treasure trove of human history and obsession&#8230;the breadth of research and insight is dazzling.&#8217; Glasgow Herald Colour unlocks the history of the colours of the rainbow, and reveals how paints came to be invented, discovered, traded and used. This remarkable and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/">Colour : Travels Through the Paintbox &#8211; Victoria Finlay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A rare and wonderful book&#8230; I could not be more enthusiastic.&#8217; Simon Winchester    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A treasure trove of human history and obsession&#8230;the breadth of research and insight is dazzling.&#8217; Glasgow Herald    </p>
<p>                    Colour unlocks the history of the colours of the rainbow, and reveals how paints came to be invented, discovered, traded and used. This remarkable and beautifully written book, part travelogue part narrative history, remembers a time when red paint was really the colour of blood, when orange was the poison pigment, blue as expensive as gold, and yellow made from the urine of cows force-fed with mangoes. It looks at how green was carried by yaks along the silk road, and how an entire nation was founded on the colour purple.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A highly companionable guide, adventurous and romantic&#8217; Independent on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    Exciting, richly informative, and always surprising, Colour lifts the lid on the historical palette and unearths an astonishing wealth of stories about the quest for colours, and our efforts to understand them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/">Colour : Travels Through the Paintbox &#8211; Victoria Finlay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Sleep, There are Snakes : Life and Language in the Amazonian Jungle &#8211; Daniel Everett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dont-sleep-there-are-snakes-life-and-language-in-the-amazonian-jungle-daniel-everett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indigenous Peoples]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dont-sleep-there-are-snakes-life-and-language-in-the-amazonian-jungle-daniel-everett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Although Daniel Everett was a missionary, far from converting the Pirahas, they converted him. He shows the slow, meticulous steps by which he gradually mastered their language and his gradual realisation that its unusual nature closely reflected its speakers&#8217; startlingly original perceptions of the world. Everett describes how he began to realise that his discoveries [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-sleep-there-are-snakes-life-and-language-in-the-amazonian-jungle-daniel-everett-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Sleep, There are Snakes : Life and Language in the Amazonian Jungle &#8211; Daniel Everett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although Daniel Everett was a missionary, far from converting the Pirahas, they converted him. He shows the slow, meticulous steps by which he gradually mastered their language and his gradual realisation that its unusual nature closely reflected its speakers&#8217; startlingly original perceptions of the world.    </p>
<p>                    Everett describes how he began to realise that his discoveries about the Piraha language opened up a new way of understanding how language works in our minds and in our lives, and that this way was utterly at odds with Noam Chomsky&#8217;s universally accepted linguistic theories. The perils of passionate academic opposition were then swiftly conjoined to those of the Amazon in a debate whose outcome has yet to be won. Everett&#8217;s views are most recently discussed in Tom Wolfe&#8217;s bestselling The Kingdom of Speech.    </p>
<p>                    Adventure, personal enlightenment and the makings of a scientific revolution proceed together in this vivid, funny and moving book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-sleep-there-are-snakes-life-and-language-in-the-amazonian-jungle-daniel-everett-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Sleep, There are Snakes : Life and Language in the Amazonian Jungle &#8211; Daniel Everett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Geography of Genius : Lessons from the World&#8217;s Most Creative Places &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tag along on this New York Times bestselling &#8220;witty, entertaining romp&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) as Eric Winer travels the world, from Athens to Silicon Valley&#8211;and back through history, too&#8211;to show how creative genius flourishes in specific places at specific times. In this &#8220;intellectual odyssey, traveler&#8217;s diary, and comic novel all rolled into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/">The Geography of Genius : Lessons from the World&#8217;s Most Creative Places &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tag along on this New York Times bestselling &#8220;witty, entertaining romp&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) as Eric Winer travels the world, from Athens to Silicon Valley&#8211;and back through history, too&#8211;to show how creative genius flourishes in specific places at specific times.     </p>
<p>                    In this &#8220;intellectual odyssey, traveler&#8217;s diary, and comic novel all rolled into one&#8221; (Daniel Gilbert, author of Stumbling on Happiness), acclaimed travel writer Weiner sets out to examine the connection between our surroundings and our most innovative ideas. A &#8220;superb travel guide: funny, knowledgeable, and self-deprecating&#8221; (The Washington Post), he explores the history of places like Vienna of 1900, Renaissance Florence, ancient Athens, Song Dynasty Hangzhou, and Silicon Valley to show how certain urban settings are conducive to ingenuity. With his trademark insightful humor, this &#8220;big-hearted humanist&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal) walks the same paths as the geniuses who flourished in these settings to see if the spirit of what inspired figures like Socrates, Michelangelo, and Leonardo remains. In these places, Weiner asks, &#8220;What was in the air, and can we bottle it?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Fun and thought provoking&#8221; (Miami Herald), The Geography of Genius reevaluates the importance of culture in nurturing creativity and &#8220;offers a practical map for how we can all become a bit more inventive&#8221; (Adam Grant, author of Originals).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/">The Geography of Genius : Lessons from the World&#8217;s Most Creative Places &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Maps & Atlases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from the foreword     </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s nothing like vagabonding: taking time off from your normal life&#8211;from six weeks to four months to two years&#8211;to discover and experience the world on your own terms. In this one-of-a-kind handbook, veteran travel writer Rolf Potts explains how anyone armed with an independent spirit can achieve the dream of extended overseas travel. Now completely revised and updated, Vagabonding is an accessible and inspiring guide to     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; financing your travel time<br />
                     &#8211; determining your destination<br />
                     &#8211; adjusting to life on the road<br />
                     &#8211; working and volunteering overseas<br />
                     &#8211; handling travel adversity<br />
                     &#8211; re-assimilating back into ordinary life     </p>
<p>                     Praise for Vagabonding    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A crucial reference for any budget wanderer.&#8221;&#8211;Time    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The book is a meditation on the joys of hitting the road. . . . It&#8217;s also a primer for those with a case of pent-up wanderlust seeking to live the dream.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I couldn&#8217;t put this book down. It&#8217;s a whole different ethic of travel. . . . [Potts&#8217;s] practical advice might just convince you to enjoy that open-ended trip of a lifetime.&#8221;&#8211;Rick Steves     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Potts wants us to wander, to explore, to embrace the unknown, and, finally, to take our own damn time about it. I think this is the most sensible book of travel-related advice ever written.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Cahill, founding editor of Outside</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazillionaires : The Godfathers of Modern Brazil &#8211; Alex Cuadros (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year Award Wealth and power on the trail of the super-rich In 2012, Brazilian tycoon Eike Batista was the eighth richest man in the world, his $30bn fortune built on Brazil&#8217;s incredible natural resources. By the middle of 2013 he had lost it all, engulfed in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/">Brazillionaires : The Godfathers of Modern Brazil &#8211; Alex Cuadros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Financial Times  Business Book of the Year Award     </p>
<p>                    Wealth and power on the trail of the super-rich    </p>
<p>                    In 2012, Brazilian tycoon Eike Batista was the eighth richest man in the world, his $30bn fortune built on Brazil&#8217;s incredible natural resources. By the middle of 2013 he had lost it all, engulfed in scandal.    </p>
<p>                    Brazillionaires is a fast-paced account of Batista&#8217;s rise and fall: a story of helicopter flights, beach-front penthouses and high-speed car crashes. Along the way, it tells the parallel story of Brazil itself, a country caught in the cycle of boom and bust, renewed hope and dashed promise; a country where the hyper-rich are at the heart of the economy &#8211; and where their wealth can buy immense political power.    </p>
<p>                    Stefan Zweig said in 1941 that Brazil was the country of the future; Brazilians joke that it always will be. Today, rampant corruption and endemic inequality threaten to derail the new Brazilian Dream. The brazillionaires are the key to understanding that dream; through them Brazillionaires tells the story of their country&#8217;s past, present and future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/">Brazillionaires : The Godfathers of Modern Brazil &#8211; Alex Cuadros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Excellent Daughters : The Secret Lives of Young Women Who Are Transforming the Arab World &#8211; Katherine Zoepf (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For more than a decade, Katherine Zoepf has lived in or traveled throughout the Arab world, reporting on the lives of women, whose role in the region has never been more in flux. Only a generation ago, female adolescence as we know it in the West did not exist in the Middle East. There were [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/">Excellent Daughters : The Secret Lives of Young Women Who Are Transforming the Arab World &#8211; Katherine Zoepf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For more than a decade, Katherine Zoepf has lived in or traveled throughout the Arab world, reporting on the lives of women, whose role in the region has never been more in flux. Only a generation ago, female adolescence as we know it in the West did not exist in the Middle East. There were only children and married women. Today, young Arab women outnumber men in universities, and a few are beginning to face down religious and social tradition in order to live independently, to delay marriage, and to pursue professional goals. Hundreds of thousands of devout girls and women are attending Qur&#8217;anic schools&#8211;and using the training to argue for greater rights and freedoms from an Islamic perspective. And, in 2011, young women helped to lead antigovernment protests in the Arab Spring. But their voices have not been heard. Their stories have not been told. In Syria, before its civil war, she documents a complex society in the midst of soul searching about its place in the world and about the role of women. In Lebanon, she documents a country that on the surface is freer than other Arab nations but whose women must balance extreme standards of self-presentation with Islamic codes of virtue. In Abu Dhabi, Zoepf reports on a generation of Arab women who&#8217;ve found freedom in work outside the home. In Saudi Arabia she chronicles driving protests and women entering the retail industry for the first time. In the aftermath of Tahrir Square, she examines the crucial role of women in Egypt&#8217;s popular uprising. Deeply informed, heartfelt, and urgent, Excellent Daughters brings us a new understanding of the changing Arab societies&#8211;from 9/11 to Tahrir Square to the rise of ISIS&#8211;and gives voice to the remarkable women at the forefront of this change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/excellent-daughters-the-secret-lives-of-young-women-who-are-transforming-the-arab-world-katherine-zoepf-abridged/">Excellent Daughters : The Secret Lives of Young Women Who Are Transforming the Arab World &#8211; Katherine Zoepf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Down Under : Travels in a Sunburned Country &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/down-under-travels-in-a-sunburned-country-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/down-under-travels-in-a-sunburned-country-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It is the driest, flattest, hottest, most desiccated, infertile and climatically aggressive of all the inhabited continents and still Australia teems with life &#8211; a large portion of it quite deadly. In fact, Australia has more things that can kill you in a very nasty way than anywhere else. Ignoring such dangers &#8211; and yet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/down-under-travels-in-a-sunburned-country-bill-bryson-abridged/">Down Under : Travels in a Sunburned Country &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is the driest, flattest, hottest, most desiccated, infertile and climatically aggressive of all the inhabited continents and still Australia teems with life &#8211; a large portion of it quite deadly. In fact, Australia has more things that can kill you in a very nasty way than anywhere else.    </p>
<p>                    Ignoring such dangers &#8211; and yet curiously obsessed by them &#8211; Bill Bryson journeyed to Australia and promptly fell in love with the country. And who can blame him? The people are cheerful, extrovert, quick-witted and unfailingly obliging: their cities are safe and clean and nearly always built on water; the food is excellent; the beer is cold and the sun nearly always shines. Life doesn&#8217;t get much better than this&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/down-under-travels-in-a-sunburned-country-bill-bryson-abridged/">Down Under : Travels in a Sunburned Country &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Geography of Bliss &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-geography-of-bliss-eric-weiner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-geography-of-bliss-eric-weiner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What makes a nation happy? Is one country&#8217;s sense of happiness the same as another&#8217;s? In the last two decades, psychologists and economists have learned a lot about who&#8217;s happy and who isn&#8217;t. The Dutch are, the Romanians aren&#8217;t, and Americans are somewhere in between&#8230; After years of going to the world&#8217;s least happy countries, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geography-of-bliss-eric-weiner-abridged/">The Geography of Bliss &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What makes a nation happy? Is one country&#8217;s sense of happiness the same as another&#8217;s? In the last two decades, psychologists and economists have learned a lot about who&#8217;s happy and who isn&#8217;t. The Dutch are, the Romanians aren&#8217;t, and Americans are somewhere in between&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    After years of going to the world&#8217;s least happy countries, Eric Weiner, a veteran foreign correspondent, decided to travel and evaluate each country&#8217;s different sense of happiness and discover the nation that seemed happiest of all.     </p>
<p>                    *He discovers the relationship between money and happiness in tiny and extremely wealthy Qatar (and it&#8217;s not a good one)<br />
                    *He goes to Thailand, and finds that not thinking is a contented way of life.<br />
                    *He goes to the tiny Himalayan kingdom of Bhutan, and discovers they have an official policy of Gross National Happiness!<br />
                    *He asks himself why the British don&#8217;t do happiness?    </p>
<p>                    In Weiner&#8217;s quest to find the world&#8217;s happiest places, he eats rotten Icelandic shark, meditates in Bangalore, visits strip clubs in Bangkok and drinks himself into a stupor in Reykjavik. Full of inspired moments, The Geography of Bliss accomplishes a feat few travel books dare and even fewer achieve: to make you happier.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geography-of-bliss-eric-weiner-abridged/">The Geography of Bliss &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rocks, Minerals & Fossils]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Homer called it a divine substance. Plato described it as especially dear to the gods. As Mark Kurlansky so brilliantly relates here, salt has shaped civilisation from the beginning, and its story is a glittering, often surprising part of the history of mankind. Wars have been fought over salt and, while salt taxes secured empires [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Homer called it a divine substance. Plato described it as especially dear to the gods. As Mark Kurlansky so brilliantly relates here, salt has shaped civilisation from the beginning, and its story is a glittering, often surprising part of the history of mankind. Wars have been fought over salt and, while salt taxes secured empires across Europe and Asia, they have also inspired revolution &#8211; Gandhi&#8217;s salt march in 1930 began the overthrow of British rule in India.     </p>
<p>                    From the rural Sichuan province where the last home-made soya sauce is produced to the Cheshire brine springs that supplied salt around the globe, Mark Kurlansky has produced a kaleidoscope of world history, a multi-layered masterpiece that blends political, commercial, scientific, religious and culinary records into a rich and memorable tale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>50th Anniversary Edition &#8211; With an introduction by Caity Weaver, acclaimed New York Times journalist This cult classic of gonzo journalism is the best chronicle of drug-soaked, addle-brained, rollicking good times ever committed to the printed page. It is also the tale of a long weekend road trip that has gone down in the annals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/">Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>50th Anniversary Edition &#8211; With an introduction by Caity Weaver, acclaimed New York Times journalist     </p>
<p>                    This cult classic of gonzo journalism is the best chronicle of drug-soaked, addle-brained, rollicking good times ever committed to the printed page. It is also the tale of a long weekend road trip that has gone down in the annals of American pop culture as one of the strangest journeys ever undertaken.     </p>
<p>                    Also a major motion picture directed by Terry Gilliam, starring Johnny Depp and Benicio del Toro.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/">Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Sky Full of Birds &#8211; Matt Merritt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-sky-full-of-birds-matt-merritt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Birds & Birdwatching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-sky-full-of-birds-matt-merritt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Prose from a poet and a personal take on the spectacles&#8217; Chris Packham, author of Fingers in the Sparkle Jar Shortlisted for Richard Jefferies Society &#038; White Horse Bookshop Literary Prize 2017 Longlisted for the Wainwright Prize 2017 Britain is a nation of bird-lovers. However, few of us fully appreciate the sheer scale, variety and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-sky-full-of-birds-matt-merritt-abridged/">A Sky Full of Birds &#8211; Matt Merritt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prose from a poet and a personal take on the spectacles&#8217; Chris Packham, author of Fingers in the Sparkle Jar    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for Richard Jefferies Society &#038; White Horse Bookshop Literary Prize 2017<br />
                    Longlisted for the Wainwright Prize 2017    </p>
<p>                    Britain is a nation of bird-lovers. However, few of us fully appreciate the sheer scale, variety and drama of our avian life. From city-centre hunters to vast flocks straight out of the Arctic wilderness, much-loved dawn songsters to the exotic invaders of supermarket car parks, a host of remarkable wildlife spectacles are waiting to be discovered right outside our front doors.    </p>
<p>                    In A Sky Full of Birds, poet and nature writer Matt Merritt shares his passion for birdwatching by taking us to some of the great avian gatherings that occur around the British isles &#8211; from ravens in Anglesey and raptors on the Wirral, to Kent nightingales and Scottish capercaillies. By turns lyrical, informative and entertaining, he shows how natural miracles can be found all around us, if only we know where to look for them.    </p>
<p>                    A Sky Full of Birds is the perfect read for avid birdwatchers and a beautiful gift for lovers of nature and poetic prose.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-sky-full-of-birds-matt-merritt-abridged/">A Sky Full of Birds &#8211; Matt Merritt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Walk in the Woods : Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Outdoor Survival Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Walking, Hiking, Trekking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Appalachian Trail trail stretches from Georgia to Maine and covers some of the most breathtaking terrain in America-majestic mountains, silent forests, sparking lakes. If you&#8217;re going to take a hike, it&#8217;s probably the place to go. And Bill Bryson is surely the most entertaining guide you&#8217;ll find. He introduces us to the history and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/">A Walk in the Woods : Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Appalachian Trail trail stretches from Georgia to Maine and covers some of the most breathtaking terrain in America-majestic mountains, silent forests, sparking lakes. If you&#8217;re going to take a hike, it&#8217;s probably the place to go. And Bill Bryson is surely the most entertaining guide you&#8217;ll find. He introduces us to the history and ecology of the trail and to some of the other hardy (or just foolhardy) folks he meets along the way-and a couple of bears. Already a classic, A Walk in the Woods  will make you long for the great outdoors (or at least a comfortable chair to sit and read in).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/">A Walk in the Woods : Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Born to Run : The hidden tribe, the ultra-runners, and the greatest race the world has never seen &#8211; Christopher Mcdougall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/born-to-run-the-hidden-tribe-the-ultra-runners-and-the-greatest-race-the-world-has-never-seen-christopher-mcdougall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Extreme Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marathon & Cross-country Running]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Outdoor Survival Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Track & Field Sports, Athletics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/born-to-run-the-hidden-tribe-the-ultra-runners-and-the-greatest-race-the-world-has-never-seen-christopher-mcdougall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At the heart of Born to Run lies a mysterious tribe of Mexican Indians, the Tarahumara, who live quietly in canyons and are reputed to be the best distance runners in the world; in 1993, one of them, aged 57, came first in a prestigious 100-mile race wearing a toga and sandals. A small group [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/born-to-run-the-hidden-tribe-the-ultra-runners-and-the-greatest-race-the-world-has-never-seen-christopher-mcdougall-abridged/">Born to Run : The hidden tribe, the ultra-runners, and the greatest race the world has never seen &#8211; Christopher Mcdougall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the heart of Born to Run lies a mysterious tribe of Mexican Indians, the Tarahumara, who live quietly in canyons and are reputed to be the best distance runners in the world; in 1993, one of them, aged 57, came first in a prestigious 100-mile race wearing a toga and sandals. A small group of the world&#8217;s top ultra-runners (and the awe-inspiring author) make the treacherous journey into the canyons to try to learn the tribe&#8217;s secrets and then take them on over a course 50 miles long.    </p>
<p>                    With incredible energy and smart observation, McDougall tells this story while asking what the secrets are to being an incredible runner. Travelling to labs at Harvard, Nike, and elsewhere, he comes across an incredible cast of characters, including the woman who recently broke the world record for 100 miles and for her encore ran a 2:50 marathon in a bikini, pausing to down a beer at the 20 mile mark.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/born-to-run-the-hidden-tribe-the-ultra-runners-and-the-greatest-race-the-world-has-never-seen-christopher-mcdougall-abridged/">Born to Run : The hidden tribe, the ultra-runners, and the greatest race the world has never seen &#8211; Christopher Mcdougall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes. &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world. Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen. 54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves. Norway is the richest country on earth. 5 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world.    </p>
<p>                    Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen.    </p>
<p>                    54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves.    </p>
<p>                    Norway is the richest country on earth.    </p>
<p>                    5 per cent of Danish men have had sex with an animal.    </p>
<p>                    Michael Booth has lived among the Scandinavians, on and off, for over ten years, perplexed by their many strange paradoxes and character traits and equally bemused by the unquestioning enthusiasm for all things Nordic and hygge that has engulfed the rest of the world.     </p>
<p>                    He leaves his adopted home of Denmark and embarks on a journey through all five of the Nordic countries to discover who these curious tribes are, the secrets of their success and, most intriguing of all, what they think of each other. Along the way a more nuanced, often darker picture emerges of a region plagued by taboos, characterised by suffocating parochialism and populated by extremists of various shades.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The next Bill Bryson.&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Best Narrative Travel Book Award from the British Guild of Travel Writers</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Travel as a Political Act (Third Edition) &#8211; Rick Steves (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the world through travel is a vital way to shape our political views and our social awareness. These days, it&#8217;s more important than ever to engage in travel as an activist. In this fully revised edition of his award-winning book Travel as a Political Act, acclaimed author and activist Rick Steves explains how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/">Travel as a Political Act (Third Edition) &#8211; Rick Steves (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the world through travel is a vital way to shape our political views and our social awareness. These days, it&#8217;s more important than ever to engage in travel as an activist.    </p>
<p>                    In this fully revised edition of his award-winning book Travel as a Political Act, acclaimed author and activist Rick Steves explains how to travel thoughtfully and honestly, and to come home with a better understanding of how our nation fits into a universal puzzle. In Rick&#8217;s own words, travel connects us with nature, with culture, and most importantly, with people. When we experience the rest of the world, instead of fearing its diversity, we can learn to celebrate it.    </p>
<p>                    With entirely new chapters focused on the far-reaching impact of global events such as Brexit, Trump, and so much more, Rick shows readers how to travel with intention and an open mind. In times of political and cultural turmoil, his ardent philosophy rings truer than ever: beyond new experiences, great art, and tasty cuisine, travel emboldens us to become better citizens of this planet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/">Travel as a Political Act (Third Edition) &#8211; Rick Steves (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motorcycles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed as one of the most exciting books in the history of American letters, this modern epic became an instant bestseller upon publication in 1974, transforming a generation and continuing to inspire millions. A narration of a summer motorcycle trip undertaken by a father and his son, the book becomes a personal and philosophical odyssey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/">Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed as one of the most exciting books in the history of American letters, this modern epic became an instant bestseller upon publication in 1974, transforming a generation and continuing to inspire millions. A narration of a summer motorcycle trip undertaken by a father and his son, the book becomes a personal and philosophical odyssey into fundamental questions of how to live. Resonant with the confusions of existence, Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance is a touching and transcendent book of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/">Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER &#8216;Honest, funny and dripping with witty aphorisms. Extremely entertaining and enlightening [&#8230;] all the way to journey&#8217;s end&#8217; Herald One of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life, presents a travel guide [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Honest, funny and dripping with witty aphorisms. Extremely entertaining and enlightening [&#8230;] all the way to journey&#8217;s end&#8217; Herald     </p>
<p>                    One of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life, presents a travel guide with a difference &#8211; an exploration of why we travel, and what we learn along the way&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Few activities seem to promise as much happiness as going travelling: taking off for somewhere else, somewhere far from home, a place with more interesting weather, customs and landscapes. But although we are inundated with advice on where to travel to, we seldom ask why we go and how we might become more fulfilled by doing so.    </p>
<p>                    With the help of a selection of writers, artists and thinkers &#8211; including Flaubert, Edward Hopper, Wordsworth and Van Gogh &#8211; Alain de Botton provides invaluable insights into everything from holiday romance to hotel minibars, airports to sightseeing. The perfect antidote to those guides that tell us what to do when we get there, The Art of Travel tries to explain why we really went in the first place &#8211; and helpfully suggest how we might be happier on our journeys.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Delightful, profound, entertaining. I doubt if de Botton has written a dull sentence in his life&#8217; Jan Morris    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An elegant and subtle work, unlike any other. Beguiling&#8217; Colin Thubron, The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
