<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Economic Systems &amp; Structures Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/economic-systems-structures/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/economic-systems-structures/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Economic Systems &amp; Structures Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/economic-systems-structures/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Economic Facts and Fallacies : Second Edition &#8211; Thomas Sowell</title>
		<link>/economic-facts-and-fallacies-second-edition-thomas-sowell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/economic-facts-and-fallacies-second-edition-thomas-sowell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Economic Facts and Fallacies , Thomas Sowell exposes some of the most popular fallacies about economic issues in a lively manner that does not require any prior knowledge of economics. These fallacies include many beliefs widely disseminated in the media and by politicians, such as fallacies about urban problems, income differences, male-female economic differences, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/economic-facts-and-fallacies-second-edition-thomas-sowell/">Economic Facts and Fallacies : Second Edition &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In  Economic Facts and Fallacies , Thomas Sowell exposes some of the most popular fallacies about economic issues in a lively manner that does not require any prior knowledge of economics. These fallacies include many beliefs widely disseminated in the media and by politicians, such as fallacies about urban problems, income differences, male-female economic differences, as well as economic fallacies about academia, about race, and about Third World countries. Sowell shows that fallacies are not simply crazy ideas but in fact have a certain plausibility that gives them their staying power- and makes careful examination of their flaws both necessary and important.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/economic-facts-and-fallacies-second-edition-thomas-sowell/">Economic Facts and Fallacies : Second Edition &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Humankind : A Hopeful History &#8211; Rutger Bregman</title>
		<link>/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER A Guardian, Daily Telegraph, New Statesman and Daily Express Book of the Year &#8216;Hugely, highly and happily recommended&#8217; Stephen Fry &#8216;You should read Humankind. You&#8217;ll learn a lot (I did) and you&#8217;ll have good reason to feel better about the human race&#8217; Tim Harford &#8216;Made me see humanity from a fresh perspective&#8217; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/">Humankind : A Hopeful History &#8211; Rutger Bregman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER<br />
                    A Guardian, Daily Telegraph, New Statesman and Daily Express Book of the Year</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hugely, highly and happily recommended&#8217; Stephen Fry<br />
                    &#8216;You should read Humankind. You&#8217;ll learn a lot (I did) and you&#8217;ll have good reason to feel better about the human race&#8217; Tim Harford<br />
                    &#8216;Made me see humanity from a fresh perspective&#8217; Yuval Noah Harari</p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s a belief that unites the left and right, psychologists and philosophers, writers and historians. It drives the headlines that surround us and the laws that touch our lives. From Machiavelli to Hobbes, Freud to Dawkins, the roots of this belief have sunk deep into Western thought. Human beings, we&#8217;re taught, are by nature selfish and governed by self-interest.</p>
<p>                    Humankind makes a new argument: that it is realistic, as well as revolutionary, to assume that people are good. By thinking the worst of others, we bring out the worst in our politics and economics too.</p>
<p>                    In this major book, internationally bestselling author Rutger Bregman takes some of the world&#8217;s most famous studies and events and reframes them, providing a new perspective on the last 200,000 years of human history. From the real-life Lord of the Flies to the Blitz, a Siberian fox farm to an infamous New York murder, Stanley Milgram&#8217;s Yale shock machine to the Stanford prison experiment, Bregman shows how believing in human kindness and altruism can be a new way to think &#8211; and act as the foundation for achieving true change in our society.</p>
<p>                    It is time for a new view of human nature.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/">Humankind : A Hopeful History &#8211; Rutger Bregman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</title>
		<link>/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate. Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate.    </p>
<p>                    Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence to challenge the idea that different economic outcomes can be explained by any one factor, be it discrimination, exploitation, or genetics. This revised and enlarged edition also analyzes the human consequences of the prevailing social vision of these disparities and the policies based on that vision&#8211;from educational disasters to widespread crime and violence.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New New Thing : A Silicon Valley Story &#8211; Michael Lewis</title>
		<link>/the-new-new-thing-a-silicon-valley-story-michael-lewis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-new-thing-a-silicon-valley-story-michael-lewis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the weird glow of the dying millennium, Michael Lewis set out on a safari through Silicon Valley to find the world&#8217;s most important technology entrepreneur. He found this in Jim Clark, a man whose achievements include the founding of three separate billion-dollar companies. Lewis also found much more, and the result-the best-selling book The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-new-thing-a-silicon-valley-story-michael-lewis/">The New New Thing : A Silicon Valley Story &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the weird glow of the dying millennium, Michael Lewis set out on a safari through Silicon Valley to find the world&#8217;s most important technology entrepreneur. He found this in Jim Clark, a man whose achievements include the founding of three separate billion-dollar companies. Lewis also found much more, and the result-the best-selling book The New New Thing-is an ingeniously conceived history of the Internet revolution.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-new-thing-a-silicon-valley-story-michael-lewis/">The New New Thing : A Silicon Valley Story &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most powerful and instructive change manual you&#8217;ll ever read. It will persuade and inspire you to change your business, your work, and maybe your life.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, bestselling author of A Whole New Mind In Practically Radical, William C. Taylor, the New York Times bestselling co-author of Mavericks at Work offers a refreshing, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/">Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most powerful and instructive change manual you&#8217;ll ever read. It will persuade and inspire you to change your business, your work, and maybe your life.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, bestselling author of A Whole New Mind     </p>
<p>                    In Practically Radical, William C. Taylor, the New York Times bestselling co-author of Mavericks at Work offers a refreshing, rigorous new look at pragmatic ways to shake things up and make positive change in difficult times.     </p>
<p>                    Exploring how twenty-five for-profit companies and nonprofit organizations&#8211;including IBM, Zappos, Swatch, the Girl Scouts, and Interpol&#8211;made remarkable strides in tough circumstances, Practically Radical raises (and answers) the make-or-break questions facing today&#8217;s leaders in every field: Do you see opportunities the competition doesn&#8217;t see? The most successful organizations embrace one-of-a-kind ideas in a world filled with me-too thinking.Do you have new ideas about where to look for new ideas? Routine practices in one field can be revolutionary when they migrate to another.Are you the most of anything? In business today, the middle of the road is the road to ruin.Are you getting the best contributions from the most people? Change is not a game best played by loners.    </p>
<p>                    Anything but your typical business book, Practically Radical is a must-own for small business owners and CEOs, for managers at all levels, and innovators and entrepreneurs of every stripe.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/">Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE MONTH FROM THE WALL STREET JOURNAL: &#8220;Nothing Mr. Gilder says or writes is ever delivered at anything less than the fullest philosophical decibel&#8230; Mr. Gilder sounds less like a tech guru than a poet, and his words tumble out in a romantic cascade.&#8221; &#8220;Google&#8217;s algorithms assume the world&#8217;s future [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/">Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE MONTH      </p>
<p>                     FROM THE WALL STREET JOURNAL: &#8220;Nothing Mr. Gilder says or writes is ever delivered at anything less than the fullest philosophical decibel&#8230; Mr. Gilder sounds less like a tech guru than a poet, and his words tumble out in a romantic cascade.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Google&#8217;s algorithms assume the world&#8217;s future is nothing more than the next moment in a random process. George Gilder shows how deep this assumption goes, what motivates people to make it, and why it&#8217;s wrong: the future depends on human action.&#8221; &#8212; Peter Thiel, founder of PayPal and Palantir Technologies and author of Zero to One: Notes on Startups, or How to Build the Future     </p>
<p>                     The Age of Google, built on big data and machine intelligence, has been an awesome era. But it&#8217;s coming to an end. In Life after Google, George Gilder&#8211;the peerless visionary of technology and culture&#8211;explains why Silicon Valley is suffering a nervous breakdown and what to expect as the post-Google age dawns.     </p>
<p>                     Google&#8217;s astonishing ability to &#8220;search and sort&#8221; attracts the entire world to its search engine and countless other goodies&#8211;videos, maps, email, calendars&#8230;.And everything it offers is free, or so it seems. Instead of paying directly, users submit to advertising. The system of &#8220;aggregate and advertise&#8221; works&#8211;for a while&#8211;if you control an empire of data centers, but a market without prices strangles entrepreneurship and turns the Internet into a wasteland of ads.     </p>
<p>                     The crisis is not just economic. Even as advances in artificial intelligence induce delusions of omnipotence and transcendence, Silicon Valley has pretty much given up on security. The Internet firewalls supposedly protecting all those passwords and personal information have proved hopelessly permeable.     </p>
<p>                     The crisis cannot be solved within the current computer and network architecture. The future lies with the &#8220;cryptocosm&#8221;&#8211;the new architecture of the blockchain and its derivatives. Enabling cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin and ether, NEO and Hashgraph, it will provide the Internet a secure global payments system, ending the aggregate-and-advertise Age of Google.     </p>
<p>                     Silicon Valley, long dominated by a few giants, faces a &#8220;great unbundling,&#8221; which will disperse computer power and commerce and transform the economy and the Internet.     </p>
<p>                     Life after Google is almost here.     </p>
<p>                     For fans of &#8220;Wealth and Poverty,&#8221; &#8220;Knowledge and Power,&#8221; and &#8220;The Scandal of Money.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/">Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reinventing the Product : How to Transform your Business and Create Value in the Digital Age &#8211; Eric Schaeffer, David Sovie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Create the personalized and compelling experiences that today&#8217;s customers expect by harnessing AI and digital technologies to create smart connected products, with this cutting-edge guide from senior leaders at Accenture. Digital technology is both friend and foe: highly disruptive, yet it cannot be ignored. As traditional products transform into smart connected products faster than ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/">Reinventing the Product : How to Transform your Business and Create Value in the Digital Age &#8211; Eric Schaeffer, David Sovie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Create the personalized and compelling experiences that today&#8217;s customers expect by harnessing AI and digital technologies to create smart connected products, with this cutting-edge guide from senior leaders at Accenture.      </p>
<p>                    Digital technology is both friend and foe: highly disruptive, yet it cannot be ignored. As traditional products transform into smart connected products faster than ever before, companies that fail to make use of it now put themselves in the firing line for disintermediation or even eradication.     </p>
<p>                    However, digital technology is also the biggest opportunity for product-making businesses to create the next generation of goods in the marketplace. In Reinventing the Product, Eric Schaeffer and David Sovie, both Senior Managing Directors at Accenture, show how this reinvention is made possible, to deliver truly intelligent, and often even autonomous, products.     </p>
<p>                    Reinventing the Product makes the case for companies to rethink their product strategy, innovation and engineering processes, including:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; How to harness the opportunities of AI and digital technologies, such as IoT sensors, blockchain, advanced analytics, cloud and edge computing<br />
                    &#8211; Practical advice on transforming their entire culture to build the future of successful &#8216;living products&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Features case studies from global organizations such as Faurecia, Signify, Symmons and Haier and interviews with thought leaders from top companies including Amazon, ABB, Tesla, Samsung and Google    </p>
<p>                    This book provides the only advice any product-making company needs as it embarks on, or accelerates, its digitization journey.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/">Reinventing the Product : How to Transform your Business and Create Value in the Digital Age &#8211; Eric Schaeffer, David Sovie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Portfolios of the Poor : How the World&#8217;s Poor Live on $2 a Day &#8211; Daryl Collins, Jonathan Morduch, Stuart Rutherford, Orlanda Ruthven (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nearly forty percent of humanity lives on an average of two dollars a day or less. If you&#8217;ve never had to survive on an income so small, it is hard to imagine. How would you put food on the table, afford a home, and educate your children? How would you handle emergencies and old age? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/">Portfolios of the Poor : How the World&#8217;s Poor Live on $2 a Day &#8211; Daryl Collins, Jonathan Morduch, Stuart Rutherford, Orlanda Ruthven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nearly forty percent of humanity lives on an average of two dollars a day or less. If you&#8217;ve never had to survive on an income so small, it is hard to imagine. How would you put food on the table, afford a home, and educate your children? How would you handle emergencies and old age? Every day, more than a billion people around the world must answer these questions. Portfolios of the Poor is the first book to systematically explain how the poor find solutions to their everyday financial problems. The authors conducted year-long interviews with impoverished villagers and slum dwellers in Bangladesh, India, and South Africa&#8211;records that track penny by penny how specific households manage their money. The stories of these families are often surprising and inspiring. Most poor households do not live hand to mouth, spending what they earn in a desperate bid to keep afloat. Instead, they employ financial tools, many linked to informal networks and family ties. They push money into savings for reserves, squeeze money out of creditors whenever possible, run sophisticated savings clubs, and use microfinancing wherever available.<br />
                    Their experiences reveal new methods to fight poverty and ways to envision the next generation of banks for the &#8220;bottom billion.&#8221; Indispensable for those in development studies, economics, and microfinance, Portfolios of the Poor will appeal to anyone interested in knowing more about poverty and what can be done about it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/">Portfolios of the Poor : How the World&#8217;s Poor Live on $2 a Day &#8211; Daryl Collins, Jonathan Morduch, Stuart Rutherford, Orlanda Ruthven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WASHINGTON POST BESTSELLER Winner of the getAbstract 17th International Book Award &#8220;The Seventh Sense is a concept every businessman, diplomat, or student should aspire to master&#8211;a powerful idea, backed by stories and figures that will be impossible to forget.&#8221; &#8212; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs and Leonardo da Vinci Endless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/">The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    WASHINGTON POST BESTSELLER Winner of the getAbstract 17th International Book Award &#8220;The Seventh Sense is a concept every businessman, diplomat, or student should aspire to master&#8211;a powerful idea, backed by stories and figures that will be impossible to forget.&#8221; &#8212; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs and Leonardo da Vinci Endless terror. Refugee waves. An unfixable global economy. Surprising election results. New billion-dollar fortunes. Miracle medical advances. What if they were all connected? What if you could understand why?  The Seventh Sense is the story of what all of today&#8217;s successful figures see and feel: the forces that are invisible to most of us but explain everything from explosive technological change to uneasy political ripples. The secret to power now is understanding our new age of networks. Not merely the Internet, but also webs of trade, finance, and even DNA. Based on his years of advising generals, CEOs, and politicians, Ramo takes us into the opaque heart of our world&#8217;s rapidly connected systems and teaches us what the losers are not yet seeing&#8211;and what the victors of this age already know.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/">The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electricity, Electromagnetism & Magnetism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Power Generation & Distribution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory look at our national power grid&#8211;how it developed, its current flaws, and how it must be completely reimagined for our fast-approaching energy future. America&#8217;s electrical grid, an engineering triumph of the twentieth century, is turning out to be a poor fit for the present. It&#8217;s not just that the grid has grown old [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/">The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory look at our national power grid&#8211;how it developed, its current flaws, and how it must be completely reimagined for our fast-approaching energy future.     </p>
<p>                    America&#8217;s electrical grid, an engineering triumph of the twentieth century, is turning out to be a poor fit for the present. It&#8217;s not just that the grid has grown old and is now in dire need of basic repair. Today, as we invest great hope in new energy sources&#8211;solar, wind, and other alternatives&#8211;the grid is what stands most firmly in the way of a brighter energy future. If we hope to realize this future, we need to reimagine the grid according to twenty-first-century values. It&#8217;s a project which forces visionaries to work with bureaucrats, legislators with storm-flattened communities, moneymen with hippies, and the left with the right. And though it might not yet be obvious, this revolution is already well under way.     </p>
<p>                     Cultural anthropologist Gretchen Bakke unveils the many facets of America&#8217;s energy infrastructure, its most dynamic moments and its most stable ones, and its essential role in personal and national life. The grid, she argues, is an essentially American artifact, one which developed with us: a product of bold expansion, the occasional foolhardy vision, some genius technologies, and constant improvisation. Most of all, her focus is on how Americans are changing the grid right now, sometimes with gumption and big dreams and sometimes with legislation or the brandishing of guns.     </p>
<p>                    The Grid tells&#8211;entertainingly, perceptively&#8211;the story of what has been called the largest machine in the world: its fascinating history, its problematic present, and its potential role in a brighter, cleaner future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/">The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After everything that&#8217;s happened, how is it possible that conservatives still win debates about the economy? Time and again the right wins over voters by claiming that their solutions are only common sense, even as their tired policies of budgetary sacrifice and corporate plunder both create and prolong economic disaster. Why does the electorate keep [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After everything that&#8217;s happened, how is it possible that conservatives still win debates about the economy? Time and again the right wins over voters by claiming that their solutions are only common sense, even as their tired policies of budgetary sacrifice and corporate plunder both create and prolong economic disaster. Why does the electorate keep buying what they&#8217;re selling? According to political communications expert Anat Shenker-Osorio, it&#8217;s all about language,and not just theirs, but ours.In  Don&#8217;t Buy It  Shenker-Osorio diagnoses our economic discourse as stricken with faulty messages, deceptive personification, and, worst of all, a barely coherent concept of what the economy actually is. Opening up the business section of most newspapers or flipping on cable news unleashes an onslaught of economic doomsaying that treats the economy as an ungovernable force of nature. Alternately, by calling the economy  unhealthy&#8221; or  recovering&#8221; as we so often do, we unconsciously give it the status of a living being. No wonder Americans become willing to submit to any indignity required to keep the economy happy. Tread lightly, we can&#8217;t risk irritating the economy!Cutting through conservative myth-making, messaging muddles, and destructive misinformation, Shenker-Osorio suggests a new way to win the most important arguments of our day. The left doesn&#8217;t have to self-destruct every time matters economic come to the fore,there are metaphors and frames that can win, and Shenker-Osorio shows what they are and how to use them. Don&#8217;t Buy It  is a vital handbook for seizing victory in the economic debate. In the end, it convincingly shows that radically altering our politics and policies for the better is a matter of first changing the conversation,literally.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Poverty : Economic Possibilities for Our Time &#8211; Jeffrey D. Sachs, Foreword by Bono (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Book and man are brilliant, passionate, optimistic and impatient . . . Outstanding.&#8221; -The Economist The landmark exploration of economic prosperity and how the world can escape from extreme poverty for the world&#8217;s poorest citizens, from one of the world&#8217;s most renowned economists Hailed by Time as one of the world&#8217;s hundred most influential people, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/">The End of Poverty : Economic Possibilities for Our Time &#8211; Jeffrey D. Sachs, Foreword by Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Book and man are brilliant, passionate, optimistic and impatient . . . Outstanding.&#8221; -The Economist    </p>
<p>                    The landmark exploration of economic prosperity and how the world can escape from extreme poverty for the world&#8217;s poorest citizens, from one  of the world&#8217;s most renowned economists    </p>
<p>                     Hailed by Time as one of the world&#8217;s hundred most influential people, Jeffrey D. Sachs is renowned for his work around the globe advising economies in crisis. Now a classic of its genre, The End of Poverty distills more than thirty years of experience to offer a uniquely informed vision of the steps that can transform impoverished countries into prosperous ones. Marrying vivid storytelling with rigorous analysis, Sachs lays out a clear conceptual map of the world economy. Explaining his own work in Bolivia, Russia, India, China, and Africa, he offers an integrated set of solutions to the interwoven economic, political, environmental, and social problems that challenge the world&#8217;s poorest countries.    </p>
<p>                     Ten years after its initial publication, The End of Poverty remains an indispensible and influential work. In this 10th anniversary edition, Sachs presents an extensive new foreword assessing the progress of the past decade, the work that remains to be done, and how each of us can help. He also looks ahead across the next fifteen years to 2030, the United Nations&#8217; target date for ending extreme poverty, offering new insights and recommendations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/">The End of Poverty : Economic Possibilities for Our Time &#8211; Jeffrey D. Sachs, Foreword by Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumerism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about? Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about?     </p>
<p>                    Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to balance economic growth with the human costs of globalisation, Small Is Beautiful puts forward the revolutionary yet viable case for building our economies around the needs of communities, not corporations.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the 100 most influential books published since World War II&#8217; The Times Literary Supplement</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism    </p>
<p>                    NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST    </p>
<p>                    From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a four-hundred-year journey of this spirit of innovation and ambition through a series of Next Big Things &#8212; the inventions, techniques, and industries that drove American history forward: from the telegraph, the railroad, guns, radio, and banking to flight, suburbia, and sneakers, culminating with the Internet and mobile technology at the turn of the twenty-first century. The result is a thrilling alternative history of modern America that reframes events, trends, and people we thought we knew through the prism of the value that, for better or for worse, this nation holds dearest: capitalism.     </p>
<p>                    In a winning, accessible style, Bhu Srinivasan boldly takes on four centuries of American enterprise, revealing the unexpected connections that link them. We learn how Andrew Carnegie&#8217;s early job as a telegraph messenger boy paved the way for his leadership of the steel empire that would make him one of the nation&#8217;s richest men; how the gunmaker Remington reinvented itself in the postwar years to sell typewriters; how the inner workings of the Mafia mirrored the trend of consolidation and regulation in more traditional business; and how a 1950s infrastructure bill triggered a series of events that produced one of America&#8217;s most enduring brands: KFC. Reliving the heady early days of Silicon Valley, we are reminded that the start-up is an idea as old as America itself.    </p>
<p>                    Entertaining, eye-opening, and sweeping in its reach, Americana is an exhilarating new work of narrative history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Road to Reinvention : How to Drive Disruption and Accelerate Transformation &#8211; Josh Linkner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-road-to-reinvention-how-to-drive-disruption-and-accelerate-transformation-josh-linkner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-road-to-reinvention-how-to-drive-disruption-and-accelerate-transformation-josh-linkner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Companies, communities, and individuals fall for many reasons, but one of the most common and easily avoidable is the failure to reinvent. When people and organizations rest on prior successes rather than driving purposeful transformation, they discover too late that they have lost their market position altogether to competitors and external forces. The most successful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-to-reinvention-how-to-drive-disruption-and-accelerate-transformation-josh-linkner-abridged/">The Road to Reinvention : How to Drive Disruption and Accelerate Transformation &#8211; Josh Linkner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Companies, communities, and individuals fall for many reasons, but one of the most common and easily avoidable is the failure to reinvent. When people and organizations rest on prior successes rather than driving purposeful transformation, they discover too late that they have lost their market position altogether to competitors and external forces. The most successful companies, brands, and individuals make reinvention a regular part of their business strategies. Transformation demands an ongoing process of discovery and imagination, and The Road to Reinvention lays out a systematic approach for continually challenging and reinventing yourself and your business. Venture capitalist and serial entrepreneur Josh Linkner identifies six elements in any business that are ripe for reinvention and shares examples, methods, and step-by-step techniques for creating deliberate, productive disruption. Throughout The Road to Reinvention, Linkner also explores the history the great rise, unprecedented fall, and now rebirth of his beloved hometown, Detroit.<br />
                    First rising to greatness as the result of breathtaking innovation, Detroit had generations of booming growth before succumbing to apathy, atrophy, and finally bankruptcy. Now, the city is rising from the ashes and driving sustainable success through an intense focus on reinvention. Linkner brings an insider&#8217;s view of this incredible story of grit, determination, and creativity, sharing his perspective on Detroit&#8217;s successes and setbacks as a profound example of large-scale organizational and personal transformation. Change is inevitable. You need to decide: Will you drive that change, or be driven away by it? Will you disrupt or be disrupted? By choosing to deliberately reimagine your own status quo, you can secure a strong future for both your company and your career.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-to-reinvention-how-to-drive-disruption-and-accelerate-transformation-josh-linkner-abridged/">The Road to Reinvention : How to Drive Disruption and Accelerate Transformation &#8211; Josh Linkner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Referral Engine &#8211; John Jantsch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The small business guru behind Duct Tape Marketing shares his most valuable lesson: how to get your customers to do your best marketing for you. The power of glitzy advertising and elaborate marketing campaigns is on the wane; word- of-mouth referrals are what drive business today. People trust the recommendation of a friend, family member, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/">The Referral Engine &#8211; John Jantsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The small business guru behind Duct Tape Marketing shares his most valuable lesson: how to get your customers to do your best marketing for you.   The power of glitzy advertising and elaborate marketing campaigns is on the wane; word- of-mouth referrals are what drive business today. People trust the recommendation of a friend, family member, colleague, or even stranger with similar tastes over anything thrust at them by a faceless company.  Most business owners believe that whether customers refer them is entirely out of their hands. But science shows that people can&#8217;t help recommending products and services to their friends-it&#8217;s an instinct wired deep in the brain. And smart businesses can tap into that hardwired desire.  Marketing expert John Jantsch offers practical techniques for harnessing the power of referrals to ensure a steady flow of new customers. Keep those customers happy, and they will refer your business to even more customers. Some of Jantsch&#8217;s strategies include:  -Talk with your customers, not at them. Thanks to social networking sites, companies of any size have the opportunity to engage with their customers on their home turf as never before-but the key is listening.  -The sales team is the most important part of your marketing team. Salespeople are the company&#8217;s main link to customers, who are the main source of referrals. Getting them on board with your referral strategy is critical.  -Educate your customers. Referrals are only helpful if they&#8217;re given to the right people. Educate your customers about whom they should be talking to.  The secret to generating referrals lies in understanding the Customer Referral Cycle-the way customers refer others to your company who, in turn, generate even more referrals. Businesses can ensure a healthy referral cycle by moving customers and prospects along the path of Know, Like, Trust, Try, Buy, Repeat, and Refer. If everyone in an organization keeps this sequence in mind, Jantsch argues, your business will generate referrals like a well-oiled machine.  This practical, smart, and original guide is essential reading for any company looking to grow without a fat marketing budget.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/">The Referral Engine &#8211; John Jantsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Building Social Business : The New Kind of Capitalism that Serves Humanity&#8217;s Most Pressing Needs &#8211; Muhammad Yunus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/building-social-business-the-new-kind-of-capitalism-that-serves-humanitys-most-pressing-needs-muhammad-yunus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-profitmaking Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/building-social-business-the-new-kind-of-capitalism-that-serves-humanitys-most-pressing-needs-muhammad-yunus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Muhammad Yunus, the practical visionary who pioneered microcredit and, with his Grameen Bank, won the 2006 Nobel Peace Prize, has developed a new dimension for capitalism which he calls &#8220;social business.&#8221; The social business model has been adopted by corporations, entrepreneurs, and social activists across the globe. Its goal is to create self-supporting, viable commercial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-social-business-the-new-kind-of-capitalism-that-serves-humanitys-most-pressing-needs-muhammad-yunus-abridged/">Building Social Business : The New Kind of Capitalism that Serves Humanity&#8217;s Most Pressing Needs &#8211; Muhammad Yunus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Muhammad Yunus, the practical visionary who pioneered microcredit and, with his Grameen Bank, won the 2006 Nobel Peace Prize, has developed a new dimension for capitalism which he calls &#8220;social business.&#8221; The social business model has been adopted by corporations, entrepreneurs, and social activists across the globe. Its goal is to create self-supporting, viable commercial enterprises that generate economic growth as they produce goods and services to fulfill human needs. In  Building Social Business , Yunus shows how social business can be put into practice and explains why it holds the potential to redeem the failed promise of free-market enterprise.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-social-business-the-new-kind-of-capitalism-that-serves-humanitys-most-pressing-needs-muhammad-yunus-abridged/">Building Social Business : The New Kind of Capitalism that Serves Humanity&#8217;s Most Pressing Needs &#8211; Muhammad Yunus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Meat Racket : The Secret Takeover of America&#8217;s Food Business &#8211; Christopher Leonard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An investigative journalist takes you inside the corporate meat industry&#8211;a shocking, in-depth report every American should read. How much do you know about the meat on your dinner plate? Journalist Christopher Leonard spent more than a decade covering the country&#8217;s biggest meat companies, including four years as the national agribusiness reporter for the Associated Press. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/">The Meat Racket : The Secret Takeover of America&#8217;s Food Business &#8211; Christopher Leonard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An investigative journalist takes you inside the corporate meat industry&#8211;a shocking, in-depth report every American should read.     </p>
<p>                    How much do you know about the meat on your dinner plate? Journalist Christopher Leonard spent more than a decade covering the country&#8217;s biggest meat companies, including four years as the national agribusiness reporter for the Associated Press. Now he delivers the first comprehensive look inside the industrial meat system, exposing how a handful of companies executed an audacious corporate takeover of the nation&#8217;s meat supply.     </p>
<p>                    Leonard&#8217;s revealing account shines a light on the inner workings of Tyson Foods, a pioneer of the industrial system that dominates the market. You&#8217;ll learn how the food industry got to where it is today, and how companies like Tyson have escaped the scrutiny they deserve. You&#8217;ll discover how these companies are able to raise meat prices for consumers while pushing down the price they pay to farmers. And you&#8217;ll even see how big business and politics have derailed efforts to change the system, from a years-long legal fight in Iowa to the Obama administration&#8217;s recent failed attempt to pass reforms.     </p>
<p>                    Important, timely, and explosive, The Meat Racket is an unvarnished portrait of the food industry that now dominates America&#8217;s heartland.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/">The Meat Racket : The Secret Takeover of America&#8217;s Food Business &#8211; Christopher Leonard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capitalism without Capital : The Rise of the Intangible Economy &#8211; Jonathan Haskel, Stian Westlake (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/capitalism-without-capital-the-rise-of-the-intangible-economy-jonathan-haskel-stian-westlake-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/capitalism-without-capital-the-rise-of-the-intangible-economy-jonathan-haskel-stian-westlake-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Early in the twenty-first century, a quiet revolution occurred. For the first time, the major developed economies began to invest more in intangible assets, like design, branding, and software, than in tangible assets, like machinery, buildings, and computers. For all sorts of businesses, the ability to deploy assets that one can neither see nor touch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-without-capital-the-rise-of-the-intangible-economy-jonathan-haskel-stian-westlake-abridged/">Capitalism without Capital : The Rise of the Intangible Economy &#8211; Jonathan Haskel, Stian Westlake (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Early in the twenty-first century, a quiet revolution occurred. For the first time, the major developed economies began to invest more in intangible assets, like design, branding, and software, than in tangible assets, like machinery, buildings, and computers. For all sorts of businesses, the ability to deploy assets that one can neither see nor touch is increasingly the main source of long-term success. But this is not just a familiar story of the so-called new economy. Capitalism without Capital shows that the growing importance of intangible assets has also played a role in some of the larger economic changes of the past decade, including the growth in economic inequality and the stagnation of productivity. Jonathan Haskel and Stian Westlake explore the unusual economic characteristics of intangible investment and discuss how an economy rich in intangibles is fundamentally different from one based on tangibles. Capitalism without Capital concludes by outlining how managers, investors, and policymakers can exploit the characteristics of an intangible age to grow their businesses, portfolios, and economies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-without-capital-the-rise-of-the-intangible-economy-jonathan-haskel-stian-westlake-abridged/">Capitalism without Capital : The Rise of the Intangible Economy &#8211; Jonathan Haskel, Stian Westlake (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A classic.-Jay Conrad Levinson, author of Guerrilla Marketing Now in paperback, the bestselling business playbook that introduced a simple framework for turbocharging any organization. What if you could create the finest, most profitable and best-run version of your business without wasting precious dollars on a thousand different strategies? Legendary sales expert Chet Holmes says you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/">Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A classic.-Jay Conrad Levinson, author of Guerrilla Marketing     </p>
<p>                    Now in paperback, the bestselling business playbook that introduced a simple framework for turbocharging any organization.     </p>
<p>                     What if you could create the finest, most profitable and best-run version of your business without wasting precious dollars on a thousand different strategies? Legendary sales expert Chet Holmes says you can. All you need is to focus on twelve key areas of improvement&#8211;and practice them over and over with pigheaded discipline.     </p>
<p>                     The Ultimate Sales Machine is essential reading for anyone who wants to transform their organization into a high-performing, moneymaking force. By spending just an hour per week on crucial aspects of your business&#8211;from sales and marketing to management and hiring&#8211;you can systematically improve how your business operates. With practical tools, real-life examples, and proven strategies presented in Holmes&#8217; signature tell-it-like-it-is style, this book will show you how to:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Teach your team to work smarter, not harder<br />
                     &#8211; Get more bang from your marketing for less<br />
                     &#8211; Perfect every sales interaction by working on sales, not just in sales<br />
                     &#8211; Land your dream clients     </p>
<p>                    For every CEO, manager, and business owner who wants to take their organization to the next level, The Ultimate Sales Machine will put you and your company on the path to success&#8211;and help you stay there!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/">Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Only the Paranoid Survive : How to Exploit the Crisis Points That Challenge Every Company &#8211; Andrew S. Grove (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/only-the-paranoid-survive-how-to-exploit-the-crisis-points-that-challenge-every-company-andrew-s-grove-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/only-the-paranoid-survive-how-to-exploit-the-crisis-points-that-challenge-every-company-andrew-s-grove-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Andy Grove, founder and former CEO of Intel shares his strategy for success as he takes the reader deep inside the workings of a major company in Only the Paranoid Survive. Under Andy Grove&#8217;s leadership, Intel became the world&#8217;s largest chip maker and one of the most admired companies in the world. In Only the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/only-the-paranoid-survive-how-to-exploit-the-crisis-points-that-challenge-every-company-andrew-s-grove-abridged/">Only the Paranoid Survive : How to Exploit the Crisis Points That Challenge Every Company &#8211; Andrew S. Grove (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Andy Grove, founder and former CEO of Intel shares his strategy for success as he takes the reader deep inside the workings of a major company in Only the Paranoid Survive.     </p>
<p>                    Under Andy Grove&#8217;s leadership, Intel became the world&#8217;s largest chip maker and one of the most admired companies in the world. In Only the Paranoid Survive, Grove reveals his strategy for measuring the nightmare moment every leader dreads&#8211;when massive change occurs and a company must, virtually overnight, adapt or fall by the wayside&#8211;in a new way.     </p>
<p>                    Grove calls such a moment a Strategic Inflection Point, which can be set off by almost anything: mega-competition, a change in regulations, or a seemingly modest change in technology. When a Strategic Inflection Point hits, the ordinary rules of business go out the window. Yet, managed right, a Strategic Inflection Point can be an opportunity to win in the marketplace and emerge stronger than ever.     </p>
<p>                    Grove underscores his message by examining his own record of success and failure, including how he navigated the events of the Pentium flaw, which threatened Intel&#8217;s reputation in 1994, and how he has dealt with the explosions in growth of the Internet. The work of a lifetime, Only the Paranoid Survive is a classic of managerial and leadership skills.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/only-the-paranoid-survive-how-to-exploit-the-crisis-points-that-challenge-every-company-andrew-s-grove-abridged/">Only the Paranoid Survive : How to Exploit the Crisis Points That Challenge Every Company &#8211; Andrew S. Grove (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Third Pillar : How Markets and the State Leave the Community Behind &#8211; Raghuram Rajan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-pillar-how-markets-and-the-state-leave-the-community-behind-raghuram-rajan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-pillar-how-markets-and-the-state-leave-the-community-behind-raghuram-rajan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 From one of the most important economic thinkers of our time, a brilliant and far-seeing analysis of the current populist backlash against globalization and how revitalising community can save liberal market democracy. Raghuram Rajan, author of the 2010 FT &#038; Goldman-Sachs [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-pillar-how-markets-and-the-state-leave-the-community-behind-raghuram-rajan-abridged/">The Third Pillar : How Markets and the State Leave the Community Behind &#8211; Raghuram Rajan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019    </p>
<p>                                From one of the most important economic thinkers of our time, a brilliant and far-seeing analysis of the current populist backlash against globalization and how revitalising community can save liberal market democracy.     </p>
<p>                              Raghuram Rajan, author of the 2010 FT &#038; Goldman-Sachs Book of the Year Fault Lines, has an unparalleled vantage point onto the social and economic consequences of globalization and their ultimate effect on politics and society.     </p>
<p>                              In The Third Pillar he offers up a magnificent big-picture framework for understanding how three key forces &#8211; the economy, society, and the state &#8211; interact, why things begin to break down, and how we can find our way back to a more secure and stable plane.    </p>
<p>                              The &#8216;third pillar&#8217; of the title is society. Economists all too often understand their field as the relationship between the market and government, and leave social issues for other people. That&#8217;s not just myopic, Rajan argues; it&#8217;s dangerous. All economics is actually socioeconomics &#8211; all markets are embedded in a web of human relations, values and norms. As he shows, throughout history, technological innovations have ripped the market out of old webs and led to violent backlashes, and to what we now call populism. Eventually, a new equilibrium is reached, but it can be ugly and messy, especially if done wrong.     </p>
<p>                              Right now, we&#8217;re doing it wrong. As markets scale up, government scales up with it, concentrating economic and political power in flourishing central hubs and leaving the periphery to decompose, figuratively and even literally. Instead, Rajan offers a way to rethink the relationship between the market and civil society and argues for a return to strengthening and empowering local communities as an antidote to growing despair and unrest.    </p>
<p>                              The Third Pillar is a masterpiece of explication, a book that will be a classic of its kind for its offering of a wise, authoritative and humane explanation of the forces that have wrought such a sea change in our lives. His ultimate argument that decision-making has to be watered at the grass roots or our democracy will continue to wither is sure to be both provocative and agenda-setting across the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-pillar-how-markets-and-the-state-leave-the-community-behind-raghuram-rajan-abridged/">The Third Pillar : How Markets and the State Leave the Community Behind &#8211; Raghuram Rajan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job? That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves. The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job?     </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves.     </p>
<p>                    The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even many full-time and professional jobs are experiencing this precarious shift. Within a decade, a near-majority of the 145 million employed Americans will be impacted. Add to that the steamroller of automation, robots and artificial intelligence already replacing millions of workers and projected to obsolesce millions more, and the jobs picture starts looking grim.     </p>
<p>                    Now a weird yet historic mash-up of Silicon Valley technology and Wall Street greed is thrusting upon us the latest economic fraud: the so-called sharing economy, with companies like Uber, Airbnb and TaskRabbit allegedly liberating workers to become independent and their own CEOs, hiring themselves out for ever-smaller jobs and wages while the companies profit.     </p>
<p>                    But this share the crumbs economy is just the tip of a looming iceberg that the middle class is drifting toward. Raw Deal: How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers, by veteran journalist Steven Hill, is an exposé that challenges conventional thinking, and the hype celebrating this new economy, by showing why the vision of the techno sapien leaders and their Ayn Rand libertarianism is a dead end.     </p>
<p>                    In Raw Deal, Steven Hill proposes pragmatic policy solutions to transform the US economy and its safety net and social contract, launching a new kind of deal to restore power back into the hands of American workers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capitalism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; James Fulcher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/capitalism-a-very-short-introduction-james-fulcher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/capitalism-a-very-short-introduction-james-fulcher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is capitalism? Is capitalism the same everywhere? Is there an alternative? The word &#8216;capitalism&#8217; is one that is heard and used frequently, but what is capitalism really all about, and what does it mean? This Very Short Introduction addresses questions such as &#8216;what is capital?&#8217; before discussing the history and development of capitalism through [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-a-very-short-introduction-james-fulcher-abridged/">Capitalism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; James Fulcher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is capitalism? Is capitalism the same everywhere? Is there an alternative?     </p>
<p>                    The word &#8216;capitalism&#8217; is one that is heard and used frequently, but what is capitalism really all about, and what does it mean? This Very Short Introduction addresses questions such as &#8216;what is capital?&#8217; before discussing the history and development of capitalism through several detailed case studies, ranging from the tulipomania of 17th century Holland, the Great Depression of the 1930s, and in this new edition, the impact of the global financial crisis that started in 2007-8.    </p>
<p>                    James Fulcher looks at the different forms that capitalism takes in Britain, Japan, Sweden, and the United States, and explores whether capitalism has escaped the nation-state by going global. It ends by asking whether there is an alternative to capitalism, discussing socialism, communal and cooperative experiments, and the alternatives proposed by environmentalists.    </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books are the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-a-very-short-introduction-james-fulcher-abridged/">Capitalism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; James Fulcher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating investigation combining history, science and ideas, William Davies shows how well-being influences all aspects of our lives: business, finance, marketing and smart technology. This book will make you rethink everything from the way you work, the power of the &#8216;Nudge&#8217;, the ever-expanding definitions of depression, and the commercialization of your most private feelings. The Happiness Industry is a shocking and brilliantly argued warning about the new religion of the age: our emotions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a rational explanation of the ways in which the AI revolution will affect us all. Tackling the implications of Artificial Intelligence on growth, productivity, inflation and the distribution of wealth and power, THE AI ECONOMY also examines coming changes to the the way we educate, work and spend our leisure time.    </p>
<p>                    A fundamentally optimistic view which will help you plan for changing times, this book explains AI and leads you towards a more certain future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Textile Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 2015 BANCROFT PRIZE WINNER OF THE 2015 PHILIP TAFT PRIZE FINALIST FOR THE 2015 PULITZER PRIZE FOR HISTORY SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2015 CUNDHILL PRIZE IN HISTORICAL LITERATURE Economist BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015 &#8216;Knowledgeable and stunning&#8217; Orhan Pamuk &#8216;A masterpiece of the historian&#8217;s craft&#8217; The Nation For about 900 years, from 1000 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/">Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 2015 BANCROFT PRIZE<br />
                    WINNER OF THE 2015 PHILIP TAFT PRIZE<br />
                    FINALIST FOR THE 2015 PULITZER PRIZE FOR HISTORY<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2015 CUNDHILL PRIZE IN HISTORICAL LITERATURE<br />
                    Economist BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Knowledgeable and stunning&#8217; Orhan Pamuk     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A masterpiece of the historian&#8217;s craft&#8217; The Nation    </p>
<p>                    For about 900 years, from 1000 to 1900, cotton was the world&#8217;s most important manufacturing industry. It remains a vast business &#8211; if all the cotton bales produced in 2013 had been stacked on top of each other they would have made a somewhat unstable tower 40,000 miles high.      </p>
<p>                    Sven Beckert&#8217;s superb new book is a history of the overwhelming role played by cotton in dictating the shape of our world. It is both a gripping narrative and a brilliant case history of how the world works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/">Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commodities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous decision and examine the psychological factors behind bad financial practices in several economic sectors.  This book-winner of a 2014 Axiom Business Book award gold medal-begins with the unbroken string of successes that helped Paul achieve a jet-setting lifestyle and land a key spot with the Chicago Mercantile Exchange. It then describes the circumstances leading up to Paul&#8217;s $1.6 million loss and the essential lessons he learned from it-primarily that, although there are as many ways to make money in the markets as there are people participating in them, all losses come from the same few sources. Investors lose money in the markets either because of errors in their analysis or because of psychological barriers preventing the application of analysis.<br />
                    While all analytical methods have some validity and make allowances for instances in which they do not work, psychological factors can keep an investor in a losing position, causing him to abandon one method for another in order to rationalize the decisions already made. Paul and Moynihan&#8217;s cautionary tale includes strategies for avoiding loss tied to a simple framework for understanding, accepting, and dodging the dangers of investing, trading, and speculating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>23 Things They Don&#8217;t Tell You About Capitalism &#8211; Ha-Joon Chang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/23-things-they-dont-tell-you-about-capitalism-ha-joon-chang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/23-things-they-dont-tell-you-about-capitalism-ha-joon-chang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ha-Joon Chang&#8217;s 23 Things They Don&#8217;t Tell You About Capitalism turns received economic wisdom on its head to show you how the world really works. In this revelatory book, Ha-Joon Chang destroys the biggest myths of our times and shows us an alternative view of the world, including: There&#8217;s no such thing as a &#8216;free&#8217; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/23-things-they-dont-tell-you-about-capitalism-ha-joon-chang-abridged/">23 Things They Don&#8217;t Tell You About Capitalism &#8211; Ha-Joon Chang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ha-Joon Chang&#8217;s 23 Things They Don&#8217;t Tell You About Capitalism turns received economic wisdom on its head to show you how the world really works.     </p>
<p>                      In this revelatory book, Ha-Joon Chang destroys the biggest myths of our times and shows us an alternative view of the world, including:     </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s no such thing as a &#8216;free&#8217; market<br />
                    Globalization isn&#8217;t making the world richer<br />
                    We don&#8217;t live in a digital world &#8211; the washing machine has changed lives more than the internet<br />
                    Poor countries are more entrepreneurial than rich ones<br />
                    Higher paid managers don&#8217;t produce better results    </p>
<p>                      We don&#8217;t have to accept things as they are any longer. Ha-Joon Chang is here to show us there&#8217;s a better way.     </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Lively, accessible and provocative &#8230; read this book&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;A witty and timely debunking of some of the biggest myths surrounding the global economy&#8217; &#8211; Observer    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;The new kid on the economics block &#8230; Chang&#8217;s iconoclastic attitude has won him fans&#8217; &#8211; Independent on Sunday    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Lucid &#8230; audacious &#8230; increasingly influential &#8230; will provoke physical symptoms of revulsion if you are in any way involved in high finance&#8217; &#8211; Guardian    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Important &#8230; persuasive &#8230; an engaging case for a more caring era of globalization&#8217; &#8211; Financial Times    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;A must-read &#8230; incisive and entertaining&#8217; &#8211; New Statesman Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Ha-Joon Chang is a Reader in the Political Economy of Development at the University of Cambridge. He is author of Kicking Away the Ladder: Development Strategy in Historical Perspective, which won the 2003 Gunnar Myrdal Prize, and Bad Samaritans: Rich Nations, Poor Policies and the Threat to the Developing World. Since the beginning of the 2008 economic crisis, he has been a regular contributor to the Guardian, and a vocal critic of the failures of our economic system.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/23-things-they-dont-tell-you-about-capitalism-ha-joon-chang-abridged/">23 Things They Don&#8217;t Tell You About Capitalism &#8211; Ha-Joon Chang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drugs Trade / Drug Trafficking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organized Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like Ryanair or Apple. So when the drug cartels start to think like big business, the only way to understand them is using economics.     </p>
<p>                    In Narconomics, Tom Wainwright meets everyone from coca farmers in secret Andean locations, deluded heads of state in presidential palaces, journalists with a price on their head, gang leaders who run their empires from dangerous prisons and teenage hitmen on city streets &#8211; all in search of the economic truth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations & Safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers. Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell    </p>
<p>                    Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers.    </p>
<p>                    Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into the hands of the &#8216;managers&#8217;. Burnham explains how Capitalism had virtually lost its control, and would be displaced not by labour, nor by socialism, but by the rule of administartors in business and in government.    </p>
<p>                    This revolution, he posited, is as broad as the world and as comprehensive as human society, asking &#8220;Why is &#8216;totalitarianism&#8217; not the issue?&#8221; &#8220;Can civilization be destroyed?&#8221; And &#8220;Why is the New Deal something bigger than Roosevelt can handle?&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    In a volume extraordinary for its dispassionate handling of those and other fundamental questions, James Burnham explores fully the implications of the managerial revolution.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capitalism and Freedom &#8211; Milton Friedman, Foreword by Binyamin Appelbaum (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of TIME magazine&#8217;s All-TIME 100 Best Nonfiction Books One of Times Literary Supplement&#8217;s Hundred Most Influential Books Since the War One of National Review&#8217;s 100 Best Nonfiction Books of the Century One of Intercollegiate Studies Institute&#8217;s 50 Best Books of the 20th Century How can we benefit from the promise of government while avoiding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/">Capitalism and Freedom &#8211; Milton Friedman, Foreword by Binyamin Appelbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of TIME magazine&#8217;s All-TIME 100 Best Nonfiction Books<br />
                     One of Times Literary Supplement&#8217;s Hundred Most Influential Books Since the War<br />
                     One of National Review&#8217;s 100 Best Nonfiction Books of the Century<br />
                      One of Intercollegiate Studies Institute&#8217;s 50 Best Books of the 20th Century  How can we benefit from the promise of government while avoiding the threat it poses to individual freedom? In this classic book, Milton Friedman provides the definitive statement of an immensely influential economic philosophy&#8211;one in which competitive capitalism serves as both a device for achieving economic freedom and a necessary condition for political freedom.     </p>
<p>                     First published in 1962, Friedman&#8217;s Capitalism and Freedom is one of the most significant works of economic theory ever written. Enduring in its eminence and esteem, it has sold nearly a million copies in English, has been translated into eighteen languages, and continues to inform economic thinking and policymaking around the world. This new edition includes prefaces written by Friedman for both the 1982 and 2002 reissues of the book, as well as a new foreword by Binyamin Appelbaum, lead economics writer for the New York Times editorial board.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/">Capitalism and Freedom &#8211; Milton Friedman, Foreword by Binyamin Appelbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
