<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cultural Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/cultural-studies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/cultural-studies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Cultural Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/cultural-studies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve &#8211; Stephen Greenblatt</title>
		<link>/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bolder, even, than the ambitious books for which Stephen Greenblatt is already renowned, The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve explores the enduring story of humanity&#8217;s first parents. Comprising only a few ancient verses, the story of Adam and Eve has served as a mirror in which we seem to glimpse the whole, long [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/">The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve &#8211; Stephen Greenblatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bolder, even, than the ambitious books for which Stephen Greenblatt is already renowned, The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve explores the enduring story of humanity&#8217;s first parents. Comprising only a few ancient verses, the story of Adam and Eve has served as a mirror in which we seem to glimpse the whole, long history of our fears and desires, as both a hymn to human responsibility and a dark fable about human wretchedness.    </p>
<p>                     Tracking the tale into the deep past, Greenblatt uncovers the tremendous theological, artistic, and cultural investment over centuries that made these fictional figures so profoundly resonant in the Jewish, Christian, and Muslim worlds and, finally, so very &#8220;real&#8221; to millions of people even in the present. With the uncanny brilliance he previously brought to his depictions of William Shakespeare and Poggio Bracciolini (the humanist monk who is the protagonist of The Swerve), Greenblatt explores the intensely personal engagement of Augustine, Durer, and Milton in this mammoth project of collective creation, while he also limns the diversity of the story&#8217;s offspring: rich allegory, vicious misogyny, deep moral insight, and some of the greatest triumphs of art and literature.    </p>
<p>                     The biblical origin story, Greenblatt argues, is a model for what the humanities still have to offer: not the scientific nature of things, but rather a deep encounter with problems that have gripped our species for as long as we can recall and that continue to fascinate and trouble us today.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/">The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve &#8211; Stephen Greenblatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler</title>
		<link>/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Gender]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the better &#8211; and thus we don&#8217;t like to talk or even think about the extent of our selfishness. This is &#8220;the elephant in the brain.&#8221; Such<br />
                    an introspective taboo makes it hard for us to think clearly about our nature and the explanations for our behavior. The aim of this book, then, is to confront our hidden motives directly &#8211; to track down the darker, unexamined corners of our psyches and blast them with floodlights. Then, once<br />
                    everything is clearly visible, we can work to better understand ourselves: Why do we laugh? Why are artists sexy? Why do we brag about travel? Why do we prefer to speak rather than listen?</p>
<p>                    Our unconscious motives drive more than just our private behavior; they also infect our venerated social institutions such as Art, School, Charity, Medicine, Politics, and Religion. In fact, these institutions are in many ways designed to accommodate our hidden motives, to serve covert agendas alongside their &#8220;official&#8221; ones. The existence of big hidden motives can upend the usual political debates, leading one to question the legitimacy of these social institutions, and of standard policies<br />
                    designed to favor or discourage them. You won&#8217;t see yourself &#8211; or the world &#8211; the same after confronting the elephant in the brain.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Distinction : A Social Critique of the Judgement of Taste &#8211; Pierre Bourdieu (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No judgement of taste is innocent &#8211; we are all snobs. Pierre Bourdieu&#8217;s Distinction brilliantly illuminates the social pretentions of the middle classes in the modern world, focusing on the tastes and preferences of the French bourgeoisie. First published in 1979, the book is at once a vast ethnography of contemporary France and a dissection [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/">Distinction : A Social Critique of the Judgement of Taste &#8211; Pierre Bourdieu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No judgement of taste is innocent &#8211; we are all snobs. Pierre Bourdieu&#8217;s Distinction brilliantly illuminates the social pretentions of the middle classes in the modern world, focusing on the tastes and preferences of the French bourgeoisie. First published in 1979, the book is at once a vast ethnography of contemporary France and a dissection of the bourgeois mind.     </p>
<p>                    In the course of everyday life we constantly choose between what we find aesthetically pleasing, and what we consider tacky, merely trendy, or ugly. Taste is not pure. Bourdieu demonstrates that our different aesthetic choices are all distinctions &#8211; that is, choices made in opposition to those made by other classes. This fascinating work argues that the social world functions simultaneously as a system of power relations and as a symbolic system in which minute distinctions of taste become the basis for social judgement.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/">Distinction : A Social Critique of the Judgement of Taste &#8211; Pierre Bourdieu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When to Rob a Bank : A Rogue Economist&#8217;s Guide to the World &#8211; Steven D. Levitt, Stephen J. Dubner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/when-to-rob-a-bank-a-rogue-economists-guide-to-the-world-steven-d-levitt-stephen-j-dubner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/when-to-rob-a-bank-a-rogue-economists-guide-to-the-world-steven-d-levitt-stephen-j-dubner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is the ultimate guide to the world of the Freak. Renegade thinkers and bestselling sensations Levitt and Dubner have carefully curated the very best of their blogs, conversations, wisecracks and advice from the last decade to reveal the outlandish truth about everything from lying to bankrobbing, fast food to sex taxes. &#8216;We are all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-to-rob-a-bank-a-rogue-economists-guide-to-the-world-steven-d-levitt-stephen-j-dubner-abridged/">When to Rob a Bank : A Rogue Economist&#8217;s Guide to the World &#8211; Steven D. Levitt, Stephen J. Dubner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the ultimate guide to the world of the Freak. Renegade thinkers  and bestselling sensations Levitt and Dubner have carefully curated the  very best of their blogs, conversations, wisecracks and advice from the  last decade to reveal the outlandish truth about everything from lying  to bankrobbing, fast food to sex taxes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We are all Freakonomists now&#8217; Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A phenomenon &#8230; their approach has won them a cult following&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Lie back and let Levitt and Dubner&#8217;s bouncy prose style carry you along from one peculiarity to the next&#8217; Sunday Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You are guaranteed a good time&#8217; Financial Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-to-rob-a-bank-a-rogue-economists-guide-to-the-world-steven-d-levitt-stephen-j-dubner-abridged/">When to Rob a Bank : A Rogue Economist&#8217;s Guide to the World &#8211; Steven D. Levitt, Stephen J. Dubner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historiography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Liberation & Independence, Post-colonialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton In this highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our  understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton    </p>
<p>                    In this  highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of  Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a  powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for writers, philosophers  and colonial administrators to deal with the &#8216;otherness&#8217; of eastern  culture, customs and beliefs. He traces this view through the writings  of Homer, Nerval and Flaubert, Disraeli and Kipling, whose imaginative  depictions have greatly contributed to the West&#8217;s romantic and exotic  picture of the Orient. Drawing on his own experiences as an Arab  Palestinian living in the West, Said examines how these ideas can be a  reflection of European imperialism and racism.<br />
                    &#8216;Beautifully patterned and passionately argued&#8217;<br />
                    New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Very exciting &#8230; his case is not merely persuasive, but conclusive&#8217;<br />
                    John Leonard, New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>For Small Creatures Such As We : Rituals and reflections for finding wonder &#8211; Sasha Sagan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/for-small-creatures-such-as-we-rituals-and-reflections-for-finding-wonder-sasha-sagan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanist & Secular Alternatives To Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/for-small-creatures-such-as-we-rituals-and-reflections-for-finding-wonder-sasha-sagan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sasha Sagan&#8217;s parents &#8211; the astronomer Carl Sagan and the writer and producer, Ann Druyan &#8211; taught her that the natural world and vast cosmos are full of profound beauty, and that science reveals truths more wondrous than any myth or fable. When Sagan herself became a mother, she began her own hunt for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-small-creatures-such-as-we-rituals-and-reflections-for-finding-wonder-sasha-sagan-abridged/">For Small Creatures Such As We : Rituals and reflections for finding wonder &#8211; Sasha Sagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sasha Sagan&#8217;s parents &#8211; the astronomer Carl Sagan and the writer and producer, Ann Druyan &#8211; taught her that the natural world and vast cosmos are full of profound beauty, and that science reveals truths more wondrous than any myth or fable. When Sagan herself became a mother, she began her own hunt for the phenomena behind our most treasured occasions &#8211; from births to deaths, holidays to weddings, anniversaries, and more &#8211; growing these roots into a new set of rituals for her young daughter to honour the joy and significance of each experience without relying on a religious framework.    </p>
<p>                    Part memoir, part handbook and part social history, For Small Creatures Such as We is a luminous exploration of all of Earth&#8217;s marvels that requires no faith in order to be believed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-small-creatures-such-as-we-rituals-and-reflections-for-finding-wonder-sasha-sagan-abridged/">For Small Creatures Such As We : Rituals and reflections for finding wonder &#8211; Sasha Sagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Culture &#8211; Edward T. Hall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned American anthropologist comes a proud celebration of human capacities. For too long, people have taken their own ways of life for granted, ignoring the vast, international cultural community that srrounds them. Humankind must now embark on the difficult journey beyond culture, to the discovery of a lost self a sense of perspective. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/">Beyond Culture &#8211; Edward T. Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned American anthropologist comes a proud celebration of human capacities. For too long, people have taken their own ways of life for granted, ignoring the vast, international cultural community that srrounds them. Humankind must now embark on the difficult journey beyond culture, to the discovery of a lost self a sense of perspective. By holding up a mirror, Hall permits us to see the awesome grip of unconscious culture. With concrete examples ranging from James Joyce&#8217;s Finnegans Wake to the mating habits of the bowerbird of New Guinea, Hall shows us ourselves. Beyond Culture is a book about self-discovery; it is a voyage we all must embark on if mankind is to survive.     </p>
<p>                    Fascinating and emotionally challenging. . . . The book&#8217;s graceful, non-technical style and the many illuminating, real-life illustrations make it a delight to read. &#8211;Library Journal    </p>
<p>                    Hall&#8217;s book helps us to rethink our values. . . . We come away from it exhilarated. &#8211;Ashley Montagu     </p>
<p>                    In this penetrating analysis of the culturally determined yet &#8216;unconscious&#8217; attitudes that mold our thought, feeling, communication and behavior. . . . Hall makes explicit taken-for-granted linguistic patterns, body rhythms, personality dynamics, educational goals. . . . Many of Hall&#8217;s ideas are original and incisive . . . [and] should reward careful readers with new ways of thinking about themselves and others. &#8211;Publishers Weekly    </p>
<p>                    A fascintaing book which stands beside The Hidden Dimension and The Silent Language to prove Hall one of the most original anthropologists of our era. &#8211;Paul Bohannan</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/">Beyond Culture &#8211; Edward T. Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late    </p>
<p>                    A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and living standards. The bottom line of this outrage is the same; people are demanding their governments do more to improve their lives faster, something which policymakers are unable to deliver under conditions of anaemic growth. Rising income inequality and a stagnant economy are threats to both the developed and the developing world, and leaders can no longer afford to ignore this gathering storm.    </p>
<p>                    In Edge of Chaos, Dambisa Moyo sets out the new political and economic challenges facing the world, and the specific, radical solutions needed to resolve these issues and reignite global growth. Dambisa enumerates the four headwinds of demographics, inequality, commodity scarcity and technological innovation that are driving social and economic unrest, and argues for a fundamental retooling of democratic capitalism to address current problems and deliver better outcomes in the future. In the twenty-first century, a crisis in one country can quickly become our own, and fragile economies produce a fragile international community. Edge of Chaos is a warning for advanced and emerging nations alike: we must reverse the dramatic erosion in growth, or face the consequences of a fragmented and unstable global future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fox &#8211; Martin Wallen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fox-martin-wallen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fox-martin-wallen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Foxes live throughout the world in widely different habitats from forest to desert to the Arctic. What is surprising, though, is that scientists admit that very little is actually known about the lives and habits of foxes. The reason, which this book explores in depth, is that foxes are almost universally despised as being wicked. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fox-martin-wallen-abridged/">Fox &#8211; Martin Wallen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Foxes live throughout the world in widely different habitats from forest to desert to the Arctic. What is surprising, though, is that scientists admit that very little is actually known about the lives and habits of foxes. The reason, which this book explores in depth, is that foxes are almost universally despised as being wicked. From the time of Aristotle, naturalists have succumbed to the general bias against foxes, either openly asserting that foxes are barely worthy of consideration or worrying about the health threat they pose. While this low regard is understandable, since foxes steal chickens and have a strong odour, they are strikingly beautiful animals possessed of a startling intelligence. Throughout Europe and Asia, folk tales and myths have built up around the fox, depicting it variously as unrepentant thief and seducer, shapeshifter and deceiver, as an outlaw whose primary purpose is to disrupt human social order. The fear and loathing people feel (paradoxically mixed with fascination) toward foxes are reflected in the many fox-terms that have entered different languages.<br />
                    In Japan, for example, various plants are identified with fox-names to indicate how they are supposedly used by foxes in an alternate universe. The contradictory attitudes toward foxes are exemplified in America and Europe by their classification as vermin at the same time as they are preserved and propagated by foxhunters and fur trappers, and depicted as loveable furry creatures in the movies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fox-martin-wallen-abridged/">Fox &#8211; Martin Wallen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stoned : Jewelry, Obsession, and How Desire Shapes the World &#8211; Aja Raden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stoned-jewelry-obsession-and-how-desire-shapes-the-world-aja-raden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Jewellery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fashion & Textiles: Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewellery & Beadcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stoned-jewelry-obsession-and-how-desire-shapes-the-world-aja-raden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As entertaining as it is incisive, Stoned is a raucous journey through the history of human desire for what is rare, and therefore precious. What makes a stone a jewel? What makes a jewel priceless? And why do we covet beautiful things? In this brilliant account of how eight jewels shaped the course of history, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stoned-jewelry-obsession-and-how-desire-shapes-the-world-aja-raden-abridged/">Stoned : Jewelry, Obsession, and How Desire Shapes the World &#8211; Aja Raden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As entertaining as it is incisive, Stoned is a raucous journey through the history of human desire for what is rare, and therefore precious.  What makes a stone a jewel? What makes a jewel priceless? And why do we covet beautiful things? In this brilliant account of how eight jewels shaped the course of history, jeweler and scientist Aja Raden tells an original and often startling story about our unshakeable addiction to beauty and the darker side of human desire.  What moves the world is what moves each of us: desire. Jewelry-which has long served as a stand-in for wealth and power, glamor and success-has birthed cultural movements, launched political dynasties, and started wars. Masterfully weaving together pop science and history, Stoned breaks history into three categories-Want, Take, and Have-and explains what the diamond on your finger has to do with the GI Bill, why green-tinted jewelry has been exalted by so many cultures, why the glass beads that bought Manhattan for the Dutch were initially considered a fair trade, and how the French Revolution started over a coveted necklace.<br />
                    Studded with lively personalities and fascinating details, Stoned tells the remarkable story of our abiding desire for the rare and extraordinary.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stoned-jewelry-obsession-and-how-desire-shapes-the-world-aja-raden-abridged/">Stoned : Jewelry, Obsession, and How Desire Shapes the World &#8211; Aja Raden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler, Robin Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Gender]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler, Robin Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the better &#8211; and thus we don&#8217;t like to talk or even think about the extent of our selfishness. This is &#8220;the elephant in the brain.&#8221; Such<br />
                    an introspective taboo makes it hard for us to think clearly about our nature and the explanations for our behavior. The aim of this book, then, is to confront our hidden motives directly &#8211; to track down the darker, unexamined corners of our psyches and blast them with floodlights. Then, once<br />
                    everything is clearly visible, we can work to better understand ourselves: Why do we laugh? Why are artists sexy? Why do we brag about travel? Why do we prefer to speak rather than listen?    </p>
<p>                    Our unconscious motives drive more than just our private behavior; they also infect our venerated social institutions such as Art, School, Charity, Medicine, Politics, and Religion. In fact, these institutions are in many ways designed to accommodate our hidden motives, to serve covert agendas alongside their &#8220;official&#8221; ones. The existence of big hidden motives can upend the usual political debates, leading one to question the legitimacy of these social institutions, and of standard policies<br />
                    designed to favor or discourage them. You won&#8217;t see yourself &#8211; or the world &#8211; the same after confronting the elephant in the brain.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler, Robin Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Story Of Sushi : An Unlikely Story of Raw Fish and Rice &#8211; Trevor Corson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking With Fish & Seafood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Editor&#8217;s Choice Everything you never knew about sushi&#8211; its surprising origins, the colorful lives of its chefs, and the bizarre behavior of the creatures that compose it Trevor Corson takes us behind the scenes at America&#8217;s first sushi-chef training academy, as eager novices strive to master the elusive art of cooking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/">The Story Of Sushi : An Unlikely Story of Raw Fish and Rice &#8211; Trevor Corson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Editor&#8217;s Choice    </p>
<p>                    Everything you never knew about sushi&#8211; its surprising origins, the colorful lives of its chefs, and the bizarre behavior of the creatures that compose it    </p>
<p>                    Trevor Corson takes us behind the scenes at America&#8217;s first sushi-chef training academy, as eager novices strive to master the elusive art of cooking without cooking. He delves into the biology and natural history of the edible creatures of the sea, and tells the fascinating story of an Indo-Chinese meal reinvented in nineteenth-century Tokyo as a cheap fast food. He reveals the pioneers who brought sushi to the United States and explores how this unlikely meal is exploding into the American heartland just as the long-term future of sushi may be unraveling.    </p>
<p>                    The Story of Sushi is at once a compelling tale of human determination and a delectable smorgasbord of surprising food science, intrepid reporting, and provocative cultural history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/">The Story Of Sushi : An Unlikely Story of Raw Fish and Rice &#8211; Trevor Corson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Necessity : Adventures In The World Of Human Waste &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Produced behind closed doors, disposed of discreetly, hidden by euphemism, shit is rarely out in the open in &#8216;civilized&#8217; society, but the world of waste &#8211; and the people who deal with it, work with it and in it &#8211; is a rich one.This book takes us underground to the sewers of New York and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/">The Big Necessity : Adventures In The World Of Human Waste &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Produced behind closed doors, disposed of discreetly, hidden by euphemism, shit is rarely out in the open in &#8216;civilized&#8217; society, but the world of waste &#8211; and the people who deal with it, work with it and in it &#8211; is a rich one.This book takes us underground to the sewers of New York and London and overground to meet the heroes of India&#8217;s sanitation movement, American sewage schoolteachers, the Japanese genius at the cutting edge of toilet technology and the biosolids lobbying team. With a journalist&#8217;s nose for story and a campaigner&#8217;s desire for change, Rose George also addresses the politics of this under-reported social and environmental effluent, and the consequences of our reluctance to talk about it. Witty and original, The Big Necessity proves that shit doesn&#8217;t have to be a dirty word.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/">The Big Necessity : Adventures In The World Of Human Waste &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rocks, Minerals & Fossils]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Homer called it a divine substance. Plato described it as especially dear to the gods. As Mark Kurlansky so brilliantly relates here, salt has shaped civilisation from the beginning, and its story is a glittering, often surprising part of the history of mankind. Wars have been fought over salt and, while salt taxes secured empires [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Homer called it a divine substance. Plato described it as especially dear to the gods. As Mark Kurlansky so brilliantly relates here, salt has shaped civilisation from the beginning, and its story is a glittering, often surprising part of the history of mankind. Wars have been fought over salt and, while salt taxes secured empires across Europe and Asia, they have also inspired revolution &#8211; Gandhi&#8217;s salt march in 1930 began the overthrow of British rule in India.     </p>
<p>                    From the rural Sichuan province where the last home-made soya sauce is produced to the Cheshire brine springs that supplied salt around the globe, Mark Kurlansky has produced a kaleidoscope of world history, a multi-layered masterpiece that blends political, commercial, scientific, religious and culinary records into a rich and memorable tale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selfie : How the West Became Self-Obsessed &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Electrifying&#8217; Financial Times &#8216;So interesting I literally couldn&#8217;t put it down&#8217; Sunday Times We are living in an age of heightened individualism. Success is a personal responsibility. Our culture tells us that to succeed is to be slim, rich, happy, extroverted, popular &#8211; flawless. The pressure to conform to this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/">Selfie : How the West Became Self-Obsessed &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Evening Standard<br />
                    &#8216;Electrifying&#8217; Financial Times<br />
                    &#8216;So interesting I literally couldn&#8217;t put it down&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    We are living in an age of heightened individualism. Success is a personal responsibility. Our culture tells us that to succeed is to be slim, rich, happy, extroverted, popular &#8211; flawless.    </p>
<p>                    The pressure to conform to this ideal has changed who we are. We have become self-obsessed. And our expectation of perfection comes at a cost. Millions are suffering under the torture of this impossible fantasy.    </p>
<p>                    It was not always like this. To explain how we got here, Will Storr takes us on a journey across continents and centuries. Full of thrilling and unexpected connections between history, psychology, economics, neuroscience and more, Selfie is an unforgettable book that makes sense of who we have become.    </p>
<p>                    As featured on Russell Brand&#8217;s Under The Skin podcast.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/">Selfie : How the West Became Self-Obsessed &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>People are now exposed to more information than ever before, provided both by technology and by increasing access to every level of education. These societal gains, however, have also helped fuel a surge in narcissistic and misguided intellectual egalitarianism that has crippled informed debates on any number of issues. Today, everyone knows everything: with only [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/">The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>People are now exposed to more information than ever before, provided both by technology and by increasing access to every level of education. These societal gains, however, have also helped fuel a surge in narcissistic and misguided intellectual egalitarianism that has crippled informed debates on any number of issues. Today, everyone knows everything: with only a quick trip through WebMD or Wikipedia, average citizens believe themselves to be on an equal<br />
                    intellectual footing with doctors and diplomats. All voices, even the most ridiculous, demand to be taken with equal seriousness, and any claim to the contrary is dismissed as undemocratic elitism.    </p>
<p>                    As Tom Nichols shows in The Death of Expertise, this rejection of experts has occurred for many reasons, including the openness of the internet, the emergence of a customer satisfaction model in higher education, and the transformation of the news industry into a 24-hour entertainment machine. Paradoxically, the increasingly democratic dissemination of information, rather than producing an educated public, has instead created an army of ill-informed and angry citizens who denounce<br />
                    intellectual achievement.    </p>
<p>                    Nichols has deeper concerns than the current rejection of expertise and learning, noting that when ordinary citizens believe that no one knows more than anyone else, democratic institutions themselves are in danger of falling either to populism or to technocracy-or in the worst case, a combination of both. The Death of Expertise is not only an exploration of a dangerous phenomenon but also a warning about the stability and survival of modern democracy in the Information<br />
                    Age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/">The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now the subject of a film by Richard Linklater, Eric Schlosser&#8217;s explosive bestseller Fast Food Nation: What the All-American Meal is Doing to the World tells the story of our love affair with fast food. Britain eats more fast food than any other country in Europe. It looks good, tastes good, and it&#8217;s cheap. But [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now the subject of a film by Richard Linklater, Eric Schlosser&#8217;s explosive bestseller Fast Food Nation: What the All-American Meal is Doing to the World tells the story of our love affair with fast food.    </p>
<p>                      Britain eats more fast food than any other country in Europe. It looks good, tastes good, and it&#8217;s cheap. But the real cost never appears on the menu.    </p>
<p>                      Eric Schlosser visits the lab that re-creates the smell of strawberries; examines the safety records of abattoirs; reveals why the fries really taste so good and what lurks between the sesame buns &#8211; and shows how fast food is transforming not only our diets but our world.    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Fast Food Nation has lifted the polystyrene lid on the global fast food industry &#8230; and sparked a storm&#8217;<br />
                      Observer    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Has wiped that smirk off the Happy Meal &#8230; Thanks to this man, you&#8217;ll never eat a burger again&#8217;<br />
                      Evening Standard    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Startling &#8230; Junk food, we learn, is just that &#8230; left this reader vowing never to set foot in one of those outlets again&#8217;<br />
                      Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;This book tells you more than you really want to know when you&#8217;re chomping on that hamburger &#8230; Have a nice day? Listen &#8211; you should live so long&#8217;<br />
                      The Times    </p>
<p>                      Eric Schlosser is a correspondent for the Atlantic Monthly. His first book, Fast Food Nation, was a major international bestseller. His work has appeared in the Atlantic Monthly, Rolling Stone and the Guardian. He has received a number of journalistic honours, including a National Magazine Award for an Atlantic Review article on the drug trade, which was later adapted into the book Reefer Madness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Makes Us Human? &#8211; Edited byCharles Pasternak (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In What Makes us Human? some of the world&#8217;s most brilliant thinkers answer this perennial puzzle. Is it our imagination or our knack for cooking? Is it because we are social, scientific, or spiritual? Exploring the true nature of human nature, What Makes us Human? sheds new light on how and why our ancestors produced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/">What Makes Us Human? &#8211; Edited byCharles Pasternak (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In What Makes us Human? some of the world&#8217;s    </p>
<p>                    most brilliant thinkers answer this perennial    </p>
<p>                    puzzle. Is it our imagination or our knack for    </p>
<p>                    cooking? Is it because we are social, scientific,    </p>
<p>                    or spiritual? Exploring the true nature of human    </p>
<p>                    nature, What Makes us Human? sheds new    </p>
<p>                    light on how and why our ancestors produced    </p>
<p>                    such clever, talented, and unlikely progeny.    </p>
<p>                    With contributions by Susan Blackmore, Robin    </p>
<p>                    Dunbar, Stephen Oppenheimer, Ian Tattersall, and    </p>
<p>                    more.For all to enjoy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/">What Makes Us Human? &#8211; Edited byCharles Pasternak (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Logic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order to coordinate its actions, a group of people must form &#8220;common knowledge.&#8221; Each person wants to participate only if others also participate. Members must have knowledge of each other, knowledge of that knowledge, knowledge of the knowledge of that knowledge, and so on. Michael Chwe applies this insight, with striking erudition, to analyze a range of rituals across history and cultures. He shows that public ceremonies are powerful not simply because they transmit meaning from a central source to each audience member but because they let audience members know what other members know. For instance, people watching the Super Bowl know that many others are seeing precisely what they see and that those people know in turn that many others are also watching.<br />
                    This creates common knowledge, and advertisers selling products that depend on consensus are willing to pay large sums to gain access to it. Remarkably, a great variety of rituals and ceremonies, such as formal inaugurations, work in much the same way. By using a rational-choice argument to explain diverse cultural practices, Chwe argues for a close reciprocal relationship between the perspectives of rationality and culture. He illustrates how game theory can be applied to an unexpectedly broad spectrum of problems, while showing in an admirably clear way what game theory might hold for scholars in the social sciences and humanities who are not yet acquainted with it. In a new afterword, Chwe delves into new applications of common knowledge, both in the real world and in experiments, and considers how generating common knowledge has become easier in the digital age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Better Living Through Criticism: How to Think about Art, Pleasure, Beauty and Truth &#8211; A. O. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Few could explain, let alone seek out, a career in criticism. Yet what A. O. Scott shows in Better Living Through Criticism is that we are, in fact, all critics: because critical thinking informs almost every aspect of artistic creation, of civil action, of interpersonal life. With penetrating insight and humour, Scott shows that while [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/">Better Living Through Criticism: How to Think about Art, Pleasure, Beauty and Truth &#8211; A. O. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Few could explain, let alone seek out, a career in criticism. Yet what A. O. Scott shows in Better Living Through Criticism is that we are, in fact, all critics: because critical thinking informs almost every aspect of artistic creation, of civil action, of interpersonal life. With penetrating insight and humour, Scott shows that while individual critics &#8211; himself included &#8211; can make mistakes and find flaws where they shouldn&#8217;t, criticism as a discipline is one of the noblest, most creative and urgent activities.    </p>
<p>                    Using his own film criticism as a starting point &#8211; everything from an infamous dismissal of the international blockbuster The Avengers to his intense affection for Pixar&#8217;s animated Ratatouille &#8211; Scott expands outwards, easily guiding readers through the complexities of Rilke and Shelley, the origins of Chuck Berry and the Rolling Stones, the power of Marina Abramovic and &#8216;Ode on a Grecian Urn&#8217; Scott shows that real criticism was and always will be the breath of fresh air that allows true creativity to thrive. As he puts it: &#8216;The time for criticism is always now, because the imperative to think clearly, never goes away.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/">Better Living Through Criticism: How to Think about Art, Pleasure, Beauty and Truth &#8211; A. O. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why the troll problem is actually a culture problem: how online trolling fits comfortably within today&#8217;s media landscape. Internet trolls live to upset as many people as possible, using all the technical and psychological tools at their disposal. They gleefully whip the media into a frenzy over a fake teen drug crisis; they post offensive [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/">This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why the troll problem is actually a culture problem: how online trolling fits comfortably within today&#8217;s media landscape.    </p>
<p>                    Internet trolls live to upset as many people as possible, using all the technical and psychological tools at their disposal. They gleefully whip the media into a frenzy over a fake teen drug crisis; they post offensive messages on Facebook memorial pages, traumatizing grief-stricken friends and family; they use unabashedly racist language and images. They take pleasure in ruining a complete stranger&#8217;s day and find amusement in their victim&#8217;s anguish. In short, trolling is the obstacle to a kinder, gentler Internet. To quote a famous Internet meme, trolling is why we can&#8217;t have nice things online. Or at least that&#8217;s what we have been led to believe. In this provocative book, Whitney Phillips argues that trolling, widely condemned as obscene and deviant, actually fits comfortably within the contemporary media landscape. Trolling may be obscene, but, Phillips argues, it isn&#8217;t all that deviant. Trolls&#8217; actions are born of and fueled by culturally sanctioned impulses&#8211;which are just as damaging as the trolls&#8217; most disruptive behaviors.     </p>
<p>                    Phillips describes, for example, the relationship between trolling and sensationalist corporate media&#8211;pointing out that for trolls, exploitation is a leisure activity; for media, it&#8217;s a business strategy. She shows how trolls, &#8220;the grimacing poster children for a socially networked world,&#8221; align with social media. And she documents how trolls, in addition to parroting media tropes, also offer a grotesque pantomime of dominant cultural tropes, including gendered notions of dominance and success and an ideology of entitlement. We don&#8217;t just have a trolling problem, Phillips argues; we have a culture problem. This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things isn&#8217;t only about trolls; it&#8217;s about a culture in which trolls thrive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/">This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals. In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals.     </p>
<p>                    In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind societies. He explores how the tension between identity and anonymity defines how societies develop, function, and fail. In the vein of Guns, Germs, and Steel and Sapiens, The Human Swarm reveals how mankind created sprawling civilizations of unrivalled complexity &#8211; and what it will take to sustain them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truth About Trust : How It Determines Success in Life, Love, Learning, and More &#8211; David DeSteno (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-truth-about-trust-how-it-determines-success-in-life-love-learning-and-more-david-desteno-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-about-trust-how-it-determines-success-in-life-love-learning-and-more-david-desteno-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This one&#8217;s worth reading. Trust me.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, PhD, bestselling author of Stumbling on Happiness Issues of trust come attached to almost every human interaction, yet few people realize how powerfully their ability to determine trustworthiness predicts future success. David DeSteno&#8217;s cutting-edge research on reading trust cues with humanoid robots has already excited widespread media [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-trust-how-it-determines-success-in-life-love-learning-and-more-david-desteno-abridged/">The Truth About Trust : How It Determines Success in Life, Love, Learning, and More &#8211; David DeSteno (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This one&#8217;s worth reading. Trust me.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, PhD, bestselling author of Stumbling on Happiness     </p>
<p>                    Issues of trust come attached to almost every human interaction, yet few people realize how powerfully their ability to determine trustworthiness predicts future success. David DeSteno&#8217;s cutting-edge research on reading trust cues with humanoid robots has already excited widespread media interest. In The Truth About Trust, the renowned psychologist shares his findings and debunks numerous popular beliefs, including Paul Zak&#8217;s theory that oxytocin is the &#8220;moral molecule.&#8221; From education and business to romance and dieting, DeSteno&#8217;s fascinating, paradigm-shifting book offers new insights and practical takeaways that will forever change how readers understand, communicate, and make decisions in every area of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-trust-how-it-determines-success-in-life-love-learning-and-more-david-desteno-abridged/">The Truth About Trust : How It Determines Success in Life, Love, Learning, and More &#8211; David DeSteno (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
