<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Maturation &amp; Ageing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/maturation-ageing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/maturation-ageing/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Maturation &amp; Ageing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/maturation-ageing/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Women Rowing North : Navigating Life&#8217;s Currents and Flourishing As We Age &#8211; Mary Pipher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maturation & Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller * USA Today Bestseller * Los Angeles Times Bestseller * Publishers Weekly Bestseller The instant New York Times bestseller from the author of Reviving Ophelia&#8211;a guide to wisdom, authenticity, and bliss for women as they age. Women growing older contend with ageism, misogyny, and loss. Yet as Mary Pipher shows, most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/">Women Rowing North : Navigating Life&#8217;s Currents and Flourishing As We Age &#8211; Mary Pipher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller * USA Today Bestseller * Los Angeles Times Bestseller * Publishers Weekly Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    The instant New York Times bestseller from the author of Reviving Ophelia&#8211;a guide to wisdom, authenticity, and bliss for women as they age.     </p>
<p>                    Women growing older contend with ageism, misogyny, and loss. Yet as Mary Pipher shows, most older women are deeply happy and filled with gratitude for the gifts of life. Their struggles help them grow into the authentic, empathetic, and wise people they have always wanted to be.     </p>
<p>                    In Women Rowing North, Pipher offers a timely examination of the cultural and developmental issues women face as they age. Drawing on her own experience as daughter, sister, mother, grandmother, caregiver, clinical psychologist, and cultural anthropologist, she explores ways women can cultivate resilient responses to the challenges they face. &#8220;If we can keep our wits about us, think clearly, and manage our emotions skillfully,&#8221; Pipher writes, &#8220;we will experience a joyous time of our lives. If we have planned carefully and packed properly, if we have good maps and guides, the journey can be transcendent.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/">Women Rowing North : Navigating Life&#8217;s Currents and Flourishing As We Age &#8211; Mary Pipher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maturation & Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life. From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life.    </p>
<p>                    From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of his career. He knows that everyone thinks they want to live forever, until they hit middle age and witness the suffering of their parents and even their peers. So how do we solve the paradox of wanting to live to a ripe old age-but enjoy the benefits of youth?    </p>
<p>                    This groundbreaking book holds the answer. Working with thousands of patients, Dr. Gundry has discovered that the &#8220;diseases of aging&#8221; we most fear are not simply a function of age; rather, they are a byproduct of the way we have lived over the decades. In The Longevity Paradox, he maps out a new approach to aging well-one that is based on supporting the health of the &#8220;oldest&#8221; parts of us: the microorganisms that live within our bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Our gut bugs-the bacteria that make up the microbiome-largely determine our health over the years. From diseases like cancer and Alzheimer&#8217;s to common ailments like arthritis to our weight and the appearance of our skin, these bugs are in the driver&#8217;s seat, controlling our quality of life as we age.    </p>
<p>                    The good news is, it&#8217;s never too late to support these microbes and give them what they need to help them-and you-thrive. In The Longevity Paradox, Dr. Gundry outlines a nutrition and lifestyle plan to support gut health and live well for decades to come. A progressive take on the new science of aging, The Longevity Paradox offers an action plan to prevent and reverse disease as well as simple hacks to help anyone look and feel younger and more vital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
