<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>DNA &amp; Genome Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/dna-genome/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/dna-genome/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>DNA &amp; Genome Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/dna-genome/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Life at the Speed of Light : From the Double Helix to the Dawn of Digital Life &#8211; J. Craig Venter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2010, scientists led by J. Craig Venter became the first to successfully create &#8216;synthetic life&#8217; &#8212; putting humankind at the threshold of the most important and exciting phase of biological research, one that will enable us to actually write the genetic code for designing new species to help us adapt and evolve for long-term [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/">Life at the Speed of Light : From the Double Helix to the Dawn of Digital Life &#8211; J. Craig Venter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2010, scientists led by J. Craig Venter became the first to successfully create &#8216;synthetic life&#8217; &#8212; putting humankind at the threshold of the most important and exciting phase of biological research, one that will enable us to actually write the genetic code for designing new species to help us adapt and evolve for long-term survival. The science of synthetic genomics will have a profound impact on human existence, including chemical and energy generation, health, clean water and food production, environmental control, and possibly even our evolution.    </p>
<p>                    In Life at the Speed of Light, Venter presents a fascinating and authoritative study of this emerging field from the inside &#8212; detailing its origins, current challenges and controversies, and projected effects on our lives. This scientific frontier provides an opportunity to ponder anew the age-old question &#8216;What is life?&#8217; and examine what we really mean by &#8216;playing God&#8217;. Life at the Speed of Light is a landmark work, written by a visionary at the dawn of a new era of biological engineering.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/">Life at the Speed of Light : From the Double Helix to the Dawn of Digital Life &#8211; J. Craig Venter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction and A New York Times Notable Book of 2018. Our understanding of the &#8216;tree of life&#8217;, with powerful implications for human genetics, human health and our own human nature, has recently completely changed. This book is about a new method of telling the story of life on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/">The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction and A New York Times Notable Book of 2018.    </p>
<p>                              Our understanding of the &#8216;tree of life&#8217;, with powerful implications for human genetics, human health and our own human nature, has recently completely changed.    </p>
<p>                              This book is about a new method of telling the story of life on earth &#8211; through molecular phylogenetics. It involves a fairly simple method &#8211; the reading of the deep history of life by looking at the variation in protein molecules found in living organisms. For instance, we now know that roughly eight per cent of the human genome arrived not through traditional inheritance from directly ancestral forms, but sideways by viral infection.    </p>
<p>                              In The Tangled Tree, acclaimed science writer David Quammen chronicles these discoveries through the lives of the researchers who made them &#8211; such as Carl Woese, the most important little-known biologist of the twentieth century; Lynn Margulis, the notorious maverick whose wild ideas about &#8216;mosaic&#8217; creatures proved to be true; and Tsutomu Wantanabe, who discovered that the scourge of antibiotic-resistant bacteria is a direct result of horizontal gene transfer, bringing the deep study of genome histories to bear on a global crisis in public health.    </p>
<p>                              Quammen explains how molecular studies of evolution have brought startling recognitions about the tangled tree of life &#8211; including where we humans fit into it. Thanks to new technologies, we now have the ability to alter even our genetic composition &#8211; through sideways insertions, as nature has long been doing. The Tangled Tree is a brilliant exploration of our transformed understanding of evolution and of life&#8217;s history itself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/">The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeological Methodology & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, helped resolve long-existing controversies, challenged long-held views, and thrown up some remarkable surprises.    </p>
<p>                    The emerging picture is one of many waves of ancient human migrations, so that all populations existing today are mixes of ancient ones, as well as in many cases carrying a genetic component from Neanderthals, and, in some populations, Denisovans. David Reich, whose team has been at the forefront of these discoveries, explains what the genetics is telling us about ourselves and our complex and often surprising ancestry. Gone are old ideas of any kind of racial &#8216;purity&#8217;, or even deep and ancient<br />
                    divides between peoples. Instead, we are finding a rich variety of mixtures. Reich describes the cutting-edge findings from the past few years, and also considers the sensitivities involved in tracing ancestry, with science sometimes jostling with politics and tradition. He brings an important wider<br />
                    message: that we should celebrate our rich diversity, and recognize that every one of us is the result of a long history of migration and intermixing of ancient peoples, which we carry as ghosts in our DNA.    </p>
<p>                    What will we discover next?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene<br />
                    Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the future of our species for fans of Homo Deus and The Gene.<br />
                    After 3.8 billion years humankind is about to start evolving by new rules&#8230;<br />
                    From leading geopolitical expert and technology futurist Jamie Metzl comes a groundbreaking exploration of the many ways genetic-engineering is shaking the core foundations of our lives-sex, war, love, and death.<br />
                    At the dawn of the genetics revolution, our DNA is becoming as readable, writable, and hackable as our information technology. But as humanity starts retooling our own genetic code, the choices we make today will be the difference between realizing breathtaking advances in human well-being and descending into a dangerous and potentially deadly genetic arms race.<br />
                    Enter the laboratories where scientists are turning science fiction into reality. Look towards a future where our deepest beliefs, morals, religions, and politics are challenged like never before and the very essence of what it means to be human is at play. When we can engineer our future children, massively extend our lifespans, build life from scratch, and recreate the plant and animal world, should we?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Brief History of Everyone Who Ever Lived : The Stories in Our Genes &#8211; Adam Rutherford (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genealogy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Genetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A brilliant, authoritative, surprising, captivating introduction to human genetics. You&#8217;ll be spellbound&#8217; Brian Cox This is a story about you. It is the history of who you are and how you came to be. It is unique to you, as it is to each of the 100 billion modern humans who have ever drawn breath. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/">A Brief History of Everyone Who Ever Lived : The Stories in Our Genes &#8211; Adam Rutherford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A brilliant, authoritative, surprising, captivating introduction to human genetics. You&#8217;ll be spellbound&#8217; Brian Cox    </p>
<p>                    This is a story about you.     </p>
<p>                    It is the history of who you are and how you came to be. It is unique to you, as it is to each of the 100 billion modern humans who have ever drawn breath. But it is also our collective story, because in every one of our genomes we each carry the history of our species &#8211; births, deaths, disease, war, famine, migration and a lot of sex.     </p>
<p>                    In this captivating journey through the expanding landscape of genetics, Adam Rutherford reveals what our genes now tell us about human history, and what history can now tell us about our genes. From Neanderthals to murder, from redheads to race, dead kings to plague, evolution to epigenetics, this is a demystifying and illuminating new portrait of who we are and how we came to be.    </p>
<p>                    ***    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A thoroughly entertaining history of Homo sapiens and its DNA in a manner that displays popular science writing at its best&#8217; Observer     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Magisterial, informative and delightful&#8217; Peter Frankopan    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An extraordinary adventure&#8230;From the Neanderthals to the Vikings, from the Queen of Sheba to Richard III, Rutherford goes in search of our ancestors, tracing the genetic clues deep into the past&#8217; Alice Roberts</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/">A Brief History of Everyone Who Ever Lived : The Stories in Our Genes &#8211; Adam Rutherford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
