<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Technical Design Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/technical-design/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/technical-design/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Technical Design Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/technical-design/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the international bestseller Business Model Generation explain how to create value propositions customers can&#8217;t resist Value Proposition Design helps you tackle the core challenge of every business &#8211; creating compelling products and services customers want to buy. This highly practical book, paired with its online companion, will teach you the processes and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/">Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the international bestseller Business Model Generation explain how to create value propositions customers can&#8217;t resist    </p>
<p>                     Value Proposition Design helps you tackle the core challenge of every business &#8211; creating compelling products and services customers want to buy. This highly practical book, paired with its online companion, will teach you the processes and tools you need to create products that sell.    </p>
<p>                    Using the same stunning visual format as the authors&#8217; global bestseller, Business Model Generation, this sequel explains how to use the &#8220;Value Proposition Canvas&#8221; to design, test, create, and manage products and services customers actually want.    </p>
<p>                    Value Proposition Design is for anyone who has been frustrated by new product meetings based on hunches and intuitions; it&#8217;s for anyone who has watched an expensive new product launch fail in the market. The book will help you understand the patterns of great value propositions, get closer to customers, and avoid wasting time with ideas that won&#8217;t work. You&#8217;ll learn the simple process of designing and testing value propositions, that perfectly match customers&#8217; needs and desires.    </p>
<p>                    In addition the book gives you exclusive access to an online companion on Strategyzer.com. You will be able to assess your work, learn from peers, and download pdfs, checklists, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Value Proposition Design is an essential companion to the &#8220;Business Model Canvas&#8221; from Business Model Generation, a tool embraced globally by startups and large corporations such as MasterCard, 3M, Coca Cola, GE, Fujitsu, LEGO, Colgate-Palmolive, and many more.<br />
                    Value Proposition Design gives you a proven methodology for success, with value propositions that sell, embedded in profitable business models.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/">Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3D Graphics & Modelling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fabricated tells the story of 3D printers, humble manufacturing machines that are bursting out of the factory and into schools, kitchens, hospitals, even onto the fashion catwalk. Fabricated describes our emerging world of printable products, where people design and 3D print their own creations as easily as they edit an online document. A 3D printer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/">Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fabricated tells the story of 3D printers, humble manufacturing machines that are bursting out of the factory and into schools, kitchens, hospitals, even onto the fashion catwalk. Fabricated describes our emerging world of printable products, where people design and 3D print their own creations as easily as they edit an online document. A 3D printer transforms digital information into a physical object by carrying out instructions from an electronic design file, or &#8216;blueprint.&#8217; Guided by a design file, a 3D printer lays down layer after layer of a raw material to &#8216;print&#8217; out an object. That&#8217;s not the whole story, however. The magic happens when you plug a 3D printer into today s mind-boggling digital technologies. Add to that the Internet, tiny, low cost electronic circuitry, radical advances in materials science and biotech and voila! The result is an explosion of technological and social innovation. Fabricated takes the reader onto a rich and fulfilling journey that explores how 3D printing is poised to impact nearly every part of our lives.<br />
                    Aimed at people who enjoy books on business strategy, popular science and novel technology, Fabricated will provide readers with practical and imaginative insights to the question &#8216;how will this technology change my life?&#8217; Based on hundreds of hours of research and dozens of interviews with experts from a broad range of industries, Fabricated offers readers an informative, engaging and fast-paced introduction to 3D printing now and in the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/">Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FIRE : How Fast, Inexpensive, Restrained, and Elegant Methods Ignite Innovation &#8211; Dan Ward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Noted military technology expert Dan Ward&#8217;s manifesto for creating great products and projects using the methods of rapid innovation. Why do some programs deliver their product under cost, while others bust their budget? Why do some deliver ahead of schedule, while others experience endless delays? Which products work better-the quick and thrifty or the slow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/">FIRE : How Fast, Inexpensive, Restrained, and Elegant Methods Ignite Innovation &#8211; Dan Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Noted military technology expert Dan Ward&#8217;s manifesto for creating great products and projects using the methods of rapid innovation.  Why do some programs deliver their product under cost, while others bust their budget? Why do some deliver ahead of schedule, while others experience endless delays? Which products work better-the quick and thrifty or the slow and expensive? Which situation leads to superior equipment?  With nearly two decades as an engineering officer in the U. S. Air Force, Dan Ward explored these questions during tours of duty at military research laboratories, the Air Force Institute of Technology, an intelligence agency, the Pentagon and Afghanistan. The pattern he noticed revealed that the most successful project leaders in both the public and private sectors delivered top-shelf products with a skeleton crew, a shoestring budget, and a cannonball schedule. Excessive investment of time, money, or complexity actually reduced innovation. He concluded the secret to innovation is to be fast, inexpensive, simple, and small.  FIRE presents an entertaining and practical framework for pursuing rapid, frugal innovation.<br />
                    A story-filled blend of pop culture and engineering insight, FIRE has something for everyone: strategic concepts leaders can use as they cast a vision, actionable principles for managers as they make business decisions, and practical tools for workers as they design, build, assess and test new products.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/">FIRE : How Fast, Inexpensive, Restrained, and Elegant Methods Ignite Innovation &#8211; Dan Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Start At The End : How to Build Products That Create Change &#8211; Matt Wallaert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/start-at-the-end-how-to-build-products-that-create-change-matt-wallaert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/start-at-the-end-how-to-build-products-that-create-change-matt-wallaert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nudge meets Hooked in a practical approach to designing products and services that change behavior, from what we buy to how we work. Deciding what to create at modern companies often looks like an episode of Mad Men people throw ideas around until one sounds sexy enough to execute and then they scale it to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/start-at-the-end-how-to-build-products-that-create-change-matt-wallaert-abridged/">Start At The End : How to Build Products That Create Change &#8211; Matt Wallaert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nudge meets Hooked in a practical approach to designing products and services that change behavior, from what we buy to how we work. Deciding what to create at modern companies often looks like an episode of Mad Men people throw ideas around until one sounds sexy enough to execute and then they scale it to everyone. The result? Companies overspend on marketing to drive engagement with products and services that people don&#8217;t want and won&#8217;t help them be happier and healthier. Start at the End offers a new framework for design, grounded in behavioral science. Technology executive and behavioral scientist Matt Wallaert argues that the purpose of everything is behavior change. By starting with outcomes instead of processes, the most effective companies understand what people want to do and why they aren&#8217;t already doing it, then build products and services to bridge the gap. Wallaert is a behavioral psychologist who has led product design at organizations ranging from startups like Clover Health to industry leaders such as Microsoft. Whether dissecting the success behind Uber&#8217;s ridesharing service or Flamin&#8217; Hot Cheetos, he underscores with clarity and humor how this approach can improve the way we work and live. This is an essential roadmap for building products that matter&#8211;and changing behavior for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/start-at-the-end-how-to-build-products-that-create-change-matt-wallaert-abridged/">Start At The End : How to Build Products That Create Change &#8211; Matt Wallaert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Box : How the Shipping Container Made the World Smaller and the World Economy Bigger &#8211; Second Edition with a new chapter by the author &#8211; Marc Levinson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shipping Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transport Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In April 1956, a refitted oil tanker carried fifty-eight shipping containers from Newark to Houston. From that modest beginning, container shipping developed into a huge industry that made the boom in global trade possible. The Box tells the dramatic story of the container&#8217;s creation, the decade of struggle before it was widely adopted, and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/">The Box : How the Shipping Container Made the World Smaller and the World Economy Bigger &#8211; Second Edition with a new chapter by the author &#8211; Marc Levinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In April 1956, a refitted oil tanker carried fifty-eight shipping containers from Newark to Houston. From that modest beginning, container shipping developed into a huge industry that made the boom in global trade possible. The Box tells the dramatic story of the container&#8217;s creation, the decade of struggle before it was widely adopted, and the sweeping economic consequences of the sharp fall in transportation costs that containerization brought about. But the container didn&#8217;t just happen. Its adoption required huge sums of money, both from private investors and from ports that aspired to be on the leading edge of a new technology. It required years of high-stakes bargaining with two of the titans of organized labor, Harry Bridges and Teddy Gleason, as well as delicate negotiations on standards that made it possible for almost any container to travel on any truck or train or ship. Ultimately, it took McLean&#8217;s success in supplying U.S. forces in Vietnam to persuade the world of the container&#8217;s potential.<br />
                    Drawing on previously neglected sources, economist Marc Levinson shows how the container transformed economic geography, devastating traditional ports such as New York and London and fueling the growth of previously obscure ones, such as Oakland. By making shipping so cheap that industry could locate factories far from its customers, the container paved the way for Asia to become the world&#8217;s workshop and brought consumers a previously unimaginable variety of low-cost products from around the globe. Published in hardcover on the fiftieth anniversary of the first container voyage, this is the first comprehensive history of the shipping container. Now with a new chapter, The Box tells the dramatic story of how the drive and imagination of an iconoclastic entrepreneur turned containerization from an impractical idea into a phenomenon that transformed economic geography, slashed transportation costs, and made the boom in global trade possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/">The Box : How the Shipping Container Made the World Smaller and the World Economy Bigger &#8211; Second Edition with a new chapter by the author &#8211; Marc Levinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Mathematics & Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Engineering: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How do today&#8217;s most successful tech companies-Amazon, Google, Facebook, Netflix, Tesla-design, develop, and deploy the products that have earned the love of literally billions of people around the world? Perhaps surprisingly, they do it very differently than most tech companies. In INSPIRED, technology product management thought leader Marty Cagan provides readers with a master class [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/">Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do today&#8217;s most successful tech companies-Amazon, Google, Facebook, Netflix, Tesla-design, develop, and deploy the products that have earned the love of literally billions of people around the world?    </p>
<p>                     Perhaps surprisingly, they do it very differently than most tech companies.    </p>
<p>                     In INSPIRED, technology product management thought leader Marty Cagan provides readers with a master class in how to structure and staff a vibrant and successful product organization, and how to discover and deliver technology products that your customers will love-and that will work for your business.    </p>
<p>                     With sections on assembling the right people and skillsets, discovering the right product, embracing an effective yet lightweight process, and creating a strong product culture, readers can take the information they learn and immediately leverage it within their own organizations-dramatically improving their own product efforts.    </p>
<p>                     Whether you&#8217;re an early stage startup working to get to product/market fit, or a growth-stage company working to scale your product organization, or a large, long-established company trying to regain your ability to consistently deliver new value for your customers, INSPIRED will take you and your product organization to a new level of customer engagement, consistent innovation, and business success.    </p>
<p>                     Filled with the author&#8217;s own personal stories-and profiles of some of today&#8217;s most-successful product managers and technology-powered product companies, including Adobe, Apple, BBC, Google, Microsoft, and Netflix-INSPIRED will show you how to turn up the dial of your own product efforts, creating technology products your customers love.    </p>
<p>                     The first edition of INSPIRED, published ten years ago, established itself as the primary reference for technology product managers, and can be found on the shelves of nearly every successful technology product company worldwide. This thoroughly updated second edition shares the same objective of being the most valuable resource for technology product managers, yet it is completely new-sharing the latest practices and techniques of today&#8217;s most-successful tech product companies, and the men and women behind every great product.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/">Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
