<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Criminal Investigation &amp; Detection Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/criminal-investigation-detection/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/criminal-investigation-detection/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Criminal Investigation &amp; Detection Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/criminal-investigation-detection/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crime in Progress : The Secret History of the Trump-Russia Investigation &#8211; Glenn Simpson, Peter Fritsch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Campaigning & Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** The never-before-told inside story of the Steele Dossier and the Trump-Russia investigation &#8216;The best procedural yet written about the discovery of Trump&#8217;s Russia ties&#8217; New York Times In the autumn of 2015, the founders of the Washington-based intelligence firm Fusion GPS, Glenn Simpson and Peter Fritsch, were hired by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/">Crime in Progress : The Secret History of the Trump-Russia Investigation &#8211; Glenn Simpson, Peter Fritsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**<br />
                    The never-before-told inside story of the Steele Dossier and the Trump-Russia investigation    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The best procedural yet written about the discovery of Trump&#8217;s Russia ties&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    In the autumn of 2015, the founders of the Washington-based intelligence firm Fusion GPS, Glenn Simpson and Peter Fritsch, were hired by a republican client to look into the records of Donald Trump. What began as a march through a mind-boggling trove of lawsuits and sketchy overseas projects soon took a darker turn, as they became the first to uncover Trump&#8217;s disturbing ties to the Kremlin and the crimes that since have plagued his presidency.     </p>
<p>                     To help them decipher this alarming evidence, they engaged the services of an old acquaintance, the former British MI6 agent and Russia expert Christopher Steele. Steele would produce the notorious dossier which disclosed that the Trump team was deeply compromised by a hostile foreign power bent on disrupting the West and influencing the US presidential election.    </p>
<p>                     In Crime in Progress, the authors break their silence for the first time, chronicling their high-stakes investigation and their desperate efforts to warn both the American and British governments, the FBI and the media, to little avail &#8211; and no matter the costs. Yet when the dossier finally exploded onto the world stage after a leak, a ten-person research firm above a Starbucks in Washington was thrust into the centre of the biggest news story on the planet &#8211; a story that would lead to the Mueller report and disrupt Trump&#8217;s secret planned rapprochement with Putin&#8217;s Russia that could have re-ordered the western alliance. After four years on his trail, the authors&#8217; inescapable conclusion is that Trump is an asset of the Russian government, whether he knows it or not.     </p>
<p>                     A real-life political thriller with the makings of a modern classic, Crime in Progress is the definitive story of the pursuit of the truth about Trump and one of the greatest betrayals in American history.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ve read all the books on this subject &#8211; this is the one you want to read . . . I feel fairly steeped in this matter and I learned something on every page&#8217; Rachel Maddow, MSNBC     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You don&#8217;t need to read John le Carre or Tom Clancy to find espionage thrills in Washington these days, turn over any stone in the Beltway&#8217;s secret world and you&#8217;ll observe the seething mass of conspiracy and subterfuge beneath . . . Take Glenn Simpson and Peter Fritsch, who have become central characters in a quite terrifying international spy thriller&#8217; Josh Glancy, Sunday Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/">Crime in Progress : The Secret History of the Trump-Russia Investigation &#8211; Glenn Simpson, Peter Fritsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING * &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING *     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly written haymaker&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly three years of reporting, hundreds of hours of interviews and more than two hundred sources, including some of the most senior members of the administration, friends and first-hand witnesses who have never spoken before, Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig take us inside some of the most controversial moments of Trump&#8217;s presidency. They peer deeply into Trump&#8217;s White House &#8211; at the aides pressured to lie to the public, the lawyers scrambling to clear up norm-breaking disasters, and the staffers whose careers have been reduced to ashes &#8211; to paint an unparalleled group portrait of an administration driven by self-preservation and paranoia.     </p>
<p>                    Rucker and Leonnig reveal Trump at his most unvarnished, showing the unhinged decision-making and incompetence that has floored officials and stunned foreign leaders. They portray unscripted calls with Vladimir Putin, steak dinners with Kim Jong-un, and calls with Theresa May so hostile that they left her aides shaken. They also take a hard look at Robert Mueller, Trump&#8217;s greatest antagonist to date, and how his investigation slowly unravelled an administration whose universal value is loyalty &#8211; not to country, but to the president himself.    </p>
<p>                    Grippingly told, A Very Stable Genius is a behind-the-scenes account of Trump&#8217;s vainglorious pursuit of power in his first term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
