<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Office Systems &amp; Equipment Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/office-systems-equipment/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/office-systems-equipment/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Office Systems &amp; Equipment Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/office-systems-equipment/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Humanity Works : Merging Technologies and People for the Workforce of the Future &#8211; Alexandra Levit (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/humanity-works-merging-technologies-and-people-for-the-workforce-of-the-future-alexandra-levit-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Systems & Equipment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humanity-works-merging-technologies-and-people-for-the-workforce-of-the-future-alexandra-levit-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DISTINGUISHED FAVOURITE: Independent Press Award 2020 &#8211; Business General Category The professional landscape is transforming, and the only way to maintain competitive advantage is to maximize the unique skills of your workforce. In Humanity Works, bestselling author, global workplace consultant and futurist Alexandra Levit provides a guide to making the most of the human traits [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humanity-works-merging-technologies-and-people-for-the-workforce-of-the-future-alexandra-levit-abridged/">Humanity Works : Merging Technologies and People for the Workforce of the Future &#8211; Alexandra Levit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DISTINGUISHED FAVOURITE: Independent Press Award 2020 &#8211; Business General Category    </p>
<p>                    The professional landscape is transforming, and the only way to maintain competitive advantage is to maximize the unique skills of your workforce. In Humanity Works, bestselling author, global workplace consultant and futurist Alexandra Levit provides a guide to making the most of the human traits of creativity, judgement, problem solving and interpersonal sensitivity. Revealing what the &#8216;robot takeover&#8217; will really look like, how talent and machines can work side by side and how you can make organizational structures more agile and innovation focused, this book will prepare you to lead organizations of the future.    </p>
<p>                    Humanity Works doesn&#8217;t just explain the fascinating trends of the future of work; it condenses cutting-edge academic and business thinking to show what you can do about the future right now. Original, real-life case studies including Nestle, The Washington Post, Deloitte, and Pepsi combined with exercises and workplace tools will equip you for staying innovative and successful in the wake of major workplace disruption. Everything hinges on capturing the human edge in your organization.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humanity-works-merging-technologies-and-people-for-the-workforce-of-the-future-alexandra-levit-abridged/">Humanity Works : Merging Technologies and People for the Workforce of the Future &#8211; Alexandra Levit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Systems & Equipment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The essential playbook for the future of your business What To Do When Machines Do Everything is a guidebook to succeeding in the next generation of the digital economy. When systems running on Artificial Intelligence can drive our cars, diagnose medical patients, and manage our finances more effectively than humans it raises profound questions on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/">What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The essential playbook for the future of your business What To Do When Machines Do Everything is a guidebook to succeeding in the next generation of the digital economy. When systems running on Artificial Intelligence can drive our cars, diagnose medical patients, and manage our finances more effectively than humans it raises profound questions on the future of work and how companies compete. Illustrated with real-world cases, data, and insight, the authors provide clear strategic guidance and actionable steps to help you and your organization move ahead in a world where exponentially developing new technologies are changing how value is created. Written by a team of business and technology expert practitioners who also authored Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business this book provides a clear path to the future of your work. The first part of the book examines the once in a generation upheaval most every organization will soon face as systems of intelligence go mainstream.<br />
                    The authors argue that contrary to the doom and gloom that surrounds much of IT and business at the moment, we are in fact on the cusp of the biggest wave of opportunity creation since the Industrial Revolution. Next, the authors detail a clear-cut business model to help leaders take part in this coming boom; the AHEAD model outlines five strategic initiatives Automate, Halos, Enhance, Abundance, and Discovery that are central to competing in the next phase of global business by driving new levels of efficiency, customer intimacy and innovation. Business leaders today have two options: be swallowed up by the ongoing technological evolution, or ride the crest of the wave to new profits and better business. This book shows you how to avoid your own extinction event, and will help you; * Understand the untold full extent of technology&#8217;s impact on the way we work and live.<br />
                    * Find out where we&#8217;re headed, and how soon the future will arrive * Leverage the new emerging paradigm into a sustainable business advantage * Adopt a strategic model for winning in the new economy The digital world is already transforming how we work, live, and shop, how we are governed and entertained, and how we manage our money, health, security, and relationships. Don&#8217;t let your business or your career get left behind. What To Do When Machines Do Everything is your strategic roadmap to a future full of possibility and success. Or peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/">What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
