<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Age Groups: The Elderly Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/age-groups-the-elderly/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/age-groups-the-elderly/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Age Groups: The Elderly Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/age-groups-the-elderly/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pensions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface* Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time? Many of us have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface*    </p>
<p>                    Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time?     </p>
<p>                    Many of us have been raised on the traditional notion of a three-stage approach to our working lives: education, followed by work and then retirement.  But this well-established pathway is already beginning to collapse &#8211; life expectancy is rising, final-salary pensions are vanishing, and increasing numbers of people are juggling multiple careers. Whether you are 18, 45 or 60, you will need to do things very differently from previous generations and learn to structure your life in completely new ways.    </p>
<p>                    The 100-Year Life is here to help.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the unique pairing of their experience in psychology and economics, Lynda Gratton and Andrew J. Scott offer a broad-ranging analysis as well as a raft of solutions, showing how to rethink your finances, your education, your career and your relationships and create a fulfilling 100-year life.     </p>
<p>                    * How can you fashion a career and life path that defines you and your values and creates a shifting balance between work and leisure?    </p>
<p>                    * What are the most effective ways of boosting your physical and mental health over a longer and more dynamic lifespan?    </p>
<p>                    * How can you make the most of your intangible assets &#8211; such as family and friends &#8211; as you build a productive, longer life?    </p>
<p>                    * In a multiple-stage life how can you learn to make the transitions that will be so crucial and experiment with new ways of living, working and learning?    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award and featuring a new preface, The 100-Year Life is a wake-up call that describes what to expect and considers the choices and options that you will face. It is also fundamentally a call to action for individuals, politicians, firms and governments and offers the clearest demonstration that a 100-year life can be a wonderful and inspiring one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Women Rowing North : Navigating Life&#8217;s Currents and Flourishing As We Age &#8211; Mary Pipher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maturation & Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller * USA Today Bestseller * Los Angeles Times Bestseller * Publishers Weekly Bestseller The instant New York Times bestseller from the author of Reviving Ophelia&#8211;a guide to wisdom, authenticity, and bliss for women as they age. Women growing older contend with ageism, misogyny, and loss. Yet as Mary Pipher shows, most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/">Women Rowing North : Navigating Life&#8217;s Currents and Flourishing As We Age &#8211; Mary Pipher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller * USA Today Bestseller * Los Angeles Times Bestseller * Publishers Weekly Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    The instant New York Times bestseller from the author of Reviving Ophelia&#8211;a guide to wisdom, authenticity, and bliss for women as they age.     </p>
<p>                    Women growing older contend with ageism, misogyny, and loss. Yet as Mary Pipher shows, most older women are deeply happy and filled with gratitude for the gifts of life. Their struggles help them grow into the authentic, empathetic, and wise people they have always wanted to be.     </p>
<p>                    In Women Rowing North, Pipher offers a timely examination of the cultural and developmental issues women face as they age. Drawing on her own experience as daughter, sister, mother, grandmother, caregiver, clinical psychologist, and cultural anthropologist, she explores ways women can cultivate resilient responses to the challenges they face. &#8220;If we can keep our wits about us, think clearly, and manage our emotions skillfully,&#8221; Pipher writes, &#8220;we will experience a joyous time of our lives. If we have planned carefully and packed properly, if we have good maps and guides, the journey can be transcendent.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/">Women Rowing North : Navigating Life&#8217;s Currents and Flourishing As We Age &#8211; Mary Pipher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
