<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Military History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/military-history/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/military-history/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Military History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/military-history/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution &#8211; Larry Schweikart</title>
		<link>/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American War Of Independence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The truth about the American Revolution is under attack. Despite what you may have learned in school, it wasn&#8217;t a rich slaveholder&#8217;s war fought to maintain white privilege. In fact, the War of Independence wasn&#8217;t about maintaining any status quo&#8211;it was the world&#8217;s first successful bottom-up revolution by the people, ushering in a new dawn [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution &#8211; Larry Schweikart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The truth about the American Revolution is under attack. Despite what you may have learned in school, it wasn&#8217;t a rich slaveholder&#8217;s war fought to maintain white privilege. In fact, the War of Independence wasn&#8217;t about maintaining any status quo&#8211;it was the world&#8217;s first successful bottom-up revolution by the people, ushering in a new dawn of liberty that history had never seen before. But with left-wingers dominating the teaching of history, where can you go for the true story of the unprecedented events that made the United States the worlds greatest nation? </p>
<p>                     Now bestselling historian Larry Schweikart has teamed up with author Dave Dougherty to write the ground-breaking patriotic history you&#8217;ve always wanted to read about the foundation of our unique nation. The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution reveals:<br />
                     Four key factors that applied only in America, making it impossible to replicate the Revolution anywhere else  Why it matters that the Patriot ghting force was overwhelmingly Scotch-Irish  The key role of Protestantism: which denominations tended to become Patriots, and which Tories How Americans were different from the Europeans and English even at the outset of the Revolution  How the casualties of the deadliest war in American history are routinely underreported  How our Revolution became a model for hundreds of others&#8211;that all failed<br />
                     Schweikart and Dougherty take on the left-wing myths&#8211;starting with the Marxist narrative of the Revolution in Howard Zinn&#8217;s nearly ubiquitous A People&#8217;s History of the United States&#8211;and uncover the truth about America&#8217;s beginning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution &#8211; Larry Schweikart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stalingrad &#8211; Antony Beevor</title>
		<link>/stalingrad-antony-beevor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Battles & Campaigns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stalingrad-antony-beevor/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic international million copy bestseller recounting the epic turning point of the second world war In October 1942, a Panzer officer wrote &#8216;Stalingrad is no longer a town&#8230; Animals flee this hell; the hardest stones cannot bear it for long; only men endure&#8217;. The battle for Stalingrad became the focus of Hitler and Stalin&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stalingrad-antony-beevor/">Stalingrad &#8211; Antony Beevor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic international million copy bestseller recounting the epic turning point of the second world war</p>
<p>                    In October 1942, a Panzer officer wrote &#8216;Stalingrad is no longer a town&#8230; Animals flee this hell; the hardest stones cannot bear it for long; only men endure&#8217;. </p>
<p>                    The battle for Stalingrad became the focus of Hitler and Stalin&#8217;s determination to win the gruesome, vicious war on the eastern front. The citizens of Stalingrad endured unimaginable hardship; the battle, with fierce hand-to-hand fighting in each room of each building,  was brutally destructive to both armies. But the eventual victory of the Red Army, and the failure of Hitler&#8217;s Operation Barbarossa, was the first defeat of Hitler&#8217;s territorial ambitions in Europe, and the start of his decline.</p>
<p>                    An extraordinary story of tactical genius, civilian bravery and the nature of war itself, which changed how history is written, Stalingrad is a testament to the vital role of the Soviet war effort.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A superb re-telling. Beevor combines a soldier&#8217;s understanding of war&#8217;s realities with the narrative techniques of a novelist . . . This is a book that lets the reader look into the face of battle&#8217; Orlando Figes, Sunday Telegraph </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A brilliantly researched tour de force of military history&#8217; Sarah Bradford, The Times</p>
<p>                    Antony Beevor is the renowned author of Stalingrad, which won the Samuel Johnson Prize, the Wolfson Prize for History and the Hawthornden Prize for Literature, and Berlin, which received the first Longman-History Today Trustees&#8217; Award. His books have sold nearly four million copies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stalingrad-antony-beevor/">Stalingrad &#8211; Antony Beevor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bomber Command: Reflections of War: Live to Die Another Day (June 1942 &#8211; Summer 1943) &#8211; Martin Bowman</title>
		<link>/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Air Forces & Warfare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This massive work provides a comprehensive insight to the experiences of Bomber Commands pilots and aircrew throughout World War Two. From the early wartime years when the RAFs first attempts to avenge Germanys onslaught were bedeviled by poor navigation and inaccurate bombing, to the final winning onslaught that finally tamed Hitler in his Berlin lair, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/">Bomber Command: Reflections of War: Live to Die Another Day (June 1942 &#8211; Summer 1943) &#8211; Martin Bowman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This massive work provides a comprehensive insight to the experiences of Bomber Commands pilots and aircrew throughout World War Two. From the early wartime years when the RAFs first attempts to avenge Germanys onslaught were bedeviled by poor navigation and inaccurate bombing, to the final winning onslaught that finally tamed Hitler in his Berlin lair, these volumes trace the true experiences of the men who flew the bombers. Hundreds of first-hand accounts are punctuated by the authors background information that put each narrative into wartime perspective. Every aspect of Bomber Commands operational duties are covered; day and night bombing, precision low-level strikes, mass raids and operations throughout all wartime theaters. Contributions are from RAF personnel who flew the commands different aircraft from the early Blenheims and Stirlings to the later Lancasters and Mosquitoes. Each volume is full of accounts that tell of the camaraderie amongst the crews, moments of sheer terror and the stoic humor that provided the critical bond. The five volumes of this work provide the most vivid and comprehensive work on the outstanding part played by RAF Bomber Command in their vital role in the destruction of the Third Reich.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/">Bomber Command: Reflections of War: Live to Die Another Day (June 1942 &#8211; Summer 1943) &#8211; Martin Bowman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Call Sign Chaos : Learning to Lead &#8211; Jim Mattis</title>
		<link>/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A clear-eyed account of learning how to lead in a chaotic world, by General Jim Mattis&#8211;the former Secretary of Defense and one of the most formidable strategic thinkers of our time&#8211;and Bing West, a former assistant secretary of defense and combat Marine. &#8220;A four-star general&#8217;s five-star memoir.&#8221;&#8211;The Wall Street [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis/">Call Sign Chaos : Learning to Lead &#8211; Jim Mattis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A clear-eyed account of learning how to lead in a chaotic world, by General Jim Mattis&#8211;the former Secretary of Defense and one of the most formidable strategic thinkers of our time&#8211;and Bing West, a former assistant secretary of defense and combat Marine. </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A four-star general&#8217;s five-star memoir.&#8221;&#8211;The Wall Street Journal </p>
<p>                     Call Sign Chaos is the account of Jim Mattis&#8217;s storied career, from wide-ranging leadership roles in three wars to ultimately commanding a quarter of a million troops across the Middle East. Along the way, Mattis recounts his foundational experiences as a leader, extracting the lessons he has learned about the nature of warfighting and peacemaking, the importance of allies, and the strategic dilemmas&#8211;and short-sighted thinking&#8211;now facing our nation. He makes it clear why America must return to a strategic footing so as not to continue winning battles but fighting inconclusive wars. </p>
<p>                     Mattis divides his book into three parts: Direct Leadership, Executive Leadership, and Strategic Leadership. In the first part, Mattis recalls his early experiences leading Marines into battle, when he knew his troops as well as his own brothers. In the second part, he explores what it means to command thousands of troops and how to adapt your leadership style to ensure your intent is understood by your most junior troops so that they can own their mission. In the third part, Mattis describes the challenges and techniques of leadership at the strategic level, where military leaders reconcile war&#8217;s grim realities with political leaders&#8217; human aspirations, where complexity reigns and the consequences of imprudence are severe, even catastrophic. </p>
<p>                     Call Sign Chaos is a memoir of a life of warfighting and lifelong learning, following along as Mattis rises from Marine recruit to four-star general. It is a journey about learning to lead and a story about how he, through constant study and action, developed a unique leadership philosophy, one relevant to us all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis/">Call Sign Chaos : Learning to Lead &#8211; Jim Mattis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Health Service Support &#8211; Joint Chiefs of Staff Joint Publication 4-02 &#8211; Surgeon&#8217;s Office, Casualty Management, Medical Logistics, Force Health Protection, Combat Operations, Special Operations Forces &#8211; Department of Defense (Dod)</title>
		<link>/health-service-support-joint-chiefs-of-staff-joint-publication-4-02-surgeons-office-casualty-management-medical-logistics-force-health-protection-combat-operations-special-operations-forces/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/health-service-support-joint-chiefs-of-staff-joint-publication-4-02-surgeons-office-casualty-management-medical-logistics-force-health-protection-combat-operations-special-operations-forces/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This publication provides doctrine for the planning, preparation, and execution of health service support across the range of military operations. The Military Health System supports the operational mission by fostering, protecting, sustaining, and restoring health. It also provides the direction, resources, health care providers, and other means necessary for promoting the health of the beneficiary [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/health-service-support-joint-chiefs-of-staff-joint-publication-4-02-surgeons-office-casualty-management-medical-logistics-force-health-protection-combat-operations-special-operations-forces/">Health Service Support &#8211; Joint Chiefs of Staff Joint Publication 4-02 &#8211; Surgeon&#8217;s Office, Casualty Management, Medical Logistics, Force Health Protection, Combat Operations, Special Operations Forces &#8211; Department of Defense (Dod)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This publication provides doctrine for the planning, preparation, and execution of health service support across the range of military operations. The Military Health System supports the operational mission by fostering, protecting, sustaining, and restoring health. It also provides the direction, resources, health care providers, and other means necessary for promoting the health of the beneficiary population. Principles of Health Service Support &#8211; The principles of health service support (HSS) consist of conformity, proximity, flexibility, mobility, continuity, and control. Conformity &#8211; Conformity with the tactical plan is the most basic element for effectively providing health support. Medical planners must be involved early in the planning process, and once the plan is established, it must be rehearsed with the forces it supports. Proximity &#8211; The principle of proximity is to provide health support to sick, injured, and wounded military personnel at the right time and to keep morbidity and mortality to a minimum. Flexibility &#8211; Flexibility is being prepared and empowered to shift medical resources to meet changing requirements. The medical commander must build flexibility into the operation plan (OPLAN) to support the combatant commander&#8217;s (CCDR&#8217;s) scheme of maneuver. Mobility &#8211; The principle of mobility is to ensure that medical assets remain within supporting distance of maneuvering forces. Continuity &#8211; Continuity of care and treatment is achieved by moving the patient through progressive, phased roles of care, extending from the point of injury or wounding to the US-support base. Each type of medical unit contributes a measured, logical increment of care appropriate to its location and capabilities. CHAPTER I * HEALTH SUPPORT TO JOINT OPERATIONS OVERVIEW * &#8211; Introduction * Military Health System * Principles of Health Service Support * Joint Medical Capabilities * CHAPTER II * ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES * Command and Control * Joint Force Surgeon&#8217;s Office * Organizing the Joint Force Surgeon&#8217;s Office * Joint Force Surgeon&#8217;s Office Battle Rhythm * Staff Organizations * Joint Force Surgeon Reachback * CHAPTER III * HEALTH SERVICE SUPPORT * Casualty Management * Patient Movement * Medical Logistics * Health Information Management * CHAPTER IV * FORCE HEALTH PROTECTION * Casualty Prevention * Preventive Medicine * Health Surveillance * Combat and Operational Stress Control * Preventive Dentistry * Vision Readiness * Laboratory Services * Veterinary Services * CHAPTER V * HEALTH SERVICE SUPPORT OPERATIONS * Combat Operations * Stability and Civil-Military Operations * Limited Contingencies and Crisis Response * Defense Support of Civil Authorities * Special Operations Forces * Multinational Operations * Detainee Operations * Operations in a Chemical, Biological, Radiological, and Nuclear Environment * Contractor Support * CHAPTER VI * JOINT HEALTH PLANNING * Introduction * Health Support Planning Considerations * Planning Joint Medical Logistics * Systems and Planning Tools * APPENDIX * A &#8211; Hospitalization * B &#8211; Patient Movement * C &#8211; Service Component Transportation Assets * D &#8211; Medical Logistics Support * E &#8211; Blood Management * F &#8211; Intelligence Support to Joint Health Support * G &#8211; Casualty Prevention * H Patient Area Reception * J &#8211; Medical Aspects of Reintegration * K &#8211; Impacts of the Law of War and Medical Ethics * L &#8211; Planning Checklists * M &#8211; References * N &#8211; Administrative Instructions</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/health-service-support-joint-chiefs-of-staff-joint-publication-4-02-surgeons-office-casualty-management-medical-logistics-force-health-protection-combat-operations-special-operations-forces/">Health Service Support &#8211; Joint Chiefs of Staff Joint Publication 4-02 &#8211; Surgeon&#8217;s Office, Casualty Management, Medical Logistics, Force Health Protection, Combat Operations, Special Operations Forces &#8211; Department of Defense (Dod)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bombs Away : The Story of a Bomber Team &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent volume of short novels and an essential World War II report from one of America&#8217;s great twentieth-century writers A Penguin Classic On the heels of the enormous success of his masterwork The Grapes of Wrath and at the height of the American war effort John Steinbeck, one of the most prolific and influential [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/">Bombs Away : The Story of a Bomber Team &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent volume of short novels and an essential World War II report from one of America&#8217;s great twentieth-century writers </p>
<p>                    A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    On the heels of the enormous success of his masterwork The Grapes of Wrath and at the height of the American war effort John Steinbeck, one of the most prolific and influential literary figures of his generation, wrote Bombs Away, a nonfiction account of his experiences with U.S. Army Air Force bomber crews during World War II. Now, for the first time since its original publication in 1942, Penguin Classics presents this exclusive edition of Steinbeck&#8217;s introduction to the then-nascent U.S. Army Air Force and its bomber crew&#8211;the essential core unit behind American air power that Steinbeck described as the greatest team in the world. </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/">Bombs Away : The Story of a Bomber Team &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SAS Italian Job : The Secret Mission to Storm a Forbidden Nazi Fortress &#8211; Damien Lewis</title>
		<link>/sas-italian-job-the-secret-mission-to-storm-a-forbidden-nazi-fortress-damien-lewis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[War & Defence Operations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sas-italian-job-the-secret-mission-to-storm-a-forbidden-nazi-fortress-damien-lewis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Sunday Times No.1 bestselling author Damien Lewis&#8217; SAS mission series: &#8216;One of the great untold stories of WWII&#8217; &#8211; Bear Grylls on SAS Ghost Patrol &#8216;The untold story&#8217; &#8211; Daily Mail on SAS Nazi Hunters &#8216;A tale of bravery against desperate odds&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Times on Churchill&#8217;s Secret Warriors &#8216;True adventures laced with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sas-italian-job-the-secret-mission-to-storm-a-forbidden-nazi-fortress-damien-lewis/">SAS Italian Job : The Secret Mission to Storm a Forbidden Nazi Fortress &#8211; Damien Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Sunday Times No.1 bestselling author Damien Lewis&#8217; SAS mission series:</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the great untold stories of WWII&#8217; &#8211; Bear Grylls on SAS Ghost Patrol</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The untold story&#8217; &#8211; Daily Mail on SAS Nazi Hunters</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A tale of bravery against desperate odds&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Times on Churchill&#8217;s Secret Warriors</p>
<p>                    &#8216;True adventures laced with staggering bravery and sacrifice&#8217; &#8211; Sun on Hunting the Nazi Bomb</p>
<p>                    An impossible mission in wartime Italy: the next explosive bestseller from Damien Lewis.</p>
<p>                    In the hard-fought winter of 1944 the Allies advanced northwards through Italy, but stalled on the fearsome mountainous defences of the Gothic Line. Two men were parachuted in, in an effort to break the deadlock. Their mission: to penetrate deep into enemy territory and lay waste to the Germans&#8217; impregnable headquarters.</p>
<p>                    At the eleventh hour mission commanders radioed for David &#8216;The Mad Piper&#8217; Kilpatrick to be flown in, resplendent in his tartan kilt. They wanted this fearless war hero to lead the assault, piping Highland Laddie as he went &#8211; so leaving an indelible British signature to deter Nazi reprisals.</p>
<p>                    As the column of raiders formed up, there was shocking news. High command radioed through an order to stand down, having assessed the chances of success at little more than zero. But in defiance of orders, and come hell or high-water, they were going in.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sas-italian-job-the-secret-mission-to-storm-a-forbidden-nazi-fortress-damien-lewis/">SAS Italian Job : The Secret Mission to Storm a Forbidden Nazi Fortress &#8211; Damien Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reminiscences of the Cuban Revolutionary War &#8211; Ernesto Che Guevara</title>
		<link>/reminiscences-of-the-cuban-revolutionary-war-ernesto-che-guevara/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History: Post WW2 Conflicts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rebellions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uprisings]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reminiscences-of-the-cuban-revolutionary-war-ernesto-che-guevara/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Powerful and poetic &#8230; For anyone interested in the myth of Che Guevara &#8230; this book is essential reading&#8217; Colm Toibin, Observer &#8216;We were an army of shadows, of ghosts, walking as if to the beat of some dark psychic mechanism&#8230;&#8217; The Cuban Revolution changed the course of the twentieth century. Following years of brutal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reminiscences-of-the-cuban-revolutionary-war-ernesto-che-guevara/">Reminiscences of the Cuban Revolutionary War &#8211; Ernesto Che Guevara</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Powerful and poetic &#8230; For anyone interested in the myth of Che Guevara &#8230; this book is essential reading&#8217; Colm Toibin, Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We were an army of shadows, of ghosts, walking as if to the beat of some dark psychic mechanism&#8230;&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    The Cuban Revolution changed the course of the twentieth century. Following years of brutal tyranny and poverty, a band of idealistic young people fought against immense odds to overthrow a dictator and emerged victorious. This is the story of how they did it. Che Guevara&#8217;s classic eyewitness account chronicles the transformation of a country, and of Che himself, from troop doctor to revolutionary icon.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Che&#8217;s life is an inspiration for every human being who loves freedom&#8217; Nelson Mandela    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reminiscences-of-the-cuban-revolutionary-war-ernesto-che-guevara/">Reminiscences of the Cuban Revolutionary War &#8211; Ernesto Che Guevara</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cold War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*The No.1 Sunday Times Bestseller* *A BBC Between the Covers book club pick* *Shortlisted for the 2018 Baillie Gifford Prize* &#8216;THE BEST TRUE SPY STORY I HAVE EVER READ&#8217; JOHN LE CARRE An exciting Cold War story about a KGB double agent, by one of Britain&#8217;s greatest historians and the ultimate gift for anyone who [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/">The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*The No.1 Sunday Times Bestseller*<br />
                    *A BBC Between the Covers book club pick*<br />
                    *Shortlisted for the 2018 Baillie Gifford Prize*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;THE BEST TRUE SPY STORY I HAVE EVER READ&#8217; JOHN LE CARRE        </p>
<p>                    An exciting Cold War story about a KGB double agent, by one of Britain&#8217;s greatest historians and the ultimate gift for anyone who loves a good spy thriller!    </p>
<p>                    On a warm July evening in 1985, a middle-aged man stood on the pavement of a busy avenue in the heart of Moscow, holding a plastic carrier bag. In his grey suit and tie, he looked like any other Soviet citizen. The bag alone was mildly conspicuous, printed with the red logo of Safeway, the British supermarket.    </p>
<p>                    The man was a spy. A senior KGB officer, for more than a decade he had supplied his British spymasters with a stream of priceless secrets from deep within the Soviet intelligence machine. No spy had done more to damage the KGB. The Safeway bag was a signal: to activate his escape plan to be smuggled out of Soviet Russia. So began one of the boldest and most extraordinary episodes in the history of spying. Ben Macintyre reveals a tale of espionage, betrayal and raw courage that changed the course of the Cold War forever&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    BEN MACINTYRE&#8217;S NEXT BOOK AGENT SONYA IS AVAILABLE TO BUY NOW</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/">The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge. When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality. In Leaders Eat Last, Simon [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge.    </p>
<p>                    When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality.    </p>
<p>                    In Leaders Eat Last, Simon Sinek, internationally bestselling author of Start With Why, investigates these great leaders from Marine Corps Officers, who don&#8217;t just sacrifice their place at the table but often their own comfort and even their lives for those in their care, to the heads of big business and government &#8211; each putting aside their own interests to protect their teams.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Simple and elegant, it shows us how leaders should lead&#8217; William Ury, co-author of Getting to Yes</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From a preeminent presidential historian comes a &#8220;superb and important&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) saga of America&#8217;s wartime chief executives &#8220;Fascinating and heartbreaking . . . timely . . . Beschloss&#8217;s broad scope lets you draw important crosscutting lessons about presidential leadership.&#8221;&#8211;Bill Gates Widely acclaimed and ten years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/">Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From a preeminent presidential historian comes a &#8220;superb and important&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) saga of America&#8217;s wartime chief executives    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Fascinating and heartbreaking . . . timely . . . Beschloss&#8217;s broad scope lets you draw important crosscutting lessons about presidential leadership.&#8221;&#8211;Bill Gates     </p>
<p>                    Widely acclaimed and ten years in the making, Michael Beschloss&#8217;s Presidents of War is an intimate and irresistibly readable chronicle of the Chief Executives who took the United States into conflict and mobilized it for victory. From the War of 1812 to Vietnam, we see these leaders considering the difficult decision to send hundreds of thousands of Americans to their deaths; struggling with Congress, the courts, the press, and antiwar protesters; seeking comfort from their spouses and friends; and dropping to their knees in prayer. Through Beschloss&#8217;s interviews with surviving participants and findings in original letters and once-classified national security documents, we come to understand how these Presidents were able to withstand the pressures of war&#8211;or were broken by them.     </p>
<p>                    Presidents of War combines this sense of immediacy with the overarching context of two centuries of American history, traveling from the time of our Founders, who tried to constrain presidential power, to our modern day, when a single leader has the potential to launch nuclear weapons that can destroy much of the human race.    </p>
<p>                    Praise for Presidents of War     </p>
<p>                    A marvelous narrative. . . . As Beschloss explains, the greatest wartime presidents successfully leaven military action with moral concerns. . . . Beschloss&#8217;s writing is clean and concise, and he admirably draws upon new documents. Some of the more titillating tidbits in the book are in the footnotes. . . . There are fascinating nuggets on virtually every page of Presidents of War. It is a superb and important book, superbly rendered.&#8221;&#8211;Jay Winik, The New York Times Book Review     </p>
<p>                    Sparkle and bite. . . . Valuable and engrossing study of how our chief executives have discharged the most significant of all their duties. . . . Excellent. . . . A fluent narrative that covers two centuries of national conflict.&#8221; &#8211;Richard Snow,  The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/">Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Killing the Rising Sun : How America Vanquished World War II Japan &#8211; Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Martin Dugard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/killing-the-rising-sun-how-america-vanquished-world-war-ii-japan-bill-oreilly-martin-dugard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/killing-the-rising-sun-how-america-vanquished-world-war-ii-japan-bill-oreilly-martin-dugard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The powerful and riveting new book in the multimillion-selling Killing series by Bill O&#8217;Reilly and Martin Dugard Autumn 1944. World War II is nearly over in Europe but is escalating in the Pacific, where American soldiers face an opponent who will go to any length to avoid defeat. The Japanese army follows the samurai code [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/killing-the-rising-sun-how-america-vanquished-world-war-ii-japan-bill-oreilly-martin-dugard-abridged/">Killing the Rising Sun : How America Vanquished World War II Japan &#8211; Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Martin Dugard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The powerful and riveting new book in the multimillion-selling Killing series by Bill O&#8217;Reilly and Martin Dugard     </p>
<p>                    Autumn 1944. World War II is nearly over in Europe but is escalating in the Pacific, where American soldiers face an opponent who will go to any length to avoid defeat. The Japanese army follows the samurai code of Bushido, stipulating that surrender is a form of dishonor. Killing the Rising Sun takes readers to the bloody tropical-island battlefields of Peleliu and Iwo Jima and to the embattled Philippines, where General Douglas MacArthur has made a triumphant return and is plotting a full-scale invasion of Japan.     </p>
<p>                    Across the globe in Los Alamos, New Mexico, Dr. J. Robert Oppenheimer and his team of scientists are preparing to test the deadliest weapon known to mankind. In Washington, DC, FDR dies in office and Harry Truman ascends to the presidency, only to face the most important political decision in history: whether to use that weapon. And in Tokyo, Emperor Hirohito, who is considered a deity by his subjects, refuses to surrender, despite a massive and mounting death toll. Told in the same page-turning style of Killing Lincoln, Killing Kennedy, Killing Jesus, Killing Patton, and Killing Reagan, this epic saga details the final moments of World War II like never before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/killing-the-rising-sun-how-america-vanquished-world-war-ii-japan-bill-oreilly-martin-dugard-abridged/">Killing the Rising Sun : How America Vanquished World War II Japan &#8211; Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Martin Dugard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What are the causes of war? To answer this question, Professor Waltz examines the ideas of major thinkers throughout the history of Western civilization. He explores works both by classic political philosophers, such as St. Augustine, Hobbes, Kant, and Rousseau, and by modern psychologists and anthropologists to discover ideas intended to explain war among states [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/">Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are the causes of war? To answer this question, Professor Waltz examines the ideas of major thinkers throughout the history of Western civilization. He explores works both by classic political philosophers, such as St. Augustine, Hobbes, Kant, and Rousseau, and by modern psychologists and anthropologists to discover ideas intended to explain war among states and related prescriptions for peace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/">Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan. Kaplan probes the inner corridors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan.    </p>
<p>                     Kaplan probes the inner corridors of the National Security Agency, the beyond-top-secret cyber units in the Pentagon, the &#8220;information warfare&#8221; squads of the military services, and the national security debates in the White House, to tell this never-before-told story of the officers, policymakers, scientists, and spies who devised this new form of warfare and who have been planning and (more often than people know) fighting these wars for decades.    </p>
<p>                     From the 1991 Gulf War to conflicts in Haiti, Serbia, Syria, the former Soviet republics, Iraq, and Iran, where cyber warfare played a significant role, Dark Territory chronicles, in fascinating detail, a little-known past that shines an unsettling light on our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rise of the Rocket Girls : The Women Who Propelled Us, from Missiles to the Moon to Mars &#8211; Nathalia Holt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rise-of-the-rocket-girls-the-women-who-propelled-us-from-missiles-to-the-moon-to-mars-nathalia-holt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aerospace & Aviation Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronautics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rise-of-the-rocket-girls-the-women-who-propelled-us-from-missiles-to-the-moon-to-mars-nathalia-holt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the 1940s and 50s, when the newly minted Jet Propulsion Laboratory needed quick-thinking mathematicians to calculate velocities and plot trajectories, they recruited an elite group of young women who, with only pencil, paper, and mathematical prowess, transformed rocket design, helped bring about the first American satellites, and made the exploration of the solar system [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rise-of-the-rocket-girls-the-women-who-propelled-us-from-missiles-to-the-moon-to-mars-nathalia-holt-abridged/">Rise of the Rocket Girls : The Women Who Propelled Us, from Missiles to the Moon to Mars &#8211; Nathalia Holt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the 1940s and 50s, when the newly minted Jet Propulsion Laboratory needed quick-thinking mathematicians to calculate velocities and plot trajectories, they recruited an elite group of young women who, with only pencil, paper, and mathematical prowess, transformed rocket design, helped bring about the first American satellites, and made the exploration of the solar system possible. Rise of the Rocket Girls tells the stories of these women&#8211;known as &#8220;human computers&#8221;&#8211;who broke the boundaries of both gender and science. Based on extensive research and interviews, Nathalia Holt offers a unique perspective on the role of women in science: both where we&#8217;ve been, and the far reaches of space to which we&#8217;re heading.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rise-of-the-rocket-girls-the-women-who-propelled-us-from-missiles-to-the-moon-to-mars-nathalia-holt-abridged/">Rise of the Rocket Girls : The Women Who Propelled Us, from Missiles to the Moon to Mars &#8211; Nathalia Holt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Command and Control &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/command-and-control-eric-schlosser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Weapons]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pollution & Threats To The Environment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/command-and-control-eric-schlosser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Command and Control interweaves the minute-by-minute story of an accident at a missile silo in rural Arkansas, where a single crew struggled to prevent the explosion of the most powerful nuclear warhead ever built by the United States, with a historical narrative that spans more than fifty years. It depicts the urgent effort to ensure [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/command-and-control-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Command and Control &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Command and Control interweaves the minute-by-minute story of an accident at a missile silo in rural Arkansas, where a single crew struggled to prevent the explosion of the most powerful nuclear warhead ever built by the United States, with a historical narrative that spans more than fifty years. It depicts the urgent effort to ensure that nuclear weapons can&#8217;t be stolen, sabotaged, used without permission, or detonated inadvertently. Schlosser also looks at the Cold War from a new perspective, offering history from the ground up, telling the stories of bomber pilots, missile commanders, maintenance crews, and other ordinary servicemen who risked their lives to avert a nuclear holocaust. Drawing on recently declassified documents and interviews with men who designed and routinely handled nuclear weapons, Command and Control takes readers into a terrifying but fascinating world that, until now, has been largely hidden from view.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/command-and-control-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Command and Control &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Extreme Ownership : How U.S. Navy Seals Lead and Win &#8211; Jocko Willink (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/extreme-ownership-how-u-s-navy-seals-lead-and-win-jocko-willink-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/extreme-ownership-how-u-s-navy-seals-lead-and-win-jocko-willink-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Highly decorated Navy SEALs, now successful businessmen, show readers how to lead and win in business and in life with principles learned on the battlefield. In Extreme Ownership, Jocko Willink and Leif Babin share hard-hitting, Navy SEAL combat stories that translate into lessons for business and life. With riveting first-hand accounts of making high-pressure decisions [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/extreme-ownership-how-u-s-navy-seals-lead-and-win-jocko-willink-abridged/">Extreme Ownership : How U.S. Navy Seals Lead and Win &#8211; Jocko Willink (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Highly decorated Navy SEALs, now successful businessmen, show readers how to lead and win in business and in life with principles learned on the battlefield. In Extreme Ownership, Jocko Willink and Leif Babin share hard-hitting, Navy SEAL combat stories that translate into lessons for business and life. With riveting first-hand accounts of making high-pressure decisions as Navy SEAL battlefield leaders, this book is equally gripping for leaders who seek to dominate other arenas. Jocko and Leif served together in SEAL Task Unit Bruiser, the most highly decorated Special Operations unit from the war in Iraq. Their efforts contributed to the historic triumph for U.S. forces in Ramadi. Through those difficult months of sustained combat, Jocko, Leif and their SEAL brothers learned that leadership &#8211; at every level &#8211; is the most important thing on the battlefield.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/extreme-ownership-how-u-s-navy-seals-lead-and-win-jocko-willink-abridged/">Extreme Ownership : How U.S. Navy Seals Lead and Win &#8211; Jocko Willink (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hue 1968 : A Turning Point of the American War in Vietnam &#8211; Mark Bowden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hue-1968-a-turning-point-of-the-american-war-in-vietnam-mark-bowden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Postwar 20th Century History, From C 1945 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vietnam War]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hue-1968-a-turning-point-of-the-american-war-in-vietnam-mark-bowden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>By January 1968 the fighting in Vietnam seemed to be at a stalemate. Yet General William Westmoreland, commander of American forces, announced a new phase of the war in which &#8216;the end begins to come into view.&#8217; The North Vietnamese had different ideas. In mid-1967, the leadership in Hanoi had started planning an offensive intended [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hue-1968-a-turning-point-of-the-american-war-in-vietnam-mark-bowden-abridged/">Hue 1968 : A Turning Point of the American War in Vietnam &#8211; Mark Bowden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By January 1968 the fighting in Vietnam seemed to be at a stalemate. Yet General William Westmoreland, commander of American forces, announced a new phase of the war in which &#8216;the end begins to come into view.&#8217; The North Vietnamese had different ideas. In mid-1967, the leadership in Hanoi had started planning an offensive intended to win the war in a single stroke. Part military action and part popular uprising, the Tet Offensive included attacks across South Vietnam, but the most dramatic and successful would be the capture of Hue, the country&#8217;s cultural capital. At 2:30 a.m. on January 31, 10,000 National Liberation Front troops descended from hidden camps and surged across the city of 140,000. By morning, all of Hue was in Front hands save for two small military outposts.    </p>
<p>                     The commanders in country and politicians in Washington refused to believe the size and scope of the Front&#8217;s presence. After several futile and deadly days, Lieutenant Colonel Ernie Cheatham would finally come up with a strategy to retake the city, block by block and building by building, in some of the most intense urban combat since World War II.    </p>
<p>                     With unprecedented access to war archives in the U.S. and Vietnam and interviews with participants from both sides, Bowden narrates each stage of this crucial battle through multiple points of view. Played out over twenty-four days of terrible fighting and ultimately costing 10,000 combatant and civilian lives, the Battle of Hue was by far the bloodiest of the entire war. When it ended, the American debate was never again about winning, only about how to leave. In Hue 1968, Bowden masterfully reconstructs this pivotal moment in the American war in Vietnam.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hue-1968-a-turning-point-of-the-american-war-in-vietnam-mark-bowden-abridged/">Hue 1968 : A Turning Point of the American War in Vietnam &#8211; Mark Bowden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sea Stories : My Life in Special Operations &#8211; William H. McRaven (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sea-stories-my-life-in-special-operations-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Afghan War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Iraq War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History: Post WW2 Conflicts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Veterans]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Special & Elite Forces]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sea-stories-my-life-in-special-operations-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Admiral William H. McRaven is a part of American military history, having been involved in some of the most famous missions in recent memory, including the capture of Saddam Hussein, the rescue of Captain Richard Phillips, and the raid to kill Osama bin Laden.Sea Stories begins in 1960 at the American Officers&#8217; Club in France, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-stories-my-life-in-special-operations-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Sea Stories : My Life in Special Operations &#8211; William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Admiral William H. McRaven is a part of American military history, having been involved in some of the most famous missions in recent memory, including the capture of Saddam Hussein, the rescue of Captain Richard Phillips, and the raid to kill Osama bin Laden.Sea Stories begins in 1960 at the American Officers&#8217; Club in France, where Allied officers and their wives gathered to have drinks and tell stories about their adventures during World War II &#8212; the place where a young Bill McRaven learned the value of a good story. Sea Stories is an unforgettable look back on one man&#8217;s incredible life, from childhood days sneaking into high-security military sites to a day job of hunting terrorists and rescuing hostages.Action-packed, inspiring, and full of thrilling stories from life in the special operations world, Sea Stories is a remarkable memoir from one of America&#8217;s most accomplished leaders.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-stories-my-life-in-special-operations-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Sea Stories : My Life in Special Operations &#8211; William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Call Sign Chaos : Learning to Lead &#8211; Jim Mattis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A clear-eyed account of learning how to lead in a chaotic world, by General Jim Mattis&#8211;the former Secretary of Defense and one of the most formidable strategic thinkers of our time&#8211;and Bing West, a former assistant secretary of defense and combat Marine. &#8220;A four-star general&#8217;s five-star memoir.&#8221;&#8211;The Wall Street [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis-abridged/">Call Sign Chaos : Learning to Lead &#8211; Jim Mattis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A clear-eyed account of learning how to lead in a chaotic world, by General Jim Mattis&#8211;the former Secretary of Defense and one of the most formidable strategic thinkers of our time&#8211;and Bing West, a former assistant secretary of defense and combat Marine.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A four-star general&#8217;s five-star memoir.&#8221;&#8211;The Wall Street Journal     </p>
<p>                     Call Sign Chaos is the account of Jim Mattis&#8217;s storied career, from wide-ranging leadership roles in three wars to ultimately commanding a quarter of a million troops across the Middle East. Along the way, Mattis recounts his foundational experiences as a leader, extracting the lessons he has learned about the nature of warfighting and peacemaking, the importance of allies, and the strategic dilemmas&#8211;and short-sighted thinking&#8211;now facing our nation. He makes it clear why America must return to a strategic footing so as not to continue winning battles but fighting inconclusive wars.     </p>
<p>                     Mattis divides his book into three parts: Direct Leadership, Executive Leadership, and Strategic Leadership. In the first part, Mattis recalls his early experiences leading Marines into battle, when he knew his troops as well as his own brothers. In the second part, he explores what it means to command thousands of troops and how to adapt your leadership style to ensure your intent is understood by your most junior troops so that they can own their mission. In the third part, Mattis describes the challenges and techniques of leadership at the strategic level, where military leaders reconcile war&#8217;s grim realities with political leaders&#8217; human aspirations, where complexity reigns and the consequences of imprudence are severe, even catastrophic.     </p>
<p>                     Call Sign Chaos is a memoir of a life of warfighting and lifelong learning, following along as Mattis rises from Marine recruit to four-star general. It is a journey about learning to lead and a story about how he, through constant study and action, developed a unique leadership philosophy, one relevant to us all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-sign-chaos-learning-to-lead-jim-mattis-abridged/">Call Sign Chaos : Learning to Lead &#8211; Jim Mattis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sea Power : The History and Geopolitics of the World&#8217;s Oceans &#8211; Admiral James Stavridis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Naval Forces & Warfare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From one of the most admired admirals of his generation-and the only admiral to serve as Supreme Allied Commander at NATO-comes a remarkable voyage through all of the world&#8217;s most important bodies of water, providing the story of naval power as a driver of human history and a crucial element in our current geopolitical path. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/">Sea Power : The History and Geopolitics of the World&#8217;s Oceans &#8211; Admiral James Stavridis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From one of the most admired admirals of his generation-and the only admiral to serve as Supreme Allied Commander at NATO-comes a remarkable voyage through all of the world&#8217;s most important bodies of water, providing the story of naval power as a driver of human history and a crucial element in our current geopolitical path.     </p>
<p>                     From the time of the Greeks and the Persians clashing in the Mediterranean, sea power has determined world power.  To an extent that is often underappreciated, it still does. No one understands this better than Admiral Jim Stavridis. In Sea Power, Admiral Stavridis takes us with him on a tour of the world&#8217;s oceans from the admiral&#8217;s chair, showing us how the geography of the oceans has shaped the destiny of nations, and how naval power has in a real sense made the world we live in today, and will shape the world we live in tomorrow.      </p>
<p>                     Not least, Sea Power is marvelous naval history, giving us fresh insight into great naval engagements from the battles of Salamis and Lepanto through to Trafalgar, the Battle of the Atlantic, and submarine conflicts of the Cold War. It is also a keen-eyed reckoning with the likely sites of our next major naval conflicts, particularly the Arctic Ocean, Eastern Mediterranean, and the South China Sea. Finally, Sea Power steps back to take a holistic view of the plagues to our oceans that are best seen that way, from piracy to pollution.    </p>
<p>                     When most of us look at a globe, we focus on the shape of the of the seven continents. Admiral Stavridis sees the shapes of the seven seas.  After reading Sea Power, you will too. Not since Alfred Thayer Mahan&#8217;s legendary The Influence of Sea Power upon History have we had such a powerful reckoning with this vital subject.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/">Sea Power : The History and Geopolitics of the World&#8217;s Oceans &#8211; Admiral James Stavridis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Napoleonic Wars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions, Uprisings, Rebellions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217; Simon Sebag Montefiore &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon. Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the  momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217;   Simon Sebag Montefiore<br />
                    &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell    </p>
<p>                    From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon.    </p>
<p>                    Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of all human lives. In the space of just twenty years, from October 1795 when as a young artillery captain he cleared the streets of Paris of insurrectionists, to his final defeat at the (horribly mismanaged) battle of Waterloo in June 1815, Napoleon transformed France and Europe. After seizing power in a coup d&#8217;etat he ended the corruption and incompetence into which the Revolution had descended. In a series of dazzling battles he reinvented the art of warfare; in peace, he completely remade the laws of France, modernised her systems of education and administration, and presided over a flourishing of the beautiful &#8216;Empire style&#8217; in the arts. The impossibility of defeating his most persistent enemy, Great Britain, led him to make draining and ultimately fatal expeditions into Spain and Russia, where half a million Frenchmen died and his Empire began to unravel.    </p>
<p>                    More than any other modern biographer, Andrew Roberts conveys Napoleon&#8217;s tremendous energy, both physical and intellectual, and the attractiveness of his personality, even to his enemies. He has walked 53 of Napoleon&#8217;s 60 battlefields, and has absorbed the gigantic new French edition of Napoleon&#8217;s letters, which allows a complete re-evaluation of this exceptional man. He overturns many received opinions, including the myth of a great romance with Josephine: she took a lover immediately after their marriage, and, as Roberts shows, he had three times as many mistresses as he acknowledged.    </p>
<p>                    Of the climactic Battle of Leipzig in 1813, as the fighting closed around them, a French sergeant-major wrote, &#8216;No-one who has not experienced it can have any idea of the enthusiasm that burst forth among the half-starved, exhausted soldiers when the Emperor was there in person. If all were demoralised and he appeared, his presence was like an electric shock. All shouted &#8220;Vive l&#8217;Empereur!&#8221; and everyone charged blindly into the fire.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    The reader of this biography will understand why this was so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING * &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING *     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly written haymaker&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly three years of reporting, hundreds of hours of interviews and more than two hundred sources, including some of the most senior members of the administration, friends and first-hand witnesses who have never spoken before, Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig take us inside some of the most controversial moments of Trump&#8217;s presidency. They peer deeply into Trump&#8217;s White House &#8211; at the aides pressured to lie to the public, the lawyers scrambling to clear up norm-breaking disasters, and the staffers whose careers have been reduced to ashes &#8211; to paint an unparalleled group portrait of an administration driven by self-preservation and paranoia.     </p>
<p>                    Rucker and Leonnig reveal Trump at his most unvarnished, showing the unhinged decision-making and incompetence that has floored officials and stunned foreign leaders. They portray unscripted calls with Vladimir Putin, steak dinners with Kim Jong-un, and calls with Theresa May so hostile that they left her aides shaken. They also take a hard look at Robert Mueller, Trump&#8217;s greatest antagonist to date, and how his investigation slowly unravelled an administration whose universal value is loyalty &#8211; not to country, but to the president himself.    </p>
<p>                    Grippingly told, A Very Stable Genius is a behind-the-scenes account of Trump&#8217;s vainglorious pursuit of power in his first term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Doomsday Machine : Confessions of a Nuclear War Planner &#8211; Daniel Ellsberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-doomsday-machine-confessions-of-a-nuclear-war-planner-daniel-ellsberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arms Negotiation & Control]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Postwar 20th Century History, From C 1945 To C 2000]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-doomsday-machine-confessions-of-a-nuclear-war-planner-daniel-ellsberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Andrew Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction Finalist for The California Book Award in Nonfiction The San Francisco Chronicle&#8217;s Best of the Year List Foreign Affairs Best Books of the Year In These Times &#8220;Best Books of the Year Huffington Post&#8217;s Ten Excellent December Books List LitHub&#8217;s &#8220;Five Books Making News This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-doomsday-machine-confessions-of-a-nuclear-war-planner-daniel-ellsberg-abridged/">The Doomsday Machine : Confessions of a Nuclear War Planner &#8211; Daniel Ellsberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Andrew Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction<br />
                    Finalist for The California Book Award in Nonfiction<br />
                    The San Francisco Chronicle&#8217;s Best of the Year List<br />
                    Foreign Affairs Best Books of the Year<br />
                    In These Times &#8220;Best Books of the Year<br />
                    Huffington Post&#8217;s Ten Excellent December Books List<br />
                    LitHub&#8217;s &#8220;Five Books Making News This Week&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    From the legendary whistle-blower who revealed the Pentagon Papers, an eyewitness expos of the dangers of America&#8217;s Top Secret, seventy-year-long nuclear policy that continues to this day.     </p>
<p>                    Here, for the first time, former high-level defense analyst Daniel Ellsberg reveals his shocking firsthand account of America&#8217;s nuclear program in the 1960s. From the remotest air bases in the Pacific Command, where he discovered that the authority to initiate use of nuclear weapons was widely delegated, to the secret plans for general nuclear war under Eisenhower, which, if executed, would cause the near-extinction of humanity, Ellsberg shows that the legacy of this most dangerous arms buildup in the history of civilization&#8211;and its proposed renewal under the Trump administration&#8211;threatens our very survival. No other insider with high-level access has written so candidly of the nuclear strategy of the late Eisenhower and early Kennedy years, and nothing has fundamentally changed since that era.     </p>
<p>                    Framed as a memoir&#8211;a chronicle of madness in which Ellsberg acknowledges participating&#8211;this gripping expos reads like a thriller and offers feasible steps we can take to dismantle the existing doomsday machine and avoid nuclear catastrophe, returning Ellsberg to his role as whistle-blower. The Doomsday Machine is thus a real-life Dr. Strangelove story and an ultimately hopeful&#8211;and powerfully important&#8211;book about not just our country, but the future of the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-doomsday-machine-confessions-of-a-nuclear-war-planner-daniel-ellsberg-abridged/">The Doomsday Machine : Confessions of a Nuclear War Planner &#8211; Daniel Ellsberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lawrence in Arabia : War, Deceit, Imperial Folly and the Making of the Modern Middle East &#8211; Scott Anderson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Battles & Campaigns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 1 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Arab Revolt against the Turks in World War One was, in the words of T.E. Lawrence, &#8216;a sideshow of a sideshow&#8217;. Amidst the slaughter in European trenches, the Western combatants paid scant attention to the Middle Eastern theatre. As a result, the conflict was shaped to a remarkable degree by a small handful of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/">Lawrence in Arabia : War, Deceit, Imperial Folly and the Making of the Modern Middle East &#8211; Scott Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Arab Revolt against the Turks in World War One was, in the words of T.E. Lawrence, &#8216;a sideshow of a sideshow&#8217;. Amidst the slaughter in European trenches, the Western combatants paid scant attention to the Middle Eastern theatre. As a result, the conflict was shaped to a remarkable degree by a small handful of adventurers and low-level officers far removed from the corridors of power.   At the centre of it all was Lawrence. In early 1914 he was an archaeologist excavating ruins in the sands of Syria; by 1917 he was battling both the enemy and his own government to bring about the vision he had for the Arab people. Operating in the Middle East at the same time, but to wildly different ends, were three other important players: a German attache, an American oilman and a committed Zionist. The intertwined paths of these four young men &#8211; the schemes they put in place, the battles they fought, the betrayals they endured and committed &#8211; mirror the grandeur, intrigue and tragedy of the war in the desert.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lawrence-in-arabia-war-deceit-imperial-folly-and-the-making-of-the-modern-middle-east-scott-anderson-abridged/">Lawrence in Arabia : War, Deceit, Imperial Folly and the Making of the Modern Middle East &#8211; Scott Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Way of the SEAL : Think Like an Elite Warrior to Lead and Succeed &#8211; Mark Divine, Allyson Edelhertz Machate (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-way-of-the-seal-think-like-an-elite-warrior-to-lead-and-succeed-mark-divine-allyson-edelhertz-machate-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-way-of-the-seal-think-like-an-elite-warrior-to-lead-and-succeed-mark-divine-allyson-edelhertz-machate-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blending the tactics he learned from America&#8217;s elite force with lessons from the Spartans, samurai, Apache scouts, and other great warrior traditions, Mark Divine has distilled the fundamentals of success into eight powerful principles that will transform you into the leader you always knew you could be. Learn to think like a SEAL and lead. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-of-the-seal-think-like-an-elite-warrior-to-lead-and-succeed-mark-divine-allyson-edelhertz-machate-abridged/">The Way of the SEAL : Think Like an Elite Warrior to Lead and Succeed &#8211; Mark Divine, Allyson Edelhertz Machate (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blending the tactics he learned from America&#8217;s elite force with lessons from the Spartans, samurai, Apache scouts, and other great warrior traditions, Mark Divine has distilled the fundamentals of success into eight powerful principles that will transform you into the leader you always knew you could be. Learn to think like a SEAL and lead.     </p>
<p>                    In The Way of the SEAL, ex-Navy Commander Mark Divine reveals exercises, meditations and focusing techniques to train your mind for mental toughness, emotional resilience and uncanny intuition. Along the way you&#8217;ll reaffirm your ultimate purpose, define your most important goals, and take concrete steps to make them happen. A practical guide for businesspeople or anyone who wants to be an elite operator in life, this book will teach you how to:<br />
                      Lead from the front, so that others will want to work for you  Practice front-sight focus, the radical ability to focus on one thing until victory is achieved  Think offense, all the time, to eradicate fear and indecisiveness  Smash the box and be an unconventional thinker so you&#8217;re never thrown off-guard by chaotic conditions Access your intuition so you can make hard right decisions  Achieve twenty times more than you think you can  and much more Blending the tactics he learned from America&#8217;s elite forces with lessons from the Spartans, samurai, Apache scouts, and other great warrior traditions, Divine has distilled the fundamentals of success into eight powerful principles that will transform you into the leader you always knew you could be.     </p>
<p>                    Learn to think like a SEAL, and take charge of your destiny at work, home and in life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-of-the-seal-think-like-an-elite-warrior-to-lead-and-succeed-mark-divine-allyson-edelhertz-machate-abridged/">The Way of the SEAL : Think Like an Elite Warrior to Lead and Succeed &#8211; Mark Divine, Allyson Edelhertz Machate (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
