<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Behavioural Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/behavioural-economics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/behavioural-economics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Behavioural Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/behavioural-economics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Curse of Bigness : Antitrust in the New Gilded Age &#8211; Tim Wu (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Company, Commercial & Competition Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Competition Law / Antitrust Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law As It Applies To Other Professions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the man who coined the term net neutrality, comes a warning about the dangers of excessive corporate and industrial concentration for our economic and political future. We live in an age of extreme corporate concentration, in which global industries are controlled by just a few giant firms&#8211;big banks, big pharma, and big tech, just [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/">The Curse of Bigness : Antitrust in the New Gilded Age &#8211; Tim Wu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the man who coined the term net neutrality, comes a warning about the dangers of excessive corporate and industrial concentration for our economic and political future.     </p>
<p>                    We live in an age of extreme corporate concentration, in which global industries are controlled by just a few giant firms&#8211;big banks, big pharma, and big tech, just to name a few. But concern over what Louis Brandeis called the curse of bigness can no longer remain the province of specialist lawyers and economists, for it has spilled over into policy and politics, even threatening democracy itself. History suggests that tolerance of inequality and failing to control excessive corporate power may prompt the rise of populism, nationalism, extremist politicians, and fascist regimes. In short, as Wu warns, we are in grave danger of repeating the signature errors of the twentieth century.     </p>
<p>                    In The Curse of Bigness, Tim Wu, special assistant to President Biden for technology and competition policy, explains how figures like Brandeis and Theodore Roosevelt first confronted the democratic threats posed by the great trusts of the Gilded Age&#8211;but the lessons of the Progressive Era were forgotten in the last 40 years. He calls for recovering the lost tenets of the trustbusting age as part of a broader revival of American progressive ideas as we confront the fallout of persistent and extreme economic inequality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/">The Curse of Bigness : Antitrust in the New Gilded Age &#8211; Tim Wu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hug Your Haters &#8211; Jay Baer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Haters are not your problem. . . . Ignoring them is. Eighty percent of companies say they deliver out­standing customer service, but only 8 percent of their customers agree. This book will help you close that gap by reconfiguring your customer service to deliver knockout experiences. The near-universal adoption of smartphones and social media has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/">Hug Your Haters &#8211; Jay Baer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Haters are not your problem. . . .<br />
                    Ignoring them is.     </p>
<p>                    Eighty percent of companies say they deliver out­standing customer service, but only 8 percent of their customers agree. This book will help you close that gap by reconfiguring your customer service to deliver knockout experiences.     </p>
<p>                    The near-universal adoption of smartphones and social media has fundamentally altered the science of complaints. Critics (&#8220;haters&#8221;) can now express their displeasure faster and more pub­licly than ever. These trends have resulted in an overall increase in complaints and a belief by many businesses that they have to &#8220;pick their spots&#8221; when choosing to answer criticisms.     </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author Jay Baer shows why that approach is a major mistake. Based on an exten­sive proprietary study of how, where, and why we complain, Hug Your Haters proves that there are two types of complainers, each with very differ­ent motivations:     </p>
<p>                    -Offstage haters. These people simply want solutions to their problems. They complain via legacy channels where the likelihood of a response is highest&#8211;phone, e-mail, and com­pany websites. Offstage haters don&#8217;t care if any­one else finds out, as long as they get answers.<br />
                    -Onstage haters. These people are often disap­pointed by a substandard interaction via tradi­tional channels, so they turn to indirect venues, such as social media, online review sites, and discussion boards. Onstage haters want more than solutions&#8211;they want an audience to share their righteous indignation.     </p>
<p>                    Hug Your Haters shows exactly how to deal with both groups, drawing on meticulously researched case studies from businesses of all types and sizes from around the world. It includes specific play­books and formulas as well as a fold-out poster of &#8220;the Hatrix,&#8221; which summarizes the best strate­gies for different situations. The book is also filled with poignant and hilarious examples of haters gone wild, and companies gone crazy, as well as inspirational stories of companies responding with speed, compassion, and humanity.     </p>
<p>                    Whether you work for a mom-and-pop store or a global brand, you will have haters&#8211;and you can&#8217;t afford to ignore them. Baer&#8217;s insights and tactics will teach you how to embrace complaints, put haters to work for you, and turn bad news into good outcomes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/">Hug Your Haters &#8211; Jay Baer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Foolproof : A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8211; Greg Ip (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/foolproof-a-financial-times-book-of-the-year-greg-ip-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insurance & Actuarial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/foolproof-a-financial-times-book-of-the-year-greg-ip-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why anti-lock brakes make us drive faster Why saving money can lead to financial crises How football helmets make the game more dangerous Why letting forest fires burn can be safer than putting them out We have learned a staggering amount about human nature and disaster-yet we are continually unprepared for car crashes, floods, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/foolproof-a-financial-times-book-of-the-year-greg-ip-abridged/">Foolproof : A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8211; Greg Ip (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why anti-lock brakes make us drive faster    </p>
<p>                      Why saving money can lead to financial crises    </p>
<p>                    How football helmets make the game more dangerous    </p>
<p>                    Why letting forest fires burn can be safer than putting them out    </p>
<p>                    We have learned a staggering amount about human nature and disaster-yet we are continually unprepared for car crashes, floods, and financial crises. Partly this is because the very success we&#8217;ve had making life safer enables us to take more extreme, different risks. As our cities, transport systems, and financial markets become more interconnected and complex, so does the potential for disaster.     </p>
<p>                    How do we stay safe? Should we? What if our attempts are exposing us even more to the very risks we are trying to avoid? What if acceptance of danger ultimately makes us more secure and prosperous? Is there such a thing as foolproof?     </p>
<p>                    In this fascinating account of risk-taking and crisis, Greg Ip presents a macro theory of human nature and disaster that explains how we can keep ourselves safe in our increasingly dangerous world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/foolproof-a-financial-times-book-of-the-year-greg-ip-abridged/">Foolproof : A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8211; Greg Ip (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doughnut Economics : Seven Ways to Think Like a 21st-Century Economist &#8211; Kate Raworth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/doughnut-economics-seven-ways-to-think-like-a-21st-century-economist-kate-raworth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/doughnut-economics-seven-ways-to-think-like-a-21st-century-economist-kate-raworth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Economics is broken, and the planet is paying the price. Unforeseen financial crises. Extreme wealth inequality. Relentless pressure on the environment. Can we go on like this? Is there an alternative? In Doughnut Economics, Oxford academic Kate Raworth lays out the seven deadly mistakes of economics and offers a radical re-envisioning of the system that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doughnut-economics-seven-ways-to-think-like-a-21st-century-economist-kate-raworth-abridged/">Doughnut Economics : Seven Ways to Think Like a 21st-Century Economist &#8211; Kate Raworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Economics is broken, and the planet is paying the price.    </p>
<p>                    Unforeseen financial crises. Extreme wealth inequality. Relentless pressure on the environment. Can we go on like this? Is there an alternative?    </p>
<p>                    In Doughnut Economics, Oxford academic Kate Raworth lays out the seven deadly mistakes of economics and offers a radical re-envisioning of the system that has brought us to the point of ruin. Moving beyond the myths of &#8216;rational economic man&#8217; and unlimited growth, Doughnut Economics zeroes in on the sweet spot: a system that meets all our needs without exhausting the planet.    </p>
<p>                    The demands of the 21st century require a new shape of economics. This might just be it.    </p>
<p>                    *The Sunday Times Bestseller*<br />
                     *A Financial Times and Forbes Book of the Year*<br />
                     *Winner of the Transmission Prize 2018*<br />
                     *Longlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2017*    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The John Maynard Keynes of the 21st century.&#8217; George Monbiot, Guardian    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This is sharp, significant scholarship . . . Thrilling.&#8217; Times Higher Education    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Raworth&#8217;s magnum opus . . . A fascinating reminder to business leaders and economists alike to stand back at a distance to examine our modern economics.&#8217; Books of the Year, Forbes    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;There are some really important economic and political thinkers around at the moment &#8211; such as Kate Raworth&#8217;s Doughnut Economics.&#8217; Andrew Marr, Guardian    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An admirable attempt to broaden the horizons of economic thinking.&#8217; Martin Wolf, Books of the Year, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A compelling and timely intervention.&#8217; Caroline Lucas MP, Books of the Year, The Ecologist</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doughnut-economics-seven-ways-to-think-like-a-21st-century-economist-kate-raworth-abridged/">Doughnut Economics : Seven Ways to Think Like a 21st-Century Economist &#8211; Kate Raworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new, evolutionary explanation of markets and investor behavior Half of all Americans have money in the stock market, yet economists can&#8217;t agree on whether investors and markets are rational and efficient, as modern financial theory assumes, or irrational and inefficient, as behavioral economists believe&#8211;and as financial bubbles, crashes, and crises suggest. This is one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/">Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new, evolutionary explanation of markets and investor behavior  Half of all Americans have money in the stock market, yet economists can&#8217;t agree on whether investors and markets are rational and efficient, as modern financial theory assumes, or irrational and inefficient, as behavioral economists believe&#8211;and as financial bubbles, crashes, and crises suggest. This is one of the biggest debates in economics and the value or futility of investment management and financial regulation hang on the outcome. In this groundbreaking book, Andrew Lo cuts through this debate with a new framework, the Adaptive Markets Hypothesis, in which rationality and irrationality coexist. Drawing on psychology, evolutionary biology, neuroscience, artificial intelligence, and other fields, Adaptive Markets shows that the theory of market efficiency isn&#8217;t wrong but merely incomplete. When markets are unstable, investors react instinctively, creating inefficiencies for others to exploit. Lo&#8217;s new paradigm explains how financial evolution shapes behavior and markets at the speed of thought&#8211;a fact revealed by swings between stability and crisis, profit and loss, and innovation and regulation.<br />
                    A fascinating intellectual journey filled with compelling stories, Adaptive Markets starts with the origins of market efficiency and its failures, turns to the foundations of investor behavior, and concludes with practical implications&#8211;including how hedge funds have become the Galapagos Islands of finance, what really happened in the 2008 meltdown, and how we might avoid future crises. An ambitious new answer to fundamental questions in economics, Adaptive Markets is essential reading for anyone who wants to know how markets really work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/">Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You May Also Like : Taste in an Age of Endless Choice &#8211; Tom Vanderbilt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-may-also-like-taste-in-an-age-of-endless-choice-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-may-also-like-taste-in-an-age-of-endless-choice-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why do we get so embarrassed when a colleague wears the same shirt? Why do we eat the same thing for breakfast every day, but seek out novelty at lunch and dinner? How has streaming changed the way Netflix makes recommendations? Why do people think the music of their youth is the best? How can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-may-also-like-taste-in-an-age-of-endless-choice-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/">You May Also Like : Taste in an Age of Endless Choice &#8211; Tom Vanderbilt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why do we get so embarrassed when a colleague wears the same shirt? Why do we eat the same thing for breakfast every day, but seek out novelty at lunch and dinner? How has streaming changed the way Netflix makes recommendations? Why do people think the music of their youth is the best? How can you spot a fake review on Yelp?     </p>
<p>                     Our preferences and opinions are constantly being shaped by countless forces &#8211; especially in the digital age with its nonstop procession of &#8220;thumbs up&#8221; and &#8220;likes&#8221; and &#8220;stars.&#8221; Tom Vanderbilt, bestselling author of Traffic, explains why we like the things we like, why we hate the things we hate, and what all this tell us about ourselves.     </p>
<p>                     With a voracious curiosity, Vanderbilt stalks the elusive beast of taste, probing research in psychology, marketing, and neuroscience to answer myriad complex and fascinating questions. If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how Netflix recommends movies or why books often see a sudden decline in Amazon ratings after they win a major prize, Tom Vanderbilt has answers to these questions and many more that you&#8217;ve probably never thought to ask.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-may-also-like-taste-in-an-age-of-endless-choice-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/">You May Also Like : Taste in an Age of Endless Choice &#8211; Tom Vanderbilt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Hour Between Dog and Wolf : Risk-Taking, Gut Feelings and the Biology of Boom and Bust &#8211; John Coates (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book Prize, The Hour Between Dog and Wolf is a resonant exploration of economic behaviour and its consequences. Shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times and Goldman Sachs Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/">The Hour Between Dog and Wolf : Risk-Taking, Gut Feelings and the Biology of Boom and Bust &#8211; John Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book Prize, The Hour Between Dog and Wolf is a resonant exploration of economic behaviour and its consequences.    </p>
<p>                              Shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times and Goldman Sachs Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book Prize, this startling and unconventional book from neuroscientist and former Wall Street trader John Coates shows us the bankers in their natural environment, revealing how their biochemistry has a lasting and significant impact on our economy.    </p>
<p>                              We learn how risk stimulates the most primitive part of the banker&#8217;s brain and how making the deals our bank balances depend on provokes an overwhelming fight-or-flight response. Constant swinging between aggression and apprehension impairs their judgment, causing economic upheaval in the wider world. The transformation between each split-second decision is what Coates calls the hour between dog and wolf, and understanding the biology behind bubbles and crashes may be the key to stabilising the markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/">The Hour Between Dog and Wolf : Risk-Taking, Gut Feelings and the Biology of Boom and Bust &#8211; John Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Algebra of Happiness : The pursuit of success, love and what it all means &#8211; Scott Galloway (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author, a provocative book of hard-won wisdom for achieving a fulfilling career and life. &#8211; How can you have a meaningful career, not just a lucrative one? &#8211; Is a work/life balance really possible? &#8211; What does it take to make a long-term relationship succeed? &#8211; What can you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/">The Algebra of Happiness : The pursuit of success, love and what it all means &#8211; Scott Galloway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author, a provocative book of hard-won wisdom for achieving a  fulfilling career and life.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; How can you have a meaningful career, not just a lucrative one?<br />
                    &#8211; Is a work/life balance really possible?<br />
                    &#8211; What does it take to make a long-term relationship succeed?<br />
                    &#8211; What can you do now so there are no regrets aged 40, 50 or 80?    </p>
<p>                                   As Scott Galloway puts it, by the time you hit your mid twenties sh*t gets real. Life become stressful. Even the smart, the hard working and the elite can feel lost in a chaotic, noisy and unpredictable world. As a professor at New York University&#8217;s Stern School of Business, the debate in Galloway&#8217;s MBA class often veers away from business strategy to the challenging issue of life strategies. Which is why Galloway, in his signature, take-no-prisoners style, has developed a dynamic formula for a life well lived.    </p>
<p>                     In The Algebra of Happiness Galloway tells you how life can be navigated and negotiated better to maximise happiness and minimise the inevitable stress. Delivering practical advice and hard-won wisdom on everything from when to own property to how hard to work, this is self-help for anyone struggling with life&#8217;s big questions. Through simple equations that measure the relationship between success, resilience and failure or the correlation between happiness and money, Galloway attempts to convert intangible advice to tangible equations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/">The Algebra of Happiness : The pursuit of success, love and what it all means &#8211; Scott Galloway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that philosophy and illustrates how successful businesses have redefined themselves in the new customer universe.    </p>
<p>                    Personality Not Included is a powerhouse resource packed with bold new insights that show you how to shed the lifeless armor of your business and rediscover the soul of your brand. Sharing stories from the ethos of the world&#8217;s weirdest city, to how Manga has taken the comic book industry by storm, to showcasing brands like Intel, Boeing, ING, and Dyson, Bhargava shows you why personality matters from the inside out.    </p>
<p>                    In Part One, you&#8217;ll be introduced to the key components to building a personality and learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    Recognize the greatest myth that most marketers blindly follow, and how to get past itUse the &#8220;UAT Filter&#8221; to understand the personality of your organization and products in order to develop a communication strategy that drives your marketingCreate your company&#8217;s &#8220;marketing backstory&#8221; using techniques pioneered by Hollywood screenwritersHarness the influence of &#8220;accidental spokespeople&#8221; and use it to your advantageNavigate the roadblocks of using personality that come from bosses, peers, investors, and lawyers, without getting fired or flamedPinpoint and capitalize on the moments where personality can make a difference<br />
                    Part Two is packed with guides, tools, and techniques to help you flawlessly implement your plan. It features practical, step-by-step lessons that help you effectively move from theory to action, and includes a valuable collection of guides, checklists, question forms, printable resources, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Don&#8217;t be another faceless company-learn the new rules for succeeding in the social media era with Personality Not Included.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buyology : Truth and Lies About Why We Buy &#8211; Martin Lindstrom, Foreword by Paco Underhill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Purchasing & Supply Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; &#8220;A fascinating look at how consumers perceive logos, ads, commercials, brands, and products.&#8221;&#8211;Time How much do we know about why we buy? What truly influences our decisions in today&#8217;s message-cluttered world? In Buyology, Martin Lindstrom presents the astonishing findings from his groundbreaking three-year, seven-million-dollar neuromarketing study&#8211;a cutting-edge experiment that peered [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/">Buyology : Truth and Lies About Why We Buy &#8211; Martin Lindstrom, Foreword by Paco Underhill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; &#8220;A fascinating look at how consumers perceive logos, ads, commercials, brands, and products.&#8221;&#8211;Time     </p>
<p>                    How much do we know about why we buy? What truly influences our decisions in today&#8217;s message-cluttered world? In Buyology, Martin Lindstrom presents the astonishing findings from his groundbreaking three-year, seven-million-dollar neuromarketing study&#8211;a cutting-edge experiment that peered inside the brains of 2,000 volunteers from all around the world as they encountered various ads, logos, commercials, brands, and products. His startling results shatter much of what we have long believed about what captures our interest&#8211;and drives us to buy. Among the questions he explores:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Does sex actually sell?<br />
                    &#8211; Does subliminal advertising still surround us?<br />
                    &#8211; Can &#8220;cool&#8221; brands trigger our mating instincts?<br />
                    &#8211; Can our other senses&#8211;smell, touch, and sound&#8211;be aroused when we see a product?     </p>
<p>                    Buyology is a fascinating and shocking journey into the mind of today&#8217;s consumer that will captivate anyone who&#8217;s been seduced&#8211;or turned off&#8211;by marketers&#8217; relentless attempts to win our loyalty, our money, and our minds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/">Buyology : Truth and Lies About Why We Buy &#8211; Martin Lindstrom, Foreword by Paco Underhill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Drunk Tank Pink : And Other Unexpected Forces That Shape How We Think, Feel, and Behave &#8211; Adam Alter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/drunk-tank-pink-and-other-unexpected-forces-that-shape-how-we-think-feel-and-behave-adam-alter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/drunk-tank-pink-and-other-unexpected-forces-that-shape-how-we-think-feel-and-behave-adam-alter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller! A revelatory look at how our environment unconsciously yet dramatically shapes the judgments and decisions we make every day Most of us go through life believing that we are in control of the choices we make-that we think and behave almost independently from the world around us. But as Drunk [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drunk-tank-pink-and-other-unexpected-forces-that-shape-how-we-think-feel-and-behave-adam-alter-abridged/">Drunk Tank Pink : And Other Unexpected Forces That Shape How We Think, Feel, and Behave &#8211; Adam Alter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller!     </p>
<p>                    A revelatory look at how our environment unconsciously yet dramatically shapes the judgments and decisions we make every day    </p>
<p>                    Most of us go through life believing that we are in control of the choices we make-that we think and behave almost independently from the world around us. But as Drunk Tank Pink illustrates, the truth is our environment shapes our thoughts and actions in myriad ways without our permission or even our knowledge. Armed with surprising data and endlessly fascinating examples, Adam Alter addresses the subtle but substantial ways in which outside forces influence us-such as color&#8217;s influence on mood, our bias in favor of names with which we identify, and how sunny days can induce optimism as well as aggression. Drunk Tank Pink proves that the truth behind our feelings and actions goes much deeper than the choices we take for granted every day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drunk-tank-pink-and-other-unexpected-forces-that-shape-how-we-think-feel-and-behave-adam-alter-abridged/">Drunk Tank Pink : And Other Unexpected Forces That Shape How We Think, Feel, and Behave &#8211; Adam Alter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable. We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable.    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the time of Columbus, Copernicus, Gutenberg and others, redrew all maps of the world, liberated information and shifted Western civilization from the medieval to the early modern era. Such change came at a price: social division, political extremism, economic shocks, pandemics and other unintended consequences of human endeavour.    </p>
<p>                    Now is our second Renaissance. In the face of terrorism, Brexit, refugee crises and the global impact of a Trump presidency, we can flourish-if we heed the urgent lessons of history. Age of Discovery, revised and updated for this paperback edition, shows us how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Non-Obvious 2018 Edition : How To Predict Trends And Win The Future &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Seller (2015 Edition) Gold Medal: Non-Fiction Book Awards (2018 Edition) Winner: IPPY Book Awards Silver Medal (2018 Edition) Winner: Axiom Business Theory Silver Medal (2017 Edition) Official Selection: Gary&#8217;s Book Club at CES (2017 Edition) #1 AMAZON OVERALL BUSINESS BEST SELLER (2015 Edition) What secrets can a 400-year-old Turkish cymbal maker [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Non-Obvious 2018 Edition : How To Predict Trends And Win The Future &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Seller (2015 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Gold Medal: Non-Fiction Book Awards (2018 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Winner: IPPY Book Awards Silver Medal (2018 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Winner: Axiom Business Theory Silver Medal (2017 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Official Selection: Gary&#8217;s Book Club at CES (2017 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    #1 AMAZON OVERALL BUSINESS BEST SELLER (2015 Edition)     </p>
<p>                    What secrets can a 400-year-old Turkish cymbal maker and an Icelandic hot tub etiquette video teach you about the power of storytelling?     </p>
<p>                    How do Michelin-ranked food stalls in Singapore and the decline of Swiss watches force all luxury brands to rethink their business models?     </p>
<p>                    What insights can the world&#8217;s quietest place and a clothing dye produced by former tobacco farmers reveal about serving enlightened consumers?    </p>
<p>                    The answers to these questions may not be all that obvious. And that&#8217;s exactly the point. For the past eight years, innovation expert Rohit Bhargava and his team have predicted 15 &#8220;Non-Obvious&#8221; trends each year. In this book, get a sneak peek at the proven methods exclusively taught to thousands of executives at leading brands, organizations and governments to develop unexpected solutions to critical problems. The power of non-obvious thinking can help you see what others miss, grow your business and make a bigger impact in the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this all-new eighth edition, discover what more than a million readers already have: how to use the power of non-obvious thinking to grow your business and make a bigger impact in the world.    </p>
<p>                    In total, the Non-Obvious 2018 Edition features 15 all-new trends across 5 categories including Culture &#038; Consumer Behavior, Marketing &#038; Social Media, Media &#038; Education, Technology &#038; Design plus Economics &#038; Entrepreneurship. The book also features a detailed section with a review and rating for more than 100 previously predicted trends &#8211; with longevity ratings for each.    </p>
<p>                    As with the original version, this new edition of Non-Obvious also delves into the curation process the author has used for years to build his Trend Reports and takes readers behind the scenes of trend curation (much to the delight of past readers who have been asking about this for years), and show them the methodology they can use to predict the future for themselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Non-Obvious 2018 Edition : How To Predict Trends And Win The Future &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good People : The Only Leadership Decision That Really Matters &#8211; Anthony Tjan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-people-the-only-leadership-decision-that-really-matters-anthony-tjan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-people-the-only-leadership-decision-that-really-matters-anthony-tjan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Good people are your organization&#8217;s most critical asset. But what does it really mean to be good? In this groundbreaking book, Anthony Tjan leads a movement to change the way we think about goodness, redefining it as a lifelong, proactive commitment that can be exercised, honed and taught. Packed with practical advice, Good People features [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-people-the-only-leadership-decision-that-really-matters-anthony-tjan-abridged/">Good People : The Only Leadership Decision That Really Matters &#8211; Anthony Tjan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Good people are your organization&#8217;s most critical asset. But what does it really mean to be good?    </p>
<p>                    In this groundbreaking book, Anthony Tjan leads a movement to change the way we think about goodness, redefining it as a lifelong, proactive commitment that can be exercised, honed and taught.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with practical advice, Good People features interviews with extraordinary innovators, executives, artists, academics, and role models from all walks of life, including Harvard Business School dean Nitin Nohria, Supreme Court justice Sonia Sotomayor and the late master jazz musician Clark Terry.    </p>
<p>                    Establishing a new language and framework you can use to evaluate, develop and lead with goodness, Anthony Tjan explains why choosing to work with good people is the only business decision that really matters.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An important book reminding us of the need for leadership to move beyond the individual to the culture of an organization&#8217; Dominic Barton, managing director of McKinsey &#038; Co</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-people-the-only-leadership-decision-that-really-matters-anthony-tjan-abridged/">Good People : The Only Leadership Decision That Really Matters &#8211; Anthony Tjan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?) The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect. Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?)    </p>
<p>                    The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect.    </p>
<p>                    Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover exactly what people want to buy, and how to give it to them &#8211; and in a way that makes people fall in love with you and your company.     </p>
<p>                    The proven, repeatable (yet slightly counterintuitive) Ask Method has quietly generated over $100 million in online sales across 23 different industries, and counting. In this tell-all book, Ryan Levesque reveals this exact method step-by-step, as well as the unusual story behind its discovery.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re an aspiring Internet entrepreneur, advanced online marketer, or established business owner, this book will both inspire you and show you how to skyrocket your online income-while creating a mass of raving fans in the process-simply by asking the right questions in a surprisingly different way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ryan has uncovered some enormous misunderstandings about human buying behavior and then utilized his neuroscience background to create this game-changing marketing and survey strategy. Before you finish the first third of the book, you&#8217;ll be eager to jump ahead and implement his process immediately &#8211; it&#8217;s that powerful!&#8217; &#8211; Annie Hyman Pratt, former CEO of The Coffee Bean and Tea Leaf and CEO of IMPAQ Entrepreneur Business Execution Systems    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ask may be the most important book written for anyone who sells products or services directly to consumers since Breakthrough Advertising was published in 1966. Like that masterpiece, Ask gives us a new paradigm for understanding human behavior at the deepest level, which gives rise to a more intelligent and profitable way to sell almost anything. Ryan Levsque will go down in history as the marketer who used his background to change the way products and services are sold online.&#8217; &#8211; Brian Kurtz, business builder of Boardroom Inc. and serial direct marketer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unconscious Branding : How Neuroscience Can Empower (and Inspire) Marketing &#8211; Douglas van Praet (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For too long marketers have been asking the wrong question. If consumers make decisions unconsciously, why do we persist in asking them directly through traditional marketing research why they do what they do? They simply can&#8217;t tell us because they don&#8217;t really know. Before marketers develop strategies, they need to recognize that consumers have strategies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/">Unconscious Branding : How Neuroscience Can Empower (and Inspire) Marketing &#8211; Douglas van Praet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For too long marketers have been asking the wrong question. If consumers make decisions unconsciously, why do we persist in asking them directly through traditional marketing research why they do what they do? They simply can&#8217;t tell us because they don&#8217;t really know. Before marketers develop strategies, they need to recognize that consumers have strategies too &#8230;human strategies, not consumer strategies. We need to go beyond asking why, and begin to ask how, behavior change occurs. Here, author Douglas Van Praet takes the most brilliant and revolutionary concepts from cognitive science and applies them to how we market, advertise, and consume in the modern digital age. Van Praet simplifies the most complex object in the known universe &#8211; the human brain &#8211; into seven codified actionable steps to behavior change. These steps are illustrated using real world examples from advertising, marketing, media, and business to consciously unravel what brilliant marketers and ad practitioners have long done intuitively, deconstructing the real story behind some of the greatest marketing and business successes in recent history, such as Nike&#8217;s &#8220;Just Do It&#8221; campaign; &#8220;Got Milk?&#8221;<br />
                    ; Wendy&#8217;s &#8220;Where&#8217;s the Beef?&#8221;; and the infamous Volkswagen &#8220;Punch Buggy&#8221; launch as well as their beloved &#8220;The Force&#8221; (Mini Darth Vader) Super Bowl commercial.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/">Unconscious Branding : How Neuroscience Can Empower (and Inspire) Marketing &#8211; Douglas van Praet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating investigation combining history, science and ideas, William Davies shows how well-being influences all aspects of our lives: business, finance, marketing and smart technology. This book will make you rethink everything from the way you work, the power of the &#8216;Nudge&#8217;, the ever-expanding definitions of depression, and the commercialization of your most private feelings. The Happiness Industry is a shocking and brilliantly argued warning about the new religion of the age: our emotions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The typical office worker now spends the majority of their waking hours staring at a screen. In the 21st century, every business is a digital business, which is why it&#8217;s so critical to understand how we think and behave online. Acclaimed behavioural economist Shlomo Benartzi has teamed up with science writer Jonah Lehrer to reveal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/">The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The typical office worker now spends the majority of their waking hours staring at a screen. In the 21st century, every business is a digital business, which is why it&#8217;s so critical to understand how we think and behave online.    </p>
<p>                    Acclaimed behavioural economist Shlomo Benartzi has teamed up with science writer Jonah Lehrer to reveal a toolkit of cues and nudges for the digital age. Using provocative case-studies and engaging reader exercises, Benartzi shows how businesses can update their nudges to help consumers make better decisions on screens. Up-to-the-minute research will help optimise your business&#8217;s online presence, from designing a webshop that helps your customers find what they are looking for, to laying out your website so that it both attracts and holds attention.    </p>
<p>                    This book will help you transform the challenges of the digital world into powerful new opportunities that will drive your success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/">The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Lose A Customer Again &#8211; Joey Coleman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Award-winning speaker and business consultant Joey Coleman teaches audiences and companies all over the world how to turn a one-time purchaser into a lifelong customer. Coleman&#8217;s theory of building customer loyalty isn&#8217;t about focusing on marketing or closing the sale: It&#8217;s about the First 100 Days(R) after the sale and the interactions the customer experiences. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/">Never Lose A Customer Again &#8211; Joey Coleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Award-winning speaker and business consultant Joey Coleman teaches audiences and companies all over the world how to turn a one-time purchaser into a lifelong customer.     </p>
<p>                    Coleman&#8217;s theory of building customer loyalty isn&#8217;t about focusing on marketing or closing the sale: It&#8217;s about the First 100 Days(R) after the sale and the interactions the customer experiences.     </p>
<p>                    While new customers experience joy, euphoria, and excitement, these feelings quickly shift to fear, doubt, and uncertainty as buyer&#8217;s remorse sets in. Across all industries, somewhere between 20%-70% of newly acquired customers will stop doing business with a company with the first 100 days of being a new customer because they feel neglected in the early stages of customer onboarding.     </p>
<p>                    In Never Lose a Customer Again, Coleman offers a philosophy and methodology for dramatically increasing customer retention and as a result, the bottom line. He identifies eight distinct emotional phases customers go through in the 100 days following a purchase. From an impulse buy at Starbucks to the thoughtful purchase of a first house, all customers have the potential to experience the eight phases of the customer journey. If you can understand and anticipate the customers&#8217; emotions, you can apply a myriad of tools and techniques &#8212; in-person, email, phone, mail, video, and presents &#8212; to cement a long and valuable relationship.     </p>
<p>                    Coleman&#8217;s system is presented through research and case studies showing how best-in-class companies create remarkable customer experiences at each step in the customer lifecycle.     </p>
<p>                     In the Acclimate stage, customers need you to hold their hand and over-explain how to use your product or service. They&#8217;re often too embarrassed to admit they&#8217;re confused. Take a cue from Canadian software company PolicyMedical and their challenge of getting non-technical users to undergo a complex installation and implementation process. They turned a series of project spreadsheets and installation manuals into a beautiful puzzle customers could assemble after completing each milestone.     </p>
<p>                     In the Adopt stage, customers should be welcomed to the highest tier of tribal membership with both public and private recognitions. For instance, Sephora&#8217;s VIB Rogue member welcome gift provides a metallic membership card (private recognition) and a members-only shade of lipstick (for public display).     </p>
<p>                     In the final stage, Advocate, loyal customers and raving fans are primed to provide powerful referrals. That&#8217;s how elite entrepreneurial event MastermindTalks continues to sell-out their conference year after year &#8211; with zero dollars spent on marketing. By surprising their loyal fans with amazing referral bonuses (an all-expenses paid safari?!) they guarantee their community will keep providing perfect referrals.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly two decades of consulting and keynoting, Coleman provides strategies and systems to increase customer loyalty. Applicable to companies in any industry and of any size (whether measured in employee count, revenue, or total number of customers), implementing his methods regularly leads to an increase in profits of 25-100%.     </p>
<p>                    Working with well-known clients like Hyatt Hotels, Zappos, and NASA, as well as mom-and-pop shops and solo entrepreneurs around the world, Coleman&#8217;s customer retention system has produced incredible results in dozens of industries.     </p>
<p>                    His approach to creating remarkable customer experiences requires minimal financial investment and will be fun for owners, employees, and teams to implement. This book is required reading for business owners, CEOs, and managers &#8211; as well as sales and marketing teams, account managers, and customer service representatives looking for easy to implement action steps that result in lasting change, increased profits, and lifelong customer retention.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/">Never Lose A Customer Again &#8211; Joey Coleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller that explains why certain products and ideas become popular. &#8220;Jonah Berger knows more about what makes information &#8216;go viral&#8217; than anyone in the world.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, author of the bestseller Stumbling on Happiness What makes things popular? If you said advertising, think again. People don&#8217;t listen to advertisements, they listen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/">Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller that explains why certain products and ideas become popular.      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jonah Berger knows more about what makes information &#8216;go viral&#8217; than anyone in the world.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, author of the bestseller Stumbling on Happiness     </p>
<p>                    What makes things popular? If you said advertising, think again. People don&#8217;t listen to advertisements, they listen to their peers. But why do people talk about certain products and ideas more than others? Why are some stories and rumors more infectious? And what makes online content go viral?     </p>
<p>                    Wharton marketing professor Jonah Berger has spent the last decade answering these questions. He&#8217;s studied why New York Times articles make the paper&#8217;s own Most E-mailed list, why products get word of mouth, and how social influence shapes everything from the cars we buy to the clothes we wear to the names we give our children.     </p>
<p>                    In Contagious, Berger reveals the secret science behind word-of-mouth and social transmission. Discover how six basic principles drive all sorts of things to become contagious, from consumer products and policy initiatives to workplace rumors and YouTube videos. Learn how a luxury steakhouse found popularity through the lowly cheesesteak, why anti-drug commercials might have actually increased drug use, and why more than 200 million consumers shared a video about one of the most boring products there is: a blender.     </p>
<p>                    Contagious provides specific, actionable techniques for helping information spread&#8211;for designing messages, advertisements, and content that people will share. Whether you&#8217;re a manager at a big company, a small business owner trying to boost awareness, a politician running for office, or a health official trying to get the word out, Contagious will show you how to make your product or idea catch on.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/">Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who Can You Trust? : How Technology Brought Us Together &#8211; and Why It Could Drive Us Apart &#8211; Rachel Botsman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-can-you-trust-how-technology-brought-us-together-and-why-it-could-drive-us-apart-rachel-botsman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-can-you-trust-how-technology-brought-us-together-and-why-it-could-drive-us-apart-rachel-botsman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TRUST IS FUNDAMENTAL TO EVERY ACTION, EVERY RELATIONSHIP, EVERY TRANSACTION AND IT MATTERS NOW MORE THAN EVER BEFORE&#8230; In this ground-breaking book world-renowned trust expert Rachel Botsman reveals that we are at the tipping point of one of the biggest social transformations in human history. We might have lost faith in institutions and leaders, but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-can-you-trust-how-technology-brought-us-together-and-why-it-could-drive-us-apart-rachel-botsman-abridged/">Who Can You Trust? : How Technology Brought Us Together &#8211; and Why It Could Drive Us Apart &#8211; Rachel Botsman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TRUST IS FUNDAMENTAL TO EVERY ACTION, EVERY RELATIONSHIP, EVERY TRANSACTION    </p>
<p>                    AND IT MATTERS NOW MORE THAN EVER BEFORE&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    In this ground-breaking book world-renowned trust expert Rachel Botsman reveals that we are at the tipping point of one of the biggest social transformations in human history. We might have lost faith in institutions and leaders, but millions of people travel in cars with total strangers, exchange digital currencies, or find themselves trusting a bot.     </p>
<p>                    We still trust: but not the way we used to.    </p>
<p>                    If we are to benefit from this radical shift, we must understand how trust is built, managed, lost and repaired in the digital age. In the first book to explain this new world, Botsman provides a definitive guide of this uncharted landscape &#8211; and explores what&#8217;s next for humanity.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brilliantly describes how the established trust framework is undergoing a radical transformation as digital technologies take root in every facet of our lives&#8217; Marc Benioff, Chairman &#038; CEO, Salesforce    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating and well researched&#8230;every reader will gain new insights&#8217; Geoff Mulgan, Chief Executive, Nesta    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A rare book that will cause you to think deeply about your business, your relationships and your life&#8217; Don Tapscott, bestselling author of Wikinomics and Blockchain Revolution</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-can-you-trust-how-technology-brought-us-together-and-why-it-could-drive-us-apart-rachel-botsman-abridged/">Who Can You Trust? : How Technology Brought Us Together &#8211; and Why It Could Drive Us Apart &#8211; Rachel Botsman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
