<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Management Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/management-accounting-bookkeeping/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/management-accounting-bookkeeping/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Management Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/management-accounting-bookkeeping/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Quit Like a Millionaire : No Gimmicks, Luck, or Trust Fund Required &#8211; Kristy Shen, Bryce Leung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From two leaders of the FIRE (Financial Independence, Retire Early) movement, a bold, contrarian guide to retiring at any age, with a reproducible formula to financial independence A bull***t-free guide to growing your wealth, retiring early, and living life on your own terms Kristy Shen retired with a million dollars at the age of thirty-one, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/">Quit Like a Millionaire : No Gimmicks, Luck, or Trust Fund Required &#8211; Kristy Shen, Bryce Leung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From two leaders of the FIRE (Financial Independence, Retire Early) movement, a bold, contrarian guide to retiring at any age, with a reproducible formula to financial independence     </p>
<p>                    A bull***t-free guide to growing your wealth, retiring early, and living life on your own terms     </p>
<p>                    Kristy Shen retired with a million dollars at the age of thirty-one, and she did it without hitting a home run on the stock market, starting the next Snapchat in her garage, or investing in hot real estate. Learn how to cut down on spending without decreasing your quality of life, build a million-dollar portfolio, fortify your investments to survive bear markets and black-swan events, and use the 4 percent rule and the Yield Shield&#8211;so you can quit the rat race forever. Not everyone can become an entrepreneur or a real estate baron; the rest of us need Shen&#8217;s mathematically proven approach to retire decades before sixty-five.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/">Quit Like a Millionaire : No Gimmicks, Luck, or Trust Fund Required &#8211; Kristy Shen, Bryce Leung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD. This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career. An MBA at a top business school is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold     </p>
<p>                    ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD.    </p>
<p>                    This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career.    </p>
<p>                    An MBA at a top business school is an enormous investment in time and cash. And if you don&#8217;t want to work for a consulting firm or an investment bank, the chances are it simply isn&#8217;t worth it.    </p>
<p>                    The Personal MBA gives you simple mental models for every subject that&#8217;s key to commercial success. From the basics of products and marketing to the nuances of teamwork and systems, this book distils everything you need to know to take on the MBA graduates and win.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;File this book under: NO EXCUSES&#8217; Seth Godin    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;No matter what they tell you, an MBA is not essential. If you combine reading this book with actually trying stuff, you&#8217;ll be far ahead in the business game&#8217; Kevin Kelly, founder of Wired</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Automatic Millionaire, Expanded and Updated : A Powerful One-Step Plan to Live and Finish Rich &#8211; David Bach (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-automatic-millionaire-expanded-and-updated-a-powerful-one-step-plan-to-live-and-finish-rich-david-bach-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-automatic-millionaire-expanded-and-updated-a-powerful-one-step-plan-to-live-and-finish-rich-david-bach-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD&#8211;#1 NEW YORK TIMES, WALL STREET JOURNAL, USA TODAY, BUSINESSWEEK BESTSELLER What&#8217;s the secret to becoming a millionaire? For years people have asked David Bach, the national bestselling author of Smart Women Finish Rich, Smart Couples Finish Rich, and Start Late, Finish Rich what&#8217;s the real secret to getting rich? What&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-automatic-millionaire-expanded-and-updated-a-powerful-one-step-plan-to-live-and-finish-rich-david-bach-abridged/">The Automatic Millionaire, Expanded and Updated : A Powerful One-Step Plan to Live and Finish Rich &#8211; David Bach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD&#8211;#1 NEW YORK TIMES, WALL STREET JOURNAL, USA TODAY, BUSINESSWEEK BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    What&#8217;s the secret to becoming a millionaire?     </p>
<p>                     For years people have asked David Bach, the national bestselling author of Smart Women Finish Rich, Smart Couples Finish Rich,  and Start Late, Finish Rich what&#8217;s the real secret to getting rich? What&#8217;s the one thing I need to do?     </p>
<p>                     Now, in the newly revised The Automatic Millionaire, expanded and updated, David Bach is sharing that secret.     </p>
<p>                     The Automatic Millionaire starts with the powerful story of an average American couple&#8211;he&#8217;s a low-level manager, she&#8217;s a beautician&#8211;whose joint income never exceeds $55,000 a year, yet who somehow manage to own two homes debt-free, put two kids through college, and retire at 55 with more than $1 million in savings. Through their story you&#8217;ll learn the surprising fact that you cannot get rich with a budget! You have to have a plan to pay yourself first that is totally automatic, a plan that will automatically secure your future and pay for your present.     </p>
<p>                     What makes The Automatic Millionaire unique:      </p>
<p>                     &#8211; You don&#8217;t need a budget<br />
                     &#8211; You don&#8217;t need willpower<br />
                     &#8211; You don&#8217;t need to make a lot of money<br />
                     &#8211; You don&#8217;t need to be that interested in money<br />
                     &#8211; You can set up the plan in an hour     </p>
<p>                     David gives you a totally realistic system, based on timeless principles, with everything you need to know, including phone numbers, websites and apps, so you can put the secret to becoming an Automatic Millionaire in place from the comfort of your own home.     </p>
<p>                     This powerful little book has the potential to secure your financial future. Do it once&#8211;the rest is automatic!     </p>
<p>                     The Automatic Millionaire is one of the most popular financial books of our time. It was a runaway hit when it was first published in 2004, spending thirty-one weeks on the New York Times bestseller list and appearing at at number one simultaneously on the New York Times, USA Today, BusinessWeek,  and Wall Street Journal business bestseller lists. It has sold over 1.5 million copies and been translated around the world in over a dozen languages. This is the first update since 2005 and includes updated information on taxes, investments, technologies and apps to automate your financial life as well as David&#8217;s latest systems for making the entire process even easier.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-automatic-millionaire-expanded-and-updated-a-powerful-one-step-plan-to-live-and-finish-rich-david-bach-abridged/">The Automatic Millionaire, Expanded and Updated : A Powerful One-Step Plan to Live and Finish Rich &#8211; David Bach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Languages of Leadership &#8211; Wendy Born (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-languages-of-leadership-wendy-born-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-languages-of-leadership-wendy-born-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many of us have issues trying to lead disparate teams with multiple personalities, colleagues with conflicting agendas and bosses with minds of their own. The questions we often ask ourselves are: How do I manage my team leaders?; How do I manage my peers? How do I manage my own leader to stop making big [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-languages-of-leadership-wendy-born-abridged/">The Languages of Leadership &#8211; Wendy Born (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many of us have issues trying to lead disparate teams with multiple personalities, colleagues with conflicting agendas and bosses with minds of their own. The questions we often ask ourselves are: How do I manage my team leaders?; How do I manage my peers? How do I manage my own leader to stop making big promises to my team that I know they won&#8217;t deliver on? The answer is to learn to master the languages of leadership. In this fascinating book, Wendy Born will show you how and teach you to make small changes that will have a big impact.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-languages-of-leadership-wendy-born-abridged/">The Languages of Leadership &#8211; Wendy Born (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Think and Grow Rich : The Landmark Bestseller Now Revised and Updated for the 21st Century &#8211; Napoleon Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/think-and-grow-rich-the-landmark-bestseller-now-revised-and-updated-for-the-21st-century-napoleon-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/think-and-grow-rich-the-landmark-bestseller-now-revised-and-updated-for-the-21st-century-napoleon-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Think and Grow Rich has been called the Granddaddy of All Motivational Literature. It was the first book to boldly ask, What makes a winner? The man who asked and listened for the answer, Napoleon Hill, is now counted in the top ranks of the world&#8217;s winners himself. The most famous of all teachers of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/think-and-grow-rich-the-landmark-bestseller-now-revised-and-updated-for-the-21st-century-napoleon-hill-abridged/">Think and Grow Rich : The Landmark Bestseller Now Revised and Updated for the 21st Century &#8211; Napoleon Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Think and Grow Rich has been called the Granddaddy of All Motivational Literature. It was the first book to boldly ask, What makes a winner? The man who asked and listened for the answer, Napoleon Hill, is now counted in the top ranks of the world&#8217;s winners himself.    </p>
<p>                    The most famous of all teachers of success spent a fortune and the better part of a lifetime of effort to produce the Law of Success philosophy that forms the basis of his books and that is so powerfully summarized in this one.    </p>
<p>                    In the original Think and Grow Rich, published in 1937, Hill draws on stories of Andrew Carnegie, Thomas Edison, Henry Ford, and other millionaires of his generation to illustrate his principles. In the updated version, Arthur R. Pell, Ph.D., a nationally known author, lecturer, and consultant in human resources management and an expert in applying Hill&#8217;s thought, deftly interweaves anecdotes of how contemporary millionaires and billionaires, such as Bill Gates, Mary Kay Ash, Dave Thomas, and Sir John Templeton, achieved their wealth. Outmoded or arcane terminology and examples are faithfully refreshed to preclude any stumbling blocks to a new generation of readers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/think-and-grow-rich-the-landmark-bestseller-now-revised-and-updated-for-the-21st-century-napoleon-hill-abridged/">Think and Grow Rich : The Landmark Bestseller Now Revised and Updated for the 21st Century &#8211; Napoleon Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
