<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Labour Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/labour-economics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/labour-economics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Labour Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/labour-economics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why We Work &#8211; Barry Schwartz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Part of the TED series: Why We Work Why do we work? The question seems so simple. But Professor Barry Schwartz proves that the answer is surprising, complex and urgent. We&#8217;ve long been taught that the reason we work is primarily for a paycheck. In fact, we&#8217;ve shaped much of the infrastructure of our society [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/">Why We Work &#8211; Barry Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Part of the TED series: Why We Work    </p>
<p>                    Why do we work? The question seems so simple. But Professor Barry Schwartz proves that the answer is surprising, complex and urgent.     </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve long been taught that the reason we work is primarily for a paycheck. In fact, we&#8217;ve shaped much of the infrastructure of our society to accommodate this belief. Then why are so many people dissatisfied with their work, despite healthy compensation? And why do so many people find immense fulfillment and satisfaction through &#8220;menial&#8221; jobs?     </p>
<p>                    Schwartz reveals exactly how the false idea that the goal for work should be pay came to be, how we came to believe that paying workers more leads to better work, and why this has made our society confused, unhappy and has established a dangerously misguided system.     </p>
<p>                    Ultimately, Schwartz proves that the root of what drives us to good work can rarely be incentivized, and that the cause of bad work is often an attempt to do just that. With great insight and wisdom, Schwartz illuminates the path for readers to take their first steps toward understanding, empowering us all to find great work.     </p>
<p>                    Schwartz is also the author of The Paradox of Choice: Why More Is Less, which has been translated into twenty languages. He can be seen discussing his ideas in his TEDTalks The Paradox of Choiceand Using Our Practical Wisdom.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-work-barry-schwartz-abridged/">Why We Work &#8211; Barry Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Power Up : A Woman&#8217;s Field Guide to Success in the New Economy &#8211; Magdalena Yesil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/power-up-a-womans-field-guide-to-success-in-the-new-economy-magdalena-yesil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/power-up-a-womans-field-guide-to-success-in-the-new-economy-magdalena-yesil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pioneering Silicon Valley entrepreneur and investor Magdalena Yesil came to the United States in 1976 with two suitcases and $43, blind to the challenges she would face as a woman and immigrant in Silicon Valley. Today, she is best known as the first investor and a founding board member of Salesforce, the now-multibillion dollar company [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-up-a-womans-field-guide-to-success-in-the-new-economy-magdalena-yesil-abridged/">Power Up : A Woman&#8217;s Field Guide to Success in the New Economy &#8211; Magdalena Yesil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pioneering Silicon Valley entrepreneur and investor Magdalena Yesil came to the United States in 1976 with two suitcases and $43, blind to the challenges she would face as a woman and immigrant in Silicon Valley. Today, she is best known as the first investor and a founding board member of Salesforce, the now-multibillion dollar company that ushered in the era of cloud-based computing.     </p>
<p>                    In Power Up: A Woman&#8217;s Field Guide to Success in the New Economy, Yesil urges women to look beyond the alarming gender statistics of the workplace and feel confident entering tech or any field-but also prepared to deal with the challenges. She shares what she experienced as a woman in Silicon Valley with surprising candor and heart, relying not just on her insight but that of more than a dozen top women entrepreneurs to offer pragmatic takeaways on topics such as:    </p>
<p>                    * Owning career choices while managing risk<br />
                    * Getting credit for your work<br />
                    * Managing sexual dynamics<br />
                    * Recruiting allies in the movement toward a supportive workplace for everyone    </p>
<p>                    Pragmatic, incisive, and full of highly actionable advice, Yesil prepares ambitious women to break glass ceilings and rise to the top in the New Silicon Valley-and beyond.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-up-a-womans-field-guide-to-success-in-the-new-economy-magdalena-yesil-abridged/">Power Up : A Woman&#8217;s Field Guide to Success in the New Economy &#8211; Magdalena Yesil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unfair Advantage : BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD-WINNER: How You Already Have What It Takes to Succeed &#8211; Ash Ali, Hasan Kubba (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unfair-advantage-business-book-of-the-year-award-winner-how-you-already-have-what-it-takes-to-succeed-ash-ali-hasan-kubba-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unfair-advantage-business-book-of-the-year-award-winner-how-you-already-have-what-it-takes-to-succeed-ash-ali-hasan-kubba-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2021 AND BEST START UP/SCALE UP BOOK AWARD 2021 This ground-breaking book exposes the myths behind startup success, illuminates the real forces at work and shows how they can be harnessed in your favour. The world isn&#8217;t a level playing field. Meritocracy is a myth. And if [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unfair-advantage-business-book-of-the-year-award-winner-how-you-already-have-what-it-takes-to-succeed-ash-ali-hasan-kubba-abridged/">The Unfair Advantage : BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD-WINNER: How You Already Have What It Takes to Succeed &#8211; Ash Ali, Hasan Kubba (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2021 AND BEST START UP/SCALE UP BOOK AWARD 2021    </p>
<p>                    This ground-breaking book exposes the myths behind startup success, illuminates the real forces at work and shows how they can be harnessed in your favour.    </p>
<p>                    The world isn&#8217;t a level playing field. Meritocracy is a myth. And if you look at those at the top, you realise that behind every success story is an Unfair Advantage. But that doesn&#8217;t just mean your parents&#8217; wealth or who you know. An Unfair Advantage is any element that gives you an edge over your competition. And we all have one.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on over two decades of hands-on experience, including as the first Marketing Director of Just Eat (a startup now worth over GBP5 billion), the authors show how to identify your own unfair advantages and apply them to any project. Hard work and grit aren&#8217;t enough, so they explore the importance of money, intelligence, insight, location, education, expertise, status and luck in the journey to success. From Snapchat to Spanx, Oprah to Elon Musk, unfair advantages have shaped the journeys of some of the most successful brands in the world. This book helps you too find the external circumstances and internal strengths to succeed in the world of business and beyond.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unfair-advantage-business-book-of-the-year-award-winner-how-you-already-have-what-it-takes-to-succeed-ash-ali-hasan-kubba-abridged/">The Unfair Advantage : BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD-WINNER: How You Already Have What It Takes to Succeed &#8211; Ash Ali, Hasan Kubba (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover the secrets of one of the world&#8217;s leading talent acquisition experts In the newly revised Fourth Edition of Hire With Your Head: Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Great Teams, influential recruiting and hiring expert Lou Adler delivers a practical guide to consistently identifying and hiring the best people and scaling that process throughout your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/">Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover the secrets of one of the world&#8217;s leading talent acquisition experts    </p>
<p>                     In the newly revised Fourth Edition of Hire With Your Head: Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Great Teams, influential recruiting and hiring expert Lou Adler delivers a practical guide to consistently identifying and hiring the best people and scaling that process throughout your company.    </p>
<p>                     This book will help you address your hiring and recruitment issues, not just by making you more efficient, but also by reforming your entire process to align with how top talent actually look for new jobs, compare offers, and select opportunities.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll discover:    </p>
<p>                    Discover what it takes to ensure more Win-Win Hiring outcomes by hiring for the anniversary date rather than the start date<br />
                    How to use a &#8220;High Tech, High Touch&#8221; approach to raise the talent bar<br />
                    Expand the talent pool to include more outstanding, high potential and diverse talent by defining work as a series of key performance objectives    </p>
<p>                     Perfect for hiring managers, recruiters, and HR and business leaders, Hire with Your Head is a must-read resource for anyone seeking to improve their ability to find, attract, and retain the top talent the world has to offer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/">Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE BUSINESS BOOK AWARDS 2021 In The 4 Day Week, entrepreneur and business innovator Andrew Barnes makes the case for the four-day work week as the answer to many of the ills of the 21st-century global economy. Barnes conducted an experiment in his own business, the New Zealand trust company Perpetual Guardian, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/">The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE BUSINESS BOOK AWARDS 2021    </p>
<p>                    In The 4 Day Week, entrepreneur and business innovator Andrew Barnes makes the case for the four-day work week as the answer to many of the ills of the 21st-century global economy.     </p>
<p>                     Barnes conducted an experiment in his own business, the New Zealand trust company Perpetual Guardian, and asked his staff to design a four-day week that would permit them to meet their existing productivity requirements on the same salary but with a 20% cut in work hours. The outcomes of this trial, which no business leader had previously attempted on these terms, were stunning. People were happier and healthier, more engaged in their personal lives, and more focused and productive in the office.    </p>
<p>                     The world of work has seen a dramatic shift in recent times: the former security and benefits associated with permanent employment are being displaced by the less stable gig economy. Barnes explains the dangers of a focus on flexibility at the expense of hard-won worker protections, and argues that with the four-day week, we can have the best of all worlds: optimal productivity, work-life balance, worker benefits and, at long last, a solution to pervasive economic inequities such as the gender pay gap and lack of diversity in business and governance.     </p>
<p>                     The 4 Day Week is a practical, how-to guide for business leaders and employees alike that is applicable to nearly every industry. Using qualitative and quantitative data from research gathered through the Perpetual Guardian trial and other sources by the University of Auckland and Auckland University of Technology, the book presents a step-by-step approach to preparing businesses for productivity-focused flexibility, from the necessary cultural conditions to the often complex legislative considerations.    </p>
<p>                     The story of Perpetual Guardian&#8217;s unprecedented work experiment has made headlines around the world and stormed social media, reaching a global audience in more than seventy countries. A mix of trenchant analysis, personal observation and actionable advice, The 4 Day Week is an essential guide for leaders and workers seeking to make a change for the better in their work world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/">The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Education, Continuous Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Services & Welfare, Criminology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants. As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants.    </p>
<p>                    As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise the question-how will they transform society, the economy, and politics? If companies need fewer workers due to automation and robotics, what happens to those who once held those jobs and don&#8217;t have the skills for new jobs? And since many social benefits are delivered through jobs, how are people outside the workforce for a lengthy period of time going to earn a living and get health care and social benefits?    </p>
<p>                    Looking past today&#8217;s headlines, political scientist and cultural observer Darrell M. West argues that society needs to rethink the concept of jobs, reconfigure the social contract, move toward a system of lifetime learning, and develop a new kind of politics that can deal with economic dislocations. With the U.S. governance system in shambles because of political polarization and hyper-partisanship, dealing creatively with the transition to a fully digital economy will vex political leaders and complicate the adoption of remedies that could ease the transition pain. It is imperative that we make major adjustments in how we think about work and the social contract in order to prevent society from spiraling out of control.    </p>
<p>                    This book presents a number of proposals to help people deal with the transition from an industrial to a digital economy. We must broaden the  concept of employment to include volunteering and parenting and pay greater attention to the opportunities for leisure time. New forms of identity will be possible when the &#8220;job&#8221; no longer defines people&#8217;s sense of personal meaning, and they engage in a broader range of activities. Workers will need help throughout their lifetimes to acquire new skills and develop new job capabilities. Political reforms will be necessary to  reduce polarization and restore civility so there can be open and healthy debate about where responsibility lies for economic well-being.    </p>
<p>                    This book is an important contribution to a discussion about tomorrow-one that needs to take place today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cubed : The Secret History of the Workplace &#8211; Nikil Saval (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Buildings: Civic, Commercial, Industrial, Etc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book &#8211; Daily Beast Best Nonfiction of 2014 &#8211; Inc. Magazine&#8217;s Most Thought-Provoking Books of the Year &#8220;Man is born free, but he is everywhere in cubicles.&#8221; How did we get from Scrooge&#8217;s office to &#8220;Office Space&#8221;? From bookkeepers in dark countinghouses to freelancers in bright cafes? What would the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/">Cubed : The Secret History of the Workplace &#8211; Nikil Saval (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book &#8211; Daily Beast Best Nonfiction of 2014 &#8211; Inc. Magazine&#8217;s Most Thought-Provoking Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Man is born free, but he is everywhere in cubicles.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    How did we get from Scrooge&#8217;s office to &#8220;Office Space&#8221;? From bookkeepers in dark countinghouses to freelancers in bright cafes? What would the world be like without the vertical file cabinet? What would the world be like without the office at all? In Cubed, Nikil Saval chronicles the evolution of the office in a fascinating, often funny, and sometimes disturbing anatomy of the white-collar world and how it came to be the way it is. Drawing on the history of architecture and business, as well as a host of pop culture artifacts&#8211;from Mad Men to Dilbert (and, yes, The Office)&#8211;and ranging in time from the earliest clerical houses to the surprisingly utopian origins of the cubicle to the funhouse campuses of Silicon Valley, Cubed is an all-encompassing investigation into the way we work, why we do it the way we do (and often don&#8217;t like it), and how we might do better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/">Cubed : The Secret History of the Workplace &#8211; Nikil Saval (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder and CEO, Whole Foods Market).     </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Age, Byron Reese makes the case that technology has reshaped humanity just three times in history: 100,000 years ago, we harnessed fire, which led to language; 10,000 years ago, we developed agriculture, which led to cities and warfare; 5,000 years ago, we invented the wheel and writing, which lead to the nation state.    </p>
<p>                    We are now on the doorstep of a fourth change brought about by two technologies: AI and robotics. &#8220;Timely, highly informative, and certainly optimistic&#8221; (Booklist), The Fourth Age provides an essential background on how we got to this point, and how-rather than what-we should think about the topics we&#8217;ll soon all be facing: machine consciousness, automation, changes in employment, creative computers, radical life extension, artificial life, AI ethics, the future of warfare, superintelligence, and the implications of extreme prosperity.    </p>
<p>                    By asking questions like &#8220;Are you a machine?&#8221; and &#8220;Could a computer feel anything?&#8221;, Reese leads you through a discussion along the cutting edge in robotics and AI, and provides a framework by which we can all understand, discuss, and act on the issues of the Fourth Age and how they&#8217;ll transform humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The shift toward automation is about to create a tsunami of unemployment. Not in the distant future&#8211;now. One recent estimate predicts 13 million American workers will lose their jobs within the next seven years-jobs that won&#8217;t be replaced. In a future marked by restlessness and chronic unemployment, what will happen to American society? In The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/">The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The shift toward automation is about to create a tsunami of unemployment. Not in the distant future&#8211;now. One recent estimate predicts 13 million American workers will lose their jobs within the next seven years-jobs that won&#8217;t be replaced. In a future marked by restlessness and chronic unemployment, what will happen to American society?    </p>
<p>                    In The War on Normal People, Andrew Yang paints a dire portrait of the American economy. Rapidly advancing technologies like artificial intelligence, robotics and automation software are making millions of Americans&#8217; livelihoods irrelevant. The consequences are these trends are already being felt across our communities in the form of political unrest, drug use, and other social ills. The future looks dire-but is it unavoidable?    </p>
<p>                    In The War on Normal People, Yang imagines a different future &#8212; one in which having a job is distinct from the capacity to prosper and seek fulfillment. At this vision&#8217;s core is Universal Basic Income, the concept of providing all citizens with a guaranteed income-and one that is rapidly gaining popularity among forward-thinking politicians and economists. Yang proposes that UBI is an essential step toward a new, more durable kind of economy, one he calls &#8220;human capitalism.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/">The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job? That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves. The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job?     </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves.     </p>
<p>                    The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even many full-time and professional jobs are experiencing this precarious shift. Within a decade, a near-majority of the 145 million employed Americans will be impacted. Add to that the steamroller of automation, robots and artificial intelligence already replacing millions of workers and projected to obsolesce millions more, and the jobs picture starts looking grim.     </p>
<p>                    Now a weird yet historic mash-up of Silicon Valley technology and Wall Street greed is thrusting upon us the latest economic fraud: the so-called sharing economy, with companies like Uber, Airbnb and TaskRabbit allegedly liberating workers to become independent and their own CEOs, hiring themselves out for ever-smaller jobs and wages while the companies profit.     </p>
<p>                    But this share the crumbs economy is just the tip of a looming iceberg that the middle class is drifting toward. Raw Deal: How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers, by veteran journalist Steven Hill, is an exposé that challenges conventional thinking, and the hype celebrating this new economy, by showing why the vision of the techno sapien leaders and their Ayn Rand libertarianism is a dead end.     </p>
<p>                    In Raw Deal, Steven Hill proposes pragmatic policy solutions to transform the US economy and its safety net and social contract, launching a new kind of deal to restore power back into the hands of American workers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Robots Are Coming! : The Future of Jobs in the Age of Automation &#8211; Andres Oppenheimer, Translated by Ezra E. Fitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-robots-are-coming-the-future-of-jobs-in-the-age-of-automation-andres-oppenheimer-translated-by-ezra-e-fitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations & Safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-robots-are-coming-the-future-of-jobs-in-the-age-of-automation-andres-oppenheimer-translated-by-ezra-e-fitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Staying true to his trademark journalistic approach, Andrés Oppenheimer takes his readers on yet another journey, this time across the globe, in a thought-provoking search to understand what the future holds for today&#8217;s jobs in the foreseeable age of automation. The Robots Are Coming! centers around the issue of jobs and their future in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-robots-are-coming-the-future-of-jobs-in-the-age-of-automation-andres-oppenheimer-translated-by-ezra-e-fitz-abridged/">The Robots Are Coming! : The Future of Jobs in the Age of Automation &#8211; Andres Oppenheimer, Translated by Ezra E. Fitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Staying true to his trademark journalistic approach, Andrés Oppenheimer takes his readers on yet another journey, this time across the globe, in a thought-provoking search to understand what the future holds for today&#8217;s jobs in the foreseeable age of automation.     </p>
<p>                    The Robots Are Coming! centers around the issue of jobs and their future in the context of rapid automation and the growth of online products and services. As two of Oppenheimer&#8217;s interviewees &#8212; both experts in technology and economics from Oxford University &#8212; indicate, forty-seven percent of existing jobs are at risk of becoming automated or rendered obsolete by other technological changes in the next twenty years. Oppenheimer examines current changes in several fields, including the food business, legal work, banking, and medicine, speaking with experts in the field, and citing articles and literature on automation in various areas of the workforce. He contrasts the perspectives of techno-optimists with those of techno-negativists and generally attempts to find a middle ground between an alarmist vision of the future, and one that is too uncritical. A self-described cautious optimist, Oppenheimer believes that technology will not create massive unemployment, but rather will drastically change what work looks like.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-robots-are-coming-the-future-of-jobs-in-the-age-of-automation-andres-oppenheimer-translated-by-ezra-e-fitz-abridged/">The Robots Are Coming! : The Future of Jobs in the Age of Automation &#8211; Andres Oppenheimer, Translated by Ezra E. Fitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a rational explanation of the ways in which the AI revolution will affect us all. Tackling the implications of Artificial Intelligence on growth, productivity, inflation and the distribution of wealth and power, THE AI ECONOMY also examines coming changes to the the way we educate, work and spend our leisure time.    </p>
<p>                    A fundamentally optimistic view which will help you plan for changing times, this book explains AI and leads you towards a more certain future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nickel and Dimed : Undercover in Low-Wage America &#8211; Barbara Ehrenreich, Introduction by Polly Toynbee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nickel-and-dimed-undercover-in-low-wage-america-barbara-ehrenreich-introduction-by-polly-toynbee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nickel-and-dimed-undercover-in-low-wage-america-barbara-ehrenreich-introduction-by-polly-toynbee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Millions of Americans work full time, year round, for poverty-level wages. In 1998, Barbara Ehrenreich decided to join them. Leaving her home, she took the cheapest lodgings she could find, and accepted whatever jobs she was offered. Nickel and Dimed reveals low-rent America in all its tenacity, anxiety, and surprising generosity? exposing the darker side [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nickel-and-dimed-undercover-in-low-wage-america-barbara-ehrenreich-introduction-by-polly-toynbee-abridged/">Nickel and Dimed : Undercover in Low-Wage America &#8211; Barbara Ehrenreich, Introduction by Polly Toynbee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Millions of Americans work full time, year round, for poverty-level wages. In 1998, Barbara Ehrenreich decided to join them. Leaving her home, she took the cheapest lodgings she could find, and accepted whatever jobs she was offered. Nickel and Dimed reveals low-rent America in all its tenacity, anxiety, and surprising generosity? exposing the darker side of American prosperity and the true cost of the American dream.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nickel-and-dimed-undercover-in-low-wage-america-barbara-ehrenreich-introduction-by-polly-toynbee-abridged/">Nickel and Dimed : Undercover in Low-Wage America &#8211; Barbara Ehrenreich, Introduction by Polly Toynbee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
