<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Biblical Studies &amp; Exegesis Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/biblical-studies-exegesis/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/biblical-studies-exegesis/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Biblical Studies &amp; Exegesis Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/biblical-studies-exegesis/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve &#8211; Stephen Greenblatt</title>
		<link>/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bolder, even, than the ambitious books for which Stephen Greenblatt is already renowned, The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve explores the enduring story of humanity&#8217;s first parents. Comprising only a few ancient verses, the story of Adam and Eve has served as a mirror in which we seem to glimpse the whole, long [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/">The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve &#8211; Stephen Greenblatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bolder, even, than the ambitious books for which Stephen Greenblatt is already renowned, The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve explores the enduring story of humanity&#8217;s first parents. Comprising only a few ancient verses, the story of Adam and Eve has served as a mirror in which we seem to glimpse the whole, long history of our fears and desires, as both a hymn to human responsibility and a dark fable about human wretchedness.    </p>
<p>                     Tracking the tale into the deep past, Greenblatt uncovers the tremendous theological, artistic, and cultural investment over centuries that made these fictional figures so profoundly resonant in the Jewish, Christian, and Muslim worlds and, finally, so very &#8220;real&#8221; to millions of people even in the present. With the uncanny brilliance he previously brought to his depictions of William Shakespeare and Poggio Bracciolini (the humanist monk who is the protagonist of The Swerve), Greenblatt explores the intensely personal engagement of Augustine, Durer, and Milton in this mammoth project of collective creation, while he also limns the diversity of the story&#8217;s offspring: rich allegory, vicious misogyny, deep moral insight, and some of the greatest triumphs of art and literature.    </p>
<p>                     The biblical origin story, Greenblatt argues, is a model for what the humanities still have to offer: not the scientific nature of things, but rather a deep encounter with problems that have gripped our species for as long as we can recall and that continue to fascinate and trouble us today.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/">The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve &#8211; Stephen Greenblatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sign and the Seal : The Quest for the Lost Ark of the Covenant &#8211; Graham Hancock</title>
		<link>/the-sign-and-the-seal-the-quest-for-the-lost-ark-of-the-covenant-graham-hancock/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sign-and-the-seal-the-quest-for-the-lost-ark-of-the-covenant-graham-hancock/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fact of the Lost Ark of the Covenant is one of the grant historical mysteries of all time. To believers, the Ark is the legendary vesel holding the stone tablets of the Ten Commandments. The Bible contains hundreds of references to the Ark&#8217;s power to level mountains, destroy armies, and lay waste to cities. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sign-and-the-seal-the-quest-for-the-lost-ark-of-the-covenant-graham-hancock/">The Sign and the Seal : The Quest for the Lost Ark of the Covenant &#8211; Graham Hancock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fact of the Lost Ark of the Covenant is one of the grant historical mysteries of all time. To believers, the Ark is the legendary vesel holding the stone tablets of the Ten Commandments. The Bible contains hundreds of references to the Ark&#8217;s power to level mountains, destroy armies, and lay waste to cities. The Ark itself, however, mysteriously disappears from recorded history sometime after the building of the Temple of Solomon.<br />
                     After ten years of searching through the dusty archives of Europe and the Middle East, as well as braving the real-life dangers of a bloody civil war in Ethiopia, Graham Hancock has succeeded where scores of others have failed. This intrepid journalist has tracked down the true story behind the myths and legends &#8212; revealing where the Ark is today, how it got there, and why it remains hidden.<br />
                     Part fascinating scholarship and part entertaining adventure yarn, tying together some of the most intriguing tales of all time &#8212; from the Knights Templar and Prester John to Parsival and the Holy Grail &#8212; this book will appeal to anyone fascinated by the revelation of hidden truths, the discovery of secret mysteries.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sign-and-the-seal-the-quest-for-the-lost-ark-of-the-covenant-graham-hancock/">The Sign and the Seal : The Quest for the Lost Ark of the Covenant &#8211; Graham Hancock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revelation Unveiled &#8211; Tim LaHaye</title>
		<link>/revelation-unveiled-tim-lahaye/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aspects Of Religion (non-Christian)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bible Readings, Selections & Meditations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/revelation-unveiled-tim-lahaye/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Biblical Foundation for the Best-selling Left Behind Series . . . In the twinkling of an eye, millions of people across the world vanish, resulting in highway catastrophes, plane crashes, utility breakdowns, and more. Chaos reigns. With the stage set, a dictator emerges who persecutes Christians horribly. But tribulation is about to give way [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revelation-unveiled-tim-lahaye/">Revelation Unveiled &#8211; Tim LaHaye</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Biblical Foundation for the Best-selling Left Behind Series . . . In the twinkling of an eye, millions of people across the world vanish, resulting in highway catastrophes, plane crashes, utility breakdowns, and more. Chaos reigns. With the stage set, a dictator emerges who persecutes Christians horribly. But tribulation is about to give way to incredible joy &#8212; for the return of the King of Kings is at hand. In Revelation Unveiled, Dr. Tim LaHaye, co-author with Jerry Jenkins of the best-selling novels Left Behind and Tribulation Force, reveals the scriptural foundation of this series. Revelation Unveiled explains such critical topics as: &#8211; The rapture of the church &#8211; The Return of Christ &#8211; The Great Tribulation &#8211; The Final Battle against Satan and His Hosts &#8211; The Seven Seals &#8211; The Millenial Reign &#8211; The Seven Trumpets &#8211; The Seven Bowls of Wrath &#8211; The Great White Throne &#8211; The Destruction of Babylon &#8211; The New Heaven and New Earth &#8212; Previously titled Revelation Illustrated and Made Plain, this revised and updated commentary includes numerous charts. With simple and accessible language, Revelation Unveiled will help you better understand this mysterious, final book of the Bible and its implications.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revelation-unveiled-tim-lahaye/">Revelation Unveiled &#8211; Tim LaHaye</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Murder of Jesus &#8211; John F. MacArthur</title>
		<link>/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bible Studies: For Individual Or Small Group Study]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The pieces are in place. The curtain rises for the final act. God is about to die. An unprecedented conspiracy of injustice, cruelty, and religious and political interests sentenced a man guilty of no crimes to the most barbaric method of execution ever devised. The victim was no mere man. Jesus was God in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/">The Murder of Jesus &#8211; John F. MacArthur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The pieces are in place. The curtain rises for the final act. God is about to die.    </p>
<p>                    An unprecedented conspiracy of injustice, cruelty, and religious and political interests sentenced a man guilty of no crimes to the most barbaric method of execution ever devised. The victim was no mere man. Jesus was God in the flesh. The Creator of life died.    </p>
<p>                    How did such a thing come to be? Who were the onlookers, the players, the fakes, frauds, and heroes? What was it like in the Upper Room that night, in the shadows of Gethsemane, or in the Praetorium awaiting Pilate&#8217;s verdict? What is the meaning of the last words Jesus uttered as He gasped for breath on the cross? What if all the facts you now so well could come alive in your ind and heart as a living story, rather than as a 2000-year-old ancient account?    </p>
<p>                    By piecing together the narrative from the perspective of the participants, John MacArthur invites you to relive the most awesome injustice in the history of man, the unparalleled triumph of the sovereignty of God, and the passion of Christ.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/">The Murder of Jesus &#8211; John F. MacArthur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Prophets &#8211; Abraham Joshua Heschel</title>
		<link>/the-prophets-abraham-joshua-heschel/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Commentaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early & Medieval]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Judaism: Theology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Classical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-prophets-abraham-joshua-heschel/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book has monumental stature. It is fresh and vivid. . . aflame with prophetic vision. &#8211;James Muilenburg From the author of Man is Not Alone and God in Search of Man, comes Abraham Heschel&#8217;s 1962 masterpiece of Biblical scholarship, The Prophets. The classic work on the Old Testament prophets by a major twentieth-century scholar [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-prophets-abraham-joshua-heschel/">The Prophets &#8211; Abraham Joshua Heschel</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book has monumental stature. It is fresh and vivid. . . aflame with prophetic vision. &#8211;James Muilenburg    </p>
<p>                    From the author of Man is Not Alone and God in Search of Man, comes Abraham Heschel&#8217;s 1962 masterpiece of Biblical scholarship, The Prophets.    </p>
<p>                    The classic work on the Old Testament prophets by a major twentieth-century scholar    </p>
<p>                     The Prophets provides a unique opportunity for readers of the Old Testament, both Christian and Jewish, to gain fresh and deep knowledge of Israel&#8217;s prophetic movement. The author&#8217;s profound understanding of the prophets also opens the door to new insight into the philosophy of religion.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-prophets-abraham-joshua-heschel/">The Prophets &#8211; Abraham Joshua Heschel</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Exegesis & Hermeneutics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Earliest Times To Present Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This rich and magisterial work traces Palestine&#8217;s millennia-old heritage, uncovering cultures and societies of astounding depth and complexity that stretch back to the very beginnings of recorded history. Starting with the earliest references in Egyptian and Assyrian texts, Nur Masalha explores how Palestine and its Palestinian identity have evolved over thousands of years, from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/">Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This rich and magisterial work traces Palestine&#8217;s millennia-old heritage, uncovering cultures and societies of astounding depth and complexity that stretch back to the very beginnings of recorded history.    </p>
<p>                    Starting with the earliest references in Egyptian and Assyrian texts, Nur Masalha explores how Palestine and its Palestinian identity have evolved over thousands of years, from the Bronze Age to the present day. Drawing on a rich body of sources and the latest archaeological evidence, Masalha shows how Palestine&#8217;s multicultural past has been distorted and mythologised by Biblical lore and the Israel-Palestinian conflict.    </p>
<p>                    In the process, Masalha reveals that the concept of Palestine, contrary to accepted belief, is not a modern invention or one constructed in opposition to Israel, but rooted firmly in ancient past. Palestine represents the authoritative account of the country&#8217;s history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/">Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
