<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Press &amp; Journalism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/press-journalism/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/press-journalism/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Press &amp; Journalism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/press-journalism/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider. After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry. From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider.    </p>
<p>                    After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry.     </p>
<p>                    From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that routinely rejected stories due to racial bias, to the number of papers that accepted cash bribes. Gripping, thought-provoking and revelatory, this is an insider&#8217;s look at one of the most tainted professions.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Meticulous, fair-minded and utterly gripping&#8217; Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Powerful and timely&#8230;his analysis is fair, meticulously researched and fascinating&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution. For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers. Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution.    For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers.       Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created.       They are using blogs, Twitter, and Facebook to share stories, and selecting their sources to create their own &#8216;front page&#8217;.   In this lively, biting critique, media commentator Tim Dunlop explores the rise of the audience, and how unprepared the mainstream media has been for this changing balance of power.       Drawing on his experiences as prominent political blogger, he argues that the future of meaningful journalism &#8211; the sort we need in order to be informed citizens &#8211; will increasingly rely on journalists and editors taking the audience into their confidence and working with them, rather than against them.   The New Front Page is a passionate plea on behalf of those tired of being talked down to by the fourth estate.       Perceptive and illuminating, it asks audiences and media to work together to hold the powerful to account, and to produce the sort of news and analysis that enriches public debate.   &#8216;A fascinating account of how digital technology has changed Australian media forever.&#8217;       Katharine Viner, editor-in-chief of The Guardian Australia   &#8216;An essential guide to understanding our insurgent new media.&#8217;       Lindsay Tanner, author of Sideshow   &#8216;Dunlop writes with humour, passion, and insight.&#8217;       Gay Alcorn, journalist</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN* A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood<br />
                    &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson<br />
                    &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson    </p>
<p>                    *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN*    </p>
<p>                    A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey that helped change the world.    </p>
<p>                    Hollywood was talking as never before. Kantor and Twohey outmanoeuvred Harvey Weinstein, his team of defenders and private investigators, convincing some of the most famous women in the world &#8211; and some unknown ones &#8211; to go on the record. Three years later, it helped lead to his conviction.    </p>
<p>                    This is how they did it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The War on Journalism &#8211; Andrew Fowler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The War on Journalism The War on Journalism is a harrowing story of megalomaniac press barons, conspiracies, sackings, cutbacks, and self censoring journalists, cowed by what legendary investigative reporter Seymour Hersh called ochicken shit editorso. When first Chelsea Manning and then Edward Snowden blew the whistle, they did more than reveal extraordinary secrets, they struck [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/">The War on Journalism &#8211; Andrew Fowler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The War on Journalism    </p>
<p>                    The War on Journalism is a harrowing story of  megalomaniac press barons, conspiracies, sackings, cutbacks, and self censoring journalists, cowed by what legendary investigative reporter Seymour Hersh called ochicken shit editorso.     </p>
<p>                    When first Chelsea Manning and then Edward Snowden blew the whistle, they did more than reveal extraordinary secrets, they struck the first solid blows against centuries old traditions, where journalism was played by agreed rules.  Governments oleakedo secret information to their favorite journalists in return for sympathetic coverage.     </p>
<p>                    Now racked by public distrust, the cash-starved mainstream media  is struggling to survive. Newspapers which flourished for hundreds of years  and TV networks that once ruled the world are in serious decline.   Andrew Fowler gives the inside story on how and why the media helped write its own epitaph. Fowler, an investigate reporter with Australia&#8217;s prestigious Four Corners documentary program for almost 20 years, and author of the international best seller The Most Dangerous Man in the World, the revelatory story of Julian Assange and the rise of WikiLeaks, has pieced together the extraordinary story on the decline of mainstream journalism.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s not just the notorious tabloids like Rupert Murdoch&#8217;s News of the World, infamous for its phone hacking crimes, which have caused the trouble.  The BBC,  Australia&#8217;s ABC, the Washington Post and the New York Times, and the Guardian, are also in the firing line.    </p>
<p>                    Now the establishment is fighting back with draconian laws to silence the new journalism. From the UK to the US to Australia, governments are harassing journalists, threatening to jail both the whistleblowers and those who publish  their leaks     </p>
<p>                    A battle, shrouded in the cloak of national security, pitting the public&#8217;s right to know against the powerful interests of those who want business as usual, it&#8217;s a stark choice- an increasingly democratic world, or one dominated by executive government, often unchallenged and unaccountable, spying on its own citizens and producing fraudulent arguments to fight horrific wars. Just who wins this information battle will not only define the kind of journalism that survives but also the kind of world we will all live in.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/">The War on Journalism &#8211; Andrew Fowler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Than Enough : Claiming Space for Who You Are (No Matter What They Say) &#8211; Elaine Welteroth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WINNER OF THE 2020 NAACP IMAGE AWARD FOR OUTSTANDING LITERARY WORK &#8211; BIOGRAPHY/AUTOBIOGRAPHY In this part-manifesto, part-memoir, the revolutionary editor who infused social consciousness into the pages of Teen Vogue explores what it means to come into your own &#8211; on your own terms. Elaine Welteroth has climbed the ranks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/">More Than Enough : Claiming Space for Who You Are (No Matter What They Say) &#8211; Elaine Welteroth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    WINNER OF THE 2020 NAACP IMAGE AWARD FOR OUTSTANDING LITERARY WORK &#8211; BIOGRAPHY/AUTOBIOGRAPHY    </p>
<p>                    In this part-manifesto, part-memoir, the revolutionary editor who infused social consciousness into the pages of Teen Vogue explores what it means to come into your own &#8211; on your own terms.    </p>
<p>                    Elaine Welteroth has climbed the ranks of media and fashion,  shattering ceilings along the way. In this riveting and timely memoir,  the groundbreaking editor unpacks lessons on race, identity, and  success through her own journey, from navigating her way as the  unstoppable child of a unlikely interracial marriage in small-town  California to finding herself on the frontlines of a modern movement for  the next generation of change makers.     </p>
<p>                    Welteroth moves beyond  the headlines and highlight reels to share the profound lessons and  struggles of being a barrier-breaker across so many intersections. As a  young boss and the only black woman in the room, she&#8217;s had enough of the  world telling her &#8211; and all women &#8211; they&#8217;re not enough. As she learns to  rely on herself by looking both inward and upward, we&#8217;re ultimately  reminded that we&#8217;re more than enough.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/">More Than Enough : Claiming Space for Who You Are (No Matter What They Say) &#8211; Elaine Welteroth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2016, one of the giants of modern journalism fell: Gawker Media, infamous for saying what other outlets wouldn&#8217;t say, was sued for publishing Hulk Hogan&#8217;s sex tape, lost the case and went bust. After countless other lawsuits it seemed that Gawker had finally run out of luck. But luck had nothing to do with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2016, one of the giants of modern journalism fell: Gawker Media, infamous for saying what other outlets wouldn&#8217;t say, was sued for publishing Hulk Hogan&#8217;s sex tape, lost the case and went bust. After countless other lawsuits it seemed that Gawker had finally run out of luck. But luck had nothing to do with it.     </p>
<p>                    Peter Thiel, PayPal founder and billionaire investor, had masterminded the whole thing. Still furious at an article that had outed him ten years previously, and increasingly disgusted at Gawker&#8217;s unscrupulous reporting methods, Thiel had spent nearly a decade meticulously plotting a conspiracy that would lead to the demise of Gawker and its founder, Nick Denton. After a multi-year proxy war through the Florida legal system, the settlement of $140million in favour of Hogan ended it.    </p>
<p>                    The verdict would stun the world and so would Peter&#8217;s ultimate unmasking as the man who had set it all in motion. Why had he done this? How had no one discovered it? What would this mean&#8211;for free speech? For privacy? For culture?    </p>
<p>                    In Holiday&#8217;s masterful telling of this nearly unbelievable conspiracy, informed by exclusive interviews with all the key players, this case transcends the narrative of how one billionaire took down a media empire or the current state of the free press. It&#8217;s a study in power, strategy, and one of the most wildly ambitious &#8211; and successful &#8211; secret plots in recent memory.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public. Unfreedom of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public.     </p>
<p>                    Unfreedom of the Press is not just another book about the press. In &#8220;Levin&#8217;s finest work&#8221; (Breitbart), he shows how those entrusted with news reporting today are destroying freedom of the press from within-not through actions of government officials, but with its own abandonment of reportorial integrity and objective journalism.    </p>
<p>                    With the depth of historical background for which his books are renowned, Levin takes you on a journey through the early American patriot press, which proudly promoted the principles set forth in the Declaration of Independence and the Constitution. This is followed by the early decades of the Republic during which newspapers around the young country were open and transparent about their fierce allegiance to one political party or another.    </p>
<p>                    It was only at the start of the Progressive Era and the 20th century that the supposed &#8220;objectivity of the press&#8221; first surfaced, leaving us where we are today: with a partisan party-press overwhelmingly aligned with a political ideology but hypocritically engaged in a massive untruth as to its real nature.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semiotics / Semiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They reveal how issues are framed and topics chosen, and contrast the double standards underlying accounts of free elections, a free press, and governmental repression between Nicaragua and El Salvador; between the Russian invasion of Afghanistan and the American invasion of Vietnam; between the genocide in Cambodia under a pro-American government and genocide under Pol Pot. What emerges from this groundbreaking work is an account of just how propagandistic our mass media are, and how we can learn to read them and see their function in a radically new way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media. Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media.     </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography    </p>
<p>                    In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers and Watergate, tells her story&#8211;one that is extraordinary both for the events it encompasses and for the courage, candor, and dignity of its telling.     </p>
<p>                     Here is the awkward child who grew up amid material wealth and emotional isolation; the young bride who watched her brilliant, charismatic husband&#8211;a confidant to John F. Kennedy and Lyndon Johnson&#8211;plunge into the mental illness that would culminate in his suicide. And here is the widow who shook off her grief and insecurity to take on a president and a pressman&#8217;s union as she entered the profane boys&#8217; club of the newspaper business.     </p>
<p>                     As timely now as ever, Personal History is an exemplary record of our history and of the woman who played such a shaping role within them, discovering her own strength and sense of self as she confronted&#8211;and mastered&#8211;the personal and professional crises of her fascinating life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>And the Good News Is&#8230; : Lessons and Advice from the Bright Side &#8211; Dana Perino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thoughtful, inspiring and often surprising, AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230; traces Dana&#8217;s unlikely journey through politics, the White House, and television. She has an uncanny ability for knowing what to say and how best to say it. A recurring theme in AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230;is that planning has never worked for Dana; every time [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/">And the Good News Is&#8230; : Lessons and Advice from the Bright Side &#8211; Dana Perino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thoughtful, inspiring and often surprising, AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230; traces Dana&#8217;s unlikely journey through politics, the White House, and television. She has an uncanny ability for knowing what to say and how best to say it. A recurring theme in AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230;is that planning has never worked for Dana; every time she has made a plan, something unexpected-and often better-has happened.<br />
                    AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230; blends a candid self-portrait with advice for allowing one&#8217;s very best personality traits to shine through, emphasizing that dignity and civility are choices we make for ourselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/">And the Good News Is&#8230; : Lessons and Advice from the Bright Side &#8211; Dana Perino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING * &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING *     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly written haymaker&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly three years of reporting, hundreds of hours of interviews and more than two hundred sources, including some of the most senior members of the administration, friends and first-hand witnesses who have never spoken before, Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig take us inside some of the most controversial moments of Trump&#8217;s presidency. They peer deeply into Trump&#8217;s White House &#8211; at the aides pressured to lie to the public, the lawyers scrambling to clear up norm-breaking disasters, and the staffers whose careers have been reduced to ashes &#8211; to paint an unparalleled group portrait of an administration driven by self-preservation and paranoia.     </p>
<p>                    Rucker and Leonnig reveal Trump at his most unvarnished, showing the unhinged decision-making and incompetence that has floored officials and stunned foreign leaders. They portray unscripted calls with Vladimir Putin, steak dinners with Kim Jong-un, and calls with Theresa May so hostile that they left her aides shaken. They also take a hard look at Robert Mueller, Trump&#8217;s greatest antagonist to date, and how his investigation slowly unravelled an administration whose universal value is loyalty &#8211; not to country, but to the president himself.    </p>
<p>                    Grippingly told, A Very Stable Genius is a behind-the-scenes account of Trump&#8217;s vainglorious pursuit of power in his first term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER* &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran Imagine a world where&#8230; * Your phone is too big for your hand * Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body * [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    Imagine a world where&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    *        Your phone is too big for your hand<br />
                    *        Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body<br />
                    *        In a car accident you are 47% more likely to be injured.    </p>
<p>                    If any of that sounds familiar, chances are you&#8217;re a woman.    </p>
<p>                    From government policy and medical research, to technology, workplaces, and the media. Invisible Women reveals how in a world built for and by men we are systematically ignoring half of the population, often with disastrous consequences. Caroline Criado Perez brings together for the first time an impressive range of case studies, stories and new research from across the world that illustrate the hidden ways in which women are forgotten, and the profound impact this has on us all.    </p>
<p>                    Discover the shocking gender bias that affects our everyday lives.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book that changes the way you see the world&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Revelatory, frightening, hopeful&#8217; Jeanette Winterson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
