<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Organization &amp; Management Of Education Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/organization-management-of-education/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/organization-management-of-education/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Organization &amp; Management Of Education Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/organization-management-of-education/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teacher Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Staff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching    </p>
<p>                     Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically and mentally ill, things have gone too far. Unsurprisingly, these effects are highest in difficult-to-fill positions such as math, science, and foreign languages, and in urban areas and secondary classrooms-places where we need our teachers to be especially motivated and engaged. This book offers a path to resiliency to help teachers weather the storms and bounce back-and work toward banishing the rain for good.    </p>
<p>                     This actionable framework gives you concrete steps toward rediscovering yourself, your energy, and your passion for teaching. You&#8217;ll learn how a simple shift in mindset can affect your outlook, and how taking care of yourself physically, mentally, and emotionally is one of the most important things you can do. The companion workbook helps you put the framework into action, streamlining your way toward renewal and strength.    </p>
<p>                    Cultivate resilience with a four-part framework based on 12 key habits<br />
                    Uncover your true self, understand emotions, and use your energy where it counts<br />
                    Adopt a mindful, story-telling approach to communication and community building<br />
                    Keep learning, playing, and creating to create an environment of collective celebration    </p>
<p>                     By cultivating resilience in schools, we help ensure that we are working in, teaching in, and leading organizations where every child thrives, and where the potential of every child is recognized and nurtured. Onward provides a step-by-step plan for reigniting that spark.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>#NeverAgain : A New Generation Draws the Line &#8211; David Hogg, Lauren Hogg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/neveragain-a-new-generation-draws-the-line-david-hogg-lauren-hogg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Students & Student Organisations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/neveragain-a-new-generation-draws-the-line-david-hogg-lauren-hogg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From two survivors of the Parkland, Florida, shooting comes a declaration for our times, and an in-depth look at the making of the #NeverAgain movement. On February 14, 2018, seventeen-year-old David Hogg and his fourteen-year-old sister, Lauren, went to school at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School, like any normal Wednesday. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/neveragain-a-new-generation-draws-the-line-david-hogg-lauren-hogg-abridged/">#NeverAgain : A New Generation Draws the Line &#8211; David Hogg, Lauren Hogg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From two survivors of the Parkland, Florida, shooting comes a declaration for our times, and an in-depth look at the making of the #NeverAgain movement. On February 14, 2018, seventeen-year-old David Hogg and his fourteen-year-old sister, Lauren, went to school at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School, like any normal Wednesday. That day, of course, the world changed. By the next morning, with seventeen classmates and faculty dead, they had joined the leadership of a movement to save their own lives, and the lives of all other young people in America. It&#8217;s a leadership position they did not seek, and did not want&#8211;but events gave them no choice. The morning after the massacre, David Hogg told CNN: We&#8217;re children. You guys are the adults. You need to take some action and play a role. Work together. Get over your politics and get something done. This book is a manifesto for the movement begun that day, one that has already changed America&#8211;with voices of a new generation that are speaking truth to power, and are determined to succeed where their elders have failed. With moral force and clarity, a new generation has made it clear that problems previously deemed unsolvable due to powerful lobbies and political cowardice will be theirs to solve. Born just after Columbine and raised amid seemingly endless war and routine active shooter drills, this generation now says, Enough. This book is their statement of purpose, and the story of their lives. It is the essential guide to the #NeverAgain movement.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/neveragain-a-new-generation-draws-the-line-david-hogg-lauren-hogg-abridged/">#NeverAgain : A New Generation Draws the Line &#8211; David Hogg, Lauren Hogg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Six Thinking Hats : The multi-million bestselling guide to running better meetings and making faster decisions &#8211; Edward de Bono (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/six-thinking-hats-the-multi-million-bestselling-guide-to-running-better-meetings-and-making-faster-decisions-edward-de-bono-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decision Theory: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/six-thinking-hats-the-multi-million-bestselling-guide-to-running-better-meetings-and-making-faster-decisions-edward-de-bono-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE MULTI-MILLION COPY BESTSELLING PHENOMENON Do you regularly find yourself in long, unstructured meetings which end without a decision? Are you a team leader looking for tips on increasing productivity? Or are you looking for ways to enhance collaboration? Six Thinking Hats, Edward de Bono&#8217;s classic book on meetings, remains as relevant as ever. Used [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/six-thinking-hats-the-multi-million-bestselling-guide-to-running-better-meetings-and-making-faster-decisions-edward-de-bono-abridged/">Six Thinking Hats : The multi-million bestselling guide to running better meetings and making faster decisions &#8211; Edward de Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE MULTI-MILLION COPY BESTSELLING PHENOMENON     </p>
<p>                    Do you regularly find yourself in long, unstructured meetings which end without a decision? Are you a team leader looking for tips on increasing productivity? Or are you looking for ways to enhance collaboration?    </p>
<p>                    Six Thinking Hats, Edward de Bono&#8217;s classic book on meetings, remains as relevant as ever. Used to huge success by big companies and organisations such as IBM, Siemens and NASA, the Six-Hats method is a proven way to:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Reduce meeting lengths to one quarter of what they were previously<br />
                    &#8211; Make decisions in just 15 minutes, rather than 3 hours<br />
                    &#8211; Increase productivity by nearly 500%    </p>
<p>                    This extremely simple tool not only increases efficiency in discussions and decision-making, but also encourages openness and trust among colleagues, resulting in happier team, a rise in productivity, and decisions which almost make themselves.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An inspiring man with brilliant ideas. De Bono never ceases to amaze&#8217; Sir Richard Branson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/six-thinking-hats-the-multi-million-bestselling-guide-to-running-better-meetings-and-making-faster-decisions-edward-de-bono-abridged/">Six Thinking Hats : The multi-million bestselling guide to running better meetings and making faster decisions &#8211; Edward de Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smartest Kids in the World : And How They Got That Way &#8211; Amanda Ripley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Examinations & Assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secondary Schools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Students & Student Organisations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of Gifted Students]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>America has long compared its students to top-performing kids of other nations. But how do the world&#8217;s education superpowers look through the eyes of an American high school student? Author Amanda Ripley follows three teenagers who chose to spend one school year living and learning in Finland, South Korea, and Poland. Through their adventures, Ripley [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/">The Smartest Kids in the World : And How They Got That Way &#8211; Amanda Ripley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>America has long compared its students to top-performing kids of other nations. But how do the world&#8217;s education superpowers look through the eyes of an American high school student? Author Amanda Ripley follows three teenagers who chose to spend one school year living and learning in Finland, South Korea, and Poland. Through their adventures, Ripley discovers startling truths about how attitudes, parenting, and rigorous teaching have revolutionized these countries&#8217; education results.     </p>
<p>                    In The Smartest Kids in the World, Ripley&#8217;s astonishing new insights reveal that top-performing countries have achieved greatness only in the past several decades; that the kids who live there are learning to think for themselves, partly through failing early and often; and that persistence, hard work, and resilience matter more to our children&#8217;s life chances than self-esteem or sports.     </p>
<p>                    Ripley&#8217;s investigative work seamlessly weaves narrative and research, providing in-depth analysis and gripping details that will keep you turning the pages. Written in a clear and engaging style, The Smartest Kids in the World will enliven public as well as dinner table debates over what makes for brighter and better students.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/">The Smartest Kids in the World : And How They Got That Way &#8211; Amanda Ripley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Problem Solving 101 : A simple book for smart people &#8211; Ken Watanabe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/problem-solving-101-a-simple-book-for-smart-people-ken-watanabe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/problem-solving-101-a-simple-book-for-smart-people-ken-watanabe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Problem Solving 101 started out as a simple guide to teach Japanese schoolchildren critical thinking skills. But it quickly became an international bestseller for readers of all ages, thanks to the powerful effectiveness of Ken Watanabe&#8217;s unique methods. Full of useful diagrams and quirky drawings, Problem Solving 101 is packed with practical tools and brain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/problem-solving-101-a-simple-book-for-smart-people-ken-watanabe-abridged/">Problem Solving 101 : A simple book for smart people &#8211; Ken Watanabe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Problem Solving 101 started out as a simple guide to teach Japanese schoolchildren critical thinking skills. But it quickly became an international bestseller for readers of all ages, thanks to the powerful effectiveness of Ken Watanabe&#8217;s unique methods.     </p>
<p>                    Full of useful diagrams and quirky drawings, Problem Solving 101 is packed with practical tools and brain training techniques that will improve your problem-solving and decision-making ability, and enable you to find better solutions faster.    </p>
<p>                    Simple enough for a high school student to understand but sophisticated enough for CEOs to apply to their most challenging problems, Problem Solving 101 has helped millions of people around the world to find successful solutions to even the toughest of problems.    </p>
<p>                    Once you&#8217;ve mastered the problem-solving skills in this book, you&#8217;ll wonder how you ever got by without them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/problem-solving-101-a-simple-book-for-smart-people-ken-watanabe-abridged/">Problem Solving 101 : A simple book for smart people &#8211; Ken Watanabe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decision Theory: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques in The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking, you will regularly find imaginative solutions to difficult challenges, and you will discover new ways of looking at your world and yourself&#8211;revealing previously hidden opportunities. The book offers real-life stories, explicit action items, and concrete methods that allow you to attain a deeper understanding of any issue, exploit the power of failure as a step toward success, develop a habit of creating probing questions, see the world of ideas as an ever-flowing stream of thought, and embrace the uplifting reality that we are all capable of change. No matter who you are, the practical mind-sets introduced in the book will empower you to realize any goal in a more creative, intelligent, and effective manner.<br />
                    Filled with engaging examples that unlock truths about thinking in every walk of life, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking is written for all who want to reach their fullest potential&#8211;including students, parents, teachers, businesspeople, professionals, athletes, artists, leaders, and lifelong learners. Whenever you are stuck, need a new idea, or want to learn and grow, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking will inspire and guide you on your way. To share thinking stories, go to: http://5elementsofthinking.wordpress.com/</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Learning, Home Learning, Distance Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned education writer comes a fascinating examination of the rapidly shifting world of college that every parent, student and educator needs to understand. In 2011-2012, some of the world&#8217;s most famous universities and technology entrepreneurs began a revolution in higher education. College courses that had been kept from all but an elite few [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/">The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned education writer comes a fascinating examination of the rapidly shifting world of college that every parent, student and educator needs to understand.    </p>
<p>                    In 2011-2012, some of the world&#8217;s most famous universities and technology entrepreneurs began a revolution in higher education. College courses that had been kept from all but an elite few were released to students around the world &#8212; for free. And thanks to exploding tuition prices, a volatile global economy and some high-tech innovations, we&#8217;re now poised for a total rethinking of what college is and should be. In the NEW YORK TIMES-bestselling THE END OF COLLEGE, Kevin Carey draws on new research to paint an exciting portrait of the near future of education. He explains how the college experience is being radically altered now and how it will emancipate millions of people around the world. Insightful and readable, THE END OF COLLEGE is an innovative roadmap to understanding tomorrow&#8217;s higher education today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/">The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The basis for a major documentary, two leading experts sound an urgent call for the radical reimagining of American education so we can equip students for the realities of the twenty-first-century economy. We prize academic achievement, pressuring our children to get into the &#8220;right&#8221; colleges, have the highest GPAs, and pursue advanced degrees. But while [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/">Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The basis for a major documentary, two leading experts sound an urgent call for the radical reimagining of American education so we can equip students for the realities of the twenty-first-century economy.<br />
                         We prize academic achievement, pressuring our children to get into the &#8220;right&#8221; colleges, have the highest GPAs, and pursue advanced degrees. But while students may graduate with credentials, by and large they lack the competencies needed to be thoughtful, engaged citizens and to get good jobs in our rapidly evolving economy. Alarmingly, our methods of schooling crush the creativity and initiative young people really need to thrive in the twenty-first century.<br />
                         Now bestselling author and education expert Tony Wagner and venture capitalist Ted Dintersmith call for a complete overhaul of American schools, sharing insights and stories from the front lines. Their powerful, urgent message identifies the growing gap between credentials and competence-and offers a framework for change.<br />
                        Most Likely to Succeed presents a new vision of American education, one that puts wonder, creativity, and initiative at the very heart of the learning process and prepares students for today&#8217;s economy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/">Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
