<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Genetics (non-medical) Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/genetics-non-medical/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/genetics-non-medical/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Genetics (non-medical) Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/genetics-non-medical/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Ridley leaps from chromosome to chromosome in a handy summation of our ever increasing understanding of the roles that genes play in disease, behavior, sexual differences, and even intelligence. . . . . He addresses not only the ethical quandaries faced by contemporary scientists but the reductionist danger in equating inheritability with inevitability.&#8221; &#8212; The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/">Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Ridley leaps from chromosome to chromosome in a handy summation of our ever increasing understanding of the roles that genes play in disease, behavior, sexual differences, and even intelligence. . . . . He addresses not only the ethical quandaries faced by contemporary scientists but the reductionist danger in equating inheritability with inevitability.&#8221; &#8212; The New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    The genome&#8217;s been mapped. But what does it mean? Matt Ridley&#8217;s Genome is the book that explains it all: what it is, how it works, and what it portends for the future    </p>
<p>                    Arguably the most significant scientific discovery of the new century, the mapping of the twenty-three pairs of chromosomes that make up the human genome raises almost as many questions as it answers. Questions that will profoundly impact the way we think about disease, about longevity, and about free will. Questions that will affect the rest of your life.    </p>
<p>                    Genome offers extraordinary insight into the ramifications of this incredible breakthrough. By picking one newly discovered gene from each pair of chromosomes and telling its story, Matt Ridley recounts the history of our species and its ancestors from the dawn of life to the brink of future medicine. From Huntington&#8217;s disease to cancer, from the applications of gene therapy to the horrors of eugenics, Ridley probes the scientific, philosophical, and moral issues arising as a result of the mapping of the genome. It will help you understand what this scientific milestone means for you, for your children, and for humankind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/">Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life at the Speed of Light : From the Double Helix to the Dawn of Digital Life &#8211; J. Craig Venter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2010, scientists led by J. Craig Venter became the first to successfully create &#8216;synthetic life&#8217; &#8212; putting humankind at the threshold of the most important and exciting phase of biological research, one that will enable us to actually write the genetic code for designing new species to help us adapt and evolve for long-term [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/">Life at the Speed of Light : From the Double Helix to the Dawn of Digital Life &#8211; J. Craig Venter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2010, scientists led by J. Craig Venter became the first to successfully create &#8216;synthetic life&#8217; &#8212; putting humankind at the threshold of the most important and exciting phase of biological research, one that will enable us to actually write the genetic code for designing new species to help us adapt and evolve for long-term survival. The science of synthetic genomics will have a profound impact on human existence, including chemical and energy generation, health, clean water and food production, environmental control, and possibly even our evolution.    </p>
<p>                    In Life at the Speed of Light, Venter presents a fascinating and authoritative study of this emerging field from the inside &#8212; detailing its origins, current challenges and controversies, and projected effects on our lives. This scientific frontier provides an opportunity to ponder anew the age-old question &#8216;What is life?&#8217; and examine what we really mean by &#8216;playing God&#8217;. Life at the Speed of Light is a landmark work, written by a visionary at the dawn of a new era of biological engineering.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/">Life at the Speed of Light : From the Double Helix to the Dawn of Digital Life &#8211; J. Craig Venter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized  the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much more besides. In it, Dawkins extended the gene&#8217;s eye view to argue that the genes that sit within an organism have an<br />
                    influence that reaches out beyond the visible traits in that body &#8211; the phenotype &#8211; to the wider environment, which can include other individuals. So, for instance, the genes of the beaver drive it to gather twigs to produce the substantial physical structure of a dam; and the genes of the cuckoo chick produce effects that<br />
                    manipulate the behaviour of the host bird, making it nurture the intruder as one of its own. This notion of the extended phenotype has proved to be highly influential in the way we understand evolution and the natural world. It represents a key scientific contribution to evolutionary biology, and it continues to play an important role in research in the life sciences.    </p>
<p>                    The Extended Phenotype is a conceptually deep book that forms important reading for biologists and students. But Dawkins&#8217; clear exposition is accessible to all who are prepared to put in a little effort.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Why do human beings behave as they do? &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    Why do human beings behave as they do?     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm    </p>
<p>                     We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of our nature destined to win out over the other?    </p>
<p>                     Every act of human behaviour has multiple layers of causation, spiralling back seconds, minutes, hours, days, months, years, even centuries, right back to the dawn of time and the origins of our species.     </p>
<p>                     In the epic sweep of history, how does our biology affect the arc of war and peace, justice and persecution? How have our brains evolved alongside our cultures?    </p>
<p>                     This is the exhilarating story of human morality and the science underpinning the biggest question of all: what makes us human?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the best scientist-writers of our time&#8217; Oliver Sacks</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If there is one dominant myth about the world, one huge mistake we all make &#8230; it is that we all go around assuming the world is much more of a planned place than it is.&#8217; From the industrial revolution and the rise of China, to urbanisation and the birth of bitcoin, Matt Ridley demolishes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If there is one dominant myth about the world, one huge mistake we all make &#8230; it is that we all go around assuming the world is much more of a planned place than it is.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              From the industrial revolution and the rise of China, to urbanisation and the birth of bitcoin, Matt Ridley demolishes conventional assumptions that the great events and trends of our day are dictated by those on high. On the contrary, our most important achievements develop from the ground up. In this wide-ranging and erudite book, Matt Ridley brilliantly makes the case for evolution as the force that has shaped much of our culture, our minds, and that even now is shaping our future.    </p>
<p>                              As compelling as it is controversial, as authoritative as it is ambitious, Ridley&#8217;s deeply thought-provoking book will change the way we think about the world and how it works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the revolutionary science behind the power of thought, this book will forever change how you think about your own thinking. This new updated and expanded 10th anniversary edition of The Biology of Belief contains stunning new scientific discoveries about the biochemical effects of the brain&#8217;s functioning that show all the cells of your body [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/">The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the revolutionary science behind the power of thought, this book will forever change how you think about your own thinking.    </p>
<p>                    This new updated and expanded 10th anniversary edition of The Biology of Belief contains stunning new scientific discoveries about the biochemical effects of the brain&#8217;s functioning that show all the cells of your body are affected by your thoughts. Bruce H. Lipton PhD, a renowned cell biologist, describes the precise molecular pathways through which this occurs. Using simple language, illustrations, humour and everyday examples, he demonstrates how the new science of epigenetics is revolutionizing our understanding of the link between mind and matter, and the profound effects it has on our personal lives and the collective life of our species.    </p>
<p>                    It has been 10 years since the publication of The Biology of Belief, Bruce Lipton&#8217;s seminal book on the relationship between mind and body that changed the way we think about our lives, our health and our planet. During that time, research in this field has grown exponentially &#8211; Lipton&#8217;s ground-breaking experiments have now been endorsed by more than a decade of rigorous scientific study.    </p>
<p>                    In this greatly expanded edition, Lipton explores his own experiments and those of other leading-edge scientists that have unravelled in ever greater detail how truly connected the mind, body and spirit are. It is now widely recognized that genes and DNA do not control our biology. Instead, they are controlled by signals from outside the cell, including energetic messages emanating from our thoughts.    </p>
<p>                    This profoundly hopeful synthesis of the latest and best research in cell biology and quantum physics puts the power to create a healthy, joyous life back in our own hands. When we transform our conscious and subconscious thoughts, we transform our lives, and in the process help humanity evolve to a new level of understanding and peace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/">The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction and A New York Times Notable Book of 2018. Our understanding of the &#8216;tree of life&#8217;, with powerful implications for human genetics, human health and our own human nature, has recently completely changed. This book is about a new method of telling the story of life on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/">The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction and A New York Times Notable Book of 2018.    </p>
<p>                              Our understanding of the &#8216;tree of life&#8217;, with powerful implications for human genetics, human health and our own human nature, has recently completely changed.    </p>
<p>                              This book is about a new method of telling the story of life on earth &#8211; through molecular phylogenetics. It involves a fairly simple method &#8211; the reading of the deep history of life by looking at the variation in protein molecules found in living organisms. For instance, we now know that roughly eight per cent of the human genome arrived not through traditional inheritance from directly ancestral forms, but sideways by viral infection.    </p>
<p>                              In The Tangled Tree, acclaimed science writer David Quammen chronicles these discoveries through the lives of the researchers who made them &#8211; such as Carl Woese, the most important little-known biologist of the twentieth century; Lynn Margulis, the notorious maverick whose wild ideas about &#8216;mosaic&#8217; creatures proved to be true; and Tsutomu Wantanabe, who discovered that the scourge of antibiotic-resistant bacteria is a direct result of horizontal gene transfer, bringing the deep study of genome histories to bear on a global crisis in public health.    </p>
<p>                              Quammen explains how molecular studies of evolution have brought startling recognitions about the tangled tree of life &#8211; including where we humans fit into it. Thanks to new technologies, we now have the ability to alter even our genetic composition &#8211; through sideways insertions, as nature has long been doing. The Tangled Tree is a brilliant exploration of our transformed understanding of evolution and of life&#8217;s history itself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/">The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeological Methodology & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, helped resolve long-existing controversies, challenged long-held views, and thrown up some remarkable surprises.    </p>
<p>                    The emerging picture is one of many waves of ancient human migrations, so that all populations existing today are mixes of ancient ones, as well as in many cases carrying a genetic component from Neanderthals, and, in some populations, Denisovans. David Reich, whose team has been at the forefront of these discoveries, explains what the genetics is telling us about ourselves and our complex and often surprising ancestry. Gone are old ideas of any kind of racial &#8216;purity&#8217;, or even deep and ancient<br />
                    divides between peoples. Instead, we are finding a rich variety of mixtures. Reich describes the cutting-edge findings from the past few years, and also considers the sensitivities involved in tracing ancestry, with science sometimes jostling with politics and tradition. He brings an important wider<br />
                    message: that we should celebrate our rich diversity, and recognize that every one of us is the result of a long history of migration and intermixing of ancient peoples, which we carry as ghosts in our DNA.    </p>
<p>                    What will we discover next?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inheritance : How Our Genes Change Our Lives, and Our Lives Change Our Genes &#8211; Dr Sharon Moalem (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inheritance-how-our-genes-change-our-lives-and-our-lives-change-our-genes-dr-sharon-moalem-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inheritance-how-our-genes-change-our-lives-and-our-lives-change-our-genes-dr-sharon-moalem-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking book that will transform how we understand ourselves and our families by revealing that everything we thought we knew about genetics is wrong. Your experiences, no matter how seemingly inconsequential &#8211; from bullies to crushes to what you eat for dinner &#8211; have all left an indelible mark within you. And more importantly, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inheritance-how-our-genes-change-our-lives-and-our-lives-change-our-genes-dr-sharon-moalem-abridged/">Inheritance : How Our Genes Change Our Lives, and Our Lives Change Our Genes &#8211; Dr Sharon Moalem (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking book that will transform how we understand ourselves and our families by revealing that everything we thought we knew about genetics is wrong.     </p>
<p>                    Your experiences, no matter how seemingly inconsequential &#8211; from bullies to crushes to what you eat for dinner &#8211; have all left an indelible mark within you. And more importantly, within your genes.    </p>
<p>                    Inheritance is a guidebook for change. No longer do we have to settle for what we&#8217;ve been given. We can write our own story.    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;re taught that we don&#8217;t have much of a choice in the matter of what we get or what we give, because our genetic legacy was fixed when our parents conceived us. But that&#8217;s all wrong. Our genes are constantly on the move, some are turning on while others are turning off, all in response to what you&#8217;re doing, what you&#8217;re seeing, and what you&#8217;re feeling. And all of those things can be changed, which means we can change. Genetically.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inheritance-how-our-genes-change-our-lives-and-our-lives-change-our-genes-dr-sharon-moalem-abridged/">Inheritance : How Our Genes Change Our Lives, and Our Lives Change Our Genes &#8211; Dr Sharon Moalem (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene<br />
                    Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the future of our species for fans of Homo Deus and The Gene.<br />
                    After 3.8 billion years humankind is about to start evolving by new rules&#8230;<br />
                    From leading geopolitical expert and technology futurist Jamie Metzl comes a groundbreaking exploration of the many ways genetic-engineering is shaking the core foundations of our lives-sex, war, love, and death.<br />
                    At the dawn of the genetics revolution, our DNA is becoming as readable, writable, and hackable as our information technology. But as humanity starts retooling our own genetic code, the choices we make today will be the difference between realizing breathtaking advances in human well-being and descending into a dangerous and potentially deadly genetic arms race.<br />
                    Enter the laboratories where scientists are turning science fiction into reality. Look towards a future where our deepest beliefs, morals, religions, and politics are challenged like never before and the very essence of what it means to be human is at play. When we can engineer our future children, massively extend our lifespans, build life from scratch, and recreate the plant and animal world, should we?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages. As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages.    </p>
<p>                    As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene  has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and in which organisms can be seen as vehicles for their replication. This imaginative, powerful, and stylistically brilliant work not only brought the insights of Neo-Darwinism to a wide audience, but galvanized the biology<br />
                    community, generating much debate and stimulating whole new areas of research. Forty years later, its insights remain as relevant today as on the day it was published.     </p>
<p>                    This 40th anniversary edition includes a new epilogue from the author discussing the continuing relevance of these ideas in evolutionary biology today, as well as the original prefaces and foreword, and extracts from early reviews.     </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2018 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh presents a profoundly original perspective on what we pass along from generation to generation. Charles Darwin played a crucial part in turning heredity into a scientific question, and yet he failed spectacularly to answer it. The birth of genetics in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/">She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2018 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION    </p>
<p>                    She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh presents a profoundly original perspective on what we pass along from generation to generation. Charles Darwin played a crucial part in turning heredity into a scientific question, and yet he failed spectacularly to answer it. The birth of genetics in the early 1900s seemed to do precisely that. Gradually, people translated their old notions about heredity into a language of genes. As the technology for studying genes became cheaper, millions of people ordered genetic tests to link themselves to missing parents, to distant ancestors, to ethnic identities . . .    </p>
<p>                    But, award-winning science writer Carl Zimmer argues, heredity isn&#8217;t just about genes that pass from parent to child. Heredity continues within our own bodies, as a single cell gives rise to trillions of cells that make up our bodies. We say we inherit genes from our ancestors but we inherit other things that matter as much or more to our lives, from microbes to technologies we use to make life more comfortable. We need a new definition of what heredity is and, through Carl Zimmer&#8217;s lucid exposition and storytelling, this resounding tour de force delivers it.    </p>
<p>                    Weaving together historical and current scientific research, his own experience with his two daughters, and the kind of original reporting expected of one of the world&#8217;s best science journalists, Zimmer ultimately unpacks urgent bioethical quandaries arising from new biomedical technologies, but also long-standing presumptions about who we really are and what we can pass on to future generations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/">She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Brief History of Everyone Who Ever Lived : The Stories in Our Genes &#8211; Adam Rutherford (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genealogy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Genetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A brilliant, authoritative, surprising, captivating introduction to human genetics. You&#8217;ll be spellbound&#8217; Brian Cox This is a story about you. It is the history of who you are and how you came to be. It is unique to you, as it is to each of the 100 billion modern humans who have ever drawn breath. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/">A Brief History of Everyone Who Ever Lived : The Stories in Our Genes &#8211; Adam Rutherford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A brilliant, authoritative, surprising, captivating introduction to human genetics. You&#8217;ll be spellbound&#8217; Brian Cox    </p>
<p>                    This is a story about you.     </p>
<p>                    It is the history of who you are and how you came to be. It is unique to you, as it is to each of the 100 billion modern humans who have ever drawn breath. But it is also our collective story, because in every one of our genomes we each carry the history of our species &#8211; births, deaths, disease, war, famine, migration and a lot of sex.     </p>
<p>                    In this captivating journey through the expanding landscape of genetics, Adam Rutherford reveals what our genes now tell us about human history, and what history can now tell us about our genes. From Neanderthals to murder, from redheads to race, dead kings to plague, evolution to epigenetics, this is a demystifying and illuminating new portrait of who we are and how we came to be.    </p>
<p>                    ***    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A thoroughly entertaining history of Homo sapiens and its DNA in a manner that displays popular science writing at its best&#8217; Observer     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Magisterial, informative and delightful&#8217; Peter Frankopan    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An extraordinary adventure&#8230;From the Neanderthals to the Vikings, from the Queen of Sheba to Richard III, Rutherford goes in search of our ancestors, tracing the genetic clues deep into the past&#8217; Alice Roberts</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/">A Brief History of Everyone Who Ever Lived : The Stories in Our Genes &#8211; Adam Rutherford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Crack in Creation : Gene Editing and the Unthinkable Power to Control Evolution &#8211; Jennifer A Doudna, Samuel H Sternberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BY THE WINNER OF THE 2020 NOBEL PRIZE IN CHEMISTRY Finalist for the Los Angeles Times Book Prize &#8220;A powerful mix of science and ethics . . . This book is required reading for every concerned citizen&#8211;the material it covers should be discussed in schools, colleges, and universities throughout the country.&#8221;&#8211; New York Review of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/">A Crack in Creation : Gene Editing and the Unthinkable Power to Control Evolution &#8211; Jennifer A Doudna, Samuel H Sternberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BY THE WINNER OF THE 2020 NOBEL PRIZE IN CHEMISTRY Finalist for the Los Angeles Times Book Prize     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A powerful mix of science and ethics . . . This book is required reading for every concerned citizen&#8211;the material it covers should be discussed in schools, colleges, and universities throughout the country.&#8221;&#8211; New York Review of Books      </p>
<p>                     Not since the atomic bomb has a technology so alarmed its inventors that they warned the world about its use. That is, until 2015, when biologist Jennifer Doudna called for a worldwide moratorium on the use of the gene-editing tool CRISPR&#8211;a revolutionary new technology that she helped create&#8211;to make heritable changes in human embryos. The cheapest, simplest, most effective way of manipulating DNA ever known, CRISPR may well give us the cure to HIV, genetic diseases, and some cancers. Yet even the tiniest changes to DNA could have myriad, unforeseeable consequences, to say nothing of the ethical and societal repercussions of intentionally mutating embryos to create &#8220;better&#8221; humans. Writing with fellow researcher Sam Sternberg, Doudna&#8211;who has since won the Nobel Prize for her CRISPR research&#8211;shares the thrilling story of her discovery and describes the enormous responsibility that comes with the power to rewrite the code of life.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The future is in our hands as never before, and this book explains the stakes like no other.&#8221; &#8212; George Lucas     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An invaluable account . . . We owe Doudna several times over.&#8221; &#8212; Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/">A Crack in Creation : Gene Editing and the Unthinkable Power to Control Evolution &#8211; Jennifer A Doudna, Samuel H Sternberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Compass of Pleasure : How Our Brains Make Fatty Foods, Orgasm, Exercise, Marijuana, Generosity, Vodka, Learning, and Gambling Feel So Good &#8211; David J. Linden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author comes a &#8220;hugely entertaining&#8221; (NPR.org) look at vice and virtue through cutting-edge scienceAs he did in his award-winning book The Accidental Mind, David J. Linden-highly regarded neuroscientist, professor, and writer-weaves empirical science with entertaining anecdotes to explain how the gamut of behaviors that give us a buzz actually [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/">The Compass of Pleasure : How Our Brains Make Fatty Foods, Orgasm, Exercise, Marijuana, Generosity, Vodka, Learning, and Gambling Feel So Good &#8211; David J. Linden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author comes a &#8220;hugely entertaining&#8221; (NPR.org) look at vice and virtue through cutting-edge scienceAs he did in his award-winning book The Accidental Mind, David J. Linden-highly regarded neuroscientist, professor, and writer-weaves empirical science with entertaining anecdotes to explain how the gamut of behaviors that give us a buzz actually operates. The Compass of Pleasure makes clear why drugs like nicotine and heroin are addictive while LSD is not, how fast food restaurants ensure that diners will eat more, why some people cannot resist the appeal of a new sexual encounter, and much more. Provocative and illuminating, this is a radically new and thorough look at the desires that define us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/">The Compass of Pleasure : How Our Brains Make Fatty Foods, Orgasm, Exercise, Marijuana, Generosity, Vodka, Learning, and Gambling Feel So Good &#8211; David J. Linden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Double Helix: A Personal Account of the Discovery of the Structure of DNA &#8211; James D. Watson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-double-helix-a-personal-account-of-the-discovery-of-the-structure-of-dna-james-d-watson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-double-helix-a-personal-account-of-the-discovery-of-the-structure-of-dna-james-d-watson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic personal account of Watson and Crick&#8217;s groundbreaking discovery of the structure of DNA, now with an introduction by Sylvia Nasar, author of A Beautiful Mind. By identifying the structure of DNA, the molecule of life, Francis Crick and James Watson revolutionized biochemistry and won themselves a Nobel Prize. At the time, Watson was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-double-helix-a-personal-account-of-the-discovery-of-the-structure-of-dna-james-d-watson-abridged/">The Double Helix: A Personal Account of the Discovery of the Structure of DNA &#8211; James D. Watson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic personal account of Watson and Crick&#8217;s groundbreaking discovery of the structure of DNA, now with an introduction by Sylvia Nasar, author of A Beautiful Mind.     </p>
<p>                    By identifying the structure of DNA, the molecule of life, Francis Crick and James Watson revolutionized biochemistry and won themselves a Nobel Prize. At the time, Watson was only twenty-four, a young scientist hungry to make his mark. His uncompromisingly honest account of the heady days of their thrilling sprint against other world-class researchers to solve one of science&#8217;s greatest mysteries gives a dazzlingly clear picture of a world of brilliant scientists with great gifts, very human ambitions, and bitter rivalries.     </p>
<p>                    With humility unspoiled by false modesty, Watson relates his and Crick&#8217;s desperate efforts to beat Linus Pauling to the Holy Grail of life sciences, the identification of the basic building block of life. Never has a scientist been so truthful in capturing in words the flavor of his work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-double-helix-a-personal-account-of-the-discovery-of-the-structure-of-dna-james-d-watson-abridged/">The Double Helix: A Personal Account of the Discovery of the Structure of DNA &#8211; James D. Watson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blueprint : The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society &#8211; Nicholas A. Christakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For too long, scientists have focused on the dark side of our biological heritage: our capacity for aggression, cruelty, prejudice, and self-interest. But natural selection has given us a suite of beneficial social features, including our capacity for love, friendship, cooperation, and learning. Beneath all our inventions &#8212; our tools, farms, machines, cities, nations &#8212; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/">Blueprint : The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society &#8211; Nicholas A. Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For too long, scientists have focused on the dark side of our biological heritage: our capacity for aggression, cruelty, prejudice, and self-interest. But natural selection has given us a suite of beneficial social features, including our capacity for love, friendship, cooperation, and learning. Beneath all our inventions &#8212; our tools, farms, machines, cities, nations &#8212; we carry with us innate proclivities to make a good society.     </p>
<p>                    In Blueprint, Nicholas A. Christakis introduces the compelling idea that our genes affect not only our bodies and behaviors, but also the ways in which we make societies, ones that are surprisingly similar worldwide. With many vivid examples &#8212; including diverse historical and contemporary cultures, communities formed in the wake of shipwrecks, commune dwellers seeking utopia, online groups thrown together by design or involving artificially intelligent bots, and even the tender and complex social arrangements of elephants and dolphins that so resemble our own &#8212; Christakis shows that, despite a human history replete with violence, we cannot escape our social blueprint for goodness.     </p>
<p>                    In a world of increasing political and economic polarization, it&#8217;s tempting to ignore the positive role of our evolutionary past. But by exploring the ancient roots of goodness in civilization, Blueprint shows that our genes have shaped societies for our welfare and that, in a feedback loop stretching back many thousands of years, societies have shaped, and are still shaping, our genes today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/">Blueprint : The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society &#8211; Nicholas A. Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
