<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Vintage Crime Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/vintage-crime/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/vintage-crime/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Vintage Crime Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/vintage-crime/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Thursday Murder Club : The Record-Breaking Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Richard Osman</title>
		<link>/the-thursday-murder-club-the-record-breaking-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-richard-osman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-thursday-murder-club-the-record-breaking-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-richard-osman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Such a beacon of pleasure&#8217; KATE ATKINSON &#8216;So smart and funny. Deplorably good&#8217; IAN RANKIN &#8216;A gripping read&#8217; SUNDAY TIMES THE FIRST BOOK IN THE #1 BESTSELLING THURSDAY MURDER CLUB SERIES BY TV PRESENTER RICHARD OSMAN __________________________________ In a peaceful retirement village, four unlikely friends meet up once a week to investigate unsolved murders. But [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thursday-murder-club-the-record-breaking-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-richard-osman/">The Thursday Murder Club : The Record-Breaking Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Richard Osman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Such a beacon of pleasure&#8217; KATE ATKINSON<br />
                    &#8216;So smart and funny. Deplorably good&#8217; IAN RANKIN<br />
                    &#8216;A gripping read&#8217; SUNDAY TIMES</p>
<p>                    THE FIRST BOOK IN THE #1 BESTSELLING THURSDAY MURDER CLUB SERIES BY TV PRESENTER RICHARD OSMAN<br />
                    __________________________________</p>
<p>                    In a peaceful retirement village, four unlikely friends meet up once a week to investigate unsolved murders.</p>
<p>                    But when a brutal killing takes place on their very doorstep, the Thursday Murder Club find themselves in the middle of their first live case.</p>
<p>                    Elizabeth, Joyce, Ibrahim and Ron might be pushing eighty but they still have a few tricks up their sleeves.</p>
<p>                    Can our unorthodox but brilliant gang catch the killer before it&#8217;s too late?<br />
                    __________________________________</p>
<p>                    WHAT PEOPLE ARE SAYING ABOUT THE THURSDAY MURDER CLUB</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling, moving, laugh-out-loud funny&#8217; MARK BILLINGHAM</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A great read, I really enjoyed it&#8217; GRAHAM NORTON</p>
<p>                    &#8216;As the bodies pile up, and more is revealed of the lives and loves of Joyce, Ibrahim, Ron and Elizabeth, you can&#8217;t help cheering them on &#8211; and hoping to meet them again soon&#8217; THE TIMES, CRIME BOOK OF THE MONTH</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Mystery fans are going to be enthralled&#8217; HARLAN COBEN</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Pure escapism&#8217; THE GUARDIAN, BEST CRIME AND THRILLERS OF 2020</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the most enjoyable books of the year&#8217; DAILY EXPRESS</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Smart, compassionate, warm, moving and so VERY funny&#8217; MARIAN KEYES</p>
<p>                    &#8216;As gripping as it is funny&#8217; EVENING STANDARD</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Funny, clever and achingly British&#8217; ADAM KAY</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An exciting new talent in crime fiction&#8217; DAILY MAIL</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A warm, wise and witty warning never to underestimate the elderly&#8217; VAL MCDERMID</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Delight after delight from first page to last&#8217; RED MAGAZINE</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I completely fell in love with it&#8217; SHARI LAPENA</p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is properly brilliant. The pages fly and I can&#8217;t stop smiling&#8217; STEVE CAVANAGH</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Charming, clever debut&#8217; STYLIST</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I laughed my arse off&#8217; BELINDA BAUER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A witty and poignant tale&#8217; DAILY TELEGRAPH</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Clever, clever plot&#8217; FIONA BARTON</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An absolutely delightful read&#8217; PRIMA MAGAZINE</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Utterly charming&#8217; SARAH PINBOROUGH</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Funny and original&#8217; THE SUN</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Properly funny and totally charming&#8230; steeped in Agatha Christie joy&#8217; ARAMINTA HALL</p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is one of the most delightful novels of the year&#8217; DAILY MIRROR</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A bundle of joy&#8217; JANE FALLON</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thursday-murder-club-the-record-breaking-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-richard-osman/">The Thursday Murder Club : The Record-Breaking Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8211; Richard Osman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Death of a Gossip &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/death-of-a-gossip-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/death-of-a-gossip-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Travel to the Scotland Highlands with this classic Hamish Macbeth cozy mystery where an unladylike gossip columnist meets an untimely and watery death. From the author of the Agatha Raisin series. When society widow and gossip columnist Lady Jane Winters joined the fishing class, she wasted no time in ruffling the feathers&#8211;or was it the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-gossip-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Gossip &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Travel to the Scotland Highlands with this classic Hamish Macbeth cozy mystery where an unladylike gossip columnist meets an untimely and watery death. From the author of the Agatha Raisin series.<br />
                    When society widow and gossip columnist Lady Jane Winters joined the fishing class, she wasted no time in ruffling the feathers&#8211;or was it the fins?&#8211;of those around her. Among the victims of her sharp tongue and unladylike manner was Lochdubh Constable Hamish Macbeth. Yet not even Hamish thought someone would permanently silence Lady Jane&#8217;s shrills&#8211;until her strangled body is fished out of the river.<br />
                    Now with the help of the lovely Priscilla Halburton-Smythe, Hamish must angle through the choppy waters of the tattler&#8217;s life to find the murderer. But with a school of suspects who aren&#8217;t ready to talk and dead women telling no tales, Hamish may be in over his head, for he knows that secrets are dangerous, knowledge is power, and killers usually do strike again.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-gossip-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Gossip &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Death of a Policeman &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/death-of-a-policeman-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/death-of-a-policeman-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Travel to the Scotland Highlands with this classic Hamish Macbeth cozy mystery from the author of the Agatha Raisin series. Death of a Policeman: A Hamish Macbeth Mystery Local police stations all over the Scottish Highlands are being threatened with closure. This presents the perfect opportunity for Detective Chief Inspector Blair, who would love nothing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-policeman-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Policeman &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Travel to the Scotland Highlands with this classic Hamish Macbeth cozy mystery from the author of the Agatha Raisin series.     </p>
<p>                    Death of a Policeman: A Hamish Macbeth Mystery     </p>
<p>                    Local police stations all over the Scottish Highlands are being threatened with closure. This presents the perfect opportunity for Detective Chief Inspector Blair, who would love nothing more than to get rid of Sergeant Hamish Macbeth. Blair suggests that Cyril Sessions, a keen young police officer, visit the town of Lochdubh to monitor exactly what Macbeth does every day. Macbeth hears about Blair&#8217;s plan and is prepared to insure that Cyril returns back to headquarters with a full report. But Cyril is soon found dead and Hamish quickly becomes the prime suspect in his murder.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-policeman-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Policeman &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Death of a Hussy &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/death-of-a-hussy-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/death-of-a-hussy-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Splendid fun.&#8221; The New York Times Book Review A Hamish Macbeth mystery. Wealthy Maggie Baird is neither nice nor kind nor generous. Once she was beautiful, but now, although middle-aged, she retains the appetites of a beautiful woman. When Maggie&#8217;s car catches fire with her inside it, suspicion focuses on the five houseguests staying at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-hussy-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Hussy &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Splendid fun.&#8221; The New York Times Book Review<br />
                    A Hamish Macbeth mystery.<br />
                    Wealthy Maggie Baird is neither nice nor kind nor generous. Once she was beautiful, but now, although middle-aged, she retains the appetites of a beautiful woman. When Maggie&#8217;s car catches fire with her inside it, suspicion focuses on the five houseguests staying at Maggie&#8217;s luxurious Highlands cottage: her timid niece and four former lovers, once of whom Maggie had intended to pick for a husband. All five are impecunious. All five had ample opportunity to monkey with Maggie&#8217;s car. So finding who did it requires all Police Constable Hamish Macbeth&#8217;s extraordinary common sense and insight into human nature. And lazy lout though he may be, Hamish lets no grass grow under his feet when it comes to solving a murder. Especially when he may be the next target.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-hussy-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Hussy &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Death of a Greedy Woman &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/death-of-a-greedy-woman-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/death-of-a-greedy-woman-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Travel to the Scotland Highlands with this classic Hamish Macbeth cozy mystery from the author of the Agatha Raisin series. Death of a Greedy Woman: A Hamish Macbeth Mystery There&#8217;s not a cloud in Constable Hamish Macbeth&#8217;s sky, just plenty of warm sunshine and not quite enough of beautiful Priscilla Halburton-Smythe. But as eight hopeful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-greedy-woman-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Greedy Woman &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Travel to the Scotland Highlands with this classic Hamish Macbeth cozy mystery from the author of the Agatha Raisin series.     </p>
<p>                    Death of a Greedy Woman: A Hamish Macbeth Mystery     </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s not a cloud in Constable Hamish Macbeth&#8217;s sky, just plenty of warm sunshine and not quite enough of beautiful Priscilla Halburton-Smythe. But as eight hopeful members of the Checkmate Singles Club converge on Tommel Castle Hotel for a week of serious matchmaking, the clouds roll in. The four couples, carefully matched by dating director Maria Worth, immediately dislike each other. The arrival of Maria&#8217;s gross, greedy partner, Peta, kills the last vestige of romance. And as love goes out the window, murder comes in the door. Peta soon slurps up her last meal, and Hamish is left with a baffling puzzle: Who shared the fateful outing that left Peta dead with a big red apple in her mouth? Surely not of those singles&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-greedy-woman-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Greedy Woman &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Death of an Honest Man &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/death-of-an-honest-man-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/death-of-an-honest-man-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sergeant Hamish Macbeth &#8211; Scotland&#8217;s most quick-witted but unambitious policeman &#8211; returns for the latest mystery in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s New York Times bestselling series. Nobody loves an honest man, or that was what police sergeant Hamish Macbeth tried to tell newcomer Paul English. Paul attended church in Lochdubh. He told the minister, Mr. Wellington, that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-an-honest-man-m-c-beaton/">Death of an Honest Man &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sergeant Hamish Macbeth &#8211; Scotland&#8217;s most quick-witted but unambitious policeman &#8211; returns for the latest mystery in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s New York Times bestselling series.</p>
<p>                    Nobody loves an honest man, or that was what police sergeant Hamish Macbeth tried to tell newcomer Paul English. </p>
<p>                    Paul attended church in Lochdubh. He told the minister, Mr. Wellington, that his sermons were boring. He told tweedy Mrs. Wellington that she was too fat. Angela Brody was told her detective stories were pap for the masses and it was time she wrote literature instead. He accused Hamish of having dyed his fiery red hair. He told Jessie Currie &#8211; who repeated all the last words of her twin sister &#8211; that she needed psychiatric help.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I speak as I find,&#8217; he bragged. Voices saying, &#8216;I could kill that man,&#8217; could be heard from Lochdubh to Cnothan.</p>
<p>                    And someone did.</p>
<p>                    Now Hamish is faced with a bewildering array of suspects. And he&#8217;s lost the services of his clumsy policeman, Charlie, who has resigned from the force after throwing Chief Inspector Blair into the loch. Can Hamish find the killer on his own?</p>
<p>                    Praise for M. C. Beaton</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The much-loved Hamish Macbeth series . . . a beguiling blend of wry humour and sharp observations of rural life&#8217; The Good Book Guide</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s always a special treat to return to Lochdubh&#8217;   New York Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;First rate . . . deft social comedy and wonderfully realised atmosphere&#8217;   Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;M C Beaton&#8217;s Hamish Macbeth books are a delight: clever, intricate and  sardonic&#8217; Kerry Greenwood</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-an-honest-man-m-c-beaton/">Death of an Honest Man &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magpie Murders : the Sunday Times bestseller crime thriller with a fiendish twist &#8211; Anthony Horowitz</title>
		<link>/magpie-murders-the-sunday-times-bestseller-crime-thriller-with-a-fiendish-twist-anthony-horowitz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/magpie-murders-the-sunday-times-bestseller-crime-thriller-with-a-fiendish-twist-anthony-horowitz/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Want to read a great whodunnit? Anthony Horowitz has one for you: MAGPIE MURDERS. It&#8217;s as good as an Agatha Christie. Better, in some ways. Cleverer.&#8217; Stephen King &#8216;The finest crime novel of the year&#8217; Daily Mail ***** Seven for a mystery that needs to be solved . . . Editor Susan Ryland has worked [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magpie-murders-the-sunday-times-bestseller-crime-thriller-with-a-fiendish-twist-anthony-horowitz/">Magpie Murders : the Sunday Times bestseller crime thriller with a fiendish twist &#8211; Anthony Horowitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Want to read a great whodunnit? Anthony Horowitz has one for you: MAGPIE MURDERS. It&#8217;s as good as an Agatha Christie. Better, in some ways. Cleverer.&#8217; Stephen King</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The finest crime novel of the year&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    *****</p>
<p>                     Seven for a mystery that needs to be solved . . .<br />
                    Editor Susan Ryland has worked with bestselling crime writer Alan Conway for years. Readers love his detective, Atticus Pund, a celebrated solver of crimes in the sleepy English villages of the 1950s.<br />
                    But Conway&#8217;s latest tale of murder at Pye Hall is not quite what it seems. Yes, there are dead bodies and a host of intriguing suspects, but hidden in the pages of the manuscript lies another story: a tale written between the very words on the page, telling of real-life jealousy, greed, ruthless ambition and murder.<br />
                    From the creator of Midsomer Murders comes a fiendish mystery perfect for fans of Agatha Christie&#8217;s Miss Marple and Hercule Poirot.</p>
<p>                    *****</p>
<p>                    Praise for Magpie Murders &#8211; the gripping Sunday Times bestselling crime thriller:<br />
                    &#8216;Ingenious&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling and compelling with a stunning twist&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A stylish thriller&#8217; Sunday Mirror</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A cunning reinvention of the thriller&#8217; Mail on Sunday</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magpie-murders-the-sunday-times-bestseller-crime-thriller-with-a-fiendish-twist-anthony-horowitz/">Magpie Murders : the Sunday Times bestseller crime thriller with a fiendish twist &#8211; Anthony Horowitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Death of a Kingfisher &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/death-of-a-kingfisher-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/death-of-a-kingfisher-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Travel to the Scotland Highlands with this classic Hamish Macbeth cozy mystery from the author of the Agatha Raisin series. Death of a Kingfisher: A Hamish Macbeth Mystery When Scotland is hit by the recession, Police Constable Hamish Macbeth notices that the Highland people are forced to come up with inventive ways to lure tourists [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-kingfisher-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Kingfisher &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Travel to the Scotland Highlands with this classic Hamish Macbeth cozy mystery from the author of the Agatha Raisin series.     </p>
<p>                    Death of a Kingfisher: A Hamish Macbeth Mystery     </p>
<p>                    When Scotland is hit by the recession, Police Constable Hamish Macbeth notices that the Highland people are forced to come up with inventive ways to lure tourists to their sleepy towns. The quaint village of Braikie doesn&#8217;t have much to offer, other than a place of rare beauty called Buchan&#8217;s Wood, which was bequeathed to the town. The savvy local tourist director renames the woods &#8220;The Fairy Glen,&#8221; and has brochures printed with a beautiful photograph of a kingfisher rising from a pond on the cover.     </p>
<p>                    It isn&#8217;t long before coach tours begin to arrive. But just as the town&#8217;s luck starts to turn, a kingfisher is found hanging from a branch in the woods with a noose around its neck. As a wave of vandalism threatens to ruin Braikie forever, the town turns to Hamish Macbeth. And when violence strikes again, the lawman&#8217;s investigation quickly turns from animal cruelty to murder.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/death-of-a-kingfisher-m-c-beaton/">Death of a Kingfisher &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kingdom of the Blind : A Chief Inspector Gamache Novel &#8211; Louise Penny</title>
		<link>/kingdom-of-the-blind-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/kingdom-of-the-blind-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A December 2018 Indie Next Pick One of Kirkus Reviews&#8217; Best of 2018 Picks BookPage Best of the Year 2018 A LibraryReads Pick for November 2018 A LibraryReads Hall of Fame Winner Washington Post&#8217;s 10 Books to Read This November One of PopSugar&#8217;s Best Fall Books to Curl Up [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kingdom-of-the-blind-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny/">Kingdom of the Blind : A Chief Inspector Gamache Novel &#8211; Louise Penny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A December 2018 Indie Next Pick<br />
                    One of Kirkus Reviews&#8217; Best of 2018 Picks<br />
                    BookPage Best of the Year 2018<br />
                    A LibraryReads Pick for November 2018<br />
                    A LibraryReads Hall of Fame Winner<br />
                    Washington Post&#8217;s 10 Books to Read This November<br />
                    One of PopSugar&#8217;s Best Fall Books to Curl Up With </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A captivating, wintry whodunit.&#8221; &#8211;PEOPLE</p>
<p>                    Blockbuster bestselling author Louise Penny keeps readers eyes&#8217; glued to the page in Kingdom of the Blind, an &#8220;intriguing&#8230;and satisfying&#8221; (Publishers Weekly) novel about everyday life and ever-curious death in the village of Three Pines. </p>
<p>                    Why would a complete stranger name Detective Chief Armand Gamache one of the executors of her will? The will is so bizarre and includes such wildly unlikely bequests that Gamache suspects the woman was downright delusional. But what if, Gamache begins to ask himself, she was perfectly sane? When a dead body turns up in town, the terms of the will suddenly seem far more menacing. </p>
<p>                    &#8220;[An] intricately plotted escapist mystery.&#8221;&#8211;Popsugar </p>
<p>                    Meanwhile, the investigation into the events that led to Gamache&#8217;s suspension keeps deepening. Most of the opioids Gamache let slip though his hands&#8211;in order to bring down the big-city cartels&#8211;have been retrieved, but there is one devastating exception. Soon, he enters a race against time to locate the deadly missing drug. As he uses increasingly audacious, even desperate, measures to retrieve it, Gamache begins to see his own blind spots&#8230;and the terrible truth that may be hiding in plain sight.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kingdom-of-the-blind-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny/">Kingdom of the Blind : A Chief Inspector Gamache Novel &#8211; Louise Penny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Still Life : A Chief Inspector Gamache Novel &#8211; Louise Penny</title>
		<link>/still-life-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/still-life-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Still Life, bestselling author Louise Penny introduces Monsieur L&#8217;Inspecteur Armand Gamache of the Surete du Quebec, a modern Poirot who anchors this beloved traditional mystery series Winner of the New Blood Dagger, Arthur Ellis, Barry, Anthony, and Dilys awards. Chief Inspector Armand Gamache of the Surêté du Québec and his team of investigators are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/still-life-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny-2/">Still Life : A Chief Inspector Gamache Novel &#8211; Louise Penny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Still Life, bestselling author Louise Penny introduces Monsieur L&#8217;Inspecteur Armand Gamache of the Surete du Quebec, a modern Poirot who anchors this beloved traditional mystery series     </p>
<p>                     Winner of the New Blood Dagger, Arthur Ellis, Barry, Anthony, and Dilys awards.     </p>
<p>                     Chief Inspector Armand Gamache of the Surêté du Québec and his team of investigators are called in to the scene of a suspicious death in a rural village south of Montreal. Jane Neal, a local fixture in the tiny hamlet of Three Pines, just north of the U.S. border, has been found dead in the woods. The locals are certain it&#8217;s a tragic hunting accident and nothing more, but Gamache smells something foul in these remote woods, and is soon certain that Jane Neal died at the hands of someone much more sinister than a careless bowhunter.     </p>
<p>                     Still Life introduces not only an engaging series hero in Inspector Gamache, who commands his forces&#8212;and this series&#8212;with integrity and quiet courage, but also a winning and talented new writer of traditional mysteries in the person of Louise Penny.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/still-life-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny-2/">Still Life : A Chief Inspector Gamache Novel &#8211; Louise Penny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Legacy of Spies &#8211; John Le Carré</title>
		<link>/a-legacy-of-spies-john-le-carre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-legacy-of-spies-john-le-carre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chosen as a Book of the Year in The Times Literary Supplement, the Evening Standard, the Daily Telegraph, the Guardian, The Times &#8216;A brilliant novel of deception, love and trust to join his supreme cannon&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Vintage le Carre. Immensely clever, breathtaking. Really, not since The Spy Who Came in from the Cold has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-legacy-of-spies-john-le-carre/">A Legacy of Spies &#8211; John Le Carré</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chosen as a Book of the Year in The Times Literary Supplement, the Evening Standard, the Daily Telegraph, the Guardian, The Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A brilliant novel of deception, love and trust to join his supreme cannon&#8217; Evening Standard</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Vintage le Carre. Immensely clever, breathtaking. Really, not since The Spy Who Came in from the Cold has le Carre exercised his gift as a storyteller so powerfully and to such thrilling effect&#8217; John Banville, Guardian</p>
<p>                    Peter Guillam, former disciple of George Smiley in the British Secret Service, has long retired to Brittany when a letter arrives, summoning him to London. The reason? Cold War ghosts have come back to haunt him. Intelligence operations that were once the toast of the Service are to be dissected by a generation with no memory of the Berlin Wall.  Somebody must pay for innocent blood spilt in the name of the greater good . . .</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Utterly engrossing and perfectly pitched. There is only one le Carre. Eloquent, subtle, sublimely paced&#8217;  Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Splendid, fast-paced, riveting&#8217; Andrew Marr, Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Remarkable. It gives the reader, at long last, pieces of a jigsaw puzzle that have been missing for 54 years. Like wine, le Carre&#8217;s writing has got richer with age&#8217;  The Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Perhaps the most significant novelist of the second half of the 20th century in Britain. He&#8217;s in the first rank&#8217;  Ian McEwan</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of those writers who will be read a century from now&#8217;  Robert Harris</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-legacy-of-spies-john-le-carre/">A Legacy of Spies &#8211; John Le Carré</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Partners in Crime : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Collection &#8211; Agatha Christie</title>
		<link>/partners-in-crime-a-tommy-tuppence-collection-agatha-christie/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/partners-in-crime-a-tommy-tuppence-collection-agatha-christie/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Agatha Christie&#8217;s complete Tommy and Tuppence short story collection, reissued with a striking new cover designed to appeal to the latest generation of Agatha Christie fans and book lovers. Tommy and Tuppence Beresford were restless for adventure, so when they were asked to take over Blunt&#8217;s International Detective Agency, they leapt at the chance. After [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/partners-in-crime-a-tommy-tuppence-collection-agatha-christie/">Partners in Crime : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Collection &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Agatha Christie&#8217;s complete Tommy and Tuppence short story collection, reissued with a striking new cover designed to appeal to the latest generation of Agatha Christie fans and book lovers.    </p>
<p>                              Tommy and Tuppence Beresford were restless for adventure, so when they were asked to take over Blunt&#8217;s International Detective Agency, they leapt at the chance.    </p>
<p>                              After their triumphant recovery of a pink pearl, intriguing cases kept on coming their way: a stabbing on Sunningdale golf course; cryptic messages in the personal columns of newspapers; and even a box of poisoned chocolates.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/partners-in-crime-a-tommy-tuppence-collection-agatha-christie/">Partners in Crime : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Collection &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Brutal Telling &#8211; Louise Penny</title>
		<link>/the-brutal-telling-louise-penny/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-brutal-telling-louise-penny/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chaos is coming, old son. With those words the peace of Three Pines is shattered. As families prepare to head back to the city and children say goodbye to summer, a stranger is found murdered in the village bistro and antiques store. Once again, Chief Inspector Gamache and his team are called in to strip [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brutal-telling-louise-penny/">The Brutal Telling &#8211; Louise Penny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chaos is coming, old son. </p>
<p>                    With those words the peace of Three Pines is shattered. As families prepare to head back to the city and children say goodbye to summer, a stranger is found murdered in the village bistro and antiques store. Once again, Chief Inspector Gamache and his team are called in to strip back layers of lies, exposing both treasures and rancid secrets buried in the wilderness. </p>
<p>                    No one admits to knowing the murdered man, but as secrets are revealed, chaos begins to close in on the beloved bistro owner, Olivier. How did he make such a spectacular success of his business? What past did he leave behind and why has he buried himself in this tiny village? And why does every lead in the investigation find its way back to him? </p>
<p>                    As Olivier grows more frantic, a trail of clues and treasures&#8211; from first editions of Charlotte&#8217;s Web and Jane Eyre to a spider web with the word WOE woven in it&#8211;lead the Chief Inspector deep into the woods and across the continent in search of the truth, and finally back to Three Pines as the little village braces for the truth and the final, brutal telling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brutal-telling-louise-penny/">The Brutal Telling &#8211; Louise Penny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Postern of Fate : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</title>
		<link>/postern-of-fate-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/postern-of-fate-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A poisoning many years ago may not have been accidental after all&#8230; Tommy and Tuppence Beresford have just become the proud owners of an old house in an English village. Along with the property, they have inherited some worthless bric-a-brac, including a collection of antique books. While rustling through a copy of The Black Arrow, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/postern-of-fate-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/">Postern of Fate : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A poisoning many years ago may not have been accidental after all&#8230;    </p>
<p>                              Tommy and Tuppence Beresford have just become the proud owners of an old house in an English village. Along with the property, they have inherited some worthless bric-a-brac, including a collection of antique books. While rustling through a copy of The Black Arrow, Tuppence comes upon a series of apparently random underlinings.    </p>
<p>                              However, when she writes down the letters, they spell out a very disturbing message:<br />
                    M a r y &#8211; J o r d a n &#8211; d i d &#8211; n o t &#8211; d i e &#8211; n a t u r a l l y&#8230;<br />
                    And sixty years after their first murder, Mary Jordan&#8217;s enemies are still ready to kill&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/postern-of-fate-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/">Postern of Fate : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Adversary : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</title>
		<link>/the-secret-adversary-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-adversary-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Agatha Christie&#8217;s first Tommy &#038; Tuppence book is a thrill-packed novel of international intrigue, murder and suspense. Tommy and Tuppence, two young people short of money and restless for excitement, embark on a daring business scheme &#8211; Young Adventurers Ltd. Their advertisement says they are &#8216;willing to do anything, go anywhere&#8217;. But their first assignment, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-adversary-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/">The Secret Adversary : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Agatha Christie&#8217;s first Tommy &#038; Tuppence book is a thrill-packed novel of international intrigue, murder and suspense.    </p>
<p>                              Tommy and Tuppence, two young people short of money and restless for excitement, embark on a daring business scheme &#8211; Young Adventurers Ltd.    </p>
<p>                              Their advertisement says they are &#8216;willing to do anything, go anywhere&#8217;. But their first assignment, for the sinister Mr Whittington, plunges them into more danger than they ever imagined&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-adversary-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/">The Secret Adversary : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Agent Running in the Field &#8211; John le Carre</title>
		<link>/agent-running-in-the-field-john-le-carre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/agent-running-in-the-field-john-le-carre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;No other writer has charted &#8211; pitilessly for politicians but thrillingly for readers &#8211; the public and secret histories of his times&#8217; Guardian ________________________________ Nat, a 47 year-old veteran of Britain&#8217;s Secret Intelligence Service, believes his years as an agent runner are over. He is back in London with his wife, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/agent-running-in-the-field-john-le-carre/">Agent Running in the Field &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;No other writer has charted &#8211; pitilessly for politicians but thrillingly for readers &#8211; the public and secret histories of his times&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    ________________________________</p>
<p>                    Nat, a 47 year-old veteran of Britain&#8217;s Secret Intelligence Service, believes his years as an agent runner are over.  He is back in London with his wife, the long-suffering Prue.  But with the growing threat from Moscow Centre, the office has one more job for him.  Nat is to take over The Haven, a defunct substation of London General with a rag-tag band of spies.  The only bright light on the team is young Florence, who has her eye on Russia Department and a Ukrainian oligarch with a finger in the Russia pie.  </p>
<p>                    Nat is not only a spy, he is a passionate badminton player.  His regular Monday evening opponent is half his age:  the introspective and solitary Ed.  Ed hates Brexit, hates Trump and hates his job at some soulless media agency.  And it is Ed, of all unlikely people, who will take Prue, Florence and Nat himself down the path of political anger that will ensnare them all.  Agent Running in the Field is a chilling portrait of our time, now heartbreaking, now darkly humorous, told to us with unflagging tension by the greatest chronicler of our age.<br />
                    _______________________________</p>
<p>                    &#8216;John le Carre is as recognisable a writer as Dickens or Austen&#8217; Financial Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;No writer has ever been better at turning the act of two people talking politely to each other across a desk into a blood sport&#8217; Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/agent-running-in-the-field-john-le-carre/">Agent Running in the Field &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>By the Pricking of My Thumbs : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</title>
		<link>/by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An old woman in a nursing home speaks of a child buried behind the fireplace&#8230; When Tommy and Tuppence visited an elderly aunt in her gothic nursing home, they thought nothing of her mistrust of the doctors; after all, Ada was a very difficult old lady. But when Mrs Lockett mentioned a poisoned mushroom stew [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/">By the Pricking of My Thumbs : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An old woman in a nursing home speaks of a child buried behind the fireplace&#8230;    </p>
<p>                              When Tommy and Tuppence visited an elderly aunt in her gothic nursing home, they thought nothing of her mistrust of the doctors; after all, Ada was a very difficult old lady.    </p>
<p>                              But when Mrs Lockett mentioned a poisoned mushroom stew and Mrs Lancaster talked about &#8216;something behind the fireplace&#8217;, Tommy and Tuppence found themselves caught up in an unexpected adventure involving possible black magic&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/">By the Pricking of My Thumbs : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Maltese Falcon &#8211; Dashiell Hammett</title>
		<link>/the-maltese-falcon-dashiell-hammett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-maltese-falcon-dashiell-hammett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the greatest crime novels of the 20th century. &#8216;His name remains one of the most important and recognisable in the crime fiction genre. Hammett set the standard for much of the work that would follow&#8217; Independent Sam Spade is hired by the fragrant Miss Wonderley to track down her sister, who has eloped [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-maltese-falcon-dashiell-hammett/">The Maltese Falcon &#8211; Dashiell Hammett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the greatest crime novels of the 20th century.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;His name remains one of the most important and recognisable in the crime fiction genre. Hammett set the standard for much of the work that would follow&#8217; Independent    </p>
<p>                    Sam Spade is hired by the fragrant Miss Wonderley to track down her sister, who has eloped with a louse called Floyd Thursby. But Miss Wonderley is in fact the beautiful and treacherous Brigid O&#8217;Shaughnessy, and when Spade&#8217;s partner Miles Archer is shot while on Thursby&#8217;s trail, Spade finds himself both hunter and hunted: can he track down the jewel-encrusted bird, a treasure worth killing for, before the Fat Man finds him?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-maltese-falcon-dashiell-hammett/">The Maltese Falcon &#8211; Dashiell Hammett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Still Life : A Chief Inspector Gamache Novel &#8211; Louise Penny</title>
		<link>/still-life-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/still-life-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Still Life, bestselling author Louise Penny introduces Monsieur L&#8217;Inspecteur Armand Gamache of the Surete du Quebec, a modern Poirot who anchors this beloved traditional mystery series Winner of the New Blood Dagger, Arthur Ellis, Barry, Anthony, and Dilys awards. Chief Inspector Armand Gamache of the Surêté du Québec and his team of investigators are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/still-life-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny/">Still Life : A Chief Inspector Gamache Novel &#8211; Louise Penny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Still Life, bestselling author Louise Penny introduces Monsieur L&#8217;Inspecteur Armand Gamache of the Surete du Quebec, a modern Poirot who anchors this beloved traditional mystery series     </p>
<p>                     Winner of the New Blood Dagger, Arthur Ellis, Barry, Anthony, and Dilys awards.     </p>
<p>                     Chief Inspector Armand Gamache of the Surêté du Québec and his team of investigators are called in to the scene of a suspicious death in a rural village south of Montreal. Jane Neal, a local fixture in the tiny hamlet of Three Pines, just north of the U.S. border, has been found dead in the woods. The locals are certain it&#8217;s a tragic hunting accident and nothing more, but Gamache smells something foul in these remote woods, and is soon certain that Jane Neal died at the hands of someone much more sinister than a careless bowhunter.     </p>
<p>                     Still Life introduces not only an engaging series hero in Inspector Gamache, who commands his forces&#8212;and this series&#8212;with integrity and quiet courage, but also a winning and talented new writer of traditional mysteries in the person of Louise Penny.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/still-life-a-chief-inspector-gamache-novel-louise-penny/">Still Life : A Chief Inspector Gamache Novel &#8211; Louise Penny</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
