<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Teacher Training Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/teacher-training/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/teacher-training/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Teacher Training Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/teacher-training/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teacher Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Staff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching    </p>
<p>                     Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically and mentally ill, things have gone too far. Unsurprisingly, these effects are highest in difficult-to-fill positions such as math, science, and foreign languages, and in urban areas and secondary classrooms-places where we need our teachers to be especially motivated and engaged. This book offers a path to resiliency to help teachers weather the storms and bounce back-and work toward banishing the rain for good.    </p>
<p>                     This actionable framework gives you concrete steps toward rediscovering yourself, your energy, and your passion for teaching. You&#8217;ll learn how a simple shift in mindset can affect your outlook, and how taking care of yourself physically, mentally, and emotionally is one of the most important things you can do. The companion workbook helps you put the framework into action, streamlining your way toward renewal and strength.    </p>
<p>                    Cultivate resilience with a four-part framework based on 12 key habits<br />
                    Uncover your true self, understand emotions, and use your energy where it counts<br />
                    Adopt a mindful, story-telling approach to communication and community building<br />
                    Keep learning, playing, and creating to create an environment of collective celebration    </p>
<p>                     By cultivating resilience in schools, we help ensure that we are working in, teaching in, and leading organizations where every child thrives, and where the potential of every child is recognized and nurtured. Onward provides a step-by-step plan for reigniting that spark.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
