<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Electronics Engineering Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/electronics-engineering/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/electronics-engineering/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Electronics Engineering Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/electronics-engineering/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Soul of a New Machine &#8211; Tracy Kidder</title>
		<link>/the-soul-of-a-new-machine-tracy-kidder/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-soul-of-a-new-machine-tracy-kidder/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tracy Kidder&#8217;s &#8220;riveting&#8221; (Washington Post) story of one company&#8217;s efforts to bring a new microcomputer to market won both the Pulitzer Prize and the National Book Award and has become essential reading for understanding the history of the American tech industry. Computers have changed since 1981, when The Soul of a New Machine first examined [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-soul-of-a-new-machine-tracy-kidder/">The Soul of a New Machine &#8211; Tracy Kidder</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tracy Kidder&#8217;s &#8220;riveting&#8221; (Washington Post) story of one company&#8217;s efforts to bring a new microcomputer to market won both the Pulitzer Prize and the National Book Award and has become essential reading for understanding the history of the American tech industry.  Computers have changed since 1981, when The Soul of a New Machine first examined the culture of the computer revolution. What has not changed is the feverish pace of the high-tech industry, the go-for-broke approach to business that has caused so many computer companies to win big (or go belly up), and the cult of pursuing mind-bending technological innovations.<br />
                    The Soul of a New Machine is an essential chapter in the history of the machine that revolutionized the world in the twentieth century. &#8220;Fascinating&#8230;A surprisingly gripping account of people at work.&#8221; &#8211;Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-soul-of-a-new-machine-tracy-kidder/">The Soul of a New Machine &#8211; Tracy Kidder</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper : How Innovation Keeps Proving the Catastrophists Wrong &#8211; Robert Bryce (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nanotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the face of today&#8217;s environmental and economic challenges, doomsayers preach that the only way to stave off disaster is for humans to reverse course: to de-industrialize, re-localize, ban the use of modern energy sources, and forswear prosperity. But in this provocative and optimistic rebuke to the catastrophists, Robert Bryce shows how innovation and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/">Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper : How Innovation Keeps Proving the Catastrophists Wrong &#8211; Robert Bryce (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the face of today&#8217;s environmental and economic challenges, doomsayers preach that the only way to stave off disaster is for humans to reverse course: to de-industrialize, re-localize, ban the use of modern energy sources, and forswear prosperity. But in this provocative and optimistic rebuke to the catastrophists, Robert Bryce shows how innovation and the inexorable human desire to make things Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper is providing consumers with Cheaper and more abundant energy, Faster computing, Lighter vehicles, and myriad other goods. That same desire is fostering unprecedented prosperity, greater liberty, and yes, better environmental protection.Utilizing on-the-ground reporting from Ottawa to Panama City and Pittsburgh to Bakersfield, Bryce shows how we have, for centuries, been pushing for Smaller Faster solutions to our problems. From the vacuum tube, mass-produced fertilizer, and the printing press to mobile phones, nanotech, and advanced drill rigs, Bryce demonstrates how cutting-edge companies and breakthrough technologies have created a world in which people are living longer, freer, healthier, lives than at any time in human history.The push toward Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper is happening across multiple sectors. Bryce profiles innovative individuals and companies, from long-established ones like Ford and Intel to upstarts like Aquion Energy and Khan Academy. And he zeroes in on the energy industry, proving that the future belongs to the high power density sources that can provide the enormous quantities of energy the world demands.The tools we need to save the planet aren&#8217;t to be found in the technologies or lifestyles of the past. Nor must we sacrifice prosperity and human progress to ensure our survival. The catastrophists have been wrong since the days of Thomas Malthus. This is the time to embrace the innovators and businesses all over the world who are making things Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/">Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper : How Innovation Keeps Proving the Catastrophists Wrong &#8211; Robert Bryce (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Valley of Genius : The Uncensored History of Silicon Valley (As Told by the Hackers, Founders, and Freaks Who Made It Boom) &#8211; Adam Fisher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/valley-of-genius-the-uncensored-history-of-silicon-valley-as-told-by-the-hackers-founders-and-freaks-who-made-it-boom-adam-fisher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/valley-of-genius-the-uncensored-history-of-silicon-valley-as-told-by-the-hackers-founders-and-freaks-who-made-it-boom-adam-fisher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rarely has one economy asserted itself as swiftly&#8211;and as aggressively&#8211;as the entity we now know as Silicon Valley. Built with a seemingly permanent culture of reinvention, Silicon Valley does not fight change; it embraces it, and now powers the American economy and global innovation. So how did this omnipotent and ever-morphing place come to be? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/valley-of-genius-the-uncensored-history-of-silicon-valley-as-told-by-the-hackers-founders-and-freaks-who-made-it-boom-adam-fisher-abridged/">Valley of Genius : The Uncensored History of Silicon Valley (As Told by the Hackers, Founders, and Freaks Who Made It Boom) &#8211; Adam Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rarely has one economy asserted itself as swiftly&#8211;and as aggressively&#8211;as the entity we now know as Silicon Valley. Built with a seemingly permanent culture of reinvention, Silicon Valley does not fight change; it embraces it, and now powers the American economy and global innovation.    </p>
<p>                    So how did this omnipotent and ever-morphing place come to be? It was not by planning. It was, like many an empire before it, part luck, part timing, and part ambition. And part pure, unbridled genius&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on over two hundred in-depth interviews, VALLEY OF GENIUS takes readers from the dawn of the personal computer and the internet, through the heyday of the web, up to the very moment when our current technological reality was invented. The book interweaves stories of invention and betrayal, overnight success and underground exploits, to tell the story of Silicon Valley like it has never been told before. These are the stories that Valley insiders tell each other: the tall tales that are all, improbably, true.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/valley-of-genius-the-uncensored-history-of-silicon-valley-as-told-by-the-hackers-founders-and-freaks-who-made-it-boom-adam-fisher-abridged/">Valley of Genius : The Uncensored History of Silicon Valley (As Told by the Hackers, Founders, and Freaks Who Made It Boom) &#8211; Adam Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hit Refresh : A Memoir by Microsoft&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Satya Nadella (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hit-refresh-a-memoir-by-microsofts-ceo-satya-nadella-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hit-refresh-a-memoir-by-microsofts-ceo-satya-nadella-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Quest to Rediscover Microsoft&#8217;s Soul and Imagine a Better Future for Everyone Microsoft&#8217;s CEO tells the inside story of the company&#8217;s continuing transformation, while tracing his own journey from a childhood in India to leading some of the most significant changes of the digital era. LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hit-refresh-a-memoir-by-microsofts-ceo-satya-nadella-abridged/">Hit Refresh : A Memoir by Microsoft&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Satya Nadella (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Quest to Rediscover Microsoft&#8217;s Soul and Imagine a Better Future for Everyone    </p>
<p>                                Microsoft&#8217;s CEO tells the inside story of the company&#8217;s continuing transformation, while tracing his own journey from a childhood in India to leading some of the most significant changes of the digital era.    </p>
<p>                                LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD    </p>
<p>                              Satya Nadella grew up in India, studied in the US and went on to become Microsoft&#8217;s third CEO after Bill Gates and Steve Ballmer. In Hit Refresh he offers a unique view of the transformation happening inside one of the world&#8217;s most iconic tech companies, and the arrival of the most exciting and disruptive wave of technology humankind has experienced &#8211; including artificial intelligence, mixed reality, and quantum computing.    </p>
<p>                              Nadella examines how people, organisations and societies can and must transform &#8211; &#8216;hit refresh&#8217; &#8211; in their persistent quest for new energy, new ideas, and continued relevance and renewal. Yet at its core, this book is about humans, and how one of our essential qualities &#8211; empathy &#8211; will become ever more valuable in a world where technological advancement will alter the status quo as never before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hit-refresh-a-memoir-by-microsofts-ceo-satya-nadella-abridged/">Hit Refresh : A Memoir by Microsoft&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Satya Nadella (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Geeks Bearing Gifts &#8211; Jeff Jarvis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/geeks-bearing-gifts-jeff-jarvis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/geeks-bearing-gifts-jeff-jarvis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has disrupted the news industry&#8211;its relationships, forms, and business models&#8211;but it also provides no end of opportunities for improving, expanding, reimagining, and sustaining journalism. Geeks Bearing Gifts: Imagining New Futures for News is a creative, thought-provoking and entertaining exploration of the possible future(s) of news by Professor Jeff Jarvis, who leads the Tow-Knight Center [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/geeks-bearing-gifts-jeff-jarvis-abridged/">Geeks Bearing Gifts &#8211; Jeff Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has disrupted the news industry&#8211;its relationships, forms, and business models&#8211;but it also provides no end of opportunities for improving, expanding, reimagining, and sustaining journalism. Geeks Bearing Gifts: Imagining New Futures for News is a creative, thought-provoking and entertaining exploration of the possible future(s) of news by Professor Jeff Jarvis, who leads the Tow-Knight Center for Entrepreneurial Journalism at the CUNY Graduate School of Journalism.     </p>
<p>                    To Jarvis, journalism helps a community better organize its knowledge so it can better organize itself: &#8220;But we in the field came to define ourselves less by our value and mission and more by our media and tools&#8211;ink on pulp or slick paper, sound or images over airwaves. Now we have new tools to exploit. Those tools require new skills and create new value. But at the core, we serve citizens and communities.&#8221; He offers not a single definitive future of journalism and news, but a range of possibilities depending on how journalists and journalism evolve&#8211;with the help of the &#8220;geeks&#8221; whose advances in media technology offer many opportunities for journalists and media entrepreneurs who are willing to think creatively and take risks.     </p>
<p>                    Jarvis, one of the preeminent voices on emerging forms of journalism, news delivery, and community engagement, advises many media companies, startups, and foundations. He is a former president and creative director of Advance.net, the online arm of Advance Publications, and was the creator and founding editor of Entertainment Weekly; Sunday editor and associate publisher of the New York Daily News; TV critic for TV Guide and People; a columnist on the San Francisco Examiner; and assistant city editor and reporter for the Chicago Tribune.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/geeks-bearing-gifts-jeff-jarvis-abridged/">Geeks Bearing Gifts &#8211; Jeff Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dance & Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital TV & Media Centres: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Radio & Television Industry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How big data is transforming the creative industries, and how those industries can use lessons from Netflix, Amazon, and Apple to fight back. &#8220;[The authors explain] gently yet firmly exactly how the internet threatens established ways and what can and cannot be done about it. Their book should be required for anyone who wishes to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/">Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How big data is transforming the creative industries, and how those industries can use lessons from Netflix, Amazon, and Apple to fight back.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;[The authors explain] gently yet firmly exactly how the internet threatens established ways and what can and cannot be done about it. Their book should be required for anyone who wishes to believe that nothing much has changed.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;The Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Packed with examples, from the nimble-footed who reacted quickly to adapt their businesses, to laggards who lost empires.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    Traditional network television programming has always followed the same script: executives approve a pilot, order a trial number of episodes, and broadcast them, expecting viewers to watch a given show on their television sets at the same time every week. But then came Netflix&#8217;s House of Cards. Netflix gauged the show&#8217;s potential from data it had gathered about subscribers&#8217; preferences, ordered two seasons without seeing a pilot, and uploaded the first thirteen episodes all at once for viewers to watch whenever they wanted on the devices of their choice.     </p>
<p>                    In this book, Michael Smith and Rahul Telang, experts on entertainment analytics, show how the success of House of Cards upended the film and TV industries&#8211;and how companies like Amazon and Apple are changing the rules in other entertainment industries, notably publishing and music. We&#8217;re living through a period of unprecedented technological disruption in the entertainment industries. Just about everything is affected: pricing, production, distribution, piracy. Smith and Telang discuss niche products and the long tail, product differentiation, price discrimination, and incentives for users not to steal content. To survive and succeed, businesses have to adapt rapidly and creatively. Smith and Telang explain how.    </p>
<p>                    How can companies discover who their customers are, what they want, and how much they are willing to pay for it? Data. The entertainment industries, must learn to play a little &#8220;moneyball.&#8221; The bottom line: follow the data.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/">Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
