<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Linguistics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/linguistics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/linguistics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Linguistics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/linguistics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Sleep, There are Snakes : Life and Language in the Amazonian Jungle &#8211; Daniel Everett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dont-sleep-there-are-snakes-life-and-language-in-the-amazonian-jungle-daniel-everett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Indigenous Peoples]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dont-sleep-there-are-snakes-life-and-language-in-the-amazonian-jungle-daniel-everett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Although Daniel Everett was a missionary, far from converting the Pirahas, they converted him. He shows the slow, meticulous steps by which he gradually mastered their language and his gradual realisation that its unusual nature closely reflected its speakers&#8217; startlingly original perceptions of the world. Everett describes how he began to realise that his discoveries [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-sleep-there-are-snakes-life-and-language-in-the-amazonian-jungle-daniel-everett-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Sleep, There are Snakes : Life and Language in the Amazonian Jungle &#8211; Daniel Everett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although Daniel Everett was a missionary, far from converting the Pirahas, they converted him. He shows the slow, meticulous steps by which he gradually mastered their language and his gradual realisation that its unusual nature closely reflected its speakers&#8217; startlingly original perceptions of the world.    </p>
<p>                    Everett describes how he began to realise that his discoveries about the Piraha language opened up a new way of understanding how language works in our minds and in our lives, and that this way was utterly at odds with Noam Chomsky&#8217;s universally accepted linguistic theories. The perils of passionate academic opposition were then swiftly conjoined to those of the Amazon in a debate whose outcome has yet to be won. Everett&#8217;s views are most recently discussed in Tom Wolfe&#8217;s bestselling The Kingdom of Speech.    </p>
<p>                    Adventure, personal enlightenment and the makings of a scientific revolution proceed together in this vivid, funny and moving book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-sleep-there-are-snakes-life-and-language-in-the-amazonian-jungle-daniel-everett-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Sleep, There are Snakes : Life and Language in the Amazonian Jungle &#8211; Daniel Everett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Talk : The Science of Conversation &#8211; Elizabeth Stokoe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/talk-the-science-of-conversation-elizabeth-stokoe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Phonetics, Phonology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/talk-the-science-of-conversation-elizabeth-stokoe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We spend much of our days talking. Yet we know little about the conversational engine that drives our everyday lives. We are pushed and pulled around by language far more than we realize, yet are seduced by stereotypes and myths about communication. This book will change the way you think about talk. It will explain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/talk-the-science-of-conversation-elizabeth-stokoe-abridged/">Talk : The Science of Conversation &#8211; Elizabeth Stokoe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We spend much of our days talking. Yet we know little about the conversational engine that drives our everyday lives. We are pushed and pulled around by language far more than we realize, yet are seduced by stereotypes and myths about communication.    </p>
<p>                    This book will change the way you think about talk. It will explain the big pay-offs to understanding conversation scientifically.     </p>
<p>                    Elizabeth Stokoe, a social psychologist, has spent over twenty years collecting and analysing real conversations across settings as varied as first dates, crisis negotiation, sales encounters and medical communication. This book describes some of the findings of her own research, and that of other conversation analysts around the world.     </p>
<p>                    Through numerous examples from real interactions between friends, partners, colleagues, police officers, mediators, doctors and many others, you will learn that some of what you think you know about talk is wrong. But you will also uncover fresh insights about how to have better conversations &#8211; using the evidence from fifty years of research about the science of talk.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/talk-the-science-of-conversation-elizabeth-stokoe-abridged/">Talk : The Science of Conversation &#8211; Elizabeth Stokoe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life. Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211; probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life.     </p>
<p>                    Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of<br />
                    nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211;<br />
                    probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine rock formations and fossil charcoals<br />
                    all tell the same story. High oxygen levels may also explain the global firestorm that contributed to the<br />
                    demise of the dinosaurs after the asteroid impact.    </p>
<p>                    The strange and profound effects that oxygen has had on the evolution of life pose a riddle, which this book<br />
                    sets out to answer. Oxygen is a toxic gas. Divers breathing pure oxygen at depth suffer from convulsions<br />
                    and lung injury. Fruit flies raised at twice normal atmospheric levels of oxygen live half as long as their<br />
                    siblings. Reactive forms of oxygen, known as free radicals, are thought to cause ageing in people. Yet if<br />
                    atmospheric oxygen reached 35 per cent in the Carboniferous, why did it promote exuberant growth,<br />
                    instead of rapid ageing and death?    </p>
<p>                    Oxygen takes the reader on an enthralling journey, as gripping as a thriller, as it unravels the unexpected<br />
                    ways in which oxygen spurred the evolution of life and death. The book explains far more than the size of<br />
                    ancient insects: it shows how oxygen underpins the origin of biological complexity, the birth of photosynthesis, the sudden evolution of animals, the need for two sexes, the accelerated ageing of cloned animals like Dolly the sheep, and the surprisingly long lives of bats and birds.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on this grand evolutionary canvas, Oxygen offers fresh perspectives on our own lives and deaths,<br />
                    explaining modern killer diseases, why we age, and what we can do about it. Advancing revelatory new ideas,<br />
                    following chains of evidence, the book ranges through many disciplines, from environmental sciences to<br />
                    molecular medicine. The result is a captivating vision of contemporary science and a humane synthesis of our<br />
                    place in nature. This remarkable book might just redefine the way we think about the world.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reader, Come Home : The Reading Brain in a Digital World &#8211; Maryanne Wolf (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed Proust and the Squid follows up with a lively, ambitious, and deeply informative book that considers the future of the reading brain and our capacity for critical thinking, empathy, and reflection as we become increasingly dependent on digital technologies. A decade ago, Maryanne Wolf&#8217;s Proust and the Squid revealed what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/">Reader, Come Home : The Reading Brain in a Digital World &#8211; Maryanne Wolf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed Proust and the Squid follows up with a lively, ambitious, and deeply informative book that considers the future of the reading brain and our capacity for critical thinking, empathy, and reflection as we become increasingly dependent on digital technologies.    </p>
<p>                    A decade ago, Maryanne Wolf&#8217;s Proust and the Squid revealed what we know about how the brain learns to read and how reading changes the way we think and feel. Since then, the ways we process written language have changed dramatically with many concerned about both their own changes and that of children. New research on the reading brain chronicles these changes in the brains of children and adults as they learn to read while immersed in a digitally dominated medium.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing deeply on this research, this book comprises a series of letters Wolf writes to us&#8211;her beloved readers&#8211;to describe her concerns and her hopes about what is happening to the reading brain as it unavoidably changes to adapt to digital mediums. Wolf raises difficult questions, including: Will children learn to incorporate the full range of deep reading processes that are at the core of the expert reading brain?Will the mix of a seemingly infinite set of distractions for children&#8217;s attention and their quick access to immediate, voluminous information alter their ability to think for themselves?With information at their fingertips, will the next generation learn to build their own storehouse of knowledge, which could impede the ability to make analogies and draw inferences from what they know?Will all these influences change the formation in children and the use in adults of slower cognitive processes like critical thinking, personal reflection, imagination, and empathy that comprise deep reading and that influence both how we think and how we live our lives?How can we preserve deep reading processes in future iterations of the reading brain?    </p>
<p>                    Concerns about attention span, critical reasoning, and over-reliance on technology are never just about children&#8211;Wolf herself has found that, though she is a reading expert, her ability to read deeply has been impacted as she has become increasingly dependent on screens.    </p>
<p>                    Wolf draws on neuroscience, literature, education, and philosophy and blends historical, literary, and scientific facts with down-to-earth examples and warm anecdotes to illuminate complex ideas that culminate in a proposal for a biliterate reading brain. Provocative and intriguing, Reader, Come Home is a roadmap that provides a cautionary but hopeful perspective on the impact of technology on our brains and our most essential intellectual capacities&#8211;and what this could mean for our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/">Reader, Come Home : The Reading Brain in a Digital World &#8211; Maryanne Wolf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bird by Bird : Some Instructions on Writing and Life &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bird-by-bird-some-instructions-on-writing-and-life-anne-lamott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing Skills]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bird-by-bird-some-instructions-on-writing-and-life-anne-lamott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An essential volume for generations of writers young and old, Bird by Bird is a modern classic. This twenty-fifth anniversary edition will continue to spark creative minds for years to come. For a quarter century, more than a million readers&#8211;scribes and scribblers of all ages and abilities&#8211;have been inspired by Anne Lamott&#8217;s hilarious, big-hearted, homespun [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bird-by-bird-some-instructions-on-writing-and-life-anne-lamott-abridged/">Bird by Bird : Some Instructions on Writing and Life &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An essential volume for generations of writers young and old, Bird by Bird is a modern classic. This twenty-fifth anniversary edition will continue to spark creative minds for years to come.     </p>
<p>                    For a quarter century, more than a million readers&#8211;scribes and scribblers of all ages and abilities&#8211;have been inspired by Anne Lamott&#8217;s hilarious, big-hearted, homespun advice. Advice that begins with the simple words of wisdom passed down from Anne&#8217;s father&#8211;also a writer&#8211;in the iconic passage that gives the book its title:     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Thirty years ago my older brother, who was ten years old at the time, was trying to get a report on birds written that he&#8217;d had three months to write. It was due the next day. We were out at our family cabin in Bolinas, and he was at the kitchen table close to tears, surrounded by binder paper and pencils and unopened books on birds, immobilized by the hugeness of the task ahead. Then my father sat down beside him, put his arm around my brother&#8217;s shoulder, and said, &#8216;Bird by bird, buddy. Just take it bird by bird.'&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bird-by-bird-some-instructions-on-writing-and-life-anne-lamott-abridged/">Bird by Bird : Some Instructions on Writing and Life &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind. In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind.    </p>
<p>                    In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and how it evolved. With deft use of examples of humor and wordplay, Steven Pinker weaves our vast knowledge of language into a compelling story: language is a human instinct, wired into our brains by evolution. The Language Instinct received the William James Book Prize from the American Psychological Association and the Public Interest Award from the Linguistics Society of America. This edition includes an update on advances in the science of language since The Language Instinct was first published.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Because Internet : Understanding the New Rules of Language &#8211; Gretchen McCulloch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/because-internet-understanding-the-new-rules-of-language-gretchen-mcculloch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/because-internet-understanding-the-new-rules-of-language-gretchen-mcculloch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!! Named a Best Book of 2019 by TIME, Amazon, and The Washington Post A Wired Must-Read Book of Summer   “Gretchen McCulloch is the internet’s favorite linguist, and this book is essential reading. Reading her work is like suddenly being able to see the matrix.” —Jonny Sun, author of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/because-internet-understanding-the-new-rules-of-language-gretchen-mcculloch-abridged/">Because Internet : Understanding the New Rules of Language &#8211; Gretchen McCulloch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!!    </p>
<p>                    Named a Best Book of 2019 by TIME, Amazon, and The Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    A Wired Must-Read Book of Summer       </p>
<p>                    “Gretchen McCulloch is the internet’s favorite linguist, and this book is essential reading. Reading her work is like suddenly being able to see the matrix.” —Jonny Sun, author of everyone&#8217;s a aliebn when ur a aliebn too       </p>
<p>                    Because Internet is for anyone who&#8217;s ever puzzled over how to punctuate a text message or wondered where memes come from. It&#8217;s the perfect book for understanding how the internet is changing the English language, why that&#8217;s a good thing, and what our online interactions reveal about who we are.      </p>
<p>                    Language is humanity&#8217;s most spectacular open-source project, and the internet is making our language change faster and in more interesting ways than ever before. Internet conversations are structured by the shape of our apps and platforms, from the grammar of status updates to the protocols of comments and @replies. Linguistically inventive online communities spread new slang and jargon with dizzying speed. What&#8217;s more, social media is a vast laboratory of unedited, unfiltered words where we can watch language evolve in real time.     </p>
<p>                    Even the most absurd-looking slang has genuine patterns behind it. Internet linguist Gretchen McCulloch explores the deep forces that shape human language and influence the way we communicate with one another. She explains how your first social internet experience influences whether you prefer &#8220;LOL&#8221; or &#8220;lol,&#8221; why ~sparkly tildes~ succeeded where centuries of proposals for irony punctuation had failed, what emoji have in common with physical gestures, and how the artfully disarrayed language of animal memes like lolcats and doggo made them more likely to spread.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/because-internet-understanding-the-new-rules-of-language-gretchen-mcculloch-abridged/">Because Internet : Understanding the New Rules of Language &#8211; Gretchen McCulloch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mother Tongue : The Story of the English Language &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lexicography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than 300 million people in the world speak English and the rest, it sometimes seems, try to&#8230;&#8217; Only Bill Bryson could make a book about the English language so entertaining. With his boundless enthusiasm and restless eye for the absurd, this is his astonishing tour of English. From its mongrel origins to its status [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/">Mother Tongue : The Story of the English Language &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than 300 million people in the world speak English and the rest, it sometimes seems, try to&#8230;&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Only Bill Bryson could make a book about the English language so entertaining. With his boundless enthusiasm and restless eye for the absurd, this is his astonishing tour of English. From its mongrel origins to its status as the world&#8217;s most-spoken tongue; its apparent simplicity to its deceptive complexity; its vibrant swearing to its uncertain spelling and pronunciation, Bryson covers all this as well as the many curious eccentricities that make it as maddening to learn as it is flexible to use.     </p>
<p>                    Bill Bryson&#8217;s classic Mother Tongue is a highly readable and hilarious tale of how English came to be the world&#8217;s language.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/">Mother Tongue : The Story of the English Language &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Read a Book &#8211; Mortimer J. Adler, Charles Van Doren (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-read-a-book-mortimer-j-adler-charles-van-doren-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Literacy Guides & Handbooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Companions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-read-a-book-mortimer-j-adler-charles-van-doren-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With half a million copies in print, How to Read a Book is the best and most successful guide to reading comprehension for the general reader, completely rewritten and updated with new material. Originally published in 1940, this book is a rare phenomenon, a living classic that introduces and elucidates the various levels of reading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-a-book-mortimer-j-adler-charles-van-doren-abridged/">How to Read a Book &#8211; Mortimer J. Adler, Charles Van Doren (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With half a million copies in print, How to Read a Book is the best and most successful guide to reading comprehension for the general reader, completely rewritten and updated with new material.<br />
                         Originally published in 1940, this book is a rare phenomenon, a living classic that introduces and elucidates the various levels of reading and how to achieve them-from elementary reading, through systematic skimming and inspectional reading, to speed reading. Readers will learn when and how to &#8220;judge a book by its cover,&#8221; and also how to X-ray it, read critically, and extract the author&#8217;s message from the text.<br />
                         Also included is instruction in the different techniques that work best for reading particular genres, such as practical books, imaginative literature, plays, poetry, history, science and mathematics, philosophy and social science works.<br />
                         Finally, the authors offer a recommended reading list and supply reading tests you can use measure your own progress in reading skills, comprehension, and speed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-a-book-mortimer-j-adler-charles-van-doren-abridged/">How to Read a Book &#8211; Mortimer J. Adler, Charles Van Doren (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language Teaching & Learning (other Than ELT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language Teaching & Learning Material & Coursework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; For anyone who wants to learn a foreign language, this is the method that will finally make the words stick. &#8220;A brilliant and thoroughly modern guide to learning new languages.&#8221;&#8211;Gary Marcus, cognitive psychologist and author of the New York Times bestseller Guitar Zero At thirty years old, Gabriel Wyner speaks six languages [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/">Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; For anyone who wants to learn a foreign language, this is the method that will finally make the words stick.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A brilliant and thoroughly modern guide to learning new languages.&#8221;&#8211;Gary Marcus, cognitive psychologist and author of the New York Times bestseller Guitar Zero     </p>
<p>                    At thirty years old, Gabriel Wyner speaks six languages fluently. He didn&#8217;t learn them in school&#8211;who does? Rather, he learned them in the past few years, working on his own and practicing on the subway, using simple techniques and free online resources&#8211;and here he wants to show others what he&#8217;s discovered.     </p>
<p>                    Starting with pronunciation, you&#8217;ll learn how to rewire your ears and turn foreign sounds into familiar sounds. You&#8217;ll retrain your tongue to produce those sounds accurately, using tricks from opera singers and actors. Next, you&#8217;ll begin to tackle words, and connect sounds and spellings to imagery rather than translations, which will enable you to think in a foreign language. And with the help of sophisticated spaced-repetition techniques, you&#8217;ll be able to memorize hundreds of words a month in minutes every day.     </p>
<p>                    This is brain hacking at its most exciting, taking what we know about neuroscience and linguistics and using it to create the most efficient and enjoyable way to learn a foreign language in the spare minutes of your day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/">Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. But swearing is also a uniquely well-suited lens through which to look at history, offering a fascinating record of what people care about on the<br />
                    deepest levels of a culture-what&#8217;s divine, what&#8217;s terrifying, and what&#8217;s taboo.     </p>
<p>                    Holy Sh*t tells the story of two kinds of swearing-obscenities and oaths-from ancient Rome and the Bible to today. With humor and insight, Melissa Mohr takes readers on a journey to discover how &#8220;swearing&#8221; has come to include both testifying with your hand on the Bible and calling someone a *#$&#038;!* when they cut you off on the highway. She explores obscenities in ancient Rome-which were remarkably similar to our own-and unearths the history of religious oaths in the Middle Ages,<br />
                    when swearing (or not swearing) an oath was often a matter of life and death. Holy Sh*t also explains the advancement of civility and corresponding censorship of language in the 18th century, considers the rise of racial slurs after World War II, examines the physiological effects of swearing (increased heart<br />
                    rate and greater pain tolerance), and answers a question that preoccupies the FCC, the US Senate, and anyone who has recently overheard little kids at a playground: are we swearing more now than people did in the past?     </p>
<p>                    A gem of lexicography and cultural history, Holy Sh*t is a serious exploration of obscenity-and it also just might expand your repertoire of words to choose from the next time you shut your finger in the car door.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Brands Grow : What Marketers Don&#8217;t Know &#8211; Byron Sharp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-brands-grow-what-marketers-dont-know-byron-sharp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-brands-grow-what-marketers-dont-know-byron-sharp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book provides evidence-based answers to the key questions asked by marketers every day. Tackling issues such as how brands grow, how advertising really works, what price promotions really do and how loyalty programs really affect loyalty, How Brands Grow presents decades of research in a style that is written for marketing professionals to grow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-brands-grow-what-marketers-dont-know-byron-sharp-abridged/">How Brands Grow : What Marketers Don&#8217;t Know &#8211; Byron Sharp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book provides evidence-based answers to the key questions asked by marketers every day. Tackling issues such as how brands grow, how advertising really works, what price promotions really do and how loyalty programs really affect loyalty, How Brands Grow presents decades of research in a style that is written for marketing professionals to grow their brands. It is the first book to present these laws in context and to explore their meaning and application.<br />
                    The most distinctive element to this book is that the laws presented are tried and tested; they have been found to hold over varied conditions, time and countries. This is contra to most marketing texts and indeed, much information provides evidence that much modern marketing theory is far from soundly based.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-brands-grow-what-marketers-dont-know-byron-sharp-abridged/">How Brands Grow : What Marketers Don&#8217;t Know &#8211; Byron Sharp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
