<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Secretarial, Clerical &amp; Office Skills Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/secretarial-clerical-office-skills/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/secretarial-clerical-office-skills/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Secretarial, Clerical &amp; Office Skills Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/secretarial-clerical-office-skills/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ultralearning : Accelerate Your Career, Master Hard Skills and Outsmart the Competition &#8211; Scott H. Young (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ultralearning-accelerate-your-career-master-hard-skills-and-outsmart-the-competition-scott-h-young-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secretarial, Clerical & Office Skills]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ultralearning-accelerate-your-career-master-hard-skills-and-outsmart-the-competition-scott-h-young-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Future-proof your career and maximize your competitive advantage by learning the skill necessary to stay relevant, reinvent yourself, and adapt to whatever the workplace throws your way in this essential guide. Faced with tumultuous economic times and rapid technological change, staying ahead in your career depends on continual learning-a lifelong mastery of new ideas, subjects, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultralearning-accelerate-your-career-master-hard-skills-and-outsmart-the-competition-scott-h-young-abridged/">Ultralearning : Accelerate Your Career, Master Hard Skills and Outsmart the Competition &#8211; Scott H. Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Future-proof your career and maximize your competitive advantage by learning the skill necessary to stay relevant, reinvent yourself, and adapt to whatever the workplace throws your way in this essential guide.    </p>
<p>                              Faced with tumultuous economic times and rapid technological change, staying ahead in your career depends on continual learning-a lifelong mastery of new ideas, subjects, and skills. If you want to accomplish more and stand apart from everyone else, you need to become an ultralearner.    </p>
<p>                              Scott Young incorporates the latest research about the most effective learning methods and the stories of other ultralearners like himself-among them Ben Franklin, Judit Polgar, and Richard Feynman, as well as a host of others, such as little-known modern polymaths like Nigel Richards who won the World Championship of French Scrabble-without knowing French.    </p>
<p>                              Young documents the methods he and others have used and shows that, far from being an obscure skill limited to aggressive autodidacts, ultralearning is a powerful tool anyone can use to improve their career, studies, and life. Ultralearning explores this fascinating subculture, shares the nine principles behind every successful ultralearning project, and offers insights into how you can organize and execute a plan to learn anything deeply and quickly, without teachers or budget-busting tuition costs.    </p>
<p>                              Whether the goal is to be fluent in a language (or ten languages), earn the equivalent of a college degree in a fraction of the time, or master multiple skills to build a product or business from the ground up, the principles in Ultralearning will guide you to success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultralearning-accelerate-your-career-master-hard-skills-and-outsmart-the-competition-scott-h-young-abridged/">Ultralearning : Accelerate Your Career, Master Hard Skills and Outsmart the Competition &#8211; Scott H. Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 11 Laws of Likability: Relationship Networking Because People Do Business with People They Like &#8211; Michelle Tillis Lederman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secretarial, Clerical & Office Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We all know that networking is important, and that forming relationships with others is a vital part of success. But sometimes it seems like networking removes all emotions from the equation and focuses only on immediate goals&#8230;whereas the kind of relationships that have true staying power, give us joy, and support us in the long [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/">The 11 Laws of Likability: Relationship Networking Because People Do Business with People They Like &#8211; Michelle Tillis Lederman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We all know that networking is important, and that forming relationships with others is a vital part of success. But sometimes it seems like networking removes all emotions from the equation and focuses only on immediate goals&#8230;whereas the kind of relationships that have true staying power, give us joy, and support us in the long run are founded on simply liking each other.     </p>
<p>                      This book, featuring activities, self-assessment quizzes, and real-life anecdotes from professional and social settings, shows readers how to identify what&#8217;s likable in themselves and create honest, authentic interactions that become &#8220;wins&#8221; for all parties involved. Readers will discover how to:     </p>
<p>                      * Start conversations and keep them going with ease     </p>
<p>                      * Convert acquaintances into friends     </p>
<p>                      * Uncover people&#8217;s preferences and tweak their own personal style to enable engaging, reciprocal interactions     </p>
<p>                      * Create follow-up and stay in others&#8217; minds long after the initial meeting     </p>
<p>                      The worst thing we can do when trying to establish a personal bond with someone is to come across as manipulative or self-serving. Authentic connections go much deeper-and feel much easier-than trying to hit self-imposed business card collection quotas. This book presents a new paradigm that shows how even the most networking-averse can network&#8230;and like it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/">The 11 Laws of Likability: Relationship Networking Because People Do Business with People They Like &#8211; Michelle Tillis Lederman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
