<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Food Manufacturing &amp; Related Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/food-manufacturing-related-industries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/food-manufacturing-related-industries/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Food Manufacturing &amp; Related Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/food-manufacturing-related-industries/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For the socially conscious, the intellectually curious, or the creative soul comes an inspiring, New York Times bestselling handbook for success in business, life, and the all-important task of building a more compassionate world&#8211;by the visionary founder and CEO of KIND Healthy Snacks. When Daniel Lubetzky started KIND Healthy Snacks in 2004, he aimed to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/">Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For the socially conscious, the intellectually curious, or the creative soul comes an inspiring, New York Times bestselling handbook for success in business, life, and the all-important task of building a more compassionate world&#8211;by the visionary founder and CEO of KIND Healthy Snacks.    </p>
<p>                     When Daniel Lubetzky started KIND Healthy Snacks in 2004, he aimed to defy the conventional wisdom that snack bars could never be both tasty and healthy, convenient and wholesome. A decade later, the transformative power of the company&#8217;s &#8220;AND&#8221; philosophy has resulted in an astonishing record of achievement. KIND has become the fastest-growing purveyor of healthy snacks in the country. Meanwhile, the KIND Movement&#8211;the company&#8217;s social mission to make the world a little kinder&#8211;has sparked more than a million good deeds worldwide.  In Do the KIND Thing,  Lubetzky shares the revolutionary principles that have shaped KIND&#8217;s business model and led to its success, while offering an unfiltered and intensely personal look into the mind of a pioneering social entrepreneur. Inspired by his father, who survived the Holocaust thanks to the courageous kindness of strangers, Lubetzky began his career handselling a sun-dried tomato spread made collaboratively by Arabs and Jews in the war-torn Middle East. Despite early setbacks, he never lost his faith in his vision of a &#8220;not-only-for-profit&#8221; business&#8211;one that sold great products and helped to make the world a better place.  While other companies let circumstances force them into choosing between two seemingly incompatible options, people at KIND say &#8220;AND.&#8221; At its core, this idea is about challenging assumptions and false compromises. It is about not settling for less and being willing to take greater risks, often financial. It is about learning to think boundlessly and critically, and choosing what at first may be the tougher path for later, greater rewards. By using illuminating anecdotes from his own career, and celebrating some past failures through the lessons learned from them, Lubetzky outlines his core tenets for building a successful business and a thriving social enterprise. He explores the value of staying true to your brand, highlights the importance of transparency and communication in the workplace, and explains why good intentions alone won&#8217;t sell products.  Engaging and inspirational, Do the KIND Thing shows how the power of AND worked wonders for one company&#8211;and could empower the next generation of social entrepreneurs to improve their bottom line and change the world. Advance praise for Do the KIND Thing  &#8220;An enjoyable read . . . wise advice about matters from product development to people management.&#8221;&#8211;Financial Times &#8220;By sharing the ten tenets that helped KIND grow, Daniel Lubetzky has given entrepreneurs a road map to success that includes both passion and purpose.&#8221;&#8211;Arianna Huffington, president and editor in chief, Huffington Post Media Group  &#8220;Lubetzky uses the power of kindness to build purpose into his business and his community. He&#8217;s a role model for future leaders.&#8221;&#8211;Mehmet Oz, M.D., professor of surgery, Columbia University  &#8220;I&#8217;ve always been a fan of the KIND brand. This engaging and inspirational book shows how coupling a social mission with creativity can spark change and empower a generation.&#8221;&#8211;Bobbi Brown, founder and CCO, Bobbi Brown Cosmetics</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/">Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bourbon Empire : The Past and Future of America&#8217;s Whiskey &#8211; Reid Mitenbuler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bourbon-empire-the-past-and-future-of-americas-whiskey-reid-mitenbuler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alcoholic Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brewing Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bourbon-empire-the-past-and-future-of-americas-whiskey-reid-mitenbuler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Pulls aside the curtain of puffery to show . . . the business of liquor to be every bit as fascinating as the fictions in which the distillers love to swaddle themselves.&#8221; &#8211;Wayne Curtis, The Wall Street Journal Walk into a well-stocked liquor store and you&#8217;ll see countless whiskey brands, each boasting an inspiring story [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bourbon-empire-the-past-and-future-of-americas-whiskey-reid-mitenbuler-abridged/">Bourbon Empire : The Past and Future of America&#8217;s Whiskey &#8211; Reid Mitenbuler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Pulls aside the curtain of puffery to show . . . the business of liquor to be every bit as fascinating as the fictions in which the distillers love to swaddle themselves.&#8221; &#8211;Wayne Curtis, The Wall Street Journal     </p>
<p>                     Walk into a well-stocked liquor store and you&#8217;ll see countless whiskey brands, each boasting an inspiring story of independence and heritage. And yet, more than 95% of the nation&#8217;s whiskey comes from a small handful of giant companies with links to organized crime, political controversy, and a colorful history that is far different than what appears on modern labels. In Bourbon Empire, Reid Mitenbuler shows how bourbon, America&#8217;s most iconic style of whiskey, and the industry surrounding it, really came to be&#8211;a saga of shrewd capitalism as well as dedicated craftsmanship.     </p>
<p>                     Mitenbuler traces the big names&#8211;Jim Beam, Maker&#8217;s Mark, Evan Williams, and more&#8211;back to their origins, exploring bourbon&#8217;s founding myths and great successes against the backdrop of America&#8217;s economic history. Illusion is separated from reality in a tale reaching back to the Whiskey Rebellion of 1794, when the ideologies of Thomas Jefferson and Alexander Hamilton battled to define the soul of American business. That debate continues today, punctuated along the way by Prohibition-era bootleggers, the liquor-fueled origins of NASCAR, intense consolidation driven by savvy lobbying, and a Madison Avenue plot to release five thousand parrots&#8211;trained to screech the name of a popular brand&#8211;into the nation&#8217;s bars.     </p>
<p>                     Today, the whiskey business takes a new turn as a nascent craft distilling movement offers the potential to revolutionize the industry once again. But, as Mitenbuler shows, many take advantage of this excitement while employing questionable business practices, either by masquerading whiskey made elsewhere as their own or by shortcutting the proven production standards that made many historic brands great to begin with.     </p>
<p>                     A tale of innovation, success, downfall, and resurrection, Bourbon Empire is an exploration of the spirit in all its unique forms, creating an indelible portrait of both American whiskey and the people who make it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bourbon-empire-the-past-and-future-of-americas-whiskey-reid-mitenbuler-abridged/">Bourbon Empire : The Past and Future of America&#8217;s Whiskey &#8211; Reid Mitenbuler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Fed the World &#8211; Leon Hesser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agronomy & Crop Production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Novels: Literary & Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Norman Borlaug was the only person during the twentieth century who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize for work in agriculture and food. There is no Nobel Food Prize, so the Nobel Committee chose Dr. Borlaug as the 1970 recipient of the Peace Prize based on his dramatic scientific breakthroughs and wheat production technology that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/">The Man Who Fed the World &#8211; Leon Hesser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Norman Borlaug was the only person during the twentieth century who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize for work in agriculture and food. There is no Nobel Food Prize, so the Nobel Committee chose Dr. Borlaug as the 1970 recipient of the Peace Prize based on his dramatic scientific breakthroughs and wheat production technology that relieved hunger in much of the world. During the previous decade, many people on the planet Earth, most notably in China and the Asian Subcontinent, were facing starvation, even famine. Borlaug&#8217;s revolutionary achievements relieved widespread human suffering and brought peace.    </p>
<p>                    Dr. Borlaug was hailed as the person who saved the lives of more people&#8211;hundreds of millions&#8211;from starvation than any person in history. He earned the distinction as one of the 100 most influential individuals of the 20th century. His is an inspiring story; he went from an unpretentious Iowa farm boy to scientist-cum-humanist of world acclaim.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/">The Man Who Fed the World &#8211; Leon Hesser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stories and advice for creating a business out of the food you love. Do you have a passion for delicious food and want to create your own business out of it, but have no idea where to start? Cooking Up a Business is essential reading for aspiring entrepreneurs and gives you a real-world, up-close-and-personal preview [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/">Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stories and advice for creating a business out of the food you love.      </p>
<p>                    Do you have a passion for delicious food and want to create your own business out of it, but have no idea where to start? Cooking Up a Business is essential reading for aspiring entrepreneurs and gives you a real-world, up-close-and-personal preview of the exciting journey. Through profiles and interviews with nationally known food entrepreneurs from Popchips, Vosges Haut-Chocolat, Hint Water, Mary&#8217;s Gone Crackers, Love Grown Foods, Kopali Organics, Tasty, Evol, Justin&#8217;s Nut Butters, Cameron Hughes Wine, and more, you will gain applicable, practical guidance that teaches you how to succeed today:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; How to create a national brand&#8211;with no connections or experience<br />
                    &#8211; The secret to getting meetings with grocery store buyers<br />
                    &#8211; The number one thing you need to know about food safety regulations<br />
                    &#8211; Why a grassroots budget might actually help you succeed<br />
                    &#8211; Specific advice for gluten-free, organic, wine, and beverage companies<br />
                    &#8211; What every entrepreneur wishes someone had told them at the beginning &#8211; Why doing what you love is always a good idea</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/">Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
