<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Gender Studies, Gender Groups Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/gender-studies-gender-groups/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/gender-studies-gender-groups/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Gender Studies, Gender Groups Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/gender-studies-gender-groups/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Secrets of My Life &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner</title>
		<link>/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Transsexuals & Hermaphroditism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nonfiction History Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER In this remarkable memoir &#8211; written with Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Buzz Bissinger during her pivotal first years of rebirth &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner reflects on her past as she looks to her future. With poignancy and humour, Caitlyn writes about her confusion growing up, the temporary triumph of the Olympics as Bruce [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/">The Secrets of My Life &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    In this remarkable memoir &#8211; written with Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Buzz Bissinger during her pivotal first years of rebirth &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner reflects on her past as she looks to her future.     </p>
<p>                    With poignancy and humour, Caitlyn writes about her confusion growing up, the temporary triumph of the Olympics as Bruce Jenner, and the noose of being endlessly described as the ultimate in manhood. She reveals her sense of shame and deceit she felt as she got older, as she went to great lengths to tell lies to conceal her true self. She also delves into her life in the public eye; her marriages and her troubled relationships with her children; what lead to her decision to becoming Caitlyn, and how the transgender community and the world has embraced her new life. Written with a searing honesty, this books shows you the real and true Caitlyn.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/">The Secrets of My Life &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sex and the Citadel : Intimate Life in a Changing Arab World &#8211; Shereen El Feki (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Kirkus Reviews Best Book of the Year As the &#8220;Arab Spring&#8221; and its aftermath sweep streets and squares, parliaments and presidential palaces of the Middle East, Shereen El Feki&#8211;an award-winning Canadian-Egyptian journalist&#8211;has been looking at unrest a little closer to home: in the sexual lives of Arab men and women. The result is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/">Sex and the Citadel : Intimate Life in a Changing Arab World &#8211; Shereen El Feki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Kirkus Reviews Best Book of the Year     </p>
<p>                    As the &#8220;Arab Spring&#8221; and its aftermath sweep streets and squares, parliaments and presidential palaces of the Middle East, Shereen El Feki&#8211;an award-winning Canadian-Egyptian journalist&#8211;has been looking at unrest a little closer to home: in the sexual lives of Arab men and women. The result is an informative, insightful, and engaging account of this sensitive and still largely secret aspect of Arab society.     </p>
<p>                     Sexual attitudes and behaviors are shaped by politics and economics, religion and tradition, gender and generations&#8211;not only a reflection of the conditions that led to the uprisings, but also a measure of hard-won reforms in the years to come. Highly personal, rich with original research and remarkable stories, Sex and the Citadel gives us unprecedented and timely insight into a part of the world that is changing before our eyes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/">Sex and the Citadel : Intimate Life in a Changing Arab World &#8211; Shereen El Feki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In private life, we try to induce or suppress love, envy, and anger through deep acting or &#8220;emotion work&#8221;, just as we manage our outer expressions of feeling through surface acting. In trying to bridge a gap between what we feel and what we &#8220;ought&#8221; to feel, we take guidance from &#8220;feeling rules&#8221; about what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In private life, we try to induce or suppress love, envy, and anger through deep acting or &#8220;emotion work&#8221;, just as we manage our outer expressions of feeling through surface acting. In trying to bridge a gap between what we feel and what we &#8220;ought&#8221; to feel, we take guidance from &#8220;feeling rules&#8221; about what is owing to others in a given situation. Based on our private mutual understandings of feeling rules, we make a &#8220;gift exchange&#8221; of acts of emotion management. We bow to each other not simply from the waist, but from the heart. But what occurs when emotion work, feeling rules, and the gift of exchange are introduced into the public world of work? In search of the answer, Arlie Russell Hochschild closely examines two groups of public-contact workers: flight attendants and bill collectors. The flight attendant&#8217;s job is to deliver a service and create further demand for it, to enhance the status of the customer and be &#8220;nicer than natural&#8221;. The bill collector&#8217;s job is to collect on the service, and if necessary, to deflate the status of the customer by being &#8220;nastier than natural.&#8221;<br />
                    Between these extremes, roughly one-third of American men and one-half of American women hold jobs that call for substantial emotional labor. In many of these jobs, they are trained to accept feeling rules and techniques of emotion management that serve the company&#8217;s commercial purpose. Just as we have seldom recognized or understood emotional labor, we have not appreciated its cost to those who do it for a living. Like a physical laborer who becomes estranged from what he or she makes, an emotional laborer, such as a flight attendant, can become estranged not only from her own expressions of feeling (her smile is not &#8220;her&#8221; smile), but also from what she actually feels (her managed friendliness). This estrangement, though a valuable defense against stress, is also an important occupational hazard, because it is through our feelings that we are connected with those around us. On the basis of this book, Hochschild was featured in Key Sociological Thinkers, edited by Rob Stones. This book was also the winner of the Charles Cooley Award in 1983, awarded by the American Sociological Association and received an honorable mention for the C. Wright Mills Award.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Female Eunuch &#8211; Germaine Greer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-female-eunuch-germaine-greer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-female-eunuch-germaine-greer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The 50th Anniversary edition of the ground-breaking, worldwide bestselling feminist tract. &#8216;The Female Eunuch retains that power of transformation; it asserts the possibility of creativity within female experience&#8217; Guardian A worldwide bestseller, translated into over twelve languages, The Female Eunuch is a landmark in the history of the women&#8217;s movement. Drawing liberally from history, literature [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-female-eunuch-germaine-greer-abridged/">The Female Eunuch &#8211; Germaine Greer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 50th Anniversary edition of the ground-breaking, worldwide bestselling feminist tract.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;The Female Eunuch retains that power of transformation; it asserts the possibility of creativity within female experience&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                              A worldwide bestseller, translated into over twelve languages, The Female Eunuch is a landmark in the history of the women&#8217;s movement.    </p>
<p>                              Drawing liberally from history, literature and popular culture, past and present, Germaine Greer&#8217;s searing examination of women&#8217;s oppression is at once an important social commentary and a passionately argued masterpiece of polemic.    </p>
<p>                              Probably the most famous, most widely read book on feminism ever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-female-eunuch-germaine-greer-abridged/">The Female Eunuch &#8211; Germaine Greer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Half The Sky : How to Change the World &#8211; Nicholas D. Kristof, Sheryl WuDunn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/half-the-sky-how-to-change-the-world-nicholas-d-kristof-sheryl-wudunn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/half-the-sky-how-to-change-the-world-nicholas-d-kristof-sheryl-wudunn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pulitzer Prize-winning reporting team, husband and wife Nicholas D. Kristof and Sheryl WuDunn, take us on a journey through Africa and Asia to meet an extraordinary array of exceptional women struggling against terrible circumstances. More girls have been killed in the last fifty years, precisely because they are girls, than men were killed in all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/half-the-sky-how-to-change-the-world-nicholas-d-kristof-sheryl-wudunn-abridged/">Half The Sky : How to Change the World &#8211; Nicholas D. Kristof, Sheryl WuDunn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pulitzer Prize-winning reporting team, husband and wife Nicholas D. Kristof and Sheryl WuDunn, take us on a journey through Africa and Asia to meet an extraordinary array of exceptional women struggling against terrible circumstances. More girls have been killed in the last fifty years, precisely because they are girls, than men were killed in all the wars of the twentieth century combined. More girls are killed in this routine &#8216;gendercide&#8217; in any one decade than people were slaughtered in all the genocides of the twentieth century.     </p>
<p>                    In the nineteenth century, the central moral challenge was slavery. In the twentieth, it was totalitarianism. In the twenty-first, Kristof and WuDunn demonstrate, it will be the struggle for gender equality in the developing world. Fierce, moral, pragmatic, full of amazing stories of courage and inspiration, HALF THE SKY is essential reading for every global citizen.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/half-the-sky-how-to-change-the-world-nicholas-d-kristof-sheryl-wudunn-abridged/">Half The Sky : How to Change the World &#8211; Nicholas D. Kristof, Sheryl WuDunn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Missionary Position : Mother Teresa in Theory and Practice &#8211; Christopher Hitchens, Foreword by Thomas Mallon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-missionary-position-mother-teresa-in-theory-and-practice-christopher-hitchens-foreword-by-thomas-mallon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Mission & Evangelism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-missionary-position-mother-teresa-in-theory-and-practice-christopher-hitchens-foreword-by-thomas-mallon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A religious fundamentalist, a political operative, a primitive sermonizer, and an accomplice of worldly secular powers. Her mission has always been of this kind. The irony is that she has never been able to induce anybody to believe her. It is past time that she was duly honored and taken at her word. Among his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-missionary-position-mother-teresa-in-theory-and-practice-christopher-hitchens-foreword-by-thomas-mallon-abridged/">The Missionary Position : Mother Teresa in Theory and Practice &#8211; Christopher Hitchens, Foreword by Thomas Mallon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A religious fundamentalist, a political operative, a primitive sermonizer, and an accomplice of worldly secular powers. Her mission has always been of this kind. The irony is that she has never been able to induce anybody to believe her. It is past time that she was duly honored and taken at her word.     </p>
<p>                     Among his many books, perhaps none have sparked more outrage than The Missionary Position, Christopher Hitchens&#8217;s meticulous study of the life and deeds of Mother Teresa.     </p>
<p>                     A Nobel Peace Prize recipient beatified by the Catholic Church in 2003, Mother Teresa of Calcutta was celebrated by heads of state and adored by millions for her work on behalf of the poor. In his measured critique, Hitchens asks only that Mother Teresa&#8217;s reputation be judged by her actions-not the other way around.     </p>
<p>                     With characteristic élan and rhetorical dexterity, Hitchens eviscerates the fawning cult of Teresa, recasting the Albanian missionary as a spurious, despotic, and megalomaniacal operative of the wealthy who long opposed measures to end poverty, and fraternized, for financial gain, with tyrants and white-collar criminals throughout the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-missionary-position-mother-teresa-in-theory-and-practice-christopher-hitchens-foreword-by-thomas-mallon-abridged/">The Missionary Position : Mother Teresa in Theory and Practice &#8211; Christopher Hitchens, Foreword by Thomas Mallon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A personal and powerful essay from Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie, the bestselling author of Americanah and Half of a Yellow Sun. &#8216;I would like to ask that we begin to dream about and plan for a different world. A fairer world. A world of happier men and happier women who are truer to themselves. And this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A personal and powerful essay from Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie, the bestselling author of Americanah and Half of a Yellow Sun.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;I would like to ask that we begin to dream about and plan for a different world. A fairer world. A world of happier men and happier women who are truer to themselves. And this is how to start: we must raise our daughters differently. We must also raise our sons differently&#8230;&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              What does &#8220;feminism&#8221; mean today?    </p>
<p>                              In this personal, eloquently argued essay &#8211; adapted from her much-admired Tedx talk of the same name &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie offers readers a unique definition of feminism for the twenty-first century, one rooted in inclusion and awareness. Drawing extensively on her own experiences and her deep understanding of the often masked realities of sexual politics, here is one remarkable author&#8217;s exploration of what it means to be a woman now &#8211; an of-the-moment rallying cry for why we should all be feminists.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Do Women Want? : Adventures in the Science of Female Desire &#8211; Daniel Bergner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-do-women-want-adventures-in-the-science-of-female-desire-daniel-bergner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sexual Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-do-women-want-adventures-in-the-science-of-female-desire-daniel-bergner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this headline-making book, Daniel Bergner turns everything we thought we knew about women&#8217;s desire on its head. Drawing on extensive research and interviews with renowned behavioural scientists, sexologists, psychologists and everyday women, Daniel Bergner asks: &#8211; Do women really crave intimacy and emotional connection? &#8211; Are women more disposed to sex with strangers or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-do-women-want-adventures-in-the-science-of-female-desire-daniel-bergner-abridged/">What Do Women Want? : Adventures in the Science of Female Desire &#8211; Daniel Bergner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this headline-making book, Daniel Bergner turns everything we thought we knew about women&#8217;s desire on its head. Drawing on extensive research and interviews with renowned behavioural scientists, sexologists, psychologists and everyday women, Daniel Bergner asks:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Do women really crave intimacy and emotional connection?      </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Are women more disposed to sex with strangers or multiple partners than either science or society have ever let on?      </p>
<p>                    &#8211; And is &#8216;the fairer sex&#8217; actually more sexually aggressive and anarchic than men?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-do-women-want-adventures-in-the-science-of-female-desire-daniel-bergner-abridged/">What Do Women Want? : Adventures in the Science of Female Desire &#8211; Daniel Bergner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Men]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone needs to love and be loved-even men. But to know love, men must be able to look at the ways that patriarchal culture keeps them from knowing themselves, from being in touch with their feelings, from loving. In The Will to Change, bell hooks gets to the heart of the matter and shows men [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/">The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone needs to love and be loved-even men. But to know love, men must be able to look at the ways that patriarchal culture keeps them from knowing themselves, from being in touch with their feelings, from loving.    </p>
<p>                    In The Will to Change, bell hooks gets to the heart of the matter and shows men how to express the emotions that are a fundamental part of who they are-whatever their age, marital status, ethnicity, or sexual orientation. But toxic masculinity punishes those fundamental emotions, and it&#8217;s so deeply ingrained in our society that it&#8217;s hard for men to not comply-but hooks wants to help change that.    </p>
<p>                    With trademark candor and fierce intelligence, hooks addresses the most common concerns of men, such as fear of intimacy and loss of their patriarchal place in society, in new and challenging ways. She believes men can find the way to spiritual unity by getting back in touch with the emotionally open part of themselves-and lay claim to the rich and rewarding inner lives that have historically been the exclusive province of women. A brave and astonishing work, The Will to Change is designed to help men reclaim the best part of themselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/">The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Moment of Lift : How Empowering Women Changes the World &#8211; Melinda Gates (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We need this message more than ever&#8217; Malala Yousafzai The right to: Spend your own money. Go to school. Earn an income. Access contraceptives. Work outside the home. Walk outside the home. Choose whom to marry. Get a loan. Start a business. Own property. Divorce a husband. See a doctor. Drive a car. All of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/">The Moment of Lift : How Empowering Women Changes the World &#8211; Melinda Gates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We need this message more than ever&#8217; Malala Yousafzai    </p>
<p>                    The right to:<br />
                    Spend your own money. Go to school. Earn an income. Access contraceptives. Work outside the home. Walk outside the home. Choose whom to marry. Get a loan. Start a business. Own property. Divorce a husband. See a doctor. Drive a car.<br />
                    All of these rights are denied to women in some parts of the world.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times bestselling debut from Melinda Gates, a timely and necessary call to action for women&#8217;s empowerment.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;How can we summon a moment of lift for human beings &#8211; and especially for women? Because when you lift up women, you lift up humanity.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    In this moving and compelling book, Melinda shares the stories of the inspiring people she&#8217;s met during her work and travels around the world and the lessons she&#8217;s learned from them. As she writes in the introduction, &#8220;That is why I had to write this book &#8211; to share the stories of people who have given focus and urgency to my life. I want all of us to see ways we can lift women up where we live.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Melinda&#8217;s unforgettable narrative is backed by startling data as she presents the issues that most need our attention &#8211; from child marriage to lack of access to contraceptives to gender inequity in the workplace. And, for the first time, she writes about her personal life and the road to equality in her own marriage. Throughout, she shows how there has never been more opportunity to change the world &#8211; and ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    When we lift others up, they lift us up, too.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/">The Moment of Lift : How Empowering Women Changes the World &#8211; Melinda Gates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend. A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend.<br />
                              A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. Dear Ijeawele is Adichie&#8217;s letter of response.    </p>
<p>                              Here are fifteen invaluable suggestions-compelling, direct, wryly funny, and perceptive-for how to empower a daughter to become a strong, independent woman. From encouraging her to choose a helicopter, and not only a doll, as a toy if she so desires; having open conversations with her about clothes, makeup, and sexuality; debunking the myth that women are somehow biologically arranged to be in the kitchen making dinner, and that men can &#8220;allow&#8221; women to have full careers, Dear Ijeawele goes right to the heart of sexual politics in the twenty-first century. It will start a new and urgently needed conversation about what it really means to be a woman today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sex Myth : The Gap Between Our Fantasies and Reality &#8211; Rachel Hills (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sex-myth-the-gap-between-our-fantasies-and-reality-rachel-hills-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sex-myth-the-gap-between-our-fantasies-and-reality-rachel-hills-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fifty years after the sexual revolution, we are told that we live in a time of unprecedented sexual freedom; that if anything, we are too free now. But beneath the veneer of glossy hedonism, millennial journalist Rachel Hills argues that we are controlled by a new brand of sexual convention: one which influences all of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sex-myth-the-gap-between-our-fantasies-and-reality-rachel-hills-abridged/">The Sex Myth : The Gap Between Our Fantasies and Reality &#8211; Rachel Hills (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fifty years after the sexual revolution, we are told that we live in a time of unprecedented sexual freedom; that if anything, we are too free now. But beneath the veneer of glossy hedonism, millennial journalist Rachel Hills argues that we are controlled by a new brand of sexual convention: one which influences all of us-woman or man, straight or gay, liberal or conservative. At the root of this silent code lies the Sex Myth-the defining significance we invest in sexuality that once meant we were dirty if we didhave sex, and now means we are defective if we don&#8217;tdo it enough.     </p>
<p>                    Equal parts social commentary, pop culture, and powerful personal anecdotes from people across the English-speaking world, The Sex Mythexposes the invisible norms and unspoken assumptions that shape the way we think about sex today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sex-myth-the-gap-between-our-fantasies-and-reality-rachel-hills-abridged/">The Sex Myth : The Gap Between Our Fantasies and Reality &#8211; Rachel Hills (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All About Love : New Visions &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/all-about-love-new-visions-bell-hooks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/all-about-love-new-visions-bell-hooks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The word &#8220;love&#8221; is most often defined as a noun, yet&#8230;we would all love better if we used it as a verb,&#8221; writes bell hooks as she comes out fighting and on fire in All About Love. Here, at her most provocative and intensely personal, the renowned scholar, cultural critic, and feminist skewers our view [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-about-love-new-visions-bell-hooks-abridged/">All About Love : New Visions &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The word &#8220;love&#8221; is most often defined as a noun, yet&#8230;we would all love better if we used it as a verb,&#8221; writes bell hooks as she comes out fighting and on fire in All About Love. Here, at her most provocative and intensely personal, the renowned scholar, cultural critic, and feminist skewers our view of love as romance. In its place she offers a proactive new ethic for a people and a society bereft with lovelessness.  As bell hooks uses her incisive mind and razor-sharp pen to explore the question &#8220;What is love?&#8221; her answers strike at both the mind and heart. In thirteen concise chapters, hooks examines her own search for emotional connection and society&#8217;s failure to provide a model for learning to love. Razing the cultural paradigm that the ideal love is infused with sex and desire, she provides a new path to love that is sacred, redemptive, and healing for the individuals and for a nation. The Utne Reader declared bell hooks one of the &#8220;100 Visionaries Who Can Change Your Life.&#8221; All About Love is a powerful affirmation of just how profoundly she can.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-about-love-new-visions-bell-hooks-abridged/">All About Love : New Visions &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Hour of Eugenics&#8221; : Race, Gender, and Nation in Latin America &#8211; Nancy Leys Stepan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eugenics was a term coined in 1883 to name the scientific and social theory which advocated &#8220;race improvement&#8221; through selective human breeding. In Europe and the United States the eugenics movement found many supporters before it was finally discredited by its association with the racist ideology of Nazi Germany. Examining for the first time how [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/">The Hour of Eugenics&#8221; : Race, Gender, and Nation in Latin America &#8211; Nancy Leys Stepan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eugenics was a term coined in 1883 to name the scientific and social theory which advocated &#8220;race improvement&#8221; through selective human breeding. In Europe and the United States the eugenics movement found many supporters before it was finally discredited by its association with the racist ideology of Nazi Germany. Examining for the first time how eugenics was taken up by scientists and social reformers in Latin America, Nancy Leys Stepan compares the eugenics movements in Mexico, Brazil, and Argentina with the more familiar cases of Britain, the United States, and Germany.In this highly original account, Stepan sheds new light on the role of science in reformulating issues of race, gender, reproduction, and public health in an era when the focus on national identity was particularly intense. Drawing upon a rich body of evidence concerning the technical publications and professional meetings of Latin American eugenicists, she examines how they adapted eugenic principles to local contexts between the world wars. Stepan shows that Latin American eugenicists diverged considerably from their counterparts in Europe and the United States in their ideological approach and their interpretations of key texts concerning heredity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/">The Hour of Eugenics&#8221; : Race, Gender, and Nation in Latin America &#8211; Nancy Leys Stepan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Labor of Love : The Invention of Dating &#8211; Moira Weigel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/labor-of-love-the-invention-of-dating-moira-weigel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/labor-of-love-the-invention-of-dating-moira-weigel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Does anyone date anymore?&#8221; Today, the authorities tell us that courtship is in crisis. But when Moira Weigel dives into the history of sex and romance in modern America, she discovers that authorities have always said this. Ever since young men and women started to go out together, older generations have scolded them: That&#8217;s not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/labor-of-love-the-invention-of-dating-moira-weigel-abridged/">Labor of Love : The Invention of Dating &#8211; Moira Weigel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Does anyone date anymore?&#8221; Today, the authorities tell us that courtship is in crisis. But when Moira Weigel dives into the history of sex and romance in modern America, she discovers that authorities have always said this. Ever since young men and women started to go out together, older generations have scolded them: That&#8217;s not the way to find true love. The first women who made dates with strangers were often arrested for prostitution; long before &#8220;hookup culture,&#8221; there were &#8220;petting parties&#8221;; before parents worried about cell phone apps, they fretted about joyrides and &#8220;parking.&#8221; Dating is always dying. But this does not mean that love is dead. It simply changes with the economy. Dating is, and always has been, tied to work.     </p>
<p>                    Lines like &#8220;I&#8217;ll pick you up at six&#8221; made sense at a time when people had jobs that started and ended at fixed hours. But in an age of contract work and flextime, many of us have become sexual freelancers, more likely to text a partner &#8220;u still up?&#8221; Weaving together over one hundred years of history with scenes from the contemporary landscape, Labor of Love offers a fresh feminist perspective on how we came to date the ways we do. This isn&#8217;t a guide to &#8220;getting the guy.&#8221; There are no ridiculous &#8220;rules&#8221; to follow. Instead, Weigel helps us understand how looking for love shapes who we are&#8211;and hopefully leads us closer to the happy ending that dating promises.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/labor-of-love-the-invention-of-dating-moira-weigel-abridged/">Labor of Love : The Invention of Dating &#8211; Moira Weigel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Second Sex (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Simone de Beauvoir, Translated by Constance Borde, Translated by Sheila Malovany-Chevallier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY NATALIE HAYNES When this book was first published in 1949 it was to outrage and scandal. Never before had the case for female liberty been so forcefully and successfully argued. De Beauvoir&#8217;s belief that &#8216;One is not born, but rather becomes, woman&#8217; switched [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/">The Second Sex (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Simone de Beauvoir, Translated by Constance Borde, Translated by Sheila Malovany-Chevallier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form    </p>
<p>                    WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY NATALIE HAYNES    </p>
<p>                    When this book was first published in 1949 it was to outrage and scandal. Never before had the case for female liberty been so forcefully and successfully argued. De Beauvoir&#8217;s belief that &#8216;One is not born, but rather becomes, woman&#8217; switched on light bulbs in the heads of a generation of women and began a fight for greater equality and economic independence. These pages contain the key passages of the book that changed perceptions of women forever.    </p>
<p>                    TRANSLATED BY CONSTANCE BORDE AND SHEILA MALOVANY-CHEVALLIER<br />
                    ANNOTATED AND INTRODUCED BY MARTINE REID</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/">The Second Sex (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Simone de Beauvoir, Translated by Constance Borde, Translated by Sheila Malovany-Chevallier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
