<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Consultancy &amp; Grants For Businesses Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/consultancy-grants-for-businesses/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/consultancy-grants-for-businesses/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Consultancy &amp; Grants For Businesses Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/consultancy-grants-for-businesses/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most powerful and instructive change manual you&#8217;ll ever read. It will persuade and inspire you to change your business, your work, and maybe your life.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, bestselling author of A Whole New Mind In Practically Radical, William C. Taylor, the New York Times bestselling co-author of Mavericks at Work offers a refreshing, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/">Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most powerful and instructive change manual you&#8217;ll ever read. It will persuade and inspire you to change your business, your work, and maybe your life.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, bestselling author of A Whole New Mind     </p>
<p>                    In Practically Radical, William C. Taylor, the New York Times bestselling co-author of Mavericks at Work offers a refreshing, rigorous new look at pragmatic ways to shake things up and make positive change in difficult times.     </p>
<p>                    Exploring how twenty-five for-profit companies and nonprofit organizations&#8211;including IBM, Zappos, Swatch, the Girl Scouts, and Interpol&#8211;made remarkable strides in tough circumstances, Practically Radical raises (and answers) the make-or-break questions facing today&#8217;s leaders in every field: Do you see opportunities the competition doesn&#8217;t see? The most successful organizations embrace one-of-a-kind ideas in a world filled with me-too thinking.Do you have new ideas about where to look for new ideas? Routine practices in one field can be revolutionary when they migrate to another.Are you the most of anything? In business today, the middle of the road is the road to ruin.Are you getting the best contributions from the most people? Change is not a game best played by loners.    </p>
<p>                    Anything but your typical business book, Practically Radical is a must-own for small business owners and CEOs, for managers at all levels, and innovators and entrepreneurs of every stripe.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/">Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook : A Practical Guide to Delivering High-value and Differentiated Services in a Competitive Marketplace &#8211; Samir Parikh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Delivers the essential practical skills needed to consult and make sharp, well prepared interactions in a wide range of business situations This comprehensive handbook covers the fundamental skills and attitudes required by successful consultants from novice to practitioner level, irrespective of their specialist area. It untangles the key variables present in any consulting service and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/">The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook : A Practical Guide to Delivering High-value and Differentiated Services in a Competitive Marketplace &#8211; Samir Parikh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Delivers the essential practical skills needed to consult and make sharp, well prepared interactions in a wide range of business situations This comprehensive handbook covers the fundamental skills and attitudes required by successful consultants from novice to practitioner level, irrespective of their specialist area. It untangles the key variables present in any consulting service and introduces practical ways to improve their effectiveness based upon the author&#8217;s experience of helping consulting organisations to develop and excel in the marketplace. The book explores consulting from the ground up&#8217; steering away from theory and focusing instead on practical application, providing a solid platform upon which to build further domain-specific competence. The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook provides: * An understanding of the key variables that can be addressed in order to improve one&#8217;s own consulting performance * A set of simple practices that can be implemented with immediate benefit to the reader * Practical insight into day-to-day real life consulting interactions * Confidence to implement the new ideas and approaches</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/">The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook : A Practical Guide to Delivering High-value and Differentiated Services in a Competitive Marketplace &#8211; Samir Parikh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flawless Consulting : A Guide to Getting Your Expertise Used &#8211; Peter Block (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This Third Edition to Peter Block&#8217;s Flawless Consulting addresses business changes and new challenges since the second edition was written ten years ago. It tackles the challenges next-generation consultants face, including more guidance on how to ask better questions, dealing with difficult clients, working in an increasingly virtual world, how to cope with complexities in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/">Flawless Consulting : A Guide to Getting Your Expertise Used &#8211; Peter Block (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This Third Edition to Peter Block&#8217;s Flawless Consulting addresses business changes and new challenges since the second edition was written ten years ago. It tackles the challenges next-generation consultants face, including more guidance on how to ask better questions, dealing with difficult clients, working in an increasingly virtual world, how to cope with complexities in international consulting, case studies, and guidelines on implementation. Also included are illustrative examples and exercises to help you cement the guides offered.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/">Flawless Consulting : A Guide to Getting Your Expertise Used &#8211; Peter Block (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting Started in Consulting &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-started-in-consulting-alan-weiss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-started-in-consulting-alan-weiss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The definitive guide to getting out of the office and getting into consulting Getting Started in Consulting, Fourth Edition is the acclaimed real-world blueprint to professional and financial freedom. For nearly two decades, this invaluable resource has helped thousands of people quit the daily grind and become their own boss. This practical and motivational guide [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-started-in-consulting-alan-weiss-abridged/">Getting Started in Consulting &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The definitive guide to getting out of the office and getting into consulting     </p>
<p>                     Getting Started in Consulting, Fourth Edition is the acclaimed real-world blueprint to professional and financial freedom. For nearly two decades, this invaluable resource has helped thousands of people quit the daily grind and become their own boss. This practical and motivational guide provides the tools and knowledge to control your future and secure your fortune. From establishing goals and sorting out the legal and financial paperwork, to advanced marketing strategies and relationship building techniques, this indispensable book offers step-by-step instructions for you to establish and grow your own consultancy business. This extensively revised and updated fourth edition includes new and expanded coverage on topics including utilizing informal media, changes in legal and financial guidelines, key distinctions of wholesale and retail businesses, and much more.    </p>
<p>                     Author Alan Weiss delivers expert advice on how to combine minimal overhead with optimal organization to produce maximum income. Every step in the process is clearly explained, including financing, marketing, bookkeeping, establishing your fees, and more. This guide is a comprehensive, one-stop source for everything you need to prosper in the rapidly expanding world of private consultancy.    </p>
<p>                    Adopt a pragmatic and profitable strategy to achieve incredible results from your consultancy business<br />
                    Learn to identify and address the most commons issues facing your prospects and clients<br />
                    Leverage technology to reduce labor, maximize profitability, and increase discretionary time<br />
                    Access sample budgets, case studies, references and appendices, downloadable tools and forms, and online resources    </p>
<p>                     The modern business landscape presents unique opportunities for those willing to take the leap from corporate offices to home offices. Getting Started in Consulting, Fourth Edition is the must-have guide for anyone seeking to cut their own path to their own consulting business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-started-in-consulting-alan-weiss-abridged/">Getting Started in Consulting &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting Naked : A Business Fable About Shedding The Three Fears That Sabotage Client Loyalty &#8211; Patrick M. Lencioni (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-naked-a-business-fable-about-shedding-the-three-fears-that-sabotage-client-loyalty-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-naked-a-business-fable-about-shedding-the-three-fears-that-sabotage-client-loyalty-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Another extraordinary business fable from the New York Times bestselling author Patrick LencioniWritten in the same dynamic style as his previous bestsellers including The Five Dysfunctions of a Team, Lencioni illustrates the principles of inspiring client loyalty through a fascinating business fable. He explains the theory of vulnerability in depth and presents concrete steps for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-naked-a-business-fable-about-shedding-the-three-fears-that-sabotage-client-loyalty-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/">Getting Naked : A Business Fable About Shedding The Three Fears That Sabotage Client Loyalty &#8211; Patrick M. Lencioni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Another extraordinary business fable from the New York Times bestselling author Patrick LencioniWritten in the same dynamic style as his previous bestsellers including The Five Dysfunctions of a Team, Lencioni illustrates the principles of inspiring client loyalty through a fascinating business fable. He explains the theory of vulnerability in depth and presents concrete steps for putting it to work in any organization. The story follows a small consulting firm, Lighthouse Partners, which often beats out big-name competitors for top clients. One such competitor buys out Lighthouse and learns important lessons about what it means to provide value to its clients. * Offers a key resource for gaining competitive advantage in tough times * Shows why the quality of vulnerability is so important in business * Includes ideas for inspiring customer and client loyalty * Written by the highly successful consultant and business writer Patrick LencioniThis new book in the popular Lencioni series shows what it takes to gain a real and lasting competitive edge.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-naked-a-business-fable-about-shedding-the-three-fears-that-sabotage-client-loyalty-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/">Getting Naked : A Business Fable About Shedding The Three Fears That Sabotage Client Loyalty &#8211; Patrick M. Lencioni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability. Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability.    </p>
<p>                    Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more rewarding and productive life. He no longer has to contend with an environment that constantly demands more productivity, more output and more growth.    </p>
<p>                    In Company of One, Jarvis explains how you can do the same, including:    </p>
<p>                    *         Planning to set up<br />
                    *         Determining desired revenues<br />
                    *         Keeping clients happy<br />
                    *         And, of course, doing all this on your own.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jarvis makes a compelling case for making your business better instead of bigger. A must-read for any entrepreneur who prioritizes a rich life over riches.&#8221;<br />
                     -CAL NEWPORT, bestselling author of DEEP WORK and DIGITAL MINIMALISM    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You&#8217;re not a machine, so why would you run your business like one? Company of One shows you another way. If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how to have a business that works for you-instead of the other way around-you need this book.&#8221;<br />
                    -CHRIS GUILLEBEAU, bestselling author of SIDE HUSTLE and THE $100 STARTUP</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Case Interview Secrets : A Former McKinsey Interviewer Reveals How to Get Multiple Job Offers in Consulting &#8211; Victor Cheng (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/case-interview-secrets-a-former-mckinsey-interviewer-reveals-how-to-get-multiple-job-offers-in-consulting-victor-cheng-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/case-interview-secrets-a-former-mckinsey-interviewer-reveals-how-to-get-multiple-job-offers-in-consulting-victor-cheng-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Case Interview Secrets, you&#8217;ll discover step-by-step instructions on how to dominate what many consider to be the most complex, most difficult, and most intimidating corporate job interview in the world&#8211;the infamous case interview. Victor Cheng, a former McKinsey management consultant, reveals his proven, insider&#8217;s method for acing the case interview. Having personally secured job [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/case-interview-secrets-a-former-mckinsey-interviewer-reveals-how-to-get-multiple-job-offers-in-consulting-victor-cheng-abridged/">Case Interview Secrets : A Former McKinsey Interviewer Reveals How to Get Multiple Job Offers in Consulting &#8211; Victor Cheng (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Case Interview Secrets, you&#8217;ll discover step-by-step instructions on how to dominate what many consider to be the most complex, most difficult, and most intimidating corporate job interview in the world&#8211;the infamous case interview. Victor Cheng, a former McKinsey management consultant, reveals his proven, insider&#8217;s method for acing the case interview. Having personally secured job offers from McKinsey, Bain &#038; Company, Monitor, L.E.K, Oliver Wyman, and A.T. Kearney, he has also been a McKinsey case interviewer&#8211;providing you with a hands-on, real-world perspective on what it really takes to land job offers. Cheng&#8217;s protégées work in all the major strategy management consulting firms, including McKinsey, The Boston Consulting Group, Bain &#038; Company, Monitor Company, A.T. Kearny, Oliver Wyman, L.E.K, Roland Berger, Accenture, and Deloitte, as well as in the strategic planning departments of numerous Fortune 500 companies. Whether you&#8217;re an undergraduate, MBA, PhD, or experienced-hire applicant candidate, you&#8217;ll discover: * What case interviewers really say about you behind closed doors but wouldn&#8217;t dare tell you&#8211;until now * The subtle yet specific performance differences that separate those who get management consulting offers from those who don&#8217;t * The 10 biggest mistakes candidates make in case interviews (and how to avoid them) * The 3 specific things interviewers expect in the first 5 minutes of a case that often decide the outcome on the spot * An insider&#8217;s take on what interviewers really look for and why&#8211;and how to give them what they want Praise for Victor Cheng and Case Interview Secrets &#8220;With Victor&#8217;s help, I went from not knowing anything about consulting to securing offers from McKinsey and BCG.&#8221; &#8211;Mihnea Munteanu, University of Michigan &#8220;I received six offers&#8211;from McKinsey, BCG, Booz, Deloitte, A.T. Kearney, and Marakon. Everything Victor said was right!&#8221; &#8211;Michael Yang, Northwestern University &#8220;Despite having a liberal arts degree from a state school, I landed a dream job with L.E.K. Consulting. Thanks, Victor.&#8221; &#8211;Jackson Boyar, Indiana University &#8220;Victor has put me in a very difficult position&#8211;now I have to decide between offers from two of the top three consultancies!&#8221; &#8211;Christopher Perez, The Wharton School &#8220;In my first attempt to break into consulting, I failed every one of my interviews with McKinsey, Bain, BCG, Oliver Wyman, Monitor, Booz and probably a few others. On my second attempt two years later, I followed everything Victor Cheng suggested and took advantage of every resource he provided &#8230; and received an offer from McKinsey!&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Suo, Business Analyst (Offer Recipient), McKinsey, Stamford &#8220;Without Victor&#8217;s help, I never would have gotten an offer from BCG. What he teaches really makes the difference between getting an offer and not.&#8221; &#8211;Puttipath Tasnavites, Boston Consulting Group, Thailand &#8220;After following Victor&#8217;s guidance, I had a complete breakthrough in my case interview performance and got an offer from Monitor.&#8221; &#8211;Marine Serres, Monitor &#038; Company &#8220;As a PhD candidate in engineering, I had an academic background that left me completely unprepared for the case interview process. That&#8217;s when I found Victor Cheng and ended up getting my dream job. Thank you, Victor!&#8221; &#8211;Zach Jacobson, McKinsey, New York About the Author As a former McKinsey consultant, résumé screener, and case interviewer, Victor Cheng mentors thousands of aspiring consultants via his articles and video tutorials at www.caseinterview.com. As a candidate, he passed 60 cases and received job offers from McKinsey, Bain, Monitor, LEK, AT Kearney, and Oliver Wyman. At McKinsey, he was rated in the top 10 percent of consultants worldwide in his cohort. Today he advises Inc. 500 CEOs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/case-interview-secrets-a-former-mckinsey-interviewer-reveals-how-to-get-multiple-job-offers-in-consulting-victor-cheng-abridged/">Case Interview Secrets : A Former McKinsey Interviewer Reveals How to Get Multiple Job Offers in Consulting &#8211; Victor Cheng (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Power Questions : Build Relationships, Win New Business, and Influence Others &#8211; Andrew Sobel, Jerold Panas (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/power-questions-build-relationships-win-new-business-and-influence-others-andrew-sobel-jerold-panas-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/power-questions-build-relationships-win-new-business-and-influence-others-andrew-sobel-jerold-panas-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An arsenal of powerful questions that will transform every conversation Skillfully redefine problems. Make an immediate connection with anyone. Rapidly determine if a client is ready to buy. Access the deepest dreams of others. Power Questions sets out a series of strategic questions that will help you win new business and dramatically deepen your professional [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-questions-build-relationships-win-new-business-and-influence-others-andrew-sobel-jerold-panas-abridged/">Power Questions : Build Relationships, Win New Business, and Influence Others &#8211; Andrew Sobel, Jerold Panas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An arsenal of powerful questions that will transform every conversation Skillfully redefine problems. Make an immediate connection with anyone. Rapidly determine if a client is ready to buy. Access the deepest dreams of others. Power Questions sets out a series of strategic questions that will help you win new business and dramatically deepen your professional and personal relationships. The book showcases thirty-five riveting, real conversations with CEOs, billionaires, clients, colleagues, and friends. Each story illustrates the extraordinary power and impact of a thought-provoking, incisive power question. To help readers navigate a variety of professional challenges, over 200 additional, thought-provoking questions are also summarized at the end of the book.<br />
                    In Power Questions you ll discover: * The question that stopped an angry executive in his tracks * The sales question CEOs expect you to ask versus the questions they want you to ask * The question that will radically refocus any meeting * The penetrating question that can transform a friend or colleague s life * A simple question that helped restore a marriage When you use power questions, you magnify your professional and personal influence, create intimate connections with others, and drive to the true heart of the issue every time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-questions-build-relationships-win-new-business-and-influence-others-andrew-sobel-jerold-panas-abridged/">Power Questions : Build Relationships, Win New Business, and Influence Others &#8211; Andrew Sobel, Jerold Panas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sales Bible, New Edition : The Ultimate Sales Resource &#8211; Jeffrey Gitomer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sales-bible-new-edition-the-ultimate-sales-resource-jeffrey-gitomer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sales-bible-new-edition-the-ultimate-sales-resource-jeffrey-gitomer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sales Bible softbound NEW EDITION WITH SOCIAL MEDIA ANSWERS Global sales authority Jeffrey Gitomer&#8217;s bestselling classic, The Sales Bible, has been updated and appended in this new edition, offering you the ultimate sales methods and strategies that really work every day, in real-world selling situations. With over 200,000 copies of the previous editions sold, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sales-bible-new-edition-the-ultimate-sales-resource-jeffrey-gitomer-abridged/">The Sales Bible, New Edition : The Ultimate Sales Resource &#8211; Jeffrey Gitomer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sales Bible softbound NEW EDITION WITH SOCIAL MEDIA ANSWERS Global sales authority Jeffrey Gitomer&#8217;s bestselling classic, The Sales Bible, has been updated and appended in this new edition, offering you the ultimate sales methods and strategies that really work every day, in real-world selling situations. With over 200,000 copies of the previous editions sold, The Sales Bible was listed as one of &#8220;The Ten Books Every Salesperson Should Own and Read&#8221; by the Dale Carnegie Sales Advantage Program. Jeffrey Gitomer&#8217;s column, &#8220;Sales Moves,&#8221; and blog, &#8220;SalesBlog.com&#8221; are read by more than four million people every week. His customers include Coca-Cola, BMW, Kimpton Hotels, Hilton, Wells Fargo Bank, IBM, Enterprise Rent-A-Car, Hewlett Packard, and hundreds of others. The Sales Bible is your personal, trusted, authoritative resource to reach your sales potential and shine like a star. Accept no substitutes. Here are a few highlights: * The 10.5<br />
                    Commandments of Selling * Generate leads and close sales in any market environment * Find 25 proven ways to set hard-to-get appointments * Use top-down selling to fill your sales pipeline with prospects who are ready to buy now * Ask the right questions to make more sales in half the time * How to use the top social media platforms to create inbound leads and prove value The Sales Bible has helped tens of thousands of salespeople all over the world reach their potential and close the deal and it can help you. So what are you waiting for?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sales-bible-new-edition-the-ultimate-sales-resource-jeffrey-gitomer-abridged/">The Sales Bible, New Edition : The Ultimate Sales Resource &#8211; Jeffrey Gitomer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Build a thriving consultancy with the updated edition of this classic bestseller Having inspired generations of consultants and entrepreneurs around the world, the &#8220;Rock Star of Consulting&#8221; Alan Weiss returns with a revised and completely updated edition of his authoritative guide to consulting success. Weiss provides his time-tested model on creating a flourishing consulting business, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/">Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Build a thriving consultancy with the updated edition of this classic bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Having inspired generations of consultants and entrepreneurs around the world, the &#8220;Rock Star of Consulting&#8221; Alan Weiss returns with a revised and completely updated edition of his authoritative guide to consulting success.      </p>
<p>                    Weiss provides his time-tested model on creating a flourishing consulting business, while incorporating and focusing on the many dynamic changes in solo and boutique consulting, coaching, and entrepreneurship. In addition to guidance on raising capital, attracting clients, and creating a marketing plan, he also gives brand new step-by-step advice on:    </p>
<p>                    * Harnessing today&#8217;s global opportunities<br />
                    * Developing brands across markets<br />
                    * Creating and licensing intellectual property<br />
                    * Avoiding the pitfalls of social media<br />
                    * Landing unsolicited referrals through counterintuitive methods<br />
                    * Managing and organizing your time wisely<br />
                    * Succeeding in the face of continuing turbulence    </p>
<p>                    Find out why this book has been the classic go-to for consultants for nearly twenty-five years, and learn how to grow your business into a $1 million-per-year firm today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/">Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
