<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Charities, Voluntary Services &amp; Philanthropy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/charities-voluntary-services-philanthropy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/charities-voluntary-services-philanthropy/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Charities, Voluntary Services &amp; Philanthropy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/charities-voluntary-services-philanthropy/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For the socially conscious, the intellectually curious, or the creative soul comes an inspiring, New York Times bestselling handbook for success in business, life, and the all-important task of building a more compassionate world&#8211;by the visionary founder and CEO of KIND Healthy Snacks. When Daniel Lubetzky started KIND Healthy Snacks in 2004, he aimed to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/">Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For the socially conscious, the intellectually curious, or the creative soul comes an inspiring, New York Times bestselling handbook for success in business, life, and the all-important task of building a more compassionate world&#8211;by the visionary founder and CEO of KIND Healthy Snacks.    </p>
<p>                     When Daniel Lubetzky started KIND Healthy Snacks in 2004, he aimed to defy the conventional wisdom that snack bars could never be both tasty and healthy, convenient and wholesome. A decade later, the transformative power of the company&#8217;s &#8220;AND&#8221; philosophy has resulted in an astonishing record of achievement. KIND has become the fastest-growing purveyor of healthy snacks in the country. Meanwhile, the KIND Movement&#8211;the company&#8217;s social mission to make the world a little kinder&#8211;has sparked more than a million good deeds worldwide.  In Do the KIND Thing,  Lubetzky shares the revolutionary principles that have shaped KIND&#8217;s business model and led to its success, while offering an unfiltered and intensely personal look into the mind of a pioneering social entrepreneur. Inspired by his father, who survived the Holocaust thanks to the courageous kindness of strangers, Lubetzky began his career handselling a sun-dried tomato spread made collaboratively by Arabs and Jews in the war-torn Middle East. Despite early setbacks, he never lost his faith in his vision of a &#8220;not-only-for-profit&#8221; business&#8211;one that sold great products and helped to make the world a better place.  While other companies let circumstances force them into choosing between two seemingly incompatible options, people at KIND say &#8220;AND.&#8221; At its core, this idea is about challenging assumptions and false compromises. It is about not settling for less and being willing to take greater risks, often financial. It is about learning to think boundlessly and critically, and choosing what at first may be the tougher path for later, greater rewards. By using illuminating anecdotes from his own career, and celebrating some past failures through the lessons learned from them, Lubetzky outlines his core tenets for building a successful business and a thriving social enterprise. He explores the value of staying true to your brand, highlights the importance of transparency and communication in the workplace, and explains why good intentions alone won&#8217;t sell products.  Engaging and inspirational, Do the KIND Thing shows how the power of AND worked wonders for one company&#8211;and could empower the next generation of social entrepreneurs to improve their bottom line and change the world. Advance praise for Do the KIND Thing  &#8220;An enjoyable read . . . wise advice about matters from product development to people management.&#8221;&#8211;Financial Times &#8220;By sharing the ten tenets that helped KIND grow, Daniel Lubetzky has given entrepreneurs a road map to success that includes both passion and purpose.&#8221;&#8211;Arianna Huffington, president and editor in chief, Huffington Post Media Group  &#8220;Lubetzky uses the power of kindness to build purpose into his business and his community. He&#8217;s a role model for future leaders.&#8221;&#8211;Mehmet Oz, M.D., professor of surgery, Columbia University  &#8220;I&#8217;ve always been a fan of the KIND brand. This engaging and inspirational book shows how coupling a social mission with creativity can spark change and empower a generation.&#8221;&#8211;Bobbi Brown, founder and CCO, Bobbi Brown Cosmetics</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/">Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Technologies & Applied Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).     </p>
<p>                    Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot be closed. But it is closing-fast.     </p>
<p>                    InAbundance, space entrepreneur turned innovation pioneer Peter H. Diamandis and award-winning science writer Steven Kotler document how progress in artificial intelligence, robotics, digital manufacturing synthetic biology, and other exponentially growing technologies will enable us to make greater gains in the next two decades than we have in the previous 200 years. We will soon have the ability to meet and exceed the basic needs of every person on the planet. Abundance for all is within our grasp.     </p>
<p>                    Breaking down human needs by category-water, food, energy, healthcare, education, freedom-Diamandis and Kotler introduce us to innovators and industry captains making tremendous strides in each area. &#8220;Not only isAbundancea riveting page-turner&#8230;but it&#8217;s a book that gives us a future worth fighting for. And even more than that, it shows us our place in that fight&#8221; (The Christian Science Monitor).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Moment of Lift : How Empowering Women Changes the World &#8211; Melinda Gates (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We need this message more than ever&#8217; Malala Yousafzai The right to: Spend your own money. Go to school. Earn an income. Access contraceptives. Work outside the home. Walk outside the home. Choose whom to marry. Get a loan. Start a business. Own property. Divorce a husband. See a doctor. Drive a car. All of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/">The Moment of Lift : How Empowering Women Changes the World &#8211; Melinda Gates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We need this message more than ever&#8217; Malala Yousafzai    </p>
<p>                    The right to:<br />
                    Spend your own money. Go to school. Earn an income. Access contraceptives. Work outside the home. Walk outside the home. Choose whom to marry. Get a loan. Start a business. Own property. Divorce a husband. See a doctor. Drive a car.<br />
                    All of these rights are denied to women in some parts of the world.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times bestselling debut from Melinda Gates, a timely and necessary call to action for women&#8217;s empowerment.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;How can we summon a moment of lift for human beings &#8211; and especially for women? Because when you lift up women, you lift up humanity.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    In this moving and compelling book, Melinda shares the stories of the inspiring people she&#8217;s met during her work and travels around the world and the lessons she&#8217;s learned from them. As she writes in the introduction, &#8220;That is why I had to write this book &#8211; to share the stories of people who have given focus and urgency to my life. I want all of us to see ways we can lift women up where we live.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Melinda&#8217;s unforgettable narrative is backed by startling data as she presents the issues that most need our attention &#8211; from child marriage to lack of access to contraceptives to gender inequity in the workplace. And, for the first time, she writes about her personal life and the road to equality in her own marriage. Throughout, she shows how there has never been more opportunity to change the world &#8211; and ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    When we lift others up, they lift us up, too.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/">The Moment of Lift : How Empowering Women Changes the World &#8211; Melinda Gates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>To Stop a Warlord : My Story of Justice, Grace, and the Fight for Peace &#8211; Shannon Sedgwick Davis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/to-stop-a-warlord-my-story-of-justice-grace-and-the-fight-for-peace-shannon-sedgwick-davis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Social Thought & Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/to-stop-a-warlord-my-story-of-justice-grace-and-the-fight-for-peace-shannon-sedgwick-davis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-stop-a-warlord-my-story-of-justice-grace-and-the-fight-for-peace-shannon-sedgwick-davis-abridged/">To Stop a Warlord : My Story of Justice, Grace, and the Fight for Peace &#8211; Shannon Sedgwick Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-stop-a-warlord-my-story-of-justice-grace-and-the-fight-for-peace-shannon-sedgwick-davis-abridged/">To Stop a Warlord : My Story of Justice, Grace, and the Fight for Peace &#8211; Shannon Sedgwick Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaving Microsoft To Change the World &#8211; John Wood (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leaving-microsoft-to-change-the-world-john-wood-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-profitmaking Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leaving-microsoft-to-change-the-world-john-wood-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>John Wood discovered his passion, his greatest success, and his life&#8217;s work not at business school or helping lead Microsoft&#8217;s charge into Asia in the 1990s but on a soul-searching trip to the Himalayas. He made the difficult decision to walk away from his lucrative career to create Room to Read, a nonprofit organization that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaving-microsoft-to-change-the-world-john-wood-abridged/">Leaving Microsoft To Change the World &#8211; John Wood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John Wood discovered his passion, his greatest success, and his life&#8217;s work not at business school or helping lead Microsoft&#8217;s charge into Asia in the 1990s but on a soul-searching trip to the Himalayas. He made the difficult decision to walk away from his lucrative career to create Room to Read, a nonprofit organization that promotes education across the developing world. By the end of 2007, the organization will have established over 5,000 libraries and 400 schools, and awarded long-term scholarships to more than 3,000 girls, giving more than one million children the lifelong gift of education.     </p>
<p>                    If you have ever pondered abandoning your desk job for an adventure and an opportunity to give back, Wood&#8217;s story will inspire you. He offers a vivid, emotional, and absorbing tale of how to take the lessons learned at a hard-charging company like Microsoft and apply them to the world&#8217;s most pressing social problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaving-microsoft-to-change-the-world-john-wood-abridged/">Leaving Microsoft To Change the World &#8211; John Wood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drought & Water Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An inspiring personal story of redemption, second chances, and the transformative power within us all, from the founder and CEO of the nonprofit charity: water. At 28 years old, Scott Harrison had it all. A top nightclub promoter in New York City, his life was an endless cycle of drugs, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/">Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An inspiring personal story of redemption, second chances, and the transformative power within us all, from the founder and CEO of the nonprofit charity: water.    </p>
<p>                    At 28 years old, Scott Harrison had it all. A top nightclub promoter in New York City, his life was an endless cycle of drugs, booze, models&#8211;repeat. But 10 years in, desperately unhappy and morally bankrupt, he asked himself, What would the exact opposite of my life look like? Walking away from everything, Harrison spent the next 16 months on a hospital ship in West Africa and discovered his true calling. In 2006, with no money and less than no experience, Harrison founded charity: water. Today, his organization has raised over $400 million to bring clean drinking water to more than 10 million people around the globe.     </p>
<p>                    In Thirst, Harrison recounts the twists and turns that built charity: water into one of the most trusted and admired nonprofits in the world. Renowned for its 100% donation model, bold storytelling, imaginative branding, and radical commitment to transparency, charity: water has disrupted how social entrepreneurs work while inspiring millions of people to join its mission of bringing clean water to everyone on the planet within our lifetime.     </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of such bestselling books as Shoe Dog and Mountains Beyond Mountains, Thirst is a riveting account of how to build a better charity, a better business, a better life&#8211;and a gritty tale that proves it&#8217;s never too late to make a change.     </p>
<p>                    100% of the author&#8217;s net proceeds from Thirst will go to fund charity: water projects around the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/">Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
