<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Zoology &amp; Animal Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/zoology-animal-sciences/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/zoology-animal-sciences/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Zoology &amp; Animal Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/zoology-animal-sciences/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dazzled and Deceived : Mimicry and Camouflage &#8211; Peter Forbes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dazzled-and-deceived-mimicry-and-camouflage-peter-forbes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biodiversity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Developmental Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dazzled-and-deceived-mimicry-and-camouflage-peter-forbes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The remarkable story of how mimicry is used by some of the most extraordinary creatures in the world Nature has perfected the art of deception. Thousands of creatures all over the world-including butterflies, moths, fish, birds, insects and snakes-have honed and practiced camouflage over hundreds of millions of years. Imitating other animals or their surroundings, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dazzled-and-deceived-mimicry-and-camouflage-peter-forbes-abridged/">Dazzled and Deceived : Mimicry and Camouflage &#8211; Peter Forbes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The remarkable story of how mimicry is used by some of the most extraordinary creatures in the world    </p>
<p>                     Nature has perfected the art of deception. Thousands of creatures all over the world-including butterflies, moths, fish, birds, insects and snakes-have honed and practiced camouflage over hundreds of millions of years. Imitating other animals or their surroundings, nature&#8217;s fakers use mimicry to protect themselves, to attract and repel, to bluff and warn, to forage, and to hide. The advantages of mimicry are obvious-but how does &#8220;blind&#8221; nature do it? And how has humanity learned to profit from nature&#8217;s ploys?    </p>
<p>                    Dazzled and Deceived tells the unique and fascinating story of mimicry and camouflage in science, art, warfare, and the natural world. Discovered in the 1850s by the young English naturalists Henry Walter Bates and Alfred Russel Wallace in the Amazonian rainforest, the phenomenon of mimicry was seized upon as the first independent validation of Darwin&#8217;s theory of natural selection. But mimicry and camouflage also created a huge impact outside the laboratory walls. Peter Forbes&#8217;s cultural history links mimicry and camouflage to art, literature, military tactics, and medical cures across the twentieth century, and charts its intricate involvement with the perennial dispute between evolution and creationism.    </p>
<p>                    As Dazzled and Deceived unravels the concept of mimicry, Forbes introduces colorful stories and a dazzling cast of characters-Roosevelt, Picasso, Nabokov, Churchill, and Darwin himself, to name a few-whom its mystery influenced and enthralled. Illuminating and lively, Dazzled and Deceived sheds new light on the greatest quest: to understand the processes of life at its deepest level.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dazzled-and-deceived-mimicry-and-camouflage-peter-forbes-abridged/">Dazzled and Deceived : Mimicry and Camouflage &#8211; Peter Forbes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Science Of Kissing : What Our Lips Are Telling Us &#8211; Sheril Kirshenbaum (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-science-of-kissing-what-our-lips-are-telling-us-sheril-kirshenbaum-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-science-of-kissing-what-our-lips-are-telling-us-sheril-kirshenbaum-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When did humans begin to kiss? Why is kissing integral to some cultures and alien to others? Do good kissers make the best lovers? And is that expensive lip-plumping gloss worth it? Sheril Kirshenbaum, a marine biologist and science journalist, tackles these questions and more in THE SCIENCE OF KISSING. It&#8217;s everything you always wanted [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-kissing-what-our-lips-are-telling-us-sheril-kirshenbaum-abridged/">The Science Of Kissing : What Our Lips Are Telling Us &#8211; Sheril Kirshenbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When did humans begin to kiss? Why is kissing integral to some cultures and alien to others? Do good kissers make the best lovers? And is that expensive lip-plumping gloss worth it? Sheril Kirshenbaum, a marine biologist and science journalist, tackles these questions and more in THE SCIENCE OF KISSING. It&#8217;s everything you always wanted to know about kissing but either haven&#8217;t asked, can&#8217;t find out, or didn&#8217;t realize you should understand. Sheril&#8217;s a serious scientist, and the material here is informed by the results of the latest studies and theories, but she&#8217;s also got an engaging, delightful voice and offers information with a light, humorous touch. Topics range from the kind of kissing men like to do (as distinct from women), to what animals can teach us about the kiss, to whether or not the true art of kissing was lost sometime in the Dark Ages, to what, really, makes us kiss. Employing an interdisciplinary approach&#8211;drawing upon classical history, evolutionary biology, psychology, popular culture, and more&#8211;Kirshenbaum&#8217;s winning book will appeal to romantics and armchair scientists alike.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-kissing-what-our-lips-are-telling-us-sheril-kirshenbaum-abridged/">The Science Of Kissing : What Our Lips Are Telling Us &#8211; Sheril Kirshenbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Parasite Rex (with a New Epilogue): Inside the Bizarre World of Nature&#8217;sMost Dangerous Creatures &#8211; Zimmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/parasite-rex-with-a-new-epilogue-inside-the-bizarre-world-of-naturesmost-dangerous-creatures-zimmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insects (entomology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Parasitology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Invertebrates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/parasite-rex-with-a-new-epilogue-inside-the-bizarre-world-of-naturesmost-dangerous-creatures-zimmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For decades parasites were the pariahs of science. Only recently have biologists begun to appreciate that these diverse and complex organisms are the most highly evolved life forms on earth. In this work, Carl Zimmer takes the reader on a tour of the strange and bizzare world that parasites inhabit, and recounts the voyages of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/parasite-rex-with-a-new-epilogue-inside-the-bizarre-world-of-naturesmost-dangerous-creatures-zimmer-abridged/">Parasite Rex (with a New Epilogue): Inside the Bizarre World of Nature&#8217;sMost Dangerous Creatures &#8211; Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For decades parasites were the pariahs of science. Only recently have biologists begun to appreciate that these diverse and complex organisms are the most highly evolved life forms on earth. In this work, Carl Zimmer takes the reader on a tour of the strange and bizzare world that parasites inhabit, and recounts the voyages of these wonders of creation. Parasites can: rewrite DNA; rewire the brain; genetically engineer viruses as weapons; and turn healthy hosts into the living dead. This book follows researchers in parasitology as they attempt to penetrate the mysteries of these omnipotent creatures who control evolution, ecxosystems, and perhaps the future of the human race.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/parasite-rex-with-a-new-epilogue-inside-the-bizarre-world-of-naturesmost-dangerous-creatures-zimmer-abridged/">Parasite Rex (with a New Epilogue): Inside the Bizarre World of Nature&#8217;sMost Dangerous Creatures &#8211; Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Words : What Animals Think and Feel &#8211; Carl Safina (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-words-what-animals-think-and-feel-carl-safina-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animals & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-words-what-animals-think-and-feel-carl-safina-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I wanted to know what they were experiencing, and why to us they feel so compelling, and so-close. This time I allowed myself to ask them the question that for a scientist was forbidden fruit: Who are you? Weaving decades of field observations with exciting new discoveries about the brain, Carl Safina&#8217;s landmark book offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-words-what-animals-think-and-feel-carl-safina-abridged/">Beyond Words : What Animals Think and Feel &#8211; Carl Safina (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I wanted to know what they were experiencing, and why to us they feel so compelling, and so-close. This time I allowed myself to ask them the question that for a scientist was forbidden fruit: Who are you?     </p>
<p>                    Weaving decades of field observations with exciting new discoveries about the brain, Carl Safina&#8217;s landmark book offers an intimate view of animal behavior to challenge the fixed boundary between humans and nonhuman animals. In Beyond Words, readers travel to Amboseli National Park in the threatened landscape of Kenya and witness struggling elephant families work out how to survive poaching and drought, then to Yellowstone National Park to observe wolves sort out the aftermath of one pack&#8217;s personal tragedy, and finally plunge into the astonishingly peaceful society of killer whales living in the crystalline waters of the Pacific Northwest.     </p>
<p>                    Beyond Words brings forth powerful and illuminating insight into the unique personalities of animals through extraordinary stories of animal joy, grief, jealousy, anger, and love. The similarity between human and nonhuman consciousness, self-awareness, and empathy calls us to re-evaluate how we interact with animals. Wise, passionate, and eye-opening at every turn, Beyond Words is ultimately a graceful examination of humanity&#8217;s place in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-words-what-animals-think-and-feel-carl-safina-abridged/">Beyond Words : What Animals Think and Feel &#8211; Carl Safina (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Contain Multitudes : The Microbes Within Us and a Grander View of Life &#8211; Ed Yong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE WINNER OF THE 2021 PULITZER PRIZE Your body is teeming with tens of trillions of microbes. It&#8217;s an entire world, a colony full of life. In other words, you contain multitudes. They sculpt our organs, protect us from diseases, guide our behaviour, and bombard us with their genes. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/">I Contain Multitudes : The Microbes Within Us and a Grander View of Life &#8211; Ed Yong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE WINNER OF THE 2021 PULITZER PRIZE    </p>
<p>                     Your body is teeming with tens of trillions of microbes. It&#8217;s an entire world, a colony full of life.    </p>
<p>                     In other words, you contain multitudes.    </p>
<p>                     They sculpt our organs, protect us from diseases, guide our behaviour, and bombard us with their genes. They also hold the key to understanding all life on earth.    </p>
<p>                     In I Contain Multitudes, Ed Yong opens our eyes and invites us to marvel at ourselves and other animals in a new light, less as individuals and more as thriving ecosystems.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll never think about your mind, body or preferences in the same way again.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Super-interesting&#8230; He just keeps imparting one surprising, fascinating insight after the next. I Contain Multitudes is science journalism at its best&#8217; Bill Gates<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2017<br />
                     SHORTLISTED FOR THE ROYAL SOCIETY SCIENCE BOOK PRIZE 2017</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/">I Contain Multitudes : The Microbes Within Us and a Grander View of Life &#8211; Ed Yong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
