<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/cognitivism-cognitive-theory/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/cognitivism-cognitive-theory/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/cognitivism-cognitive-theory/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Micromastery : Learn Small, Learn Fast, and Unlock Your Potential to Achieve Anything &#8211; Robert Twigger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/micromastery-learn-small-learn-fast-and-unlock-your-potential-to-achieve-anything-robert-twigger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/micromastery-learn-small-learn-fast-and-unlock-your-potential-to-achieve-anything-robert-twigger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Want to be a lifelong learner? Think small. Forget spending 10,000 hours in the pursuit of perfecting just one thing. The true path to success and achievement lies in the pursuit of perfecting lots and lots of small things&#8211;for a big payoff. Combining positive psychology, neuroscience, self-help and more, this delightfully illuminating book encourages us [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/micromastery-learn-small-learn-fast-and-unlock-your-potential-to-achieve-anything-robert-twigger-abridged/">Micromastery : Learn Small, Learn Fast, and Unlock Your Potential to Achieve Anything &#8211; Robert Twigger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Want to be a lifelong learner? Think small. Forget spending 10,000 hours in the pursuit of perfecting just one thing. The true path to success and achievement lies in the pursuit of perfecting lots and lots of small things&#8211;for a big payoff. Combining positive psychology, neuroscience, self-help and more, this delightfully illuminating book encourages us to circumvent all the reasons we can&#8217;t learn and grow (we&#8217;re too busy, it&#8217;s too complicated, we&#8217;re not experts, we didn&#8217;t start when we were young) &#8212; by tackling small, satisfying skills. Wish you were a seasoned chef? Learn to make a perfect omelette. Dream of being a racecar driver? Perfect a handbrake turn. Wish you could draw? Make Zen circles your first challenge. These small, doable tasks offer a big payoff &#8212; and motivate us to keep learning and growing, with payoffs that include a boost in optimism, confidence, memory, cognitive skills, and more. Filled with surprising insights and even a compendium of micromastery skills to try yourself, this engaging and inspiring guide reminds us of the simple joy of learning &#8212; and opens the door to limitless, lifelong achievement, one small step at a time. Micromasteries presented in the book (with illustrations) include: Learn How to Climb a Rope, Surf Standing Up, Talk for Fifteen Minutes about Any Subject, Bake Artisan Bread, Juggle Four Balls, Learn to Read Japanese in Three Hours, and more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/micromastery-learn-small-learn-fast-and-unlock-your-potential-to-achieve-anything-robert-twigger-abridged/">Micromastery : Learn Small, Learn Fast, and Unlock Your Potential to Achieve Anything &#8211; Robert Twigger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Everyone (Else) Is a Hypocrite : Evolution and the Modular Mind &#8211; Robert Kurzban (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-everyone-else-is-a-hypocrite-evolution-and-the-modular-mind-robert-kurzban-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-everyone-else-is-a-hypocrite-evolution-and-the-modular-mind-robert-kurzban-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re all hypocrites. Why? Hypocrisy is the natural state of the human mind. Robert Kurzban shows us that the key to understanding our behavioral inconsistencies lies in understanding the mind&#8217;s design. The human mind consists of many specialized units designed by the process of evolution by natural selection. While these modules sometimes work together seamlessly, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-everyone-else-is-a-hypocrite-evolution-and-the-modular-mind-robert-kurzban-abridged/">Why Everyone (Else) Is a Hypocrite : Evolution and the Modular Mind &#8211; Robert Kurzban (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re all hypocrites. Why? Hypocrisy is the natural state of the human mind. Robert Kurzban shows us that the key to understanding our behavioral inconsistencies lies in understanding the mind&#8217;s design. The human mind consists of many specialized units designed by the process of evolution by natural selection. While these modules sometimes work together seamlessly, they don&#8217;t always, resulting in impossibly contradictory beliefs, vacillations between patience and impulsiveness, violations of our supposed moral principles, and overinflated views of ourselves. This modular, evolutionary psychological view of the mind undermines deeply held intuitions about ourselves, as well as a range of scientific theories that require a &#8220;self&#8221; with consistent beliefs and preferences. Modularity suggests that there is no &#8220;I&#8221;. Instead, each of us is a contentious &#8220;we&#8221; &#8211; a collection of discrete but interacting systems whose constant conflicts shape our interactions with one another and our experience of the world.<br />
                    In clear language, full of wit and rich in examples, Kurzban explains the roots and implications of our inconsistent minds, and why it is perfectly natural to believe that everyone else is a hypocrite.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-everyone-else-is-a-hypocrite-evolution-and-the-modular-mind-robert-kurzban-abridged/">Why Everyone (Else) Is a Hypocrite : Evolution and the Modular Mind &#8211; Robert Kurzban (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smarter : The New Science of Building Brain Power &#8211; Dan Hurley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A riveting look at the birth of a new science.&#8221; -Daniel H. Pink, author of Drive When he was eight years old, Dan Hurley was labeled a &#8220;slow learner&#8221; because he still couldn&#8217;t read. Three years later, he had become a straight A student. Until the publication of a major study in 2008, psychologists believed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/">Smarter : The New Science of Building Brain Power &#8211; Dan Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A riveting look at the birth of a new science.&#8221; -Daniel H. Pink, author of Drive    </p>
<p>                    When he was eight years old, Dan Hurley was labeled a &#8220;slow learner&#8221; because he still couldn&#8217;t read.  Three years later, he had become a straight A student.     </p>
<p>                    Until the publication of a major study in 2008, psychologists believed that intelligence is fixed at birth, that IQ is like a number tattooed on the soul. The new study showed that people can increase their &#8220;fluid&#8221; intelligence through training.    </p>
<p>                    Hurley, who grew up to become an award-winning science journalist, first explored the topic in The New York Times Magazine. In Smarter, he digs deeper by meeting with the field&#8217;s leading researchers-and becoming a human guinea pig. After just three months of playing computer brain-training games, joining a boot-camp exercise program, learning to play the Renaissance lute, practicing mindfulness meditation and and even getting his brain zapped in the name of science, Hurley improved his fluid intelligence by sixteen percent.    </p>
<p>                    With humor and heart, Smarter chronicles the roiling field of intelligence research and delivers practical findings to sharpen the minds of children, young adults, seniors, and those with cognitive challenges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/">Smarter : The New Science of Building Brain Power &#8211; Dan Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mind Club : Who Thinks, What Feels, and Why it Matters &#8211; David Marantz, Daniel M. Wegner, Kurt Gray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-mind-club-who-thinks-what-feels-and-why-it-matters-david-marantz-daniel-m-wegner-kurt-gray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mind-club-who-thinks-what-feels-and-why-it-matters-david-marantz-daniel-m-wegner-kurt-gray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From dogs to gods, dive into the science of mysterious minds&#8211;including your own. Nothing seems more real than the minds of other people. When you consider what your boss is thinking or whether your spouse is happy, you are admitting them into the &#8220;mind club.&#8221; It&#8217;s easy to assume other humans can think and feel, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mind-club-who-thinks-what-feels-and-why-it-matters-david-marantz-daniel-m-wegner-kurt-gray-abridged/">The Mind Club : Who Thinks, What Feels, and Why it Matters &#8211; David Marantz, Daniel M. Wegner, Kurt Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From dogs to gods, dive into the science of mysterious minds&#8211;including your own.     </p>
<p>                    Nothing seems more real than the minds of other people. When you consider what your boss is thinking or whether your spouse is happy, you are admitting them into the &#8220;mind club.&#8221; It&#8217;s easy to assume other humans can think and feel, but what about a cow, a computer, a corporation? What kinds of minds do they have?     </p>
<p>                    Daniel M. Wegner and Kurt Gray are award-winning psychologists who have discovered that minds&#8211;while incredibly important&#8211;are a matter of perception. Their research opens a trove of new findings, with insights into human behavior that are fascinating, frightening, and funny. The Mind Club explains why we love some animals and eat others, why people debate the existence of God so intensely, how good people can be so cruel, and why robots make such poor lovers. By investigating the mind perception of extraordinary targets&#8211;animals, machines, comatose people, God&#8211;Wegner and Gray explain what it means to have a mind and why it matters so much.     </p>
<p>                    Fusing cutting-edge research and personal anecdotes, The Mind Club explores the moral dimensions of mind perception with wit and compassion, revealing the surprisingly simple basis for what compels us to love and hate, to harm and to protect.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mind-club-who-thinks-what-feels-and-why-it-matters-david-marantz-daniel-m-wegner-kurt-gray-abridged/">The Mind Club : Who Thinks, What Feels, and Why it Matters &#8211; David Marantz, Daniel M. Wegner, Kurt Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Subliminal : How Your Unconscious Mind Rules Your Behavior &#8211; Leonard Mlodinow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/subliminal-how-your-unconscious-mind-rules-your-behavior-leonard-mlodinow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/subliminal-how-your-unconscious-mind-rules-your-behavior-leonard-mlodinow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of The Drunkard&#8217;s Walk and coauthor of The Grand Design (with Stephen Hawking), a startling and eye-opening examination of how the unconscious mind shapes our experience of the world. Winner of the 2013 PEN/E.O. Wilson Literary Science Writing Award Over the past two decades of neurological research, it has become increasingly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/subliminal-how-your-unconscious-mind-rules-your-behavior-leonard-mlodinow-abridged/">Subliminal : How Your Unconscious Mind Rules Your Behavior &#8211; Leonard Mlodinow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of The Drunkard&#8217;s Walk and coauthor of The Grand Design (with Stephen Hawking), a startling and eye-opening examination of how the unconscious mind shapes our experience of the world.     </p>
<p>                     Winner of the 2013 PEN/E.O. Wilson Literary Science Writing Award     </p>
<p>                     Over the past two decades of neurological research, it has become increasingly clear that the way we experience the world&#8211;our perception, behavior, memory, and social judgment&#8211;is largely driven by the mind&#8217;s subliminal processes and not by the conscious ones, as we have long believed. In Subliminal, Leonard Mlodinow employs his signature concise, accessible explanations of the most obscure scientific subjects to unravel the complexities of the subliminal mind. In the process he shows the many ways it influences how we misperceive our relationships with family, friends, and business associates; how we misunderstand the reasons for our investment decisions; and how we misremember important events&#8211;along the way, changing our view of ourselves and the world around us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/subliminal-how-your-unconscious-mind-rules-your-behavior-leonard-mlodinow-abridged/">Subliminal : How Your Unconscious Mind Rules Your Behavior &#8211; Leonard Mlodinow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE ECONOMIST &#8220;The most important book on decision making since Daniel Kahneman&#8217;s Thinking, Fast and Slow.&#8221;&#8211;Jason Zweig, The Wall Street Journal Everyone would benefit from seeing further into the future, whether buying stocks, crafting policy, launching a new product, or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/">Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE ECONOMIST      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The most important book on decision making since Daniel Kahneman&#8217;s Thinking, Fast and Slow.&#8221;&#8211;Jason Zweig, The Wall Street Journal     </p>
<p>                     Everyone would benefit from seeing further into the future, whether buying stocks, crafting policy, launching a new product, or simply planning the week&#8217;s meals. Unfortunately, people tend to be terrible forecasters. As Wharton professor Philip Tetlock showed in a landmark 2005 study, even experts&#8217; predictions are only slightly better than chance. However, an important and underreported conclusion of that study was that some experts do have real foresight, and Tetlock has spent the past decade trying to figure out why. What makes some people so good? And can this talent be taught?     </p>
<p>                     In Superforecasting, Tetlock and coauthor Dan Gardner offer a masterwork on prediction, drawing on decades of research and the results of a massive, government-funded forecasting tournament. The Good Judgment Project involves tens of thousands of ordinary people&#8211;including a Brooklyn filmmaker, a retired pipe installer, and a former ballroom dancer&#8211;who set out to forecast global events. Some of the volunteers have turned out to be astonishingly good. They&#8217;ve beaten other benchmarks, competitors, and prediction markets. They&#8217;ve even beaten the collective judgment of intelligence analysts with access to classified information. They are superforecasters.     </p>
<p>                     In this groundbreaking and accessible book, Tetlock and Gardner show us how we can learn from this elite group. Weaving together stories of forecasting successes (the raid on Osama bin Laden&#8217;s compound) and failures (the Bay of Pigs) and interviews with a range of high-level decision makers, from David Petraeus to Robert Rubin, they show that good forecasting doesn&#8217;t require powerful computers or arcane methods. It involves gathering evidence from a variety of sources, thinking probabilistically, working in teams, keeping score, and being willing to admit error and change course.     </p>
<p>                    Superforecasting offers the first demonstrably effective way to improve our ability to predict the future&#8211;whether in business, finance, politics, international affairs, or daily life&#8211;and is destined to become a modern classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/">Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
