<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Psychotherapy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/psychotherapy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/psychotherapy/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Psychotherapy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/psychotherapy/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Client Centered Therapy (New Ed) &#8211; Carl Rogers</title>
		<link>/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Counselling & Advice Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Presenting the non-directive and related points of view in counselling and therapy, this book defines the progress recently made in the development of the techniques and basic philosophy of counselling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/">Client Centered Therapy (New Ed) &#8211; Carl Rogers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Presenting the non-directive and related points of view in counselling  and therapy, this book defines the progress recently made in the  development of the techniques and basic philosophy of counselling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/">Client Centered Therapy (New Ed) &#8211; Carl Rogers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Do The Work : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Nicole LePera</title>
		<link>/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;If LePera&#8217;s Instagram feed is full of aha moments illuminating the inner workings of your psyche, the revelations in the book are more like a full firework display.&#8217; Red magazine &#8216;This book is a must-read for anyone on a path of personal growth.&#8217; GABBY BERNSTEIN, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/">How To Do The Work : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Nicole LePera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If LePera&#8217;s Instagram feed is full of aha moments illuminating the inner workings of your psyche, the revelations in the book are more like a full firework display.&#8217; Red magazine    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is a must-read for anyone on a path of personal growth.&#8217; GABBY BERNSTEIN, author of number one New York Times bestsellers Super Attractor and The Universe Has Your Back    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book I wish I had read in my twenties.&#8217; ELIZABETH DAY, author of How to Fail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;How to Do the Work will transform how you see yourself and your ability to change. I believe this book could change lives, if not the world.&#8217;  HOLLY BOURNE, bestselling author of How Do You Like Me Now?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Want more from life? Looking for answers? How to Do the Work will teach you how to find them within yourself. A masterpiece of empowerment &#8211; this book changed my life and, trust me, it&#8217;ll change yours too.&#8217; MEL ROBBINS, author of The 5 Second Rule    </p>
<p>                    As a clinical psychologist, Dr Nicole LePera found herself frustrated by the limitations of traditional psychotherapy. Wanting more for her patients &#8211; and for herself &#8211; she began a journey to develop a united philosophy of mental, physical and spiritual health that equips people with the tools necessary to heal themselves. After experiencing the life-changing results herself, she began to share what she&#8217;d learned with others &#8211; and The Holistic Psychologist was born.    </p>
<p>                    Now Dr LePera is ready to share her much-requested protocol with the world. In How to Do the Work, she offers both a manifesto for self-healing and an essential guide to creating a more vibrant, authentic, and joyful life. Drawing on the latest research from both scientific research and healing modalities, Dr LePera helps us recognise how adverse experiences and trauma in childhood live with us, keeping us stuck engaging in patterns of codependency, emotional immaturity, and trauma bonds. Unless addressed, these self-sabotaging behaviours can quickly become cyclical, leaving people feeling unhappy, unfulfilled, and unwell.    </p>
<p>                    In How to Do the Work, Dr LePera offers readers the support and tools that will allow them to break free from destructive behaviours to reclaim and recreate their lives. Nothing short of a paradigm shift, this is a celebration of empowerment that will forever change the way we approach mental wellness and self-care.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/">How To Do The Work : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Nicole LePera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A witty, compelling guide to raising open-minded and morally grounded kids in these crazy times, with an approach that&#8217;s rooted in science, psychology, and faith &#8220;Groundbreaking, profound, frank and friendly.&#8221;&#8211;Wendy Mogel, PhD, author of The Blessing of a Skinned Knee NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY LIBRARY JOURNAL When Rev. Molly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/">Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A witty, compelling guide to raising open-minded and morally grounded kids in these crazy times, with an approach that&#8217;s rooted in science, psychology, and faith     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Groundbreaking, profound, frank and friendly.&#8221;&#8211;Wendy Mogel, PhD, author of The Blessing of a Skinned Knee     </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY LIBRARY JOURNAL     </p>
<p>                    When Rev. Molly Baskette and Dr. Ellen O&#8217;Donnell first met, they were both new mothers seeking parenting wisdom. They read a lot of books on the topic, but none of them contained practical suggestions that would help their families psychologically and spiritually while maintaining their progressive values: How do we teach the art of forgiving and serving others? How do we raise kids who are tolerant, curious, and honorable? And what about the sex talk?     </p>
<p>                    Taking matters into their own hands, Baskette and O&#8217;Donnell began creating actionable steps addressing these questions and more. This book is the fruit of their many conversations begun long ago during the daycare carpool, from angsty moments to hallelujahs.     </p>
<p>                    In Bless This Mess, readers will gain constructive tools as they learn how to talk to their children about social justice, money, God, ethics, bullying, disabilities, sexuality, and their bodies. Parents will also glean insights on how to serve others with joy, give generously and gratefully, and&#8211;perhaps most important&#8211;learn how to stop being so afraid all the damn time, even while raising kids in an increasingly chaotic and often scary world. With real-life examples, relatable personal stories, and strategies tailored to the toddler, preteen, or teenager, Bless This Mess guides parents of children at all stages of their development.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/">Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raising a Secure Child : How Circle of Security Parenting Can Help You Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Attachment, Emotional Resilience, and Freedom to Explore &#8211; Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, Bert Powell, Christine M. Benton, Daniel J. Siegel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raising-a-secure-child-how-circle-of-security-parenting-can-help-you-nurture-your-childs-attachment-emotional-resilience-and-freedom-to-explore-kent-hoffman-glen-cooper-bert-powell-christine/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Counselling & Advice Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raising-a-secure-child-how-circle-of-security-parenting-can-help-you-nurture-your-childs-attachment-emotional-resilience-and-freedom-to-explore-kent-hoffman-glen-cooper-bert-powell-christine/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s parents are constantly pressured to be perfect. But in striving to do everything right, we risk missing what children really need for lifelong emotional security. Now the simple, powerful &#8220;Circle of Security&#8221; parenting strategies that Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, and Bert Powell have taught thousands of families are available in self-help form for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-a-secure-child-how-circle-of-security-parenting-can-help-you-nurture-your-childs-attachment-emotional-resilience-and-freedom-to-explore-kent-hoffman-glen-cooper-bert-powell-christine/">Raising a Secure Child : How Circle of Security Parenting Can Help You Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Attachment, Emotional Resilience, and Freedom to Explore &#8211; Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, Bert Powell, Christine M. Benton, Daniel J. Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s parents are constantly pressured to be perfect. But in striving to do everything right, we risk missing what children really need for lifelong emotional security. Now the simple, powerful &#8220;Circle of Security&#8221; parenting strategies that Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, and Bert Powell have taught thousands of families are available in self-help form for the first time.    </p>
<p>                     You will learn:<br />
                     *How to balance nurturing and protectiveness with promoting your child&#8217;s independence.<br />
                     *What emotional needs a toddler or older child may be expressing through difficult behavior.<br />
                     *How your own upbringing affects your parenting style&#8211;and what you can do about it.    </p>
<p>                     Filled with vivid stories and unique practical tools, this book puts the keys to healthy attachment within everyone&#8217;s reach&#8211;self-understanding, flexibility, and the willingness to make and learn from mistakes. Self-assessment checklists can be downloaded and printed for ease of use.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-a-secure-child-how-circle-of-security-parenting-can-help-you-nurture-your-childs-attachment-emotional-resilience-and-freedom-to-explore-kent-hoffman-glen-cooper-bert-powell-christine/">Raising a Secure Child : How Circle of Security Parenting Can Help You Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Attachment, Emotional Resilience, and Freedom to Explore &#8211; Kent Hoffman, Glen Cooper, Bert Powell, Christine M. Benton, Daniel J. Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Humble Inquiry : The Gentle Art of Asking Instead of Telling &#8211; Edgar H. Schein, Peter A. Schein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/humble-inquiry-the-gentle-art-of-asking-instead-of-telling-edgar-h-schein-peter-a-schein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humble-inquiry-the-gentle-art-of-asking-instead-of-telling-edgar-h-schein-peter-a-schein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This worldwide bestseller offers simple guidance for building the kind of open and trusting relationships vital for tackling global systemic challenges and developing adaptive, innovative organizations&#8211;over 200,000 copies sold and translated into seventeen languages! We live, say Edgar and Peter Schein, in a culture of &#8220;tell.&#8221; All too often we tell others what we think [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humble-inquiry-the-gentle-art-of-asking-instead-of-telling-edgar-h-schein-peter-a-schein-abridged/">Humble Inquiry : The Gentle Art of Asking Instead of Telling &#8211; Edgar H. Schein, Peter A. Schein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This worldwide bestseller offers simple guidance for building the kind of open and trusting relationships vital for tackling global systemic challenges and developing adaptive, innovative organizations&#8211;over 200,000 copies sold and translated into seventeen languages!     </p>
<p>                    We live, say Edgar and Peter Schein, in a culture of &#8220;tell.&#8221; All too often we tell others what we think they need to know or should do. But whether we are leading or following, what matters most is we get to the truth. We have to develop a commitment to sharing vital facts and identifying faulty assumptions&#8211;it can mean the difference between success and failure. This is why we need Humble Inquiry more than ever.     </p>
<p>                    The Scheins define Humble Inquiry as &#8220;the gentle art of drawing someone out, of asking questions to which you do not know the answer, of building relationships based on curiosity and interest in the other person.&#8221; It was inspired by Edgar&#8217;s twenty years of work in high-hazard industries and the health-care system, where honest communication can literally mean the difference between life and death.     </p>
<p>                    In this new edition the authors look at how Humble Inquiry differs from other kinds of inquiry, offer examples of it in action, and show how to overcome the barriers that keep us telling when we should be asking. This edition offers a deepening and broadening of this concept, seeing it as not just a way of posing questions but an entire attitude that includes better listening, better responding to what others are trying to tell us, and better revealing of ourselves. Packed with case examples and a full chapter of exercises and simulations, this is a major contribution to how we see human conversational dynamics and relationships, presented in a compact, personal, and eminently practical way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humble-inquiry-the-gentle-art-of-asking-instead-of-telling-edgar-h-schein-peter-a-schein-abridged/">Humble Inquiry : The Gentle Art of Asking Instead of Telling &#8211; Edgar H. Schein, Peter A. Schein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I&#8217;m Ok, You&#8217;re Ok : A practical guide to Transactional Analysis &#8211; Thomas A. Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/im-ok-youre-ok-a-practical-guide-to-transactional-analysis-thomas-a-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychoanalytical Theory (Freudian Psychology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/im-ok-youre-ok-a-practical-guide-to-transactional-analysis-thomas-a-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This practical guide to Transactional Analysis is a unique approach to your problems. Hundreds of thousands of people have found this phenomenal breakthrough in psychotherapy a turning point in their lives. In sensible, non-technical language Thomas A Harris explains how to gain control of yourself, your relationships and your future &#8211; no matter what happened [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/im-ok-youre-ok-a-practical-guide-to-transactional-analysis-thomas-a-harris-abridged/">I&#8217;m Ok, You&#8217;re Ok : A practical guide to Transactional Analysis &#8211; Thomas A. Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This practical guide to Transactional Analysis is a unique approach to your problems.     </p>
<p>                    Hundreds of thousands of people have found this phenomenal breakthrough in psychotherapy a turning point in their lives.     </p>
<p>                    In sensible, non-technical language Thomas A Harris explains how to gain control of yourself, your relationships and your future &#8211; no matter what happened in the past.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/im-ok-youre-ok-a-practical-guide-to-transactional-analysis-thomas-a-harris-abridged/">I&#8217;m Ok, You&#8217;re Ok : A practical guide to Transactional Analysis &#8211; Thomas A. Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Age of Anxiety &#8211; Scott Stossel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER and SHORTLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2015 As recently as thirty-five years ago, anxiety did not exist as a diagnostic category. Today, it is the most common form of officially classified mental illness. Scott Stossel gracefully guides us across the terrain of an affliction that is pervasive yet too [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/">My Age of Anxiety &#8211; Scott Stossel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER and SHORTLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2015     </p>
<p>                    As recently as thirty-five years ago, anxiety did not exist as a diagnostic category. Today, it is the most common form of officially classified mental illness. Scott Stossel gracefully guides us across the terrain of an affliction that is pervasive yet too often misunderstood.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own long-standing battle with anxiety, Stossel presents an astonishing history, at once intimate and authoritative, of the efforts to understand the condition from medical, cultural, philosophical and experiential perspectives. He ranges from the earliest medical reports of Galen and Hippocrates, through later observations by Robert Burton and Soren Kierkegaard, to the investigations by great nineteenth-century scientists, such as Charles Darwin, William James and Sigmund Freud, as they began to explore its sources and causes, to the latest research by neuroscientists and geneticists. Stossel reports on famous individuals who struggled with anxiety, as well as the afflicted generations of his own family. His portrait of anxiety reveals not only the emotion&#8217;s myriad manifestations and the anguish it produces, but also the countless psychotherapies, medications and other (often outlandish) treatments that have been developed to counteract it. Stossel vividly depicts anxiety&#8217;s human toll &#8211; its crippling impact, its devastating power to paralyse &#8211; while at the same time exploring how those who suffer from it find ways to manage and control it.    </p>
<p>                    My Age of Anxiety is learned and empathetic, humorous and inspirational, offering the reader great insight into the biological, cultural and environmental factors that contribute to the affliction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/">My Age of Anxiety &#8211; Scott Stossel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Coach&#8217;s Survival Guide &#8211; Kim Morgan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-coachs-survival-guide-kim-morgan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-coachs-survival-guide-kim-morgan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Written by award-winning coach Kim Morgan, this book is aimed at new coaches working in a freelance or self-employed role. It is also a valuable resource for anyone involved in coaching, including trainers of coaches. The Coach&#8217;s Survival Guide is an easy to use, accessible book, grounded in practice and experience and including case studies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-coachs-survival-guide-kim-morgan-abridged/">The Coach&#8217;s Survival Guide &#8211; Kim Morgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Written by award-winning coach Kim Morgan, this book is aimed at new coaches working in a freelance or self-employed role. It is also a valuable resource for anyone involved in coaching, including trainers of coaches.     </p>
<p>                    The Coach&#8217;s Survival Guide is an easy to use, accessible book, grounded in practice and experience and including case studies drawn from real-life practice.  It is rooted in the real world, normalizing the insecurities felt by many coaches and acknowledging the realities of building a coaching business, while addressing the everyday issues that can hinder a coach&#8217;s performance or confidence.    </p>
<p>                    Kim covers issues such as:    </p>
<p>                    * Dealing with Impostor Syndrome<br />
                    * Establishing credibility<br />
                    * Contracting and boundaries<br />
                    * Coaching dilemmas<br />
                    * Building your coaching business<br />
                    * Self-care for coaches    </p>
<p>                    This new book is intended to be a survival guide so that coaches can access instant support for dilemmas that occur in their coaching practice.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Reading this book was like spending time with a close friend; a combination of warmth, wit and illumination.&#8221;<br />
                    Professor Damian Hughes, Professor of Organisational Psychology and Change    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book is an essential companion to anyone setting out as a professional coach. It provides knowledge, expertise and, perhaps most importantly, comfort for all the challenges that new coaches face.&#8221;<br />
                    Tom Preston, C.E.O. The Preston Associates    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;At last, here is a book that acknowledges the very real challenges involved in building a coaching business &#8211; and provides a blueprint for success!&#8221;<br />
                    John Perry, Coach and Principal Teaching Fellow, the University of Southampton, UK    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is a hugely practical and accessible support guide to help you address the challenges you will face in developing your coaching practice, from setting up your practice, generating clients and managing yourself in the coaching relationship.&#8221;<br />
                    John Leary-Joyce, Exec Chair AoEC International, author Fertile Void</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-coachs-survival-guide-kim-morgan-abridged/">The Coach&#8217;s Survival Guide &#8211; Kim Morgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Gathering : How We Meet and Why It Matters &#8211; Priya Parker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to create the most transformative meetings and moments &#8216;Priya Parker has created both an art and a science to gathering in ways that can bring joy and fulfilment to any meeting&#8217; Deepak Chopra &#8216;Hosts of all kinds, this is a must-read!&#8217; Chris Anderson, creator of TED &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; Being deprived of gathering has revealed just [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/">The Art of Gathering : How We Meet and Why It Matters &#8211; Priya Parker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to create the most transformative meetings and moments    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Priya Parker has created both an art and a science to gathering in ways that can bring joy and fulfilment to any meeting&#8217; Deepak Chopra     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hosts of all kinds, this is a must-read!&#8217; Chris Anderson, creator of TED    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;     </p>
<p>                    Being deprived of gathering has revealed just how important it is to us; to connect with others, collaborate, share ideas and create moving, life-affirming experiences.    </p>
<p>                    At a time when coming together is more crucial than ever, Priya Parker sets forth a human-centered approach to gathering that can help everyone create meaningful, memorable experiences in their lives, large and small, for work and for play.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on her wide expertise as a facilitator of high-powered gatherings around the world, Parker takes us inside events of all kinds to show what works, what doesn&#8217;t, and why. She investigates a wide array of gatherings &#8211; a court hearing, a flash-mob party, an Arab-Israeli summer camp &#8211; and explains how simple changes can invigorate any group experience. The result is a book full of exciting ideas of real-world applications and one that will forever alter the way you look at your next business meeting, dinner party and garden barbecue.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A long overdue and urgent manifesto&#8217; Seth Godin, New York Times bestselling author of This is Marketing</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/">The Art of Gathering : How We Meet and Why It Matters &#8211; Priya Parker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER From the UK&#8217;s favourite therapist, as seen on Channel 4&#8217;s Grayson&#8217;s Art Club. &#8216;A wonderful book&#8217; Richard Osman &#8216;So clear and true &#8230; Helpful for all relationships in life&#8217; Nigella Lawson &#8216;A fascinating read on the emotional baggage we all carry&#8217; Elizabeth Day ______________________________________________________________________________________ How can we have better relationships? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/">The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    From the UK&#8217;s favourite therapist, as seen on Channel 4&#8217;s Grayson&#8217;s Art Club.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wonderful book&#8217; Richard Osman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;So clear and true &#8230; Helpful for all relationships in life&#8217; Nigella Lawson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fascinating read on the emotional baggage we all carry&#8217; Elizabeth Day<br />
                    ______________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    How can we have better relationships?    </p>
<p>                    In this Sunday Times bestseller, leading psychotherapist Philippa Perry reveals the vital do&#8217;s and don&#8217;ts of relationships. This is a book for us all. Whether you are interested in understanding how your upbringing has shaped you, looking to handle your child&#8217;s feelings or wishing to support your partner, you will find indispensable information and realistic tips in these pages. Philippa Perry&#8217;s sane, sage and judgement-free advice is an essential resource on how to have the best possible relationships with the people who matter to you most.<br />
                    _____________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It gave me hope as a new parent&#8217; Babita Sharma    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This has genuinely had such a positive impact on my life and my relationship with my daughter&#8217; Josh Widdicombe    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;She writes with an inquisitive elegance rarely found in parenting guides &#8230; it is forgiving and persuasive&#8217;   Hadley Freeman, the Guardian      </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Philippa Perry is one of the wisest, most sane and secure people I&#8217;ve ever met&#8217; Decca Aitkenhead, Sunday Times Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/">The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Eating Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she). When a personal crisis causes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she).    </p>
<p>                    When a personal crisis causes her world to come crashing down, Lori Gottlieb &#8211; an experienced therapist with a thriving practice in Los Angeles &#8211; is suddenly adrift. Enter Wendell, himself a veteran therapist with an unconventional style, whose sessions with Gottlieb will prove transformative for her.    </p>
<p>                    As Gottlieb explores the inner chambers of her own patients&#8217; lives &#8211; a self-absorbed Hollywood producer, a young newlywed diagnosed with a terminal illness, a senior citizen who feels she has nothing to live for, and a self-destructive twenty-something who can&#8217;t stop hooking up with the wrong guys &#8211; she finds that the questions they are struggling with are the very questions she is bringing to Wendell.    </p>
<p>                    Taking place over one year, and beginning with the devastating event that lands her in Wendell&#8217;s office, Maybe You Should Talk to Someone offers a rare and candid insight into a profession that is conventionally bound with rules and secrecy. Told with charm and compassion, vulnerability and humour, it&#8217;s also the story of an incredible relationship between two therapists, and a disarmingly funny and illuminating account of our own mysterious inner lives, as well as our power to transform them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thoughts Without A Thinker : Psychotherapy from a Buddhist Perspective &#8211; Mark Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The line between psychology and spirituality has blurred, as clinicians, their patients, and religious seekers explore new perspectives on the self. A landmark contribution to the field of psychoanalysis, Thoughts Without a Thinker describes the unique psychological contributions offered by the teachings of Buddhism. Drawing upon his own experiences as a psychotherapist and meditator, New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/">Thoughts Without A Thinker : Psychotherapy from a Buddhist Perspective &#8211; Mark Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The line between psychology and spirituality has blurred, as clinicians, their patients, and religious seekers explore new perspectives on the self. A landmark contribution to the field of psychoanalysis,  Thoughts Without a Thinker  describes the unique psychological contributions offered by the teachings of Buddhism. Drawing upon his own experiences as a psychotherapist and meditator, New York-based psychiatrist Mark Epstein lays out the path to meditation-inspired healing, and offers a revolutionary new understanding of what constitutes a healthy emotional life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/">Thoughts Without A Thinker : Psychotherapy from a Buddhist Perspective &#8211; Mark Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you    </p>
<p>                    Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around the room and see a table and a pair of pliers. How would you solve the problem?    </p>
<p>                    When confronted with challenges, most people let habits rule them (in this case, ignoring the pliers, the creative tool at your disposal). That is not surprising when you realise that at least a third of our waking hours are lived on auto-pilot &#8211; ruminating over past events, clicking through websites trawling for updates and the like. Such unconscious thoughts and actions are powerful. But the habits of the mind do not have to control us &#8211; we can steer them.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on hundreds of fascinating studies, psychologist Jeremy Dean &#8211; the mind behind the hugely popular and insightful website PsyBlog &#8211; shares how the new brain science of habit can be harnessed to your benefit, whether you&#8217;re hoping to eat moreveg, take an evening run, clear out your email backlog, or be more creative when faced with challenges at work and at home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fully Present : The Science, Art, and Practice of Mindfulness &#8211; Diana Winston, Susan Smalley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fully-present-the-science-art-and-practice-of-mindfulness-diana-winston-susan-smalley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fully-present-the-science-art-and-practice-of-mindfulness-diana-winston-susan-smalley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mindfulness,the art of paying attention with an open and curious mind to present-moment experiences,has attracted ever-growing interest and tens of thousands of practitioners, who have come to the discipline from both within and outside the Buddhist tradition. In Fully Present, leading mindfulness researchers and educators Dr. Sue Smalley and Diana Winston provide an all-in-one guide [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fully-present-the-science-art-and-practice-of-mindfulness-diana-winston-susan-smalley-abridged/">Fully Present : The Science, Art, and Practice of Mindfulness &#8211; Diana Winston, Susan Smalley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mindfulness,the art of paying attention with an open and curious mind to present-moment experiences,has attracted ever-growing interest and tens of thousands of practitioners, who have come to the discipline from both within and outside the Buddhist tradition. In Fully Present, leading mindfulness researchers and educators Dr. Sue Smalley and Diana Winston provide an all-in-one guide for anyone interested in bringing mindfulness to daily life as a means of enhancing well-being. Fully Present provides both a scientific explanation for how mindfulness positively and powerfully affects the brain and the body as well as practical guidance to develop both a practice and mindfulness in daily living, not only through meditation but also during daily experiences, such as waiting in line at the supermarket, exercising, or facing difficult news.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fully-present-the-science-art-and-practice-of-mindfulness-diana-winston-susan-smalley-abridged/">Fully Present : The Science, Art, and Practice of Mindfulness &#8211; Diana Winston, Susan Smalley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Radical Acceptance : Embracing Your Life With the Heart of a Buddha &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/radical-acceptance-embracing-your-life-with-the-heart-of-a-buddha-tara-brach-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/radical-acceptance-embracing-your-life-with-the-heart-of-a-buddha-tara-brach-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For many of us, feelings of deficiency are right around the corner. It doesn&#8217;t take much&#8211;just hearing of someone else&#8217;s accomplishments, being criticized, getting into an argument, making a mistake at work&#8211;to make us feel that we are not okay. Beginning to understand how our lives have become ensnared in this trance of unworthiness is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-acceptance-embracing-your-life-with-the-heart-of-a-buddha-tara-brach-abridged/">Radical Acceptance : Embracing Your Life With the Heart of a Buddha &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For many of us, feelings of deficiency are right around the corner. It doesn&#8217;t take much&#8211;just hearing of someone else&#8217;s accomplishments, being criticized, getting into an argument, making a mistake at work&#8211;to make us feel that we are not okay. Beginning to understand how our lives have become ensnared in this trance of unworthiness is our first step toward reconnecting with who we really are and what it means to live fully.<br />
                     &#8211;from Radical Acceptance     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Believing that something is wrong with us is a deep and tenacious suffering,&#8221; says Tara Brach at the start of this illuminating book. This suffering emerges in crippling self-judgments and conflicts in our relationships, in addictions and perfectionism, in loneliness and overwork&#8211;all the forces that keep our lives constricted and unfulfilled. Radical Acceptance offers a path to freedom, including the day-to-day practical guidance developed over Dr. Brach&#8217;s twenty years of work with therapy clients and Buddhist students.     </p>
<p>                     Writing with great warmth and clarity, Tara Brach brings her teachings alive through personal stories and case histories, fresh interpretations of Buddhist tales, and guided meditations. Step by step, she leads us to trust our innate goodness, showing how we can develop the balance of clear-sightedness and compassion that is the essence of Radical Acceptance. Radical Acceptance does not mean self-indulgence or passivity. Instead it empowers genuine change: healing fear and shame and helping to build loving, authentic relationships. When we stop being at war with ourselves, we are free to live fully every precious moment of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-acceptance-embracing-your-life-with-the-heart-of-a-buddha-tara-brach-abridged/">Radical Acceptance : Embracing Your Life With the Heart of a Buddha &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Helping: How to Offer, Give, and Receive Help &#8211; Edgar H. Schein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/helping-how-to-offer-give-and-receive-help-edgar-h-schein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/helping-how-to-offer-give-and-receive-help-edgar-h-schein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Helping is a fundamental human activity, but it can also be a frustrating one. All too often, to our bewilderment, our sincere offers of help are resented, resisted, or refused&#8211;and we often react the same way when people try to help us. Why is it so difficult to provide or accept help? How can we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/helping-how-to-offer-give-and-receive-help-edgar-h-schein-abridged/">Helping: How to Offer, Give, and Receive Help &#8211; Edgar H. Schein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Helping is a fundamental human activity, but it can also be a frustrating one. All too often, to our bewilderment, our sincere offers of help are resented, resisted, or refused&#8211;and we often react the same way when people try to help us. Why is it so difficult to provide or accept help? How can we make the whole process easier?     </p>
<p>                     In this seminal book on the topic, corporate culture and organizational development guru Ed Schein analyzes the social and psychological dynamics common to all types of helping relationships, explains why help is often not helpful, and shows what any would-be helpers must do to ensure that their assistance is both welcomed and genuinely useful.     </p>
<p>                     The moment of asking for and offering help is a delicate and complex one, fraught with inequities and ambiguities. Schein helps us navigate that moment so we avoid potential pitfalls, mitigate power imbalances, and establish a solid foundation of trust. He identifies three roles a helper can play, explaining which one is nearly always the best starting point if we are to provide truly effective help. So that readers can determine exactly what kind of help is needed, he describes an inquiry process that puts the helper and the recipient on an equal footing. These dynamics not only apply to all kinds of one-on-one helping in personal and professional relationships, teaching, social work, and medicine but also can be usefully applied to teamwork and to organizational leadership.     </p>
<p>                     Using examples from many types of relationships&#8211;doctors and patients, consultants and clients, husbands and wives&#8211;Ed Schein offers a concise, definitive analysis of what it takes to establish successful, mutually satisfying helping relationships.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/helping-how-to-offer-give-and-receive-help-edgar-h-schein-abridged/">Helping: How to Offer, Give, and Receive Help &#8211; Edgar H. Schein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paediatric Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;courageous, compassionate, and rigorous every-person&#8217;s guide&#8221; (Christina Bethell, PhD, Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health) that shows the link between Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs) and diseases, and how to cope and heal from these emotional traumas. Your biography becomes your biology. The emotional trauma we suffer as children not only shapes our emotional [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/">Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;courageous, compassionate, and rigorous every-person&#8217;s guide&#8221; (Christina Bethell, PhD, Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health) that shows the link between Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs)  and diseases, and how to cope and heal from these emotional traumas.    </p>
<p>                    Your biography becomes your biology. The emotional trauma we suffer as children not only shapes our emotional lives as adults, but it also affects our physical health, longevity, and overall well-being. Scientists now know on a bio-chemical level exactly how parents&#8217; chronic fights, divorce, death in the family, being bullied or hazed, and growing up with a hypercritical, alcoholic, or mentally ill parent can leave permanent, physical &#8220;fingerprints&#8221; on our brains.    </p>
<p>                    When children encounter sudden or chronic adversity, stress hormones cause powerful changes in the body, altering the body&#8217;s chemistry. The developing immune system and brain react to this chemical barrage by permanently resetting children&#8217;s stress response to &#8220;high,&#8221; which in turn can have a devastating impact on their mental and physical health as they grow up.    </p>
<p>                    Donna Jackson Nakazawa shares stories from people who have recognized and overcome their adverse experiences, shows why some children are more immune to stress than others, and explains why women are at particular risk. &#8220;Groundbreaking&#8221; (Tara Brach, PhD, author of Radical Acceptance) in its research, inspiring in its clarity, Childhood Disrupted explains how you can reset your biology-and help your loved ones find ways to heal. &#8220;A truly important gift of understanding-illuminates the heartbreaking costs of childhood trauma and like good medicine offers the promising science of healing and prevention&#8221; (Jack Kornfield, author of A Path With Heart).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/">Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Becoming Attached : First Relationships &#8211; Robert Karen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/becoming-attached-first-relationships-robert-karen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/becoming-attached-first-relationships-robert-karen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The struggle to understand the infant-parent bond ranks as one of the great quests of modern psychology, one that touches us deeply because it holds so many clues to how we become who we are. How are our personalities formed? How do our early struggles with our parents reappear in the way we relate to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-attached-first-relationships-robert-karen-abridged/">Becoming Attached : First Relationships &#8211; Robert Karen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The struggle to understand the infant-parent bond ranks as one of the great quests of modern psychology, one that touches us deeply because it holds so many clues to how we become who we are. How are our personalities formed? How do our early struggles with our parents reappear in the way we relate to others as adults? Why do we repeat with our own children&#8211;seemingly against our will&#8211;the very behaviors we most disliked about our parents? In Becoming Attached, psychologist and noted journalist Robert Karen offers fresh insight into some of the most fundamental and fascinating questions of emotional life.<br />
                     Karen begins by tracing the history of attachment theory through the controversial work of John Bowlby, a British psychoanalyst, and Mary Ainsworth, an American developmental psychologist, who together launched a revolution in child psychology. Karen tells about their personal and professional struggles, their groundbreaking discoveries, and the recent flowering of attachment theory research in universities all over the world, making it one of the century&#8217;s most enduring ideas in developmental psychology.<br />
                     In a world of working parents and makeshift day care, the need to assess the impact of parenting styles and the bond between child and caregiver is more urgent than ever. Karen addresses such issues as: What do children need to feel that the world is a positive place and that they have value? Is day care harmful for children under one year? What experiences in infancy will enable a person to develop healthy relationships as an adult?, and he demonstrates how different approaches to mothering are associated with specific infant behaviors, such as clinginess, avoidance, or secure exploration. He shows how these patterns become ingrained and how they reveal themselves at age two, in the preschool years, in middle childhood, and in adulthood. And, with thought-provoking insights, he gives us a new understanding of how negative patterns and insecure attachment can be changed and resolved throughout a person&#8217;s life.<br />
                     The infant is in many ways a great mystery to us. Every one of us has been one; many of us have lived with or raised them. Becoming Attached is not just a voyage of discovery in child emotional development and its pertinence to adult life but a voyage of personal discovery as well, for it is impossible to read this book without reflecting on one&#8217;s own life as a child, a parent, and an intimate partner in love or marriage.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-attached-first-relationships-robert-karen-abridged/">Becoming Attached : First Relationships &#8211; Robert Karen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It Didn&#8217;t Start With You : How Inherited Family Trauma Shapes Who We Are and How to End the Cycle &#8211; Mark Wolynn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/it-didnt-start-with-you-how-inherited-family-trauma-shapes-who-we-are-and-how-to-end-the-cycle-mark-wolynn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/it-didnt-start-with-you-how-inherited-family-trauma-shapes-who-we-are-and-how-to-end-the-cycle-mark-wolynn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Inherited family trauma is currently an area of growing interest, as science increasingly explores what we know intuitively: that the effects of trauma can pass from one generation to the next, and that the answers to some of our greatest life problems often lie not within our own story, but in the experiences of our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-didnt-start-with-you-how-inherited-family-trauma-shapes-who-we-are-and-how-to-end-the-cycle-mark-wolynn-abridged/">It Didn&#8217;t Start With You : How Inherited Family Trauma Shapes Who We Are and How to End the Cycle &#8211; Mark Wolynn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Inherited family trauma is currently an area of growing interest, as science increasingly explores what we know intuitively: that the effects of trauma can pass from one generation to the next, and that the answers to some of our greatest life problems often lie not within our own story, but in the experiences of our parents, grandparents, great-grandparents and extended family. Here, pioneer Mark Wolyn shows readers how they can overcome inherited trauma and reclaim their lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-didnt-start-with-you-how-inherited-family-trauma-shapes-who-we-are-and-how-to-end-the-cycle-mark-wolynn-abridged/">It Didn&#8217;t Start With You : How Inherited Family Trauma Shapes Who We Are and How to End the Cycle &#8211; Mark Wolynn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Minimalist Parenting : Enjoy Modern Family Life More by Doing Less &#8211; Christine K. Koh, Asha Dornfest (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/minimalist-parenting-enjoy-modern-family-life-more-by-doing-less-christine-k-koh-asha-dornfest-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/minimalist-parenting-enjoy-modern-family-life-more-by-doing-less-christine-k-koh-asha-dornfest-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re in the midst of a parenting climate that feeds on more. More expert advice, more gear, more fear about competition and safety, and more choices to make about education, nutrition, even entertainment. The result? Overwhelmed, confused parents and overscheduled, overparented kids. In MINIMALIST PARENTING, Christine Koh and Asha Dornfest offer a fresh approach to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/minimalist-parenting-enjoy-modern-family-life-more-by-doing-less-christine-k-koh-asha-dornfest-abridged/">Minimalist Parenting : Enjoy Modern Family Life More by Doing Less &#8211; Christine K. Koh, Asha Dornfest (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re in the midst of a parenting climate that feeds on more. More expert advice, more gear, more fear about competition and safety, and more choices to make about education, nutrition, even entertainment. The result? Overwhelmed, confused parents and overscheduled, overparented kids.    </p>
<p>                    In MINIMALIST PARENTING, Christine Koh and Asha Dornfest offer a fresh approach to navigating all of this conflicting background &#8220;noise.&#8221;  They show how to tune into your family&#8217;s unique values and priorities and confidently identify the activities, stuff, information, and people that truly merit space in your life.    </p>
<p>                    The book begins by showing the value of a minimalist approach, backed by the authors&#8217; personal experience practicing it. It then leads parents through practical strategies for managing time, decluttering the home space, simplifying mealtimes, streamlining recreation, and prioritizing self-care. Filled with parents&#8217; personal stories, readers will come away with a unique plan for a simpler life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/minimalist-parenting-enjoy-modern-family-life-more-by-doing-less-christine-k-koh-asha-dornfest-abridged/">Minimalist Parenting : Enjoy Modern Family Life More by Doing Less &#8211; Christine K. Koh, Asha Dornfest (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
