<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Urban &amp; Municipal Planning Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/urban-municipal-planning/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/urban-municipal-planning/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Urban &amp; Municipal Planning Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/urban-municipal-planning/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Happy City : Transforming Our Lives Through Urban Design &#8211; Charles Montgomery (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[City & Town Planning - Architectural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban & Municipal Planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Happy City is the story of how the solutions to this century&#8217;s problems lie in unlocking the secrets to great city living This is going to be the century of the city. But what actually makes a good city? Why are some cities a joy to live in? As Charles Montgomery reveals, it&#8217;s not how [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/">Happy City : Transforming Our Lives Through Urban Design &#8211; Charles Montgomery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happy City is the story of how the solutions to this century&#8217;s problems lie in unlocking the secrets to great city living    </p>
<p>                    This is going to be the century of the city. But what actually makes a good city? Why are some cities a joy to live in?    </p>
<p>                    As Charles Montgomery reveals, it&#8217;s not how much money your neighbours earn, or how pleasant the climate is that makes the most difference. Journeying to dozens of cities &#8211; from Atlanta to Bogota to Vancouver &#8211; he talks to the new champions of the happy city to explore the urban innovations already transforming people&#8217;s lives. He meets the visionary Colombian mayor who turned some of the world&#8217;s most dangerous roads into an urban cycling haven; the Danish architect who brought the lessons of medieval Tuscan towns to modern-day Copenhagen; and the New York City transport commissioner who turned the gridlock of Times Square into a place to lounge in the sun.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the lessons from their stories, from brain science, and from the fascinating realm of urban experimentation, Happy City offers solutions we can all use to improve our livesandshows that simple changes can make all the difference.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Do we live in neighbourhoods that make us happy? Montgomery encourages us to ask without embarrassment, and to think intelligently about the answer&#8217; The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Excellent . . . Montgomery believes in the importance of smart town planning and Happy City is a compendium of its major ideas&#8217; Will Dean, Independent    </p>
<p>                    Charles Montgomery is a journalist and urban experimentalist from Vancouver, Canada. His writings on urban planning, psychology, culture, and history have appeared in magazines and journals on three continents. He is the author of one previous book, and was an original member of the BMW Guggenheim Lab.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/">Happy City : Transforming Our Lives Through Urban Design &#8211; Charles Montgomery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ghetto : The Invention of a Place, the History of an Idea &#8211; Professor of Sociology Mitchell Duneier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban & Municipal Planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book of 2016 Winner of the Zócalo Public Square Book Prize On March 29, 1516, the city council of Venice issued a decree forcing Jews to live in il geto&#8211;a closed quarter named for the copper foundry that once occupied the area. The term stuck. In this sweeping and original [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/">Ghetto : The Invention of a Place, the History of an Idea &#8211; Professor of Sociology Mitchell Duneier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book of 2016<br />
                    Winner of the Zócalo Public Square Book Prize     </p>
<p>                    On March 29, 1516, the city council of Venice issued a decree forcing Jews to live in il geto&#8211;a closed quarter named for the copper foundry that once occupied the area. The term stuck.     </p>
<p>                    In this sweeping and original account, Mitchell Duneier traces the idea of the ghetto from its beginnings in the sixteenth century and its revival by the Nazis to the present. As Duneier shows, we cannot comprehend the entanglements of race, poverty, and place in America today without recalling the ghettos of Europe, as well as earlier efforts to understand the problems of the American city.     </p>
<p>                    Ghetto is the story of the scholars and activists who tried to achieve that understanding. As Duneier shows, their efforts to wrestle with race and poverty cannot be divorced from their individual biographies, which often included direct encounters with prejudice and discrimination in the academy and elsewhere. Using new and forgotten sources, Duneier introduces us to Horace Cayton and St. Clair Drake, graduate students whose conception of the South Side of Chicago established a new paradigm for thinking about Northern racism and poverty in the 1940s. We learn how the psychologist Kenneth Clark subsequently linked Harlem&#8217;s slum conditions with the persistence of black powerlessness, and we follow the controversy over Daniel Patrick Moynihan&#8217;s report on the black family. We see how the sociologist William Julius Wilson redefined the debate about urban America as middle-class African Americans increasingly escaped the ghetto and the country retreated from racially specific remedies. And we trace the education reformer Geoffrey Canada&#8217;s efforts to transform the lives of inner-city children with ambitious interventions, even as other reformers sought to help families escape their neighborhoods altogether.     </p>
<p>                    Duneier offers a clear-eyed assessment of the thinkers and doers who have shaped American ideas about urban poverty&#8211;and the ghetto. The result is a valuable new estimation of an age-old concept.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/">Ghetto : The Invention of a Place, the History of an Idea &#8211; Professor of Sociology Mitchell Duneier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Dark Age : Technology and the End of the Future &#8211; James Bridle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/new-dark-age-technology-and-the-end-of-the-future-james-bridle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban & Municipal Planning]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/new-dark-age-technology-and-the-end-of-the-future-james-bridle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We live in times of increasing inscrutability. Our news feeds are filled with unverified, unverifiable speculation, much of it automatically generated by anonymous software. As a result, we no longer understand what is happening around us. Underlying all of these trends is a single idea: the belief that quantitative data can provide a coherent model [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-dark-age-technology-and-the-end-of-the-future-james-bridle-abridged/">New Dark Age : Technology and the End of the Future &#8211; James Bridle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We live in times of increasing inscrutability. Our news feeds are filled with unverified, unverifiable speculation, much of it automatically generated by anonymous software. As a result, we no longer understand what is happening around us. Underlying all of these trends is a single idea: the belief that quantitative data can provide a coherent model of the world, and the efficacy of computable information to provide us with ways of acting within it. Yet the sheer volume of information available to us today reveals less than we hope. Rather, it heralds a new Dark Age: a world of ever-increasing incomprehension.    </p>
<p>                    In his brilliant new work, leading artist and writer James Bridle offers us a warning against the future in which the contemporary promise of a new technologically assisted Enlightenment may just deliver its opposite: an age of complex uncertainty, predictive algorithms, surveillance, and the hollowing out of empathy. Surveying the history of art, technology and information systems he reveals the dark clouds that gather over discussions of the digital sublime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-dark-age-technology-and-the-end-of-the-future-james-bridle-abridged/">New Dark Age : Technology and the End of the Future &#8211; James Bridle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
