<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Computer Viruses, Trojans &amp; Worms Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/computer-viruses-trojans-worms/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/computer-viruses-trojans-worms/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Computer Viruses, Trojans &amp; Worms Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/computer-viruses-trojans-worms/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan. Kaplan probes the inner corridors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan.    </p>
<p>                     Kaplan probes the inner corridors of the National Security Agency, the beyond-top-secret cyber units in the Pentagon, the &#8220;information warfare&#8221; squads of the military services, and the national security debates in the White House, to tell this never-before-told story of the officers, policymakers, scientists, and spies who devised this new form of warfare and who have been planning and (more often than people know) fighting these wars for decades.    </p>
<p>                     From the 1991 Gulf War to conflicts in Haiti, Serbia, Syria, the former Soviet republics, Iraq, and Iran, where cyber warfare played a significant role, Dark Territory chronicles, in fascinating detail, a little-known past that shines an unsettling light on our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award! There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life. In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award!<br />
                    There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life.<br />
                    In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest spam and hacker operations targeting Americans and their bank accounts. Tracing the rise, fall, and alarming resurrection of the digital mafia behind the two largest spam pharmacies-and countless viruses, phishing, and spyware attacks-he delivers the first definitive narrative of the global spam problem and its threat to consumers everywhere.<br />
                    Blending cutting-edge research, investigative reporting, and firsthand interviews, this terrifying true story reveals how we unwittingly invite these digital thieves into our lives every day. From unassuming computer programmers right next door to digital mobsters like &#8220;Cosma&#8221;-who unleashed a massive malware attack that has stolen thousands of Americans&#8217; logins and passwords-Krebs uncovers the shocking lengths to which these people will go to profit from our data and our wallets.<br />
                    Not only are hundreds of thousands of Americans exposing themselves to fraud and dangerously toxic products from rogue online pharmacies, but even those who never open junk messages are at risk. As Krebs notes, spammers can-and do-hack into accounts through these emails, harvest personal information like usernames and passwords, and sell them on the digital black market. The fallout from this global epidemic doesn&#8217;t just cost consumers and companies billions, it costs lives too.<br />
                    Fast-paced and utterly gripping, Spam Nation ultimately proposes concrete solutions for protecting ourselves online and stemming this tidal wave of cybercrime-before it&#8217;s too late.<br />
                    &#8220;Krebs&#8217;s talent for exposing the weaknesses in online security has earned him respect in the IT business and loathing among cybercriminals&#8230; His track record of scoops&#8230;has helped him become the rare blogger who supports himself on the strength of his reputation for hard-nosed reporting.&#8221; -Bloomberg Businessweek</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
