<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Psycholinguistics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/psycholinguistics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/psycholinguistics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Psycholinguistics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/psycholinguistics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Sense of Style : The Thinking Person&#8217;s Guide to Writing in the 21st Century &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Pinker, the bestselling author of The Language Instinct, deploys his gift for explaining big ideas in The Sense of Style &#8211; an entertaining writing guide for the 21st century What is the secret of good prose? Does writing well even matter in an age of instant communication? Should we care? In this funny, thoughtful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Sense of Style : The Thinking Person&#8217;s Guide to Writing in the 21st Century &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steven Pinker, the bestselling author of The Language Instinct, deploys his gift for explaining big ideas in The Sense of Style &#8211; an entertaining writing guide for the 21st century    </p>
<p>                    What is the secret of good prose? Does writing well even matter in an age of instant communication? Should we care? In this funny, thoughtful book about the modern art of writing, Steven Pinker shows us why we all need a sense of style.    </p>
<p>                    More than ever before, the currency of our social and cultural lives is the written word, from Twitter and texting to blogs, e-readers and old-fashioned books. But most style guides fail to prepare people for the challenges of writing in the 21st century, portraying it as a minefield of grievous errors rather than a form of pleasurable mastery. They fail to deal with an inescapable fact about language: it changes over time, adapted by millions of writers and speakers to their needs. Confusing changes in the world with moral decline, every generation believes the kids today are degrading society and taking language with it. A guide for the new millennium, writes Steven Pinker, has to be different.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the latest research in linguistics and cognitive science, Steven Pinker replaces the recycled dogma of previous style guides with reason and evidence. This thinking person&#8217;s guide to good writing shows why style still matters: in communicating effectively, in enhancing the spread of ideas, in earning a reader&#8217;s trust and, not least, in adding beauty to the world. Eye-opening, mind-expanding and cheerful, The Sense of Style shows that good style is part of what it means to be human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Sense of Style : The Thinking Person&#8217;s Guide to Writing in the 21st Century &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind. In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind.    </p>
<p>                    In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and how it evolved. With deft use of examples of humor and wordplay, Steven Pinker weaves our vast knowledge of language into a compelling story: language is a human instinct, wired into our brains by evolution. The Language Instinct received the William James Book Prize from the American Psychological Association and the Public Interest Award from the Linguistics Society of America. This edition includes an update on advances in the science of language since The Language Instinct was first published.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Stuff of Thought : Language as a Window into Human Nature &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-stuff-of-thought-language-as-a-window-into-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-stuff-of-thought-language-as-a-window-into-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Stuff of Thought: Language as a Window into Human Nature, Steven Pinker looks at how the relationship between words and thoughts can help us understand who we are. Why do so many swear words involve topics like sex, bodily functions or the divine? Why do some children&#8217;s names thrive while others fall out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stuff-of-thought-language-as-a-window-into-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Stuff of Thought : Language as a Window into Human Nature &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Stuff of Thought: Language as a Window into Human Nature, Steven Pinker looks at how the relationship between words and thoughts can help us understand who we are.    </p>
<p>                      Why do so many swear words involve topics like sex, bodily functions or the divine? Why do some children&#8217;s names thrive while others fall out of favour? Why do we threaten and bribe and seduce in such elaborate, often comical ways? How can a choice of metaphor damn a politician or start a war? And why do we rarely say what we actually mean?     </p>
<p>                      Language, as Steven Pinker shows, is at the heart of our lives, and through the way we use it &#8211; whether to inform, persuade, entertain or manipulate &#8211; we can glimpse the very essence of what makes us human.     </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Awesome&#8217;<br />
                      Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Highly entertaining &#8230; funny and thought-provoking&#8217;<br />
                      The Times    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Anyone interested in language should read The Stuff of Thought &#8230; moments of genuine revelation and some very good jokes&#8217;<br />
                      Mark Haddon, Sunday Telegraph Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;No one writes about language as clearly as Steven Pinker, and this is his best book yet&#8217;<br />
                      David Crystal, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                      Steven Pinker is the Johnstone Family Professor in the Department of Psychology at Harvard University. Until 2003, he taught in the Department of Brain and Cognitive Sciences at MIT. He conducts research on language and cognition, writes for publications such as The New York Times, Time and Slate, and is the author of six books, including The Language Instinct, How the Mind Works and The Blank Slate.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stuff-of-thought-language-as-a-window-into-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Stuff of Thought : Language as a Window into Human Nature &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. But swearing is also a uniquely well-suited lens through which to look at history, offering a fascinating record of what people care about on the<br />
                    deepest levels of a culture-what&#8217;s divine, what&#8217;s terrifying, and what&#8217;s taboo.     </p>
<p>                    Holy Sh*t tells the story of two kinds of swearing-obscenities and oaths-from ancient Rome and the Bible to today. With humor and insight, Melissa Mohr takes readers on a journey to discover how &#8220;swearing&#8221; has come to include both testifying with your hand on the Bible and calling someone a *#$&#038;!* when they cut you off on the highway. She explores obscenities in ancient Rome-which were remarkably similar to our own-and unearths the history of religious oaths in the Middle Ages,<br />
                    when swearing (or not swearing) an oath was often a matter of life and death. Holy Sh*t also explains the advancement of civility and corresponding censorship of language in the 18th century, considers the rise of racial slurs after World War II, examines the physiological effects of swearing (increased heart<br />
                    rate and greater pain tolerance), and answers a question that preoccupies the FCC, the US Senate, and anyone who has recently overheard little kids at a playground: are we swearing more now than people did in the past?     </p>
<p>                    A gem of lexicography and cultural history, Holy Sh*t is a serious exploration of obscenity-and it also just might expand your repertoire of words to choose from the next time you shut your finger in the car door.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
