<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Business Negotiation Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/business-negotiation/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/business-negotiation/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Business Negotiation Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/business-negotiation/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</title>
		<link>/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Golf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>President Donald J. Trump lays out his professional and personal worldview in this classic work&#8211;a firsthand account of the rise of America&#8217;s foremost deal-maker. &#8220;I like thinking big. I always have. To me it&#8217;s very simple: If you&#8217;re going to be thinking anyway, you might as well think big.&#8221;&#8211;Donald J. Trump Here is Trump in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/">Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>President Donald J. Trump lays out his professional and personal worldview in this classic work&#8211;a firsthand account of the rise of America&#8217;s foremost deal-maker. </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I like thinking big. I always have. To me it&#8217;s very simple: If you&#8217;re going to be thinking anyway, you might as well think big.&#8221;&#8211;Donald J. Trump </p>
<p>                    Here is Trump in action&#8211;how he runs his organization and how he runs his life&#8211;as he meets the people he needs to meet, chats with family and friends, clashes with enemies, and challenges conventional thinking. But even a maverick plays by rules, and Trump has formulated time-tested guidelines for success. He isolates the common elements in his greatest accomplishments; he shatters myths; he names names, spells out the zeros, and fully reveals the deal-maker&#8217;s art. And throughout, Trump talks&#8211;really talks&#8211;about how he does it. Trump: The Art of the Deal is an unguarded look at the mind of a brilliant entrepreneur&#8211;the ultimate read for anyone interested in the man behind the spotlight. </p>
<p>                     Praise for Trump: The Art of the Deal </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Trump makes one believe for a moment in the American dream again.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times  </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Donald Trump is a deal maker. He is a deal maker the way lions are carnivores and water is wet.&#8221;&#8211;Chicago Tribune</p>
<p>                     &#8220;Fascinating . . . wholly absorbing . . . conveys Trump&#8217;s larger-than-life demeanor so vibrantly that the reader&#8217;s attention is instantly and fully claimed.&#8221;&#8211;Boston Herald</p>
<p>                     &#8220;A chatty, generous, chutzpa-filled autobiography.&#8221;&#8211;New York Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/">Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in their working lives.    </p>
<p>                    Overcoming Mobbing is an informative, comprehensive guidebook written for the victims of mobbing and their families who often can&#8217;t make sense of the experience or mobilize resources for recovery. In an engaging, reader-friendly style, the book distinguishes mobbing from bullying in that it takes place within organizational or institutional settings and involves organizational dynamics. Mobbing is not about the occasional negative experience at work; it is ongoing negative acts, both<br />
                    overt and covert, over time, that erode workers&#8217; confidence in themselves and in their workplaces and that no amount of sophistication or maturity can make sense of.  Duffy and Sperry, leading authorities on this special type of aggression, provide effective strategies for recovery from mobbing as well as for<br />
                    prevention, and they demystify the experience through the use of case vignettes. More than a simple self-help book, this volume brings the concept and terminology relating to mobbing into the public vocabulary by virtue of its strong foundation in psychological and organizational research. It offers a detailed presentation of the causes and consequences of mobbing, helps readers avoid falling into the trap of misplacing blame, and holds organizations at the center of responsibility for<br />
                    preventing the abuse. In addition to those who have experienced mobbing themselves, this book is an invaluable resource for workplace managers and human resources personnel who wish to prevent or reverse mobbing within their own professional settings.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rejection Proof : How to Beat Fear and Become Invincible &#8211; Jia Jiang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rejection-proof-how-to-beat-fear-and-become-invincible-jia-jiang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rejection-proof-how-to-beat-fear-and-become-invincible-jia-jiang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rejection? It&#8217;s nothing to be afraid of &#8230; Maybe you avoid situations where you might be rejected. You don&#8217;t apply for that dream job. You don&#8217;t ask for that pay rise. You don&#8217;t ask that person on a date. But it doesn&#8217;t have to be that way &#8211; the only thing standing between you and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rejection-proof-how-to-beat-fear-and-become-invincible-jia-jiang-abridged/">Rejection Proof : How to Beat Fear and Become Invincible &#8211; Jia Jiang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rejection? It&#8217;s nothing to be afraid of &#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Maybe you avoid situations where you might be rejected. You don&#8217;t apply for that dream job. You don&#8217;t ask for that pay rise. You don&#8217;t ask that person on a date. But it doesn&#8217;t have to be that way &#8211; the only thing standing between you and your goals &#8230; is you.     </p>
<p>                    Jia Jiang had allowed his fear of rejection to rule his life. But he decided to take radical action: he quit his job and spent 100 days deliberately seeking out scenarios where he would likely be rejected, from ordering donuts interlinked and iced like the Olympic rings to asking to pilot a light aircraft. And something remarkable happened; Jia not only learned how to cope with rejection but also discovered that even the most outrageous request may be granted &#8211; if you ask in the right way.    </p>
<p>                    In this infectiously positive book Jia shares what he learned in his 100 Days of Rejection, explaining how to turn a &#8216;no&#8217; into a &#8216;yes&#8217;, and revealing how you too can become Rejection Proof and achieve your dreams.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rejection-proof-how-to-beat-fear-and-become-invincible-jia-jiang-abridged/">Rejection Proof : How to Beat Fear and Become Invincible &#8211; Jia Jiang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secrets of Power Negotiating &#8211; 25th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Roger Dawson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/secrets-of-power-negotiating-25th-anniversary-edition-roger-dawson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/secrets-of-power-negotiating-25th-anniversary-edition-roger-dawson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This is perhaps the best book on negotiating ever written. Roger&#8217;s powerful, practical principles will save or make you a fortune in the months and years ahead.&#8221; &#8211;Brian Tracy, author, Eat That Frog! and Million Dollar Habits &#8220;This is the one negotiating book that really opened my eyes and gave me practical tools I could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-power-negotiating-25th-anniversary-edition-roger-dawson-abridged/">Secrets of Power Negotiating &#8211; 25th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Roger Dawson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This is perhaps the best book on negotiating ever written. Roger&#8217;s powerful, practical principles will save or make you a fortune in the months and years ahead.&#8221; &#8211;Brian Tracy, author, Eat That Frog! and Million Dollar Habits     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This is the one negotiating book that really opened my eyes and gave me practical tools I could use immediately.&#8221; &#8211;Timothy Ferriss, bestselling author of The 4-Hour Work Week     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A fast, entertaining read that should be required reading for anyone who deals with people. Highly recommended.&#8221; &#8211;Ken Blanchard, coauthor of The One Minute Manager     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I can&#8217;t believe it! Here&#8217;s a book that is packed with wisdom that will help anyone improve their life and yet it is easy and fun to read! Amazing!&#8221; &#8211;Og Mandino, author of The Greatest Salesman in the World     </p>
<p>                     Roger Dawson changed the way business thinks about negotiating.     </p>
<p>                    Secrets of Power Negotiating covers every aspect of the negotiating process with practical, proven advice, from beginning steps to critical final moves: how to recognize unethical tactics, key principles of the Power Negotiating strategy, why money is not as important as everyone thinks, negotiating pressure points, understanding the other party and gaining the upper hand, and analyses of different negotiating styles.<br />
                     Discover all of Roger&#8217;s best tactics, including: 20 surefire negotiating gambitsListening to hidden meanings in conversationWhat &#8220;powers&#8221; you have, such as situational, expertise, information, or charismaticHow to handle the different personalities you&#8217;ll encounter in negotiating</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-power-negotiating-25th-anniversary-edition-roger-dawson-abridged/">Secrets of Power Negotiating &#8211; 25th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Roger Dawson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team of Teams : New Rules of Engagement for a Complex World &#8211; General Stanley McChrystal, David Silverman, Tantum Collins, Chris Fussell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Life & Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Tactics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Administration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if you could combine the agility, adaptability, and cohesion of a small team with the power and resources of a giant organization? When General Stanley McChrystal took command of the Joint Special Operations Task Force in Iraq in 2003, he quickly realized that conventional military tactics were failing. The allied forces had a huge [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/">Team of Teams : New Rules of Engagement for a Complex World &#8211; General Stanley McChrystal, David Silverman, Tantum Collins, Chris Fussell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What if you could combine the agility, adaptability, and cohesion of a small team with the power and resources of a giant organization?    </p>
<p>                    When General Stanley McChrystal took command of the Joint Special Operations Task Force in Iraq in 2003, he quickly realized that conventional military tactics were failing. The allied forces had a huge advantage in numbers, equipment and training &#8211; but none of the enemy&#8217;s speed and flexibility.    </p>
<p>                    McChrystal and his colleagues discarded a century of conventional wisdom to create a &#8216;team of teams&#8217; that combined extremely transparent communication with decentralized decision-making authority.     </p>
<p>                    Faster, flatter and more flexible, the task force beat back al-Qaeda.    </p>
<p>                    In this powerful book, McChrystal and his colleagues show how the challenges they faced in Iraq can be relevant to any leader. Through compelling examples, the authors demonstrate that the &#8216;team of teams&#8217; strategy has worked everywhere from hospital emergency rooms to NASA and has the potential to transform organizations large and small.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A bold argument that leaders can help teams become greater than the sum of their parts&#8217; Charles Duhigg, author of The Power of Habit    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An indispensable guide to organizational change&#8217; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/">Team of Teams : New Rules of Engagement for a Complex World &#8211; General Stanley McChrystal, David Silverman, Tantum Collins, Chris Fussell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes, it makes more sense to lose today in order to win tomorrow. What do you do when you know what you want, but you have no idea how to get it? &#8216;The greatest negotiation book of all time.&#8217; Inc. Magazine ________________ Never walk away. Learn to listen, then learn to understand, then learn to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/">Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes, it makes more sense to lose today in order to win tomorrow. What do you do when you know what you want, but you have no idea how to get it?    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The greatest negotiation book of all time.&#8217; Inc. Magazine<br />
                     ________________                           </p>
<p>                     Never walk away. Learn to listen, then learn to understand, then learn to win.    </p>
<p>                    Negotiation is part of every human encounter, and most of us do it badly. Whether dealing with family, a business, or diplomacy, people often fail to meet their goals in every country and context. They focus on power and &#8220;win-win&#8221; instead of relationships and perceptions. They don&#8217;t find enough things to trade. They think others should be rational when they should be dealing with emotions. They get distracted from their goals.    </p>
<p>                    In this revolutionary and seminal bestselling book, leading negotiation practitioner, coach and professor Stuart Diamond shows how emotional intelligence, perceptions, cultural diversity and collaboration produce four times as much value as old-school, conflictive, power, leverage and logic. Drawing on thirty-plus years of research involving 30,000 people across 45 countries &#8211; ranging from political and corporate leaders to administrative assistants, lawyers, housewives, students, and labourers &#8211; he outlines specific, practical and better ways to deal with others. To this, he adds his 40-year experience as a corporate executive, Harvard-trained attorney, and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist.    </p>
<p>                    Getting More is based on Professor Diamond&#8217;s award-winning negotiations course at The Wharton Business School, where it has been the most sought-after course by students for almost two decades. It contains a powerful toolkit that can be used in any situation: with kids and jobs, travel and shopping, business, politics, relationships, cultures, partners and competitors. His advice is brought to life in an accessible and entertaining manner through the stories of hundreds of people who have used the toolkit with great success.<br />
                    ________________    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;From advising on how to negotiate with terrorists, to industrial disputes, to children, Diamond&#8217;s twelve rules of negotiation promise to open new doors every day.&#8217; Radio One    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Practical, immediately applicable and highly effective.&#8217; Evan Wittenberg, co-founder of TRUE and former Head of Global Leadership Development at Google    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I rely on Stuart Diamond&#8217;s negotiation tools every day.&#8217; Christian Hernandez, venture capitalist and former Head of International Business Development at Facebook</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/">Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We use money to solve our everyday problems, and it generally works well. Despite its economic benefits, however, money has a psychological downside: it trains us to think about negotiations narrow-mindedly, leading us to negotiate badly. Suggesting that we need a non-monetary mindset to negotiate better, The Bartering Mindset shows us how to look outside [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/">The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We use money to solve our everyday problems, and it generally works well. Despite its economic benefits, however, money has a psychological downside: it trains us to think about negotiations narrow-mindedly, leading us to negotiate badly. Suggesting that we need a non-monetary mindset to negotiate better, The Bartering Mindset shows us how to look outside the monetary economy &#8211; to the bartering economies of the past, where people traded what they had for what they needed. The book argues that, because of the economic difficulties associated with bartering, barterers had to use a more sophisticated form of negotiation &#8211; a strategic approach that can make us master negotiators today.    </p>
<p>                    This book immerses readers in the assumptions made by barterers, collectively referred to as the &#8220;bartering mindset,&#8221; and then demonstrates how to apply this mindset to modern, monetary negotiations. The Bartering Mindset concludes that our individual, organizational, and social problems fester for a predictable reason: we apply a monetary mindset to our negotiations, leading to suboptimal thinking, counterproductive behaviors, and disappointing outcomes. By offering the bartering mindset as an alternative, this book will help people negotiate better and thrive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/">The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Noticing : What the Best Leaders See &#8211; Max Bazerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-noticing-what-the-best-leaders-see-max-bazerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-noticing-what-the-best-leaders-see-max-bazerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Imagine your advantage in negotiations, decision-making, and leadership if you could teach yourself to see and evaluate information that others overlook. The Power of Noticing provides the blueprint for accomplishing precisely that. Max Bazerman, an expert in the field of applied behavioral psychology, draws on three decades of research and his experience instructing Harvard Business [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-noticing-what-the-best-leaders-see-max-bazerman-abridged/">The Power of Noticing : What the Best Leaders See &#8211; Max Bazerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine your advantage in negotiations, decision-making, and leadership if you could teach yourself to see and evaluate information that others overlook. The Power of Noticing provides the blueprint for accomplishing precisely that. Max Bazerman, an expert in the field of applied behavioral psychology, draws on three decades of research and his experience instructing Harvard Business School MBAs and corporate executives to teach you how to notice and act on information that may not be immediately obvious.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on a wealth of real-world examples and using many of the same case studies and thought experiments designed in his executive MBA classes, Bazerman challenges you to explore your cognitive blind spots, identify any salient details you are programmed to miss, and then take steps to ensure it won&#8217;t happen again. His book provides a step-by-step guide to breaking bad habits and spotting the hidden details that will change your decision-making and leadership skills for the better, teaching you to pay attention to what didn&#8217;t happen, acknowledge self-interest, invent the third choice, and realize that what you see is not all there is.     </p>
<p>                    While many bestselling business books have explained how susceptible to manipulation our irrational cognitive blind spots make us, Bazerman helps you avoid the habits that lead to poor decisions and ineffective leadership in the first place. With The Power of Noticing at your side, you can learn how to notice what others miss, make wiser decisions, and lead more successfully.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-noticing-what-the-best-leaders-see-max-bazerman-abridged/">The Power of Noticing : What the Best Leaders See &#8211; Max Bazerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Split the Difference : Negotiating as if Your Life Depended on It &#8211; Chris Voss, Tahl Raz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/never-split-the-difference-negotiating-as-if-your-life-depended-on-it-chris-voss-tahl-raz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/never-split-the-difference-negotiating-as-if-your-life-depended-on-it-chris-voss-tahl-raz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE HUGE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER A former FBI hostage negotiator offers a new, field-tested approach to negotiating &#8211; effective in any situation. &#8216;Riveting&#8217; Adam Grant &#8216;Stupendous&#8217; The Week &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian ____________________________ After a stint policing the rough streets of Kansas City, Missouri, Chris Voss joined the FBI, where his career as a kidnapping negotiator brought him [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-split-the-difference-negotiating-as-if-your-life-depended-on-it-chris-voss-tahl-raz-abridged/">Never Split the Difference : Negotiating as if Your Life Depended on It &#8211; Chris Voss, Tahl Raz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE HUGE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    A former FBI hostage negotiator offers a new, field-tested approach to negotiating &#8211; effective in any situation.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Riveting&#8217; Adam Grant<br />
                    &#8216;Stupendous&#8217; The Week<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    ____________________________<br />
                    After a stint policing the rough streets of Kansas City, Missouri, Chris Voss joined the FBI, where his career as a kidnapping negotiator brought him face-to-face with bank robbers, gang leaders and terrorists. Never Split the Difference takes you inside his world of high-stakes negotiations, revealing the nine key principles that helped Voss and his colleagues succeed when it mattered the most &#8211; when people&#8217;s lives were at stake.     </p>
<p>                    Rooted in the real-life experiences of an intelligence professional at the top of his game, Never Split the Difference will give you the competitive edge in any discussion.<br />
                    ____________________________<br />
                    PRAISE FOR NEVER SPLIT THE DIFFERENCE    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My pick for book of the year.&#8217; Forbes    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Who better to learn [negotiation] from than Chris Voss, whose skills have saved lives and averted disaster?&#8217; Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Filled with insights that apply to everyday negotiations.&#8217; Business Insider    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s rare that a book is so gripping and entertaining while still being actionable and applicable.&#8217; Inc.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A business book you won&#8217;t be able to put down.&#8217; Fortune</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-split-the-difference-negotiating-as-if-your-life-depended-on-it-chris-voss-tahl-raz-abridged/">Never Split the Difference : Negotiating as if Your Life Depended on It &#8211; Chris Voss, Tahl Raz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Thinking : Upgrade Your Reasoning and Make Better Decisions with Mental Models &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Lauren McCann (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An invaluable resource for making sense of the world, making good decisions, and placing smart bets. A fast-paced and fun read jam-packed with useful information on every page.&#8217; Annie Duke, author of Thinking in Bets ________________ Turn yourself into a superthinker and make the right decisions every time. You want to make better decisions. You [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/">Super Thinking : Upgrade Your Reasoning and Make Better Decisions with Mental Models &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Lauren McCann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An invaluable resource for making sense of the world, making good decisions, and placing smart bets. A fast-paced and fun read jam-packed with useful information on every page.&#8217; Annie Duke, author of Thinking in Bets<br />
                     ________________                           </p>
<p>                     Turn yourself into a superthinker and make the right decisions every time.    </p>
<p>                     You want to make better decisions. You want to be right more of the time professionally and personally. However, being more right consistently is a hard problem because the world is such a complex, evolving place. How do you navigate this complexity?    </p>
<p>                     Mental models are decision-making tools that guide our perception of the world and our behaviour in it. They help us understand life, make decisions and solve problems. The best models help us make intelligent investments, develop ground-breaking technologies and even travel to outer space.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Note your frame of reference before debating someone with different political views. If you understand how your perspective contrasts with someone else&#8217;s you can prevent the conversation from getting hostile.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Apply the sunk cost fallacy to the end of a doomed project. Just because you&#8217;ve put a lot of hours into it doesn&#8217;t mean that you have to keep going.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Before blaming someone, consider Hanlon&#8217;s Razor, &#8216;Never attribute to malice that which is adequately explained by carelessness&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Try to solve mysteries with Occam&#8217;s Razor, &#8216;Among competing hypotheses, the one with the fewest assumptions should be selected&#8217;. When you hear hoof beats, think of horses not zebras.    </p>
<p>                     Building on our knowledge of well-known models such as the Bandwagon Effect or Paradigm Shift and introducing us to the lesser known like the Eisenhower Matrix or the Boiling Frog Symbol, this indispensable book distils the most effective mental models into a single, digestible volume. It will make even the most complex models accessible and engaging to enable you to make better, more informed decisions in every part of your life.<br />
                     ________________    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Internalizing these mental models will help you understand the world around you. Once you can spot them, you can change your own behavior to avoid common traps, adjust how you interact with people to get better results, and maybe even articulate new mental models of the world that have yet to be discovered.&#8217; Brian Armstrong, co-founder and CEO, Coinbase    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;You can&#8217;t really know anything if you just remember isolated facts. If the facts don&#8217;t hang together on a latticework of theory, you don&#8217;t have them in a usable form. You&#8217;ve got to have models in your head.&#8217; Charlie Munger, vice chairman, Berkshire Hathaway</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/">Super Thinking : Upgrade Your Reasoning and Make Better Decisions with Mental Models &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Lauren McCann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD. This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career. An MBA at a top business school is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold     </p>
<p>                    ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD.    </p>
<p>                    This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career.    </p>
<p>                    An MBA at a top business school is an enormous investment in time and cash. And if you don&#8217;t want to work for a consulting firm or an investment bank, the chances are it simply isn&#8217;t worth it.    </p>
<p>                    The Personal MBA gives you simple mental models for every subject that&#8217;s key to commercial success. From the basics of products and marketing to the nuances of teamwork and systems, this book distils everything you need to know to take on the MBA graduates and win.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;File this book under: NO EXCUSES&#8217; Seth Godin    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;No matter what they tell you, an MBA is not essential. If you combine reading this book with actually trying stuff, you&#8217;ll be far ahead in the business game&#8217; Kevin Kelly, founder of Wired</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thanks for the Feedback : The Science and Art of Receiving Feedback Well &#8211; Douglas Stone, Sheila Heen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thanks-for-the-feedback-the-science-and-art-of-receiving-feedback-well-douglas-stone-sheila-heen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thanks-for-the-feedback-the-science-and-art-of-receiving-feedback-well-douglas-stone-sheila-heen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the classic Difficult Conversations teach you how to take criticism productively in Thanks for the Feedback. We get feedback every day of our lives, from friends and family, colleagues, customers, and bosses, teachers, doctors, and strangers. We&#8217;re assessed, coached, and criticized about our performance, personalities and appearance. We know that feedback is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thanks-for-the-feedback-the-science-and-art-of-receiving-feedback-well-douglas-stone-sheila-heen-abridged/">Thanks for the Feedback : The Science and Art of Receiving Feedback Well &#8211; Douglas Stone, Sheila Heen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the classic Difficult Conversations teach you how to take criticism productively in Thanks for the Feedback.    </p>
<p>                    We get feedback every day of our lives, from friends and family, colleagues, customers, and bosses, teachers, doctors, and strangers. We&#8217;re assessed, coached, and criticized about our performance, personalities and appearance.    </p>
<p>                    We know that feedback is essential for professional development and healthy relationships &#8211; but we dread it and even dismiss it. That&#8217;s because while want to learn and grow, we also want to be accepted just as we are.    </p>
<p>                    Thanks for the Feedback is the first book to address this tension head on. In it, the world-renowned team behind the Harvard Negotiation Project offer a simple framework and powerful tools, showing us how to take on life&#8217;s blizzard of comments and advice with curiosity and grace.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ll admit it: Thanks for the Feedback made me uncomfortable. And that&#8217;s one reason I liked it so much. With keen insight and lots of practical takeaways, it reveals why getting feedback is so hard &#8211; and then how we can do better&#8217;  Daniel H. Pink, author of To Sell Is Human and Drive    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thanks for the Feedback is a road map to more self-awareness, greater learning, and richer relationships. A tour de force&#8217;  Adam Grant, Wharton professor and author of Give and Take    </p>
<p>                    Douglas Stone and Sheila Heen are Lecturers on Law at Harvard Law School and cofounders of Triad Consulting. Their clients include the White House, Citigroup, Honda, Johnson &#038; Johnson, Time Warner, Unilever, and many others. They are co-authors of the international bestseller Difficult Conversations. Stone lives in Cambridge, MA. Heen lives with her husband and three children in a farmhouse north of Cambridge, MA.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thanks-for-the-feedback-the-science-and-art-of-receiving-feedback-well-douglas-stone-sheila-heen-abridged/">Thanks for the Feedback : The Science and Art of Receiving Feedback Well &#8211; Douglas Stone, Sheila Heen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Radical Collaboration : Five Essential Skills To Overcome Defensiveness And Build Successful Relationships &#8211; James W. Tamm, Ronald J. Luyet (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The second edition of the essential guide, updated with new research and observations to help twenty-first century organizations create models for effective collaboration. Collaborative skills have never been more important to a company&#8217;s success and these skills are essential for every worker today. Radical Collaboration is a how-to-manual for creating trusting, cooperative environments, and transforming [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/">Radical Collaboration : Five Essential Skills To Overcome Defensiveness And Build Successful Relationships &#8211; James W. Tamm, Ronald J. Luyet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The second edition of the essential guide, updated with new research and observations to help twenty-first century organizations create models for effective collaboration.    </p>
<p>                    Collaborative skills have never been more important to a company&#8217;s success and these skills are essential for every worker today. Radical Collaboration is a how-to-manual for creating trusting, cooperative environments, and transforming groups into motivated and empowered teams. James W. Tamm and Ronald J. Luyet provide tools that will help you increase your ability to work successfully with others, learn to be more aware of colleagues, and better problem-solve and negotiate.     </p>
<p>                    Radical Collaboration is an eye-opener for leaders, managers, HR professionals, agents, trainers, and consultants who are seeking constructive ways of getting the results they want.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/">Radical Collaboration : Five Essential Skills To Overcome Defensiveness And Build Successful Relationships &#8211; James W. Tamm, Ronald J. Luyet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Yes Book : The Art of Better Negotiation &#8211; Clive Rich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-yes-book-the-art-of-better-negotiation-clive-rich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-yes-book-the-art-of-better-negotiation-clive-rich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Negotiation is fundamental to our lives; whether it&#8217;s getting your kids to eat their greens, making your case for a pay rise, or trying to secure a multi-million pound deal for your company. However, negotiation has changed. It&#8217;s no longer about confrontation where there are winners and losers. Collaboration is now the name of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-yes-book-the-art-of-better-negotiation-clive-rich-abridged/">The Yes Book : The Art of Better Negotiation &#8211; Clive Rich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Negotiation is fundamental to our lives; whether it&#8217;s getting your kids to eat their greens, making your case for a pay rise, or trying to secure a multi-million pound deal for your company.     </p>
<p>                    However, negotiation has changed. It&#8217;s no longer about confrontation where there are winners and losers. Collaboration is now the name of the game. YouGov research commissioned for this book shows UK PLC is losing GBP9 million per hour from poor negotiating &#8211; GBP17 billion per year. Can you afford to be without a modern framework for deal-making?    </p>
<p>                    In The Yes Book, Clive Rich provides a method for generating success based on years of experience working for or with major organisations and super brands including Sony, Yahoo, Apple, the BBC, Tesco, and Simon Cowell&#8217;s Syco, during a negotiating career in which he has brokered more than GBP10 billion worth of deals.     </p>
<p>                    By breaking negotiation into its three key elements of Attitude, Behaviour and Process, he helps you learn how to shape, create and close deals. You will discover what your negotiating style is, and how you can apply it to influence others and give yourself the edge.    </p>
<p>                    This is the ultimate guide to using the power of negotiation to get more of what you want, in both business and life outside the office.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-yes-book-the-art-of-better-negotiation-clive-rich-abridged/">The Yes Book : The Art of Better Negotiation &#8211; Clive Rich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon    </p>
<p>                    For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With vivid stories of his closed-door sessions with warring political groups, disputing businesspeople, and families in crisis, Daniel Shapiro presents a universally applicable method to successfully navigate conflict.  A deep, provocative book to reflect on and wrestle with, this book can change your life.    </p>
<p>                     Be warned: This book is not a quick fix. Real change takes work. You will learn how to master five emotional dynamics that can sabotage conflict outside your awareness:    </p>
<p>                    1. Vertigo: How can you avoid      getting emotionally consumed in conflict?<br />
                    2. Repetition compulsion: How can you stop      repeating the same conflicts again and again?<br />
                    3. Taboos: How can you discuss      sensitive issues at the heart of the conflict?<br />
                    4. Assault on the sacred: What should you do if      your values feel threatened?<br />
                    5. Identity politics: What can you do if      others use politics against you?     </p>
<p>                    In our era of discontent, this is just the book we need to resolve conflict in our own lives and in the world around us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>60 Seconds and You&#8217;re Hired!: Revised Edition &#8211; Robin Ryan, CP (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/60-seconds-and-youre-hired-revised-edition-robin-ryan-cp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/60-seconds-and-youre-hired-revised-edition-robin-ryan-cp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fully revised and updated-the must-have guide to acing the interview and landing the dream job, from &#8220;America&#8217;s top career expert&#8221; (The Los Angeles Times) 60 Seconds &#038; You&#8217;re Hired! has already helped thousands of job seekers get their dream jobs by excelling in crucial interviews. America&#8217;s top job search expert Robin Ryan draws on her [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/60-seconds-and-youre-hired-revised-edition-robin-ryan-cp-abridged/">60 Seconds and You&#8217;re Hired!: Revised Edition &#8211; Robin Ryan, CP (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fully revised and updated-the must-have guide to acing the interview and landing the dream job, from &#8220;America&#8217;s top career expert&#8221; (The Los Angeles Times)    </p>
<p>                    60 Seconds &#038; You&#8217;re Hired! has already helped thousands of job seekers get their dream jobs by excelling in crucial interviews. America&#8217;s top job search expert Robin Ryan draws on her 20 years as a career counselor, 30 years of direct hiring, and extensive contact with hundreds of recruiters, decisions makers, and HR professionals to teach you proven strategies to help you take charge of the interview process and get the job you want. Brief, compact, and packed with insightful direction to give you the cutting edge to slip past the competition, 60 Seconds &#038; You&#8217;re Hired! is here to help you succeed! This newly revised edition features:       </p>
<p>                         * Unique techniques like &#8220;The 60 Second Sell&#8221; and &#8220;The 5-Point Agenda&#8221;<br />
                         * Over 125 answers to tough, tricky interview questions employers often ask<br />
                         * How to handle structured or behavioral interview questions<br />
                         * Questions you should always ask, and questions you should never ask<br />
                         * How to deal effectively with any salary questions to preserve your negotiating power<br />
                         * 20 interview pitfalls to avoid<br />
                         * Proven negotiation techniques that secure higher salaries &#8211; and much more!    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Robin Ryan has the inside track on how to get hired.&#8221; -ABC News</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/60-seconds-and-youre-hired-revised-edition-robin-ryan-cp-abridged/">60 Seconds and You&#8217;re Hired!: Revised Edition &#8211; Robin Ryan, CP (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The No Asshole Rule : Building a Civilised Workplace and Surviving One That Isn&#8217;t &#8211; Robert Sutton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When the Harvard Business Review asked Robert Sutton for suggestions for its annual list of Breakthrough Ideas, he told them that the best business practice he knew of was &#8216;the no asshole rule&#8217;. Sutton&#8217;s piece became one of the most popular articles ever to appear in the HBR. Spurred on by the fear and despair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/">The No Asshole Rule : Building a Civilised Workplace and Surviving One That Isn&#8217;t &#8211; Robert Sutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When the Harvard Business Review asked Robert Sutton for suggestions for its annual list of Breakthrough Ideas, he told them that the best business practice he knew of was &#8216;the no asshole rule&#8217;. Sutton&#8217;s piece became one of the most popular articles ever to appear in the HBR. Spurred on by the fear and despair that people expressed, the tricks they used to survive with dignity in asshole-infested places, the revenge stories that made him laugh out loud and the other small wins that they celebrated against mean-spirited people, Sutton was persuaded to write THE NO ASSHOLE RULE.<br />
                    He believes passionately that civilised workplaces are not a naive dream, that they do exist, do bolster performance and that widespread contempt can be erased and replaced with mutual respect when a team or organisation is managed right. There is a huge temptation by executives and those in positions of authority to overlook this trait especially when exhibited by so-called producers, but Sutton shows how overall productivity suffers when the workplace is subjected to this kind of stress.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/">The No Asshole Rule : Building a Civilised Workplace and Surviving One That Isn&#8217;t &#8211; Robert Sutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Heart of the Deal : How to Invest and Negotiate like a Real Estate Mogul &#8211; Anthony Lolli, WithBenjamin Platt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-heart-of-the-deal-how-to-invest-and-negotiate-like-a-real-estate-mogul-anthony-lolli-with-benjamin-platt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-heart-of-the-deal-how-to-invest-and-negotiate-like-a-real-estate-mogul-anthony-lolli-with-benjamin-platt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The founder and CEO of Rapid Realty, New York City&#8217;s largest rental-based real estate brokerage, shares his story, his advice, and his tips for building a successful career in the ever-growing and lucrative world of real estate. Anthony Lolli got his real estate license at age nineteen. By twenty-three, he was a millionaire and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-heart-of-the-deal-how-to-invest-and-negotiate-like-a-real-estate-mogul-anthony-lolli-with-benjamin-platt-abridged/">The Heart of the Deal : How to Invest and Negotiate like a Real Estate Mogul &#8211; Anthony Lolli, WithBenjamin Platt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The founder and CEO of Rapid Realty, New York City&#8217;s largest rental-based real estate brokerage, shares his story, his advice, and his tips for building a successful career in the ever-growing and lucrative world of real estate.    </p>
<p>                    Anthony Lolli got his real estate license at age nineteen. By twenty-three, he was a millionaire and the head of a swiftly growing company that would become one of the largest real estate brokerages in New York and a national franchise sensation. Now, he&#8217;s sharing the secrets behind his success.     </p>
<p>                    Filled with insights into Lolli&#8217;s inspirational rags-to-riches rise to the top and bursting with practical advice for real estate newcomers and veterans alike, The Heart of the Deal is essential reading for anyone with big dreams and the drive to make them come true. Learn how to set smart goals, negotiate like a pro, analyze properties and neighborhoods, overcome objections, and much more.      </p>
<p>                    Whether you want to become a top-performing broker or a savvy property investor, or simply master real estate management tactics designed to help you achieve your financial goals, Lolli&#8217;s grounded guidance will put you on the right path.      </p>
<p>                    Most importantly, The Heart of the Deal will teach you how to utilize all of these strategies to build a lucrative career without sacrificing your humanity in the process. At all times, Lolli keeps one central premise in mind: that the heart of every deal isn&#8217;t money-it&#8217;s people.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-heart-of-the-deal-how-to-invest-and-negotiate-like-a-real-estate-mogul-anthony-lolli-with-benjamin-platt-abridged/">The Heart of the Deal : How to Invest and Negotiate like a Real Estate Mogul &#8211; Anthony Lolli, WithBenjamin Platt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 3-minute Rule : Saying Less to Get More from Any Pitch or Presentation &#8211; Brant Pinvidic (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-3-minute-rule-saying-less-to-get-more-from-any-pitch-or-presentation-brant-pinvidic-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-3-minute-rule-saying-less-to-get-more-from-any-pitch-or-presentation-brant-pinvidic-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Want to deliver a pitch or presentation that grabs your audience&#8217;s ever-shrinking attention span? Ditch the colorful slides and catchy language. And follow one simple rule: Convey only what needs to be said, clearly and concisely, in three minutes or less. That&#8217;s the 3-Minute Rule. Hollywood producer and pitch master Brant Pinvidic has sold more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-3-minute-rule-saying-less-to-get-more-from-any-pitch-or-presentation-brant-pinvidic-abridged/">The 3-minute Rule : Saying Less to Get More from Any Pitch or Presentation &#8211; Brant Pinvidic (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Want to deliver a pitch or presentation that grabs your audience&#8217;s ever-shrinking attention span? Ditch the colorful slides and catchy language. And follow one simple rule: Convey only what needs to be said, clearly and concisely, in three minutes or less.     </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s the 3-Minute Rule.     </p>
<p>                    Hollywood producer and pitch master Brant Pinvidic has sold more than three hundred TV shows and movies, run a TV network, and helmed one of the largest production companies in the world with smash hits like The Biggest Loser and Bar Rescue. In his nearly twenty years of experience, he&#8217;s developed a simple, straightforward system that&#8217;shelped hundreds&#8211;from Fortune 100 CEOs to PTA presidents&#8211;use top-level Hollywood storytelling techniques to simplify their messages and say less to get more.     </p>
<p>                    Pinvidic proves that anyone can deliver a great pitch, for any idea, in any situation, so your audience not only remembers your message but can pass it on to their friends and colleagues. You&#8217;ll see how his methods work in a wide range of situations&#8211;from presenting investment opportunities in a biotech startup to pitching sponsorship deals for major sports stadiums, and more.     </p>
<p>                    Now it&#8217;s your turn. The 3-Minute Rule will equip you with an easy, foolproof method to boil down any idea to its essential elements and structure it for maximum impact.     </p>
<p>                    Simplify. Say less. Get More.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-3-minute-rule-saying-less-to-get-more-from-any-pitch-or-presentation-brant-pinvidic-abridged/">The 3-minute Rule : Saying Less to Get More from Any Pitch or Presentation &#8211; Brant Pinvidic (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ask For It : How Women Can Use the Power of Negotiation to Get What They Really Want &#8211; Linda Babcock, Sara Laschever (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ask-for-it-how-women-can-use-the-power-of-negotiation-to-get-what-they-really-want-linda-babcock-sara-laschever-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ask-for-it-how-women-can-use-the-power-of-negotiation-to-get-what-they-really-want-linda-babcock-sara-laschever-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the authors of Women Don&#8217;t Ask, the groundbreaking book that revealed just how much women lose when they avoid negotiation, here is the action plan that women all over the country requested&#8211;a guide to negotiating anything effectively using strategies that feel comfortable to you as a woman. Whether it&#8217;s a raise, that overdue promotion, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-for-it-how-women-can-use-the-power-of-negotiation-to-get-what-they-really-want-linda-babcock-sara-laschever-abridged/">Ask For It : How Women Can Use the Power of Negotiation to Get What They Really Want &#8211; Linda Babcock, Sara Laschever (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the authors of Women Don&#8217;t Ask,  the groundbreaking book that revealed just how much women lose when they avoid negotiation,  here is the action plan that women all over the country requested&#8211;a guide to negotiating anything effectively using strategies that feel comfortable to you as a woman. Whether it&#8217;s a raise, that overdue promotion, an exciting new assignment, or even extra help around the house, this four-phase program, backed by years of research and practical success, will show you how to recognize how much more you really deserve, maximize your bargaining power, develop the best strategy for your situation, and manage the reactions and emotions that may arise&#8211;on both sides. Guided step-by-step, you&#8217;ll learn how to draw on your special strengths to reach agreements that benefit everyone involved. This collaborative, problem-solving approach will propel you to new places both professionally and personally&#8211;and open doors you thought were closed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-for-it-how-women-can-use-the-power-of-negotiation-to-get-what-they-really-want-linda-babcock-sara-laschever-abridged/">Ask For It : How Women Can Use the Power of Negotiation to Get What They Really Want &#8211; Linda Babcock, Sara Laschever (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Can Negotiate Anything : The World&#8217;s Best Negotiator Tells You How To Get What You Want &#8211; Herb Cohen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-can-negotiate-anything-the-worlds-best-negotiator-tells-you-how-to-get-what-you-want-herb-cohen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-can-negotiate-anything-the-worlds-best-negotiator-tells-you-how-to-get-what-you-want-herb-cohen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Regardless of who you are or what you want, you can negotiate anything promises Herb Cohen, the world&#8217;s best negotiator. From mergers to marriages, from loans to lovemaking, the #1 bestseller You Can Negotiate Anything proves that &#8220;money, justice, prestige, love&#8211;it&#8217;s all negotiable.&#8221; Hailed by such publications as Time, People, and Newsweek, Cohen has advised [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-can-negotiate-anything-the-worlds-best-negotiator-tells-you-how-to-get-what-you-want-herb-cohen-abridged/">You Can Negotiate Anything : The World&#8217;s Best Negotiator Tells You How To Get What You Want &#8211; Herb Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Regardless of who you are or what you want, you can negotiate anything promises Herb Cohen, the world&#8217;s best negotiator.      </p>
<p>                    From mergers to marriages, from loans to lovemaking, the #1 bestseller You Can Negotiate Anything proves that &#8220;money, justice, prestige, love&#8211;it&#8217;s all negotiable.&#8221; Hailed by such publications as Time, People, and Newsweek, Cohen has advised presidents on everything from domestic policy to hostage crises to combating internal terrorism. His advice: &#8220;Be patient, be personal, be informed&#8211;and you can bargain successfully for anything.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Inside, you&#8217;ll learn the keys to using Herb Cohen&#8217;s proven strategy for dealing with your mate, your boss, your credit card company, your children, your lawyer, your best friends, and even yourself:     </p>
<p>                    -The three crucial steps to success<br />
                    &#8211; Identifying the other side&#8217;s negotiating style&#8211;and how to deal with it<br />
                    &#8211; The win-win technique<br />
                    &#8211; Using time to your advantage<br />
                    &#8211; The power of persistence, persuasion, and attitude<br />
                    &#8211; The art of the telephone negotiation, and much more     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Power is based upon perception&#8211;if you think you&#8217;ve got it then you&#8217;ve got it!&#8221; affirms Herb Cohen, the world&#8217;s expert. And with this book, you&#8217;ve got the power to get what you really want right in your hands.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-can-negotiate-anything-the-worlds-best-negotiator-tells-you-how-to-get-what-you-want-herb-cohen-abridged/">You Can Negotiate Anything : The World&#8217;s Best Negotiator Tells You How To Get What You Want &#8211; Herb Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Negotiation : How to Improvise Agreement in a Chaotic World &#8211; Michael Wheeler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-negotiation-how-to-improvise-agreement-in-a-chaotic-world-michael-wheeler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-negotiation-how-to-improvise-agreement-in-a-chaotic-world-michael-wheeler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A member of the world renowned Program on Negotiation at Harvard Law School introduces the powerful next-generation approach to negotiation. A member of the world-renowned Program on Negotiation at Harvard Law School introduces the powerful next-generation approach to negotiation. For many years, two approaches to negotiation have prevailed: the &#8220;win-win&#8221; method exemplified in Getting to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-negotiation-how-to-improvise-agreement-in-a-chaotic-world-michael-wheeler-abridged/">The Art of Negotiation : How to Improvise Agreement in a Chaotic World &#8211; Michael Wheeler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A member of the world renowned Program on Negotiation at Harvard Law School introduces the powerful next-generation approach to negotiation.     </p>
<p>                    A member of the world-renowned Program on Negotiation at Harvard Law School introduces the powerful next-generation approach to negotiation.     </p>
<p>                    For many years, two approaches to negotiation have prevailed: the &#8220;win-win&#8221; method exemplified in Getting to Yes by Roger Fisher, William Ury, and Bruce Patton; and the hard-bargaining style of Herb Cohen&#8217;s You Can Negotiate Anything. Now award-winning Harvard Business School professor Michael Wheeler provides a dynamic alternative to one-size-fits-all strategies that don&#8217;t match real world realities.     </p>
<p>                    The Art of Negotiation shows how master negotia-tors thrive in the face of chaos and uncertainty. They don&#8217;t trap themselves with rigid plans. Instead they understand negotiation as a process of exploration that demands ongoing learning, adapting, and influencing. Their agility enables them to reach agreement when others would be stalemated.     </p>
<p>                    Michael Wheeler illuminates the improvisational nature of negotiation, drawing on his own research and his work with Program on Negotiation colleagues. He explains how the best practices of diplomats such as George J. Mitchell, dealmaker Bruce Wasserstein, and Hollywood producer Jerry Weintraub apply to everyday transactions like selling a house, buying a car, or landing a new contract. Wheeler also draws lessons on agility and creativity from fields like jazz, sports, theater, and even military science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-negotiation-how-to-improvise-agreement-in-a-chaotic-world-michael-wheeler-abridged/">The Art of Negotiation : How to Improvise Agreement in a Chaotic World &#8211; Michael Wheeler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
