<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Historical Geography Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/historical-geography/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/historical-geography/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Historical Geography Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/historical-geography/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Maps of the Ancient Sea Kings : Evidence of Advanced Civilization in the Ice Age &#8211; Charles Hapgood</title>
		<link>/maps-of-the-ancient-sea-kings-evidence-of-advanced-civilization-in-the-ice-age-charles-hapgood/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Beliefs & Controversial Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Maps & Atlases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World Atlases / World Maps]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/maps-of-the-ancient-sea-kings-evidence-of-advanced-civilization-in-the-ice-age-charles-hapgood/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Hapgood&#8217;s classic 1966 book on ancient maps is back in print after 20 years. Hapgood produces concrete evidence of an advanced worldwide civilization existing many thousands of years before ancient Egypt. He has found the evidence in many beautiful maps long known to scholars, the Piri Reis Map that shows Antarctica, the Hadji Ahmed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maps-of-the-ancient-sea-kings-evidence-of-advanced-civilization-in-the-ice-age-charles-hapgood/">Maps of the Ancient Sea Kings : Evidence of Advanced Civilization in the Ice Age &#8211; Charles Hapgood</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Charles Hapgood&#8217;s classic 1966 book on ancient maps is back in print after 20 years. Hapgood produces concrete evidence of an advanced worldwide civilization existing many thousands of years before ancient Egypt. He has found the evidence in many beautiful maps long known to scholars, the Piri Reis Map that shows Antarctica, the Hadji Ahmed map, the Oronteus Finaeus and other amazing maps. Hapgood concluded that these maps were made from more ancient maps from the various ancient archives around the world, now lost. Hapgood also concluded that the ancient mapmakers were in some ways much more advanced scientifically than Europe in the 16th century, or than the ancient civilizations of Greece, Egypt, and Babylonian. Not only were these unknown people more advanced in mapmaking than any people prior to the 18th century, it appears they mapped all the continents. The Americas were mapped thousands of years before Columbus. Antarctica was mapped when its coasts were free of ice. There is evidence that these people must have lived when the ice age had not yet ended in the Northern Hemisphere and when Alaska was still connected with Siberia by the Pleistocene, ice age &#8220;land bridge.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maps-of-the-ancient-sea-kings-evidence-of-advanced-civilization-in-the-ice-age-charles-hapgood/">Maps of the Ancient Sea Kings : Evidence of Advanced Civilization in the Ice Age &#8211; Charles Hapgood</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Geography of Genius : Lessons from the World&#8217;s Most Creative Places &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tag along on this New York Times bestselling &#8220;witty, entertaining romp&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) as Eric Winer travels the world, from Athens to Silicon Valley&#8211;and back through history, too&#8211;to show how creative genius flourishes in specific places at specific times. In this &#8220;intellectual odyssey, traveler&#8217;s diary, and comic novel all rolled into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/">The Geography of Genius : Lessons from the World&#8217;s Most Creative Places &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tag along on this New York Times bestselling &#8220;witty, entertaining romp&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) as Eric Winer travels the world, from Athens to Silicon Valley&#8211;and back through history, too&#8211;to show how creative genius flourishes in specific places at specific times.     </p>
<p>                    In this &#8220;intellectual odyssey, traveler&#8217;s diary, and comic novel all rolled into one&#8221; (Daniel Gilbert, author of Stumbling on Happiness), acclaimed travel writer Weiner sets out to examine the connection between our surroundings and our most innovative ideas. A &#8220;superb travel guide: funny, knowledgeable, and self-deprecating&#8221; (The Washington Post), he explores the history of places like Vienna of 1900, Renaissance Florence, ancient Athens, Song Dynasty Hangzhou, and Silicon Valley to show how certain urban settings are conducive to ingenuity. With his trademark insightful humor, this &#8220;big-hearted humanist&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal) walks the same paths as the geniuses who flourished in these settings to see if the spirit of what inspired figures like Socrates, Michelangelo, and Leonardo remains. In these places, Weiner asks, &#8220;What was in the air, and can we bottle it?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Fun and thought provoking&#8221; (Miami Herald), The Geography of Genius reevaluates the importance of culture in nurturing creativity and &#8220;offers a practical map for how we can all become a bit more inventive&#8221; (Adam Grant, author of Originals).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/">The Geography of Genius : Lessons from the World&#8217;s Most Creative Places &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gods of the Upper Air : How a Circle of Renegade Anthropologists Reinvented Race, Sex, and Gender in the Twentieth Century &#8211; Charles King (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/gods-of-the-upper-air-how-a-circle-of-renegade-anthropologists-reinvented-race-sex-and-gender-in-the-twentieth-century-charles-king-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geographical Discovery & Exploration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/gods-of-the-upper-air-how-a-circle-of-renegade-anthropologists-reinvented-race-sex-and-gender-in-the-twentieth-century-charles-king-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2020 Anisfield-Wolf Book Award Winner Finalist for the National Book Critics Circle Award From an award-winning historian comes a dazzling history of the birth of cultural anthropology and the adventurous scientists who pioneered it&#8211;a sweeping chronicle of discovery and the fascinating origin story of our multicultural world. A century ago, everyone knew that people were [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gods-of-the-upper-air-how-a-circle-of-renegade-anthropologists-reinvented-race-sex-and-gender-in-the-twentieth-century-charles-king-abridged/">Gods of the Upper Air : How a Circle of Renegade Anthropologists Reinvented Race, Sex, and Gender in the Twentieth Century &#8211; Charles King (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2020 Anisfield-Wolf Book Award Winner<br />
                    Finalist for the National Book Critics Circle Award     </p>
<p>                    From an award-winning historian comes a dazzling history of the birth of cultural anthropology and the adventurous scientists who pioneered it&#8211;a sweeping chronicle of discovery and the fascinating origin story of our multicultural world.     </p>
<p>                    A century ago, everyone knew that people were fated by their race, sex, and nationality to be more or less intelligent, nurturing, or warlike. But Columbia University professor Franz Boas looked at the data and decided everyone was wrong. Racial categories, he insisted, were biological fictions. Cultures did not come in neat packages labeled primitive or advanced. What counted as a family, a good meal, or even common sense was a product of history and circumstance, not of nature. In Gods of the Upper Air,  a masterful narrative history of radical ideas and passionate lives, Charles King shows how these intuitions led to a fundamental reimagining of human diversity.<br />
                     Boas&#8217;s students were some of the century&#8217;s most colorful figures and unsung visionaries: Margaret Mead, the outspoken field researcher whose Coming of Age in Samoa is among the most widely read works of social science of all time; Ruth Benedict, the great love of Mead&#8217;s life, whose research shaped post-Second World War Japan; Ella Deloria, the Dakota Sioux activist who preserved the traditions of Native Americans on the Great Plains; and Zora Neale Hurston, whose studies under Boas fed directly into her now classic novel, Their Eyes Were Watching God. Together, they mapped civilizations from the American South to the South Pacific and from Caribbean islands to Manhattan&#8217;s city streets, and unearthed an essential fact buried by centuries of prejudice: that humanity is an undivided whole. Their revolutionary findings would go on to inspire the fluid conceptions of identity we know today.<br />
                     Rich in drama, conflict, friendship, and love, Gods of the Upper Air is a brilliant and groundbreaking history of American progress and the opening of the modern mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gods-of-the-upper-air-how-a-circle-of-renegade-anthropologists-reinvented-race-sex-and-gender-in-the-twentieth-century-charles-king-abridged/">Gods of the Upper Air : How a Circle of Renegade Anthropologists Reinvented Race, Sex, and Gender in the Twentieth Century &#8211; Charles King (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
