<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Grammar, Syntax Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/grammar-syntax/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/grammar-syntax/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Grammar, Syntax Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/grammar-syntax/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Sense of Style : The Thinking Person&#8217;s Guide to Writing in the 21st Century &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Pinker, the bestselling author of The Language Instinct, deploys his gift for explaining big ideas in The Sense of Style &#8211; an entertaining writing guide for the 21st century What is the secret of good prose? Does writing well even matter in an age of instant communication? Should we care? In this funny, thoughtful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Sense of Style : The Thinking Person&#8217;s Guide to Writing in the 21st Century &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steven Pinker, the bestselling author of The Language Instinct, deploys his gift for explaining big ideas in The Sense of Style &#8211; an entertaining writing guide for the 21st century    </p>
<p>                    What is the secret of good prose? Does writing well even matter in an age of instant communication? Should we care? In this funny, thoughtful book about the modern art of writing, Steven Pinker shows us why we all need a sense of style.    </p>
<p>                    More than ever before, the currency of our social and cultural lives is the written word, from Twitter and texting to blogs, e-readers and old-fashioned books. But most style guides fail to prepare people for the challenges of writing in the 21st century, portraying it as a minefield of grievous errors rather than a form of pleasurable mastery. They fail to deal with an inescapable fact about language: it changes over time, adapted by millions of writers and speakers to their needs. Confusing changes in the world with moral decline, every generation believes the kids today are degrading society and taking language with it. A guide for the new millennium, writes Steven Pinker, has to be different.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the latest research in linguistics and cognitive science, Steven Pinker replaces the recycled dogma of previous style guides with reason and evidence. This thinking person&#8217;s guide to good writing shows why style still matters: in communicating effectively, in enhancing the spread of ideas, in earning a reader&#8217;s trust and, not least, in adding beauty to the world. Eye-opening, mind-expanding and cheerful, The Sense of Style shows that good style is part of what it means to be human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Sense of Style : The Thinking Person&#8217;s Guide to Writing in the 21st Century &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities. In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities.     </p>
<p>                    In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our language carries secrets about our feelings, our self-concept, and our social intelligence. Our most forgettable words, such as pronouns and prepositions, can be the most revealing: their patterns are as distinctive as fingerprints.     </p>
<p>                    Using innovative analytic techniques, Pennebaker X-rays everything from John McCain&#8217;s tweets to the Federalist Papers. Who would have predicted that the high school student who uses too many verbs in her college admissions essay is likely to make lower grades in college? Or that a world leader&#8217;s use of pronouns could reliably presage whether he will lead his country into war? You&#8217;ll learn what Lady Gaga and William Butler Yeats have in common, and how Ebenezer Scrooge&#8217;s syntax hints at his self-deception and repressed emotion in this sprightly, surprising tour of what our words are saying-whether we mean them to or not.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Words on the Move : Why English Won&#8217;t &#8211; And Can&#8217;t &#8211; Sit Still (Like, Literally) &#8211; Professor of Linguistics John McWhorter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/words-on-the-move-why-english-wont-and-cant-sit-still-like-literally-professor-of-linguistics-john-mcwhorter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar & Vocabulary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/words-on-the-move-why-english-wont-and-cant-sit-still-like-literally-professor-of-linguistics-john-mcwhorter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Language is always changing, but the way English is spoken today rubs many of us the wrong way. Whether it&#8217;s the use of literally to mean &#8220;figuratively,&#8221; or the way young people use LOL or business jargon like What&#8217;s the ask?&#8211;it often seems as if the language is deteriorating before our eyes. But the truth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/words-on-the-move-why-english-wont-and-cant-sit-still-like-literally-professor-of-linguistics-john-mcwhorter-abridged/">Words on the Move : Why English Won&#8217;t &#8211; And Can&#8217;t &#8211; Sit Still (Like, Literally) &#8211; Professor of Linguistics John McWhorter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Language is always changing, but the way English is spoken today rubs many of us the wrong way. Whether it&#8217;s the use of literally to mean &#8220;figuratively,&#8221; or the way young people use LOL or business jargon like What&#8217;s the ask?&#8211;it often seems as if the language is deteriorating before our eyes.     </p>
<p>                    But the truth is different and a lot less scary. Drawing examples from everyday life and employing a generous helping of humor, John McWhorter shows that these shifts are common to all languages, and that we should embrace these changes, not condemn them.     </p>
<p>                    He opens our eyes to the surprising backstories to words and expressions we use every day. Did you know that silly once meant &#8220;blessed&#8221;? Or that ought was the original past tense of owe? Or that the suffix -ly in adverbs is actually a remnant of the word like?     </p>
<p>                    In Words on the Move, McWhorter encourages us to marvel at the dynamism and resilience of the English language, and his book offers a delightful journey where we see that words are ever on the move and our lives are all the richer for it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/words-on-the-move-why-english-wont-and-cant-sit-still-like-literally-professor-of-linguistics-john-mcwhorter-abridged/">Words on the Move : Why English Won&#8217;t &#8211; And Can&#8217;t &#8211; Sit Still (Like, Literally) &#8211; Professor of Linguistics John McWhorter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
