<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Myth &amp; Legend Told As Fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/myth-legend-told-as-fiction/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/myth-legend-told-as-fiction/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Myth &amp; Legend Told As Fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/myth-legend-told-as-fiction/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Godless : Feathers and Fire Book 7 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</title>
		<link>/godless-feathers-and-fire-book-7-shayne-silvers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/godless-feathers-and-fire-book-7-shayne-silvers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Slaughter is the best medicine. Callie Penrose is back to murder vampires and chew bubblegum. And she&#8217;s all out of bubblegum. Callie has had a rough few days. Five minutes after discovering she had a Godfather, she learned that the future of the world depended on the two of them taking an immediate road trip. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/godless-feathers-and-fire-book-7-shayne-silvers/">Godless : Feathers and Fire Book 7 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Slaughter is the best medicine.</p>
<p>                    Callie Penrose is back to murder vampires and chew bubblegum. And she&#8217;s all out of bubblegum.</p>
<p>                    Callie has had a rough few days. Five minutes after discovering she had a Godfather, she learned that the future of the world depended on the two of them taking an immediate road trip.</p>
<p>                    To Castle Dracula-a place even the supernatural community believed to be an urban myth, dead and abandoned long ago when Dracula had perished at the hands of Van Helsing, Mina, and Jonathan Harker.</p>
<p>                    Except&#8230;Dracula and his castle were alive and well. Worse, he had been secretly running the Sanguine Council-the governmental body of every vampire in the world-ever since his alleged death, with none the wiser. Not even the vampires.</p>
<p>                    And Callie&#8217;s first Godfather-daughter dance was to go assassinate the Sultan of Suck once and for all.</p>
<p>                    But she soon learns that Dracula is the absolute least of her concerns. And that some bonds should never be forged. Because once made, they can never be broken&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Callie Penrose is about to show the world fear in a palmful of blood.</p>
<p>                    If you like Jim Butcher, Kevin Hearne, Steve McHugh, Michael Anderle, Ilona Andrews, Patricia Briggs, Shannon Mayer, or K.F. Breene, you won&#8217;t be able to put down the highly addictive Feathers and Fire Series, or anything else in the Temple Verse.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Shayne Silvers, Jim Butcher, and Kevin Hearne are easily my favorite Urban Fantasy Authors. In that order.&#8221; &#8211; Michael Anderle, Amazon Top 25 Bestselling Author</p>
<p>                    More than 1m copies downloaded and thousands of five-star reviews. Available in digital, print, and audiobook formats.</p>
<p>                    What Amazon readers are saying: </p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His foul-mouthed unicorn murders rainbows!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Move over Dresden!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;The Temple Verse HAS to be picked up by Netflix soon.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Silvers could write a grocery list on a dirty napkin and make it an international bestseller.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I went from crying my eyes out to laughing uncontrollably, repeatedly.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;It&#8217;s like the characters walked off the page, joined me at the bar, and bought me a drink.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I am astounded as to how the author keeps the story fresh and exciting.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I usually see plot twists a mile away. Shayne has proven me wrong. Every time.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Best books I&#8217;ve read in thirty years.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His intense actions scenes let you see the fangs and claws, hear the gunshots, feel the magic, and smell the fear.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Everything you thought you knew about vampires, shifters, dragons, wizards, fairies and gods is flat wrong.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Publishers who didn&#8217;t snap up this series are missing out on a gold mine.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Silvers has pleasured over one million readers with the Temple Universe. Now it&#8217;s your turn for a little pleasuring&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/godless-feathers-and-fire-book-7-shayne-silvers/">Godless : Feathers and Fire Book 7 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wild Embers : Poems of rebellion, fire and beauty &#8211; Nikita Gill</title>
		<link>/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry By Individual Poets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A stunning collection of poetry on feminism, trauma, survival and empowerment. You cannot burn away What has always been aflame WILD EMBERS explores the fire that lies within every soul, weaving words around ideas of feeling at home in your own skin, allowing yourself to heal and learning to embrace your uniqueness with love from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/">Wild Embers : Poems of rebellion, fire and beauty &#8211; Nikita Gill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A stunning collection of poetry on feminism, trauma, survival and empowerment.    </p>
<p>                    You cannot burn away<br />
                    What has always been aflame    </p>
<p>                    WILD EMBERS explores the fire that lies within every soul, weaving words around ideas of feeling at home in your own skin, allowing yourself to heal and learning to embrace your uniqueness with love from the universe.     </p>
<p>                    Featuring rewritten fairytale heroines, goddess wisdom and poetry that burns with revolution, this collection is an explosion of femininity, empowerment and personal growth.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/">Wild Embers : Poems of rebellion, fire and beauty &#8211; Nikita Gill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Return of the King &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</title>
		<link>/the-return-of-the-king-j-r-r-tolkien/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-return-of-the-king-j-r-r-tolkien/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Classic hardback edition of the third volume of The Lord of the Rings, now featuring Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design. Includes special packaging and the definitive edition of the text, with fold-out maps. The Companions of the Ring have become involved in separate adventures as the quest continues. Aragorn, revealed as the hidden heir of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-return-of-the-king-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Return of the King &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Classic hardback edition of the third volume of The Lord of the Rings, now featuring Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design. Includes special packaging and the definitive edition of the text, with fold-out maps.</p>
<p>                              The Companions of the Ring have become involved in separate adventures as the quest continues. Aragorn, revealed as the hidden heir of the ancient Kings of the West, joined with the Riders of Rohan against the forces of Isengard, and took part in the desperate victory of the Hornburg. Merry and Pippin, captured by orcs, escaped into Fangorn Forest and there encountered the Ents.</p>
<p>                              Gandalf returned, miraculously, and defeated the evil wizard, Saruman. Meanwhile, Sam and Frodo progressed towards Mordor to destroy the Ring, accompanied by Smeagol &#8211; Gollum, still obsessed by his &#8216;preciouss&#8217;. After a battle with the giant spider, Shelob, Sam left his master for dead; but Frodo is still alive &#8211; in the hands of the orcs. And all the time the armies of the Dark Lord are massing.</p>
<p>                              This classic hardback features Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design, and its text has been fully restored with almost 400 corrections &#8211; with the full co-operation of Christopher Tolkien &#8211; making it the definitive version, and as close as possible to the version that J.R.R. Tolkien intended. Also included are the original red and black maps as fold-out sheets, and &#8211; for the first time &#8211; a fully revised and enlarged index.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-return-of-the-king-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Return of the King &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circe : The No. 1 Bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles &#8211; Madeline Miller</title>
		<link>/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The international Number One bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles, shortlisted for the Women&#8217;s Prize for Fiction Woman. Witch. Myth. Mortal. Outcast. Lover. Destroyer. Survivor. CIRCE. In the house of Helios, god of the sun and mightiest of the Titans, a daughter is born. Circe is a strange child &#8211; not powerful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/">Circe : The No. 1 Bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles &#8211; Madeline Miller</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The international Number One bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles, shortlisted for the Women&#8217;s Prize for Fiction</p>
<p>                    Woman. Witch. Myth. Mortal. Outcast. Lover. Destroyer. Survivor. CIRCE.</p>
<p>                     In the house of Helios, god of the sun and mightiest of the Titans, a daughter is born. Circe is a strange child &#8211; not powerful and terrible, like her father, nor gorgeous and mercenary like her mother. Scorned and rejected, Circe grows up in the shadows, at home in neither the world of gods or mortals. But Circe has a dark power of her own: witchcraft. When her gift threatens the gods, she is banished to the island of Aiaia where she hones her occult craft, casting spells, gathering strange herbs and taming wild beasts. Yet a woman who stands alone will never be left in peace for long &#8211; and among her island&#8217;s guests is an unexpected visitor: the mortal Odysseus, for whom Circe will risk everything. </p>
<p>                     So Circe sets forth her tale, a vivid, mesmerizing epic of family rivalry, love and loss &#8211; the defiant, inextinguishable song of woman burning hot and bright through the darkness of a man&#8217;s world.</p>
<p>                    THE NUMBER ONE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER </p>
<p>                    CHOSEN AS A BOOK OF THE YEAR BY THE GUARDIAN, TELEGRAPH, SUNDAY TELEGRAPH, I PAPER, SUNDAY EXPRESS, IRISH TIMES, TIMES LITERARY SUPPLEMENT, AMAZON, AUDIBLE, BUZZFEED, REFINERY 29, WASHINGTON POST, BOSTON GLOBE, SEATTLE TIMES, TIME MAGAZINE, NEWSWEEK, PEOPLE, ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY, KIRKUS, PUBLISHERS WEEKLY AND GOODREADS</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/">Circe : The No. 1 Bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles &#8211; Madeline Miller</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Skaar Invasion: Book Two of the Fall of Shannara &#8211; Terry Brooks</title>
		<link>/the-skaar-invasion-book-two-of-the-fall-of-shannara-terry-brooks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-skaar-invasion-book-two-of-the-fall-of-shannara-terry-brooks/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TERRY&#8217;S PLACE IS AT THE HEAD OF THE FANTASY WORLD&#8217; Philip Pullman Following The Black Elfstone comes the second book in the triumphant four-part conclusion to the Shannara series, from one of the all-time masters of fantasy. Tensions in the Four Lands are high. The mysterious force that laid waste to Paranor has revealed a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-skaar-invasion-book-two-of-the-fall-of-shannara-terry-brooks/">The Skaar Invasion: Book Two of the Fall of Shannara &#8211; Terry Brooks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TERRY&#8217;S PLACE IS AT THE HEAD OF THE FANTASY WORLD&#8217; Philip Pullman</p>
<p>                    Following The Black Elfstone comes the second book in the triumphant four-part conclusion to the Shannara series, from one of the all-time masters of fantasy.</p>
<p>                    Tensions in the Four Lands are high. The mysterious force that laid waste to Paranor has revealed a more human face. While some gain a new understanding of the invaders and what they are after, others continue their existing quests even as the peril rises. For what looked to be a formidable invading force proves only the forerunner of a much vaster army &#8211; one that is now marching against the Four Lands in all its fury.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I can&#8217;t even begin to count how many of Terry Brooks&#8217;s books I&#8217;ve read (and re-read) over the years&#8217; Patrick Rothfuss</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I would not be writing epic fantasy today if not for Shannara&#8217; Peter V. Brett</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master of the craft . . . required reading&#8217; Brent Weeks</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-skaar-invasion-book-two-of-the-fall-of-shannara-terry-brooks/">The Skaar Invasion: Book Two of the Fall of Shannara &#8211; Terry Brooks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Foundation : Book One of the Collegium Chronicles (A Valdemar Novel) &#8211; Mercedes Lackey</title>
		<link>/foundation-book-one-of-the-collegium-chronicles-a-valdemar-novel-mercedes-lackey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/foundation-book-one-of-the-collegium-chronicles-a-valdemar-novel-mercedes-lackey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this chronicle of the early history of Valdemar, a thirteen-year-old orphan named Magpie escapes a life of slavery in the gem mines when he is chosen by one of the magical Companion horses of Valdemar to be trained as a Herald. Thrust into the center of a legend in the making, Magpie discovers talents [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/foundation-book-one-of-the-collegium-chronicles-a-valdemar-novel-mercedes-lackey/">Foundation : Book One of the Collegium Chronicles (A Valdemar Novel) &#8211; Mercedes Lackey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this chronicle of the early history of Valdemar, a thirteen-year-old orphan named Magpie escapes a life of slavery in the gem mines when he is chosen by one of the magical Companion horses of Valdemar to be trained as a Herald. Thrust into the center of a legend in the making, Magpie discovers talents he never knew he had and witnesses the founding of the great Heralds&#8217; Collegium.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/foundation-book-one-of-the-collegium-chronicles-a-valdemar-novel-mercedes-lackey/">Foundation : Book One of the Collegium Chronicles (A Valdemar Novel) &#8211; Mercedes Lackey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rose Madder &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/rose-madder-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rose-madder-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Roused by a single drop of blood, Rosie Daniels wakes up to the chilling realisation that her husband is going to kill her. And she takes flight &#8211; with his credit card. Alone in a strange city, Rosie begins to build a new life: she meets Bill and she finds an odd junk shop painting, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rose-madder-stephen-king/">Rose Madder &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Roused by a single drop of blood, Rosie Daniels wakes up to the chilling realisation that her husband is going to kill her. And she takes flight &#8211; with his credit card.    </p>
<p>                     Alone in a strange city, Rosie begins to build a new life: she meets Bill and she finds an odd junk shop painting, &#8216;Rose Madder&#8217;, which strangely seems to want her as much as she wants it.    </p>
<p>                     But it&#8217;s hard for Rosie not to keep looking over her shoulder. Norman is a corrupt cop with the instincts of a predator. A man almost mythic in his monstrosity.  For Rosie to survive, she must enter the myth and become a person she never knew she could be &#8211; Rose Madder.    </p>
<p>                    Because Norman is getting close. Rosie can feel how close he is getting . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rose-madder-stephen-king/">Rose Madder &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret of the Nagas &#8211; Amish Tripathi</title>
		<link>/the-secret-of-the-nagas-amish-tripathi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-of-the-nagas-amish-tripathi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, He is a God. 4000 years ago, He was just a man. The hunt is on. The sinister Naga warrior has killed his friend Brahaspati and now stalks his wife Sati. Shiva, the Tibetan immigrant who is the prophesied destroyer of evil, will not rest till he finds his demonic adversary. His vengeance and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-of-the-nagas-amish-tripathi/">The Secret of the Nagas &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today, He is a God. 4000 years ago, He was just a man. The hunt is on.</p>
<p>                    The sinister Naga warrior has killed his friend Brahaspati and now stalks his wife Sati. Shiva, the Tibetan immigrant who is the prophesied destroyer of evil, will not rest till he finds his demonic adversary. His vengeance and the path to evil will lead him to the door of the Nagas, the serpent people. Of that he is certain.</p>
<p>                    The evidence of the malevolent rise of evil is everywhere. A kingdom is dying as it is held to ransom for a miracle drug. A crown prince is murdered. The Vasudevs &#8211; Shiva&#8217;s philosopher guides &#8211; betray his unquestioning faith as they take the aid of the dark side. Even the perfect empire, Meluha is riddled with a terrible secret in Maika, the city of births. Unknown to Shiva, a master puppeteer is playing a grand game.</p>
<p>                    In a journey that will take him across the length and breadth of ancient India, Shiva searches for the truth in a land of deadly mysteries &#8211; only to find that nothing is what it seems. Fierce battles will be fought. Surprising alliances will be forged. Unbelievable secrets will be revealed in this second book of the Shiva Trilogy, the sequel to the #1 national bestseller, The Immortals of Meluha.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-of-the-nagas-amish-tripathi/">The Secret of the Nagas &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Eyes of the Dragon &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-eyes-of-the-dragon-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-eyes-of-the-dragon-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While evidence is gathered, and the land of Delain mourns, Flagg the King&#8217;s magician, unscrupulous, greedy and powerful, plots. Soon the King&#8217;s elder son, Peter, is imprisoned in the needle, the top of a high tower, for his father&#8217;s murder. And Thomas inherits the throne. Only Peter knows the truth of his innocence, and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-eyes-of-the-dragon-stephen-king/">The Eyes of the Dragon &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While evidence is gathered, and the land of Delain mourns, Flagg the King&#8217;s magician, unscrupulous, greedy and powerful, plots. Soon the King&#8217;s elder son, Peter, is imprisoned in the needle, the top of a high tower, for his father&#8217;s murder. And Thomas inherits the throne.    </p>
<p>                    Only Peter knows the truth of his innocence, and the true evil that is Flagg. Only Peter can save Delain from the horror the magician has in store. He has a plan, but it is rife with danger. And if he fails, he won&#8217;t get a second chance . . .    </p>
<p>                    A captivating tale of heroic adventure, of dragons and princes, of mysterious mice and men from the pen of the master storyteller.There is a reason why Stephen King is one of the bestselling writers in the world, ever. Described in the Daily Express as &#8216;a fabulous teller of stories&#8217;, Stephen King writes books that draw you in and are impossible to put down.    </p>
<p>                    The King is dead, murdered by an unusual poison.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-eyes-of-the-dragon-stephen-king/">The Eyes of the Dragon &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Oath of The Vayuputras &#8211; Amish Tripathi</title>
		<link>/the-oath-of-the-vayuputras-amish-tripathi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-oath-of-the-vayuputras-amish-tripathi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, Shiva is a god. But four thousand years ago, he was just a man &#8211; until he brought his people to Meluha, a near-perfect empire founded by the great king Lord Ram. There he discovered he was the Neelkanth, a barbarian long prophesied to be Meluha&#8217;s saviour. But in his hour of victory fighting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-oath-of-the-vayuputras-amish-tripathi/">The Oath of The Vayuputras &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today, Shiva is a god. But four thousand years ago, he was just a man &#8211; until he brought his people to Meluha, a near-perfect empire founded by the great king Lord Ram. There he discovered he was the Neelkanth, a barbarian long prophesied to be Meluha&#8217;s saviour.    </p>
<p>                    But in his hour of victory fighting the Chandravanshis &#8211; Meluha&#8217;s enemy &#8211; he discovered they had their own prophecy.    </p>
<p>                    Now he must fight to uncover the treachery within his inner circle, and unmask those who are about to destroy all that he has fought for. Shiva is about to learn that good and evil are two sides of the same coin&#8230;.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-oath-of-the-vayuputras-amish-tripathi/">The Oath of The Vayuputras &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Two Towers &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</title>
		<link>/the-two-towers-j-r-r-tolkien/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-two-towers-j-r-r-tolkien/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Classic hardback edition of the second volume of The Lord of the Rings, featuring Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design. Includes special packaging and the definitive edition of the text, with fold-out map. Frodo and the Companions of the Ring have been beset by danger during their quest to prevent the Ruling Ring from falling into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-two-towers-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Two Towers &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Classic hardback edition of the second volume of The Lord of the Rings, featuring Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design. Includes special packaging and the definitive edition of the text, with fold-out map. Frodo and the Companions of the Ring have been beset by danger during their quest to prevent the Ruling Ring from falling into the hands of the Dark Lord by destroying it in the Cracks of Doom. They have lost the wizard, Gandalf, in the battle with an evil spirit in the Mines of Moria; and at the Falls of Rauros, Boromir, seduced by the power of the Ring, tried to seize it by force. While Frodo and Sam made their escape the rest of the company were attacked by Orcs. Now they continue their journey alone down the great River Anduin &#8211; alone, that is, save for the mysterious creeping figure that follows wherever they go. This classic hardback features Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design, and its text has been fully restored with almost 400 corrections &#8211; with the full co-operation of Christopher Tolkien &#8211; making it the definitive version, and as close as possible to the version that J.R.R. Tolkien intended.Also included is the original red and black map of the Shire as a foldout sheet.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-two-towers-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Two Towers &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Immortals of Meluha &#8211; Amish Tripathi</title>
		<link>/the-immortals-of-meluha-amish-tripathi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-immortals-of-meluha-amish-tripathi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>1900 BC. In what modern Indians mistakenly call the Indus Valley Civilisation. The inhabitants of that period called it the land of Meluha &#8211; a near perfect empire created many centuries earlier by Lord Ram, one of the greatest monarchs that ever lived. This once proud empire and its Suryavanshi rulers face severe perils as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortals-of-meluha-amish-tripathi/">The Immortals of Meluha &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>1900 BC. In what modern Indians mistakenly call the Indus Valley Civilisation. The inhabitants of that period called it the land of Meluha &#8211; a near perfect empire created many centuries earlier by Lord Ram, one of the greatest monarchs that ever lived. This once proud empire and its Suryavanshi rulers face severe perils as its primary river, the revered Saraswati, is slowly drying to extinction. They also face devastating terrorist attacks from the east, the land of the Chandravanshis. To make matters worse, the Chandravanshis appear to have allied with the Nagas, an ostracised and sinister race of deformed humans with astonishing martial skills. The only hope for the Suryavanshis is an ancient legend: &#8216;When evil reaches epic proportions, when all seems lost, when it appears that your enemies have triumphed, a hero will emerge.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Is the rough-hewn Tibetan immigrant Shiva, really that hero? And does he want to be that hero at all? Drawn suddenly to his destiny, by duty as well as by love, will Shiva lead the Suryavanshi vengeance and destroy evil? This is the first book in a trilogy on Shiva, the simple man whose karma re-cast him as our Mahadev, the God of Gods.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortals-of-meluha-amish-tripathi/">The Immortals of Meluha &#8211; Amish Tripathi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fellowship of the Ring &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</title>
		<link>/the-fellowship-of-the-ring-j-r-r-tolkien/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fellowship-of-the-ring-j-r-r-tolkien/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Continuing the story begun in The Hobbit, this is the first part of Tolkien&#8217;s epic masterpiece, The Lord of the Rings, featuring a striking black cover based on Tolkien&#8217;s own design, the definitive text, and a detailed map of Middle-earth. Sauron, the Dark Lord, has gathered to him all the Rings of Power &#8211; the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fellowship-of-the-ring-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Fellowship of the Ring &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Continuing the story begun in The Hobbit, this is the first part of Tolkien&#8217;s epic masterpiece, The Lord of the Rings, featuring a striking black cover based on Tolkien&#8217;s own design, the definitive text, and a detailed map of Middle-earth.</p>
<p>                              Sauron, the Dark Lord, has gathered to him all the Rings of Power &#8211; the means by which he intends to rule Middle-earth. All he lacks in his plans for dominion is the One Ring &#8211; the ring that rules them all &#8211; which has fallen into the hands of the hobbit, Bilbo Baggins.</p>
<p>                              In a sleepy village in the Shire, young Frodo Baggins finds himself faced with an immense task, as his elderly cousin Bilbo entrusts the Ring to his care. Frodo must leave his home and make a perilous journey across Middle-earth to the Cracks of Doom, there to destroy the Ring and foil the Dark Lord in his evil purpose.</p>
<p>                              Part of a set of three paperbacks, this popular edition is once again available in its classic black livery designed by Tolkien himself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fellowship-of-the-ring-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Fellowship of the Ring &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out of Oz : The Final Volume in the Wicked Years &#8211; Gregory Maguire</title>
		<link>/out-of-oz-the-final-volume-in-the-wicked-years-gregory-maguire/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-oz-the-final-volume-in-the-wicked-years-gregory-maguire/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Maguire&#8217;s work is melodic, symphonic, and beautiful; it is dejected and biting and brave. How great that people flock to these magical novels.&#8221; &#8211;Los Angeles Times Book Review Bestselling author Gregory Maguire&#8217;s remarkable series, The Wicked Years, comes full circle with this, his fourth and final excursion across a darker, richer, more complex landscape of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-oz-the-final-volume-in-the-wicked-years-gregory-maguire/">Out of Oz : The Final Volume in the Wicked Years &#8211; Gregory Maguire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Maguire&#8217;s work is melodic, symphonic, and beautiful; it is dejected and biting and brave. How great that people flock to these magical novels.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Los Angeles Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author Gregory Maguire&#8217;s remarkable series, The Wicked Years, comes full circle with this, his fourth and final excursion across a darker, richer, more complex landscape of &#8220;the magical land of Oz.&#8221; Out of Oz brilliantly reimagines L. Frank Baum&#8217;s world over the rainbow as wracked with social unrest&#8211;placing Glinda the good witch under house arrest and having the cowardly Lion on the lam from the law as the Emerald City prepares to make war on Munchkinland. Even Dorothy makes a triumphant return in Maguire&#8217;s magnificent Oz finale&#8211;tying up every loose green end of the series he began with his classic Wicked, the basis for the smash hit Broadway musical.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-oz-the-final-volume-in-the-wicked-years-gregory-maguire/">Out of Oz : The Final Volume in the Wicked Years &#8211; Gregory Maguire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Two Lost Mountains : An Action-Packed Jack West Thriller &#8211; Matthew Reilly</title>
		<link>/the-two-lost-mountains-an-action-packed-jack-west-thriller-matthew-reilly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Egyptian Archaeology / Egyptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Underwater Archaeology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-two-lost-mountains-an-action-packed-jack-west-thriller-matthew-reilly/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE HOTTEST ACTION WRITER AROUND&#8217; EVENING TELEGRAPH THE LATEST ADVENTURE IN THE WILDLY ENTERTAINING, ACTION-PACKED JACK WEST SERIES Former SAS soldier Jack West is on a mission to save the world, no matter what &#8211; or who &#8211; it might cost him. Still reeling from the loss of his daughter, and with his rivals far [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-two-lost-mountains-an-action-packed-jack-west-thriller-matthew-reilly/">The Two Lost Mountains : An Action-Packed Jack West Thriller &#8211; Matthew Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE HOTTEST ACTION WRITER AROUND&#8217; EVENING TELEGRAPH<br />
                    THE LATEST ADVENTURE IN THE WILDLY ENTERTAINING, ACTION-PACKED JACK WEST SERIES</p>
<p>                    Former SAS soldier Jack West is on a mission to save the world, no matter what &#8211; or who &#8211; it might cost him.</p>
<p>                    Still reeling from the loss of his daughter, and with his rivals far ahead of him, Jack must race across the globe to complete the ancient Trial of the Mountains.</p>
<p>                    With the odds already against them, Jack and his crew will soon discover that a new player has entered the race, a general so feared that he had been locked away in the deepest of dungeons.</p>
<p>                    Only now this general has escaped and he has a horrifying plan of his own&#8230;</p>
<p>                    * * * * *</p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR THE JACK WEST THRILLERS<br />
                    &#8216;An action hero worthy of Lee Child&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling, action-packed adventure from cover to cover&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Nobody writes action like Matthew Reilly&#8217; Vince Flynn</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Get ready for a wild ride&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Exciting and entertaining&#8217; Chicago Sun-Times</p>
<p>                    * * * * *</p>
<p>                    READERS LOVE THE JACK WEST THRILLERS</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Indiana Jones in a book . . . Immensely entertaining&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A super duper kick ass soldier&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A first class all-action historical thriller&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Heart-pounding stuff&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Enjoy the rollercoaster ride&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-two-lost-mountains-an-action-packed-jack-west-thriller-matthew-reilly/">The Two Lost Mountains : An Action-Packed Jack West Thriller &#8211; Matthew Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Son of a Witch : A Novel &#8211; Gregory Maguire</title>
		<link>/son-of-a-witch-a-novel-gregory-maguire/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/son-of-a-witch-a-novel-gregory-maguire/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Wicked Years continue in Gregory Maguire&#8217;s Son of a Witch&#8211;the heroic saga of the hapless yet determined young man who may or may not be the offspring of the fabled Wicked Witch of the West. A New York Times bestseller like its predecessor, the remarkable Wicked, Son of a Witch follows the boy Liir [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/son-of-a-witch-a-novel-gregory-maguire/">Son of a Witch : A Novel &#8211; Gregory Maguire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Wicked Years continue in Gregory Maguire&#8217;s Son of a Witch&#8211;the heroic saga of the hapless yet determined young man who may or may not be the offspring of the fabled Wicked Witch of the West. A New York Times bestseller like its predecessor, the remarkable Wicked, Son of a Witch follows the boy Liir on his dark odyssey across an ingeniously re-imagined and nearly unrecognizable Land of Oz&#8211;a journey that will take him deep into the bowels of the Emerald City, lately abandoned by the Wizard, and into the jaws of dragons. At once a grim fairy tale and an uplifting adventure, Son of a Witch is a true wonder.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/son-of-a-witch-a-novel-gregory-maguire/">Son of a Witch : A Novel &#8211; Gregory Maguire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lion Among Men &#8211; Gregory Maguire</title>
		<link>/lion-among-men-gregory-maguire/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lion-among-men-gregory-maguire/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Return to a darker Oz with Gregory Maguire. In A Lion Among Men, the third volume in Maguire&#8217;s acclaimed, New York Times bestselling series The Wicked Years, a fuller, more complex Cowardly Lion is brought to life and gets to tell his remarkable tale. It is a story of oppression and fear in a world [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lion-among-men-gregory-maguire/">Lion Among Men &#8211; Gregory Maguire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Return to a darker Oz with Gregory Maguire. In A Lion Among Men, the third volume in Maguire&#8217;s acclaimed, New York Times bestselling series The Wicked Years, a fuller, more complex Cowardly Lion is brought to life and gets to tell his remarkable tale. It is a story of oppression and fear in a world gone mad with war fever&#8211;of Munchkins, Wizards, and Wicked Witches&#8211;and especially of a gentle soul and determined survivor who is truly A Lion Among Men.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lion-among-men-gregory-maguire/">Lion Among Men &#8211; Gregory Maguire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ocean at the End of the Lane &#8211; Neil Gaiman</title>
		<link>/the-ocean-at-the-end-of-the-lane-neil-gaiman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ocean-at-the-end-of-the-lane-neil-gaiman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NATIONAL BOOK AWARD &#8216;BOOK OF THE YEAR&#8217; AN ACCLAIMED WEST END THEATRE PRODUCTION ***** &#8216;Neil Gaiman&#8217;s entire body of work is a feat of elegant sorcery. He writes with such assurance and originality that the reader has no choice but to surrender to a waking dream&#8217; ARMISTEAD MAUPIN &#8216;Some books just swallow you up, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ocean-at-the-end-of-the-lane-neil-gaiman/">The Ocean at the End of the Lane &#8211; Neil Gaiman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NATIONAL BOOK AWARD &#8216;BOOK OF THE YEAR&#8217;</p>
<p>                    AN ACCLAIMED WEST END THEATRE PRODUCTION *****</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Neil Gaiman&#8217;s entire body of work is a feat of elegant sorcery. He writes with such assurance and originality that the reader has no choice but to surrender to a waking dream&#8217; ARMISTEAD MAUPIN</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Some books just swallow you up, heart and soul&#8217; JOANNE HARRIS</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Summons both the powerlessness and wonder of childhood, and the complicated landscape of memory and forgetting&#8217; GUARDIAN</p>
<p>                    &#8212;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;My favourite response to this book is when people say, &#8216;My childhood was nothing like that &#8211; and it was as if I was reading about me&#8217; NEIL GAIMAN</p>
<p>                    &#8212;</p>
<p>                    This is what he remembers, as he sits by the ocean at the end of the lane:</p>
<p>                    A dead man on the back seat of the car, and warm milk at the farmhouse.<br />
                    An ancient little girl, and an old woman who saw the moon being made.<br />
                    A beautiful housekeeper with a monstrous smile.<br />
                    And dark forces woken that were best left undisturbed.</p>
<p>                    They are memories hard to believe, waiting at the edges of things. The recollections of a man who thought he was lost but is now, perhaps, remembering a time when he was saved . . .</p>
<p>                    NEIL GAIMAN.<br />
                    WITH STORIES COME POSSIBILITIES.</p>
<p>                    &#8212;</p>
<p>                    **Includes an interview with Neil Gaiman on creating the world of the novel**</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ocean-at-the-end-of-the-lane-neil-gaiman/">The Ocean at the End of the Lane &#8211; Neil Gaiman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
