<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Language: History &amp; General Works Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/language-history-general-works/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/language-history-general-works/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Language: History &amp; General Works Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/language-history-general-works/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities. In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities.     </p>
<p>                    In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our language carries secrets about our feelings, our self-concept, and our social intelligence. Our most forgettable words, such as pronouns and prepositions, can be the most revealing: their patterns are as distinctive as fingerprints.     </p>
<p>                    Using innovative analytic techniques, Pennebaker X-rays everything from John McCain&#8217;s tweets to the Federalist Papers. Who would have predicted that the high school student who uses too many verbs in her college admissions essay is likely to make lower grades in college? Or that a world leader&#8217;s use of pronouns could reliably presage whether he will lead his country into war? You&#8217;ll learn what Lady Gaga and William Butler Yeats have in common, and how Ebenezer Scrooge&#8217;s syntax hints at his self-deception and repressed emotion in this sprightly, surprising tour of what our words are saying-whether we mean them to or not.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making a Point : The Pernickety Story of English Punctuation &#8211; David Crystal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-a-point-the-pernickety-story-of-english-punctuation-david-crystal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dictionaries & Dictionary Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-a-point-the-pernickety-story-of-english-punctuation-david-crystal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This &#8216;engaging history of punctuation&#8217; (Wall Street Journal) is not only the first history of its kind, but a complete guide on how to use English punctuation. Behind every punctuation mark lies a thousand stories. The punctuation of English, marked with occasional rationality, is founded on arbitrariness and littered with oddities. For a system of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-a-point-the-pernickety-story-of-english-punctuation-david-crystal-abridged/">Making a Point : The Pernickety Story of English Punctuation &#8211; David Crystal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This &#8216;engaging history of punctuation&#8217; (Wall Street Journal) is not only the first history of its kind, but a complete guide on how to use English punctuation.    </p>
<p>                    Behind every punctuation mark lies a thousand stories. The punctuation of English, marked with occasional rationality, is founded on arbitrariness and littered with oddities. For a system of a few dozen marks it generates a disproportionate degree of  uncertainty and passion, inspiring organisations like the Apostrophe Protection Society and sending enthusiasts, correction-pens in hand, in a crusade against error.    </p>
<p>                    Professor Crystal leads us through this minefield with characteristic wit, clarity and commonsense. He gives a fascinating account of the origin and progress of every kind of punctuation mark over one and a half millennia, and he offers sound advice on how punctuation may be used to meet the needs of every occasion and context.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-a-point-the-pernickety-story-of-english-punctuation-david-crystal-abridged/">Making a Point : The Pernickety Story of English Punctuation &#8211; David Crystal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mother Tongue : The Story of the English Language &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lexicography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than 300 million people in the world speak English and the rest, it sometimes seems, try to&#8230;&#8217; Only Bill Bryson could make a book about the English language so entertaining. With his boundless enthusiasm and restless eye for the absurd, this is his astonishing tour of English. From its mongrel origins to its status [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/">Mother Tongue : The Story of the English Language &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than 300 million people in the world speak English and the rest, it sometimes seems, try to&#8230;&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Only Bill Bryson could make a book about the English language so entertaining. With his boundless enthusiasm and restless eye for the absurd, this is his astonishing tour of English. From its mongrel origins to its status as the world&#8217;s most-spoken tongue; its apparent simplicity to its deceptive complexity; its vibrant swearing to its uncertain spelling and pronunciation, Bryson covers all this as well as the many curious eccentricities that make it as maddening to learn as it is flexible to use.     </p>
<p>                    Bill Bryson&#8217;s classic Mother Tongue is a highly readable and hilarious tale of how English came to be the world&#8217;s language.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/">Mother Tongue : The Story of the English Language &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. But swearing is also a uniquely well-suited lens through which to look at history, offering a fascinating record of what people care about on the<br />
                    deepest levels of a culture-what&#8217;s divine, what&#8217;s terrifying, and what&#8217;s taboo.     </p>
<p>                    Holy Sh*t tells the story of two kinds of swearing-obscenities and oaths-from ancient Rome and the Bible to today. With humor and insight, Melissa Mohr takes readers on a journey to discover how &#8220;swearing&#8221; has come to include both testifying with your hand on the Bible and calling someone a *#$&#038;!* when they cut you off on the highway. She explores obscenities in ancient Rome-which were remarkably similar to our own-and unearths the history of religious oaths in the Middle Ages,<br />
                    when swearing (or not swearing) an oath was often a matter of life and death. Holy Sh*t also explains the advancement of civility and corresponding censorship of language in the 18th century, considers the rise of racial slurs after World War II, examines the physiological effects of swearing (increased heart<br />
                    rate and greater pain tolerance), and answers a question that preoccupies the FCC, the US Senate, and anyone who has recently overheard little kids at a playground: are we swearing more now than people did in the past?     </p>
<p>                    A gem of lexicography and cultural history, Holy Sh*t is a serious exploration of obscenity-and it also just might expand your repertoire of words to choose from the next time you shut your finger in the car door.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
