<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Fiction Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/fiction-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/fiction-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Fiction Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/fiction-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-girl-who-loved-tom-gordon-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-girl-who-loved-tom-gordon-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vintage King&#8217;, a delightful suspense novel in which King&#8217;s &#8216;trump card is his ability to arouse empathy for the plight of his young heroine&#8217; (Independent on Sunday), now with a stunning new cover look. The world had teeth and it could bite you with them anytime it wanted. Trisha McFarland discovered this when she was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-girl-who-loved-tom-gordon-stephen-king/">The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vintage King&#8217;, a delightful suspense novel in which King&#8217;s &#8216;trump card is his ability to arouse empathy for the plight of his young heroine&#8217; (Independent on Sunday), now with a stunning new cover look.    </p>
<p>                    The world had teeth and it could bite you with them anytime it wanted. Trisha McFarland discovered this when she was nine years old. Lost in the woods.     </p>
<p>                     Trisha has only veered a little way off the trail.  But in her panic to get back to her family, she takes a turning that leads deeper into the tangled undergrowth.      </p>
<p>                     At first it&#8217;s just the bugs, midges and mosquitoes. Then comes the hunger. For comfort she tunes her Walkman into broadcasts of the Red Sox baseball games and the performances of her hero Tom Gordon.     </p>
<p>                     But as darkness begins to fall, Trisha realises that she is not alone. There&#8217;s something else in the woods &#8211; watching. Waiting . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-girl-who-loved-tom-gordon-stephen-king/">The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Minimum Wage Magic : DFZ Book 1 &#8211; Rachel Aaron</title>
		<link>/minimum-wage-magic-dfz-book-1-rachel-aaron/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/minimum-wage-magic-dfz-book-1-rachel-aaron/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Making a living is hard. In a lawless city where gods are real, dragons are traffic hazards, and buildings move around on their own, it can feel downright impossible. Good thing freelance mage Opal Yong-ae has never let little things like impossibility stop her. She&#8217;s found a way to put her overpriced magical art history [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/minimum-wage-magic-dfz-book-1-rachel-aaron/">Minimum Wage Magic : DFZ Book 1 &#8211; Rachel Aaron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Making a living is hard. In a lawless city where gods are real, dragons are traffic hazards, and buildings move around on their own, it can feel downright impossible.    </p>
<p>                    Good thing freelance mage Opal Yong-ae has never let little things like impossibility stop her. She&#8217;s found a way to put her overpriced magical art history degree to use as a Cleaner: a contract municipal employee who empties out abandoned apartments and resells the unusual treasures she finds inside for a profit. It&#8217;s not a pretty job, or a safe one&#8211;there&#8217;s a reason she wears bite-proof gloves&#8211;but when you&#8217;re neck-deep in debt to a very magical, very nasty individual, you can&#8217;t be picky about where the money comes from.    </p>
<p>                    But even Opal&#8217;s low standards are put to the test when the only thing of value in her latest apartment is the body of the previous tenant. Dealing with the dead isn&#8217;t technically part of her job, but this mage died hiding a secret that could be worth a lot of money, and Opal&#8217;s the only one who knows. With debts she can&#8217;t pay due at the end of the week, this could be the big break she&#8217;s been waiting for, but in a city of runaway magic where getting in over your head generally means losing it, the cost of chasing this opportunity might be more than Opal can survive.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/minimum-wage-magic-dfz-book-1-rachel-aaron/">Minimum Wage Magic : DFZ Book 1 &#8211; Rachel Aaron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Part-Time Gods : DFZ Book 2 &#8211; Rachel Aaron</title>
		<link>/part-time-gods-dfz-book-2-rachel-aaron/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/part-time-gods-dfz-book-2-rachel-aaron/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Life in the magical mess of the Detroit Free Zone is never easy. When you&#8217;re laboring under the curse of a certain prideful, overbearing dragon, it can be down right impossible. My name is Opal Yong-ae, and I&#8217;m a Cleaner. At least, I used to be. Thanks to the supernatural bad luck that turns everything [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/part-time-gods-dfz-book-2-rachel-aaron/">Part-Time Gods : DFZ Book 2 &#8211; Rachel Aaron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Life in the magical mess of the Detroit Free Zone is never easy. When you&#8217;re laboring under the curse of a certain prideful, overbearing dragon, it can be down right impossible.    </p>
<p>                    My name is Opal Yong-ae, and I&#8217;m a Cleaner. At least, I used to be. Thanks to the supernatural bad luck that turns everything I do against me, these days I&#8217;m more of a walking disaster. Getting rid of this curse is the only way to get my life back. Unfortunately, dragon magic is every bit as sneaky and deadly as the monsters behind it, and just as hard to beat.    </p>
<p>                    But I&#8217;ve never been one to take her doom at face value. Cornered doesn&#8217;t mean defeated, and in an awakened city that rules herself, dragons are no longer the biggest powers around.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/part-time-gods-dfz-book-2-rachel-aaron/">Part-Time Gods : DFZ Book 2 &#8211; Rachel Aaron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Racing in the Rain &#8211; Garth Stein</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogs As Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major motion picture, this heart-warming and inspirational tale follows Enzo, a loyal family dog, tells the story of his human family, how they nearly fell apart, and what he did to bring them back together. Enzo knows he is different from other dogs: he thinks and feels in nearly human ways. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/">The Art of Racing in the Rain &#8211; Garth Stein</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major motion picture, this heart-warming and inspirational tale follows Enzo, a loyal family dog, tells the story of his human family, how they nearly fell apart, and what he did to bring them back together.    </p>
<p>                              Enzo knows he is different from other dogs: he thinks and feels in nearly human ways. He has educated himself by watching extensive television, and by listening very closely to the words of his master, Denny Swift, an up-and-coming race car driver. Through Denny, Enzo realizes that racing is a metaphor: that by applying the techniques a driver would apply on the race track, one can successfully navigate the ordeals and travails one encounters in life.    </p>
<p>                              Enzo relates the story of his human family, sharing their tragedies and triumphs. In the end, despite what he sees as his own limitations as a dog, Enzo comes through heroically to preserve the Swift family.    </p>
<p>                              The Art of Racing in the Rain is a testament to a man&#8217;s life, given by his dog. But it is also a testament to the dog, himself. Though Enzo cannot speak, he understands everything that happens around him as he bears witness to his master&#8217;s problems. His enforced muteness only refines his listening ability, and allows him to understand many of life&#8217;s nuances that are lost on most humans. With humour, sharp observation, and a courageous heart, Enzo guides the reader to the bittersweet yet ultimately satisfying conclusion: there are no limitations to what we can achieve, if we truly know where we want to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/">The Art of Racing in the Rain &#8211; Garth Stein</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Poppy Wife : A Novel of the Great War &#8211; Caroline Scott</title>
		<link>/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 1 Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A beautifully evocative reminder of what it means to come back from war and to face the age-old question of whether it is better to have survived or to have died. Highly recommended.&#8221;&#8211;Library Journal, starred review In the tradition of Jennifer Robson and Hazel Gaynor, this unforgettable debut novel is a sweeping tale of forbidden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/">The Poppy Wife : A Novel of the Great War &#8211; Caroline Scott</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A beautifully evocative reminder of what it means to come back from war and to face the age-old question of whether it is better to have survived or to have died. Highly recommended.&#8221;&#8211;Library Journal, starred review</p>
<p>                    In the tradition of Jennifer Robson and Hazel Gaynor, this unforgettable debut novel is a sweeping tale of forbidden love, profound loss, and the startling truth of the broken families left behind in the wake of World War I.</p>
<p>                    1921. Survivors of the Great War are desperately trying to piece together the fragments of their broken lives. While many have been reunited with their loved ones, Edie&#8217;s husband Francis has not come home. Francis is presumed to have been killed in action, but Edie believes he might still be alive.</p>
<p>                    Harry, Francis&#8217;s brother, was there the day Francis was wounded. He was certain it was a fatal wound&#8211;that he saw his brother die&#8211;but as time passes, Harry begins questioning his memory of what happened. Could Francis, like many soldiers, merely be lost and confused somewhere? Hired by grieving families, Harry returns to the Western Front to photograph gravesites. As he travels through battle-scarred France and Belgium gathering news for British wives and mothers, he searches for evidence of Francis.</p>
<p>                    When Edie receives a mysterious photograph of Francis, she is more convinced than ever he might still be alive. And so, she embarks on a journey in the hope of finding some trace of her husband. Is he truly gone? And if he isn&#8217;t, then why hasn&#8217;t he come home? </p>
<p>                    As Harry and Edie&#8217;s paths converge, they get closer to the truth about Francis and, as they do, are faced with the life-changing impact of the answers they discover. </p>
<p>                    Artful and incredibly moving, The Poppy Wife tells the unforgettable story of the soldiers lost amid the chaos and ruins, and those who were desperate to find them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/">The Poppy Wife : A Novel of the Great War &#8211; Caroline Scott</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them : The Original Screenplay &#8211; J.K. Rowling</title>
		<link>/fantastic-beasts-and-where-to-find-them-the-original-screenplay-j-k-rowling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's General Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Scripts & Screenplays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Plays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Plays, Playscripts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sci Fi Books for Kids]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fantastic-beasts-and-where-to-find-them-the-original-screenplay-j-k-rowling/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>J.K. Rowling&#8217;s screenwriting debut is captured in this exciting hardcover edition of the Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them screenplay. When Magizoologist Newt Scamander arrives in New York, he intends his stay to be just a brief stopover. However, when his magical case is misplaced and some of Newt&#8217;s fantastic beasts escape, it spells [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantastic-beasts-and-where-to-find-them-the-original-screenplay-j-k-rowling/">Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them : The Original Screenplay &#8211; J.K. Rowling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>J.K. Rowling&#8217;s screenwriting debut is captured in this exciting hardcover edition of the Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them screenplay.<br />
                    When Magizoologist Newt Scamander arrives in New York, he intends his stay to be just a brief stopover. However, when his magical case is misplaced and some of Newt&#8217;s fantastic beasts escape, it spells trouble for everyone&#8230;Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them marks the screenwriting debut of J.K. Rowling, author of the beloved and internationally bestselling Harry Potter books. Featuring a cast of remarkable characters, this is epic, adventure-packed storytelling at its very best. Whether an existing fan or new to the wizarding world, this is a perfect addition to any reader&#8217;s bookshelf.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantastic-beasts-and-where-to-find-them-the-original-screenplay-j-k-rowling/">Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them : The Original Screenplay &#8211; J.K. Rowling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
