<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Operational Research Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/operational-research/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/operational-research/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Operational Research Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/operational-research/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data &#8212; It&#8217;s How You Use It : Smarter Marketing with Analytics and Dashboards &#8211; Koen Pauwels (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enterprise Software]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Did you know that your business already has the world&#8217;s greatest information-tracking team working tirelessly for you 24/7 to gather all the info you could possibly need to find your next customers? Between brand tracking, CRM programs, and online behavior tracking, as well as the always-dependable trade shows and satisfaction studies, mounds of marketing metrics [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data &#8212; It&#8217;s How You Use It : Smarter Marketing with Analytics and Dashboards &#8211; Koen Pauwels (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Did you know that your business already has the world&#8217;s greatest information-tracking team working tirelessly for you 24/7 to gather all the info you could possibly need to find your next customers? Between brand tracking, CRM programs, and online behavior tracking, as well as the always-dependable trade shows and satisfaction studies, mounds of marketing metrics are being generated for you across various touchpoints and channels. The numbers available to you are mind-blowing&#8211;but the amount itself can be mind-numbing. Where can one begin to filter through it all to find what is most beneficial for their company? Locked in the vast quantity of information are accurate, data-driven answers to every marketing question&#8211;and analytic dashboards are the key to finding it all. In It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data&#8211;It&#8217;s How You Use It, marketing expert Koen Pauwels introduces readers to these transformative web-based tools that gather, synthesize, and visually display essential data in real time, directly connecting marketing with performance. He then supplies a simple yet rigorous methodology that explains step by step how to: &#8211; Gain crucial IT support &#8211; Build a rock-solid database &#8211; Select key leading performance indicators &#8211; Design the optimal dashboard layout &#8211; Use marketing analytics to improve decisions and reap rewards There is simply too much customer-produced information out there today for marketing teams to go with gut decisions or the same old standbys. Dashboard analytics will bring scientific precision and insight to the marketing efforts of any size organization, in any industry, and turn this eye-popping data into a specific plan of attack.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data &#8212; It&#8217;s How You Use It : Smarter Marketing with Analytics and Dashboards &#8211; Koen Pauwels (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gamification for Business : Why Innovators and Changemakers use Games to break down Silos, Drive Engagement and Build Trust &#8211; Sune Gudiksen, Jake Inlove (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/gamification-for-business-why-innovators-and-changemakers-use-games-to-break-down-silos-drive-engagement-and-build-trust-sune-gudiksen-jake-inlove-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/gamification-for-business-why-innovators-and-changemakers-use-games-to-break-down-silos-drive-engagement-and-build-trust-sune-gudiksen-jake-inlove-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gamification for Business shows how games and game-based design can be used to effectively tackle business challenges and improve organizational performance. From siloed working and information overload to the clash between ongoing operations and innovation, this book shows how to identify what type of game is best suited to each business issue. With guidance on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gamification-for-business-why-innovators-and-changemakers-use-games-to-break-down-silos-drive-engagement-and-build-trust-sune-gudiksen-jake-inlove-abridged/">Gamification for Business : Why Innovators and Changemakers use Games to break down Silos, Drive Engagement and Build Trust &#8211; Sune Gudiksen, Jake Inlove (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gamification for Business shows how games and game-based design can be used to effectively tackle business challenges and improve organizational performance. From siloed working and information overload to the clash between ongoing operations and innovation, this book shows how to identify what type of game is best suited to each business issue. With guidance on online games, simulations, event-based games and gamified training, this book ensures that business leaders and senior decision makers feel confident in their ability to assess the opportunities of each type of gamification for their business.     </p>
<p>                    Including case studies from more than 20 organizations who have implemented a game-based solution, this book outlines the business issue in each company and the aim of the game, the impact the game had and key learning points to help readers implement a similar type of game in their own business. Based on extensive research into the effectiveness of games and real-world examples from companies who have experienced the benefits of serious games and design thinking, Gamification for Business is essential reading for all business professionals looking to improve employee motivation, boost engagement, create a cohesive team environment and facilitate innovation in their company for improved business performance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gamification-for-business-why-innovators-and-changemakers-use-games-to-break-down-silos-drive-engagement-and-build-trust-sune-gudiksen-jake-inlove-abridged/">Gamification for Business : Why Innovators and Changemakers use Games to break down Silos, Drive Engagement and Build Trust &#8211; Sune Gudiksen, Jake Inlove (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD. This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career. An MBA at a top business school is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold     </p>
<p>                    ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD.    </p>
<p>                    This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career.    </p>
<p>                    An MBA at a top business school is an enormous investment in time and cash. And if you don&#8217;t want to work for a consulting firm or an investment bank, the chances are it simply isn&#8217;t worth it.    </p>
<p>                    The Personal MBA gives you simple mental models for every subject that&#8217;s key to commercial success. From the basics of products and marketing to the nuances of teamwork and systems, this book distils everything you need to know to take on the MBA graduates and win.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;File this book under: NO EXCUSES&#8217; Seth Godin    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;No matter what they tell you, an MBA is not essential. If you combine reading this book with actually trying stuff, you&#8217;ll be far ahead in the business game&#8217; Kevin Kelly, founder of Wired</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>User Research : Improve Product and Service Design and Enhance Your UX Research &#8211; Stephanie Marsh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many businesses are based on creating desirable experiences, products and services for users. However, companies often fail to consider the end user &#8211; the consumer &#8211; in their planning and development processes. How can marketing practitioners effectively understand their customers and create products and services that work for them? This book has the answers. User [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/">User Research : Improve Product and Service Design and Enhance Your UX Research &#8211; Stephanie Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many businesses are based on creating desirable experiences, products and services for users. However, companies often fail to consider the end user &#8211; the consumer &#8211; in their planning and development processes. How can marketing practitioners effectively understand their customers and create products and services that work for them? This book has the answers.    </p>
<p>                    User experience research, also known as UX research, focuses on understanding user behaviours, needs and motivations through a range of observational techniques, task analysis and other methodologies. User Research is a practical guide that shows readers how to use the vast array of user research methods available. Written by one of the UK&#8217;s leading UX research professionals, readers can benefit from in-depth knowledge that explores the fundamentals of user research.    </p>
<p>                    Covering all the key research methods including face-to-face user testing, card sorting, surveys, A/B testing and many more, the book gives expert insight into the nuances, advantages and disadvantages of each, while also providing guidance on how to interpret, analyze and share the data once it has been obtained. Now in its second edition, User Research provides a new chapter on research operations and infrastructure as well as new material on combining user research methodologies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/">User Research : Improve Product and Service Design and Enhance Your UX Research &#8211; Stephanie Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;brilliant and provocative&#8221; (Walter Isaacson) guide shares nine principles to adapt and survive the technological changes shaping our future from the director of the MIT Media Lab and a veteran Wired journalist. The world is more complex and volatile today than at any other time in our history. The tools of our modern existence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/">Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;brilliant and provocative&#8221; (Walter Isaacson) guide shares nine principles to adapt and survive the technological changes shaping our future from the director of the MIT Media Lab and a veteran Wired journalist.  The world is more complex and volatile today than at any other time in our history. The tools of our modern existence are getting faster, cheaper, and smaller at an exponential rate, transforming every aspect of society, from business to culture and from the public sphere to our most private moments. The people who succeed will be the ones who learn to think differently.  In Whiplash, Joi Ito and Jeff Howe distill that logic into nine organizing principles for navigating and surviving this tumultuous period: Emergence over Authority Pull over Push Compasses over Maps Risk over Safety Disobedience over Compliance Practice over Theory Diversity over Ability Resilience over Strength Systems over Objects   Filled with incredible case studies and cutting-edge research and philosophies from the MIT Media Lab and beyond, Whiplash will help you adapt and succeed in this unpredictable world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/">Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
