<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Philosophy Of Science Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/philosophy-of-science/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/philosophy-of-science/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Philosophy Of Science Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/philosophy-of-science/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</title>
		<link>/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Enlightenment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP TEN SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Bristles with pure, crystalline intelligence, deep knowledge and human sympathy&#8217; Richard Dawkins Is modernity really failing? Or have we failed to appreciate progress and the ideals that make it possible? If you follow the headlines, the world in the 21st century appears to be sinking into chaos, hatred, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/">Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP TEN SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Bristles with pure, crystalline intelligence, deep knowledge and human sympathy&#8217; Richard Dawkins  </p>
<p>                    Is modernity really failing? Or have we failed to appreciate progress and the ideals that make it possible?</p>
<p>                    If  you follow the headlines, the world in the 21st century appears to be  sinking into chaos, hatred, and irrationality. Yet Steven Pinker shows  that this is an illusion &#8211; a symptom of historical amnesia and  statistical fallacies. If you follow the trendlines rather than the  headlines, you discover that our lives have become longer, healthier,  safer, happier, more peaceful, more stimulating and more prosperous &#8211;  not just in the West, but worldwide. Such progress is no accident: it&#8217;s  the gift of a coherent and inspiring value system that many of us  embrace without even realizing it. These are the values of the  Enlightenment: of reason, science, humanism and progress.</p>
<p>                    The  challenges we face today are formidable, including inequality, climate  change, Artificial Intelligence and nuclear weapons. But the way to deal  with them is not to sink into despair or try to lurch back to a  mythical idyllic past; it&#8217;s to treat them as problems we can solve, as  we have solved other problems in the past. In making the case for an  Enlightenment newly recharged for the 21st century, Pinker shows how we  can use our faculties of reason and sympathy to solve the problems that  inevitably come with being products of evolution in an indifferent  universe. We will never have a perfect world, but &#8211; defying the chorus  of fatalism and reaction &#8211; we can continue to make it a better one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/">Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</title>
		<link>/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ego]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate, and Enlightenment Now. Believe it or not, today we may be living in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates     </p>
<p>                    A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate,  and Enlightenment Now.    </p>
<p>                    Believe it or not, today we may be living in the most peaceful moment in our species&#8217; existence. In his gripping and controversial new work, New York Times bestselling author Steven Pinker shows that despite the ceaseless news about war, crime, and terrorism, violence has actually been in decline over long stretches of history. Exploding myths about humankind&#8217;s inherent violence and the curse of modernity, this ambitious book continues Pinker&#8217;s exploration of the essence of human nature, mixing psychology and history to provide a remarkable picture of an increasingly enlightened world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Science Delusion : Freeing the Spirit of Enquiry (NEW EDITION) &#8211; Rupert Sheldrake</title>
		<link>/the-science-delusion-freeing-the-spirit-of-enquiry-new-edition-rupert-sheldrake/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-science-delusion-freeing-the-spirit-of-enquiry-new-edition-rupert-sheldrake/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW EDITION The Science Delusion is the belief that science already understands the nature of reality. The fundamental questions are answered, leaving only the details to be filled in. In this book (published in the US as Science Set Free), Dr Rupert Sheldrake, one of the world&#8217;s most innovative scientists, shows that science is being [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-delusion-freeing-the-spirit-of-enquiry-new-edition-rupert-sheldrake/">The Science Delusion : Freeing the Spirit of Enquiry (NEW EDITION) &#8211; Rupert Sheldrake</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW EDITION</p>
<p>                    The Science Delusion is the belief that science already understands the nature of reality. The fundamental questions are answered, leaving only the details to be filled in. In this book (published in the US as Science Set Free), Dr Rupert Sheldrake, one of the world&#8217;s most innovative scientists, shows that science is being constricted by assumptions that have hardened into dogmas. The &#8216;scientific worldview&#8217; has become a belief system. All reality is material or physical. The world is a machine, made up of dead matter. Nature is purposeless. Consciousness is nothing but the physical activity of the brain. Free will is an illusion. God exists only as an idea in human minds, imprisoned within our skulls.</p>
<p>                    Sheldrake examines these dogmas scientifically, and shows persuasively that science would be better off without them: freer, more interesting, and more fun.</p>
<p>                    In The God Delusion Richard Dawkins used science to bash God, but here Rupert Sheldrake shows that Dawkins&#8217; understanding of what science can do is old-fashioned and itself a delusion. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rupert Sheldrake does science, humanity and the world at large a considerable favour.&#8217;<br />
                    The Independent</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Certainly we need to accept the limitations of much current dogma and keep our minds open as we reasonably can. Sheldrake may help us do so through this well-written, challenging and always interesting book.&#8217;<br />
                    Financial Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-delusion-freeing-the-spirit-of-enquiry-new-edition-rupert-sheldrake/">The Science Delusion : Freeing the Spirit of Enquiry (NEW EDITION) &#8211; Rupert Sheldrake</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</title>
		<link>/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Giving Up Smoking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Respiratory Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Funding & Policy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19. Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19.    </p>
<p>                    Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns and border closings causing widespread business closures, economic collapse, and massive unemployment; and an unprecedented curtailment of civil liberties and freedoms in the name of keeping people safe by locking them up in their homes.    </p>
<p>                    We are now living in a world that is increasingly ruled, not by our democratic systems and institutions, but by public health fiat, carried out by politicians who rule by instilling fear and panic.    </p>
<p>                    In The Truth About COVID-19, Dr. Mercola and Cummins reveal new and emerging evidence that:    </p>
<p>                    The SARS-CoV-2 virus was, indeed, lab-engineered and emerged from a negligently managed bioweapons lab in Wuhan, China<br />
                    The global pandemic was long anticipated by global elites who have used it to facilitate and hide the largest upward transfer of wealth in human history<br />
                    PCR testing, case counts, morbidity, and vaccine safety and efficacy data have been widely manipulated and misrepresented<br />
                    Obesity, diabetes, and heart disease are known to worsen COVID-19 outcomes, but the junk food industry continues to push its agenda at the expense of public health<br />
                    Safe, simple, and inexpensive treatment and prevention for COVID-19 have been censored and suppressed to create a clear path for vaccine acceptance<br />
                    Effectiveness of the vaccines has been wildly exaggerated and major safety questions have gone unanswered    </p>
<p>                    The good news in all of this is that we can take control of our health and that, together, we have the power to unite and fight back for our health, democracy, and freedom. The time is now for a global awakening. As Dr. Mercola and Cummins remind us, this is the fight of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reality Is Not What It Seems : The Journey to Quantum Gravity &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gravity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relativity Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theoretical & Mathematical Astronomy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The physicist transforming how we see the universe&#8217; (Financial Times) &#8216;An utter joy&#8217; (Adam Rutherford) &#8216;A hugely engaging book&#8230; Rovelli is a charming, thought-provoking tour guide&#8217; (Manjit Kumar Prospect) Do space and time truly exist? What is reality made of? Can we understand its deep texture? Scientist Carlo Rovelli has spent his whole life exploring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Reality Is Not What It Seems : The Journey to Quantum Gravity &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The physicist transforming how we see the universe&#8217; (Financial Times)    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An utter joy&#8217; (Adam Rutherford)    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A hugely engaging book&#8230; Rovelli is a charming, thought-provoking tour guide&#8217; (Manjit Kumar Prospect)    </p>
<p>                    Do space and time truly exist? What is reality made of? Can we understand its deep texture?<br />
                    Scientist Carlo Rovelli has spent his whole life exploring these questions and pushing the boundaries of what we know. In this mind-expanding book, he shows how our understanding of reality has changed throughout centuries, from Democritus to loop quantum gravity. Taking us on a wondrous journey, he invites us to imagine a whole new world where black holes are waiting to explode, spacetime is made up of grains, and infinity does not exist &#8212; a vast universe still largely undiscovered.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Reality Is Not What It Seems : The Journey to Quantum Gravity &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum & Theoretical Chemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Napoleon&#8217;s Buttons is the fascinating account of seventeen groups of molecules that have greatly influenced the course of history. These molecules provided the impetus for early exploration, and made possible the voyages of discovery that ensued. The molecules resulted in grand feats of engineering and spurred advances in medicine and law; they determined what we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/">Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Napoleon&#8217;s Buttons is the fascinating account of seventeen groups of molecules that have greatly influenced the course of history. These molecules provided the impetus for early exploration, and made possible the voyages of discovery that ensued. The molecules resulted in grand feats of engineering and spurred advances in medicine and law; they determined what we now eat, drink, and wear. A change as small as the position of an atom can lead to enormous alterations in the properties of a substance-which, in turn, can result in great historical shifts.     </p>
<p>                     With lively prose and an eye for colorful and unusual details, Le Couteur and Burreson offer a novel way to understand the shaping of civilization and the workings of our contemporary world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/">Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Why do human beings behave as they do? &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    Why do human beings behave as they do?     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm    </p>
<p>                     We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of our nature destined to win out over the other?    </p>
<p>                     Every act of human behaviour has multiple layers of causation, spiralling back seconds, minutes, hours, days, months, years, even centuries, right back to the dawn of time and the origins of our species.     </p>
<p>                     In the epic sweep of history, how does our biology affect the arc of war and peace, justice and persecution? How have our brains evolved alongside our cultures?    </p>
<p>                     This is the exhilarating story of human morality and the science underpinning the biggest question of all: what makes us human?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the best scientist-writers of our time&#8217; Oliver Sacks</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ignorance : How It Drives Science &#8211; Stuart Firestein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ignorance-how-it-drives-science-stuart-firestein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ignorance-how-it-drives-science-stuart-firestein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Knowledge is a big subject, says Stuart Firestein, but ignorance is a bigger one. And it is ignorance-not knowledge-that is the true engine of science. Most of us have a false impression of science as a surefire, deliberate, step-by-step method for finding things out and getting things done. In fact, says Firestein, more often than [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ignorance-how-it-drives-science-stuart-firestein-abridged/">Ignorance : How It Drives Science &#8211; Stuart Firestein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Knowledge is a big subject, says Stuart Firestein, but ignorance is a bigger one. And it is ignorance-not knowledge-that is the true engine of science.     </p>
<p>                        Most of us have a false impression of science as a surefire, deliberate, step-by-step method for finding things out and getting things done. In fact, says Firestein, more often than not, science is like looking for a black cat in a dark room, and there may not be a cat in the room. The process is more hit-or-miss than you might imagine, with much stumbling and groping after phantoms. But it is exactly this &#8220;not knowing,&#8221; this puzzling over thorny questions or inexplicable data, that gets<br />
                    researchers into the lab early and keeps them there late, the thing that propels them, the very driving force of science. Firestein shows how scientists use ignorance to program their work, to identify what should be done, what the next steps are, and where they should concentrate their energies. And<br />
                    he includes a catalog of how scientists use ignorance, consciously or unconsciously-a remarkable range of approaches that includes looking for connections to other research, revisiting apparently settled questions, using small questions to get at big ones, and tackling a problem simply out of curiosity. The book concludes with four case histories-in cognitive psychology, theoretical physics, astronomy, and neuroscience-that provide a feel for the nuts and bolts of ignorance, the day-to-day<br />
                    battle that goes on in scientific laboratories and in scientific minds with questions that range from the quotidian to the profound.     </p>
<p>                       Turning the conventional idea about science on its head, Ignorance opens a new window on the true nature of research. It is a must-read for anyone curious about science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ignorance-how-it-drives-science-stuart-firestein-abridged/">Ignorance : How It Drives Science &#8211; Stuart Firestein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Brian Cox, Mail on Sunday Books of the Year Where are we? Who are we? Do our beliefs, hopes and dreams hold any significance out there in the void? Can human purpose and meaning ever fit into a scientific worldview? Award-winning author Sean Carroll brings his extraordinary intellect to bear on the realms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Brian Cox, Mail on Sunday Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Where are we? Who are we? Do our beliefs, hopes and dreams hold any significance out there in the void? Can human purpose and meaning ever fit into a scientific worldview?    </p>
<p>                    Award-winning author Sean Carroll brings his extraordinary intellect to bear on the realms of knowledge, the laws of nature and the most profound questions about life, death and our place in it all.    </p>
<p>                    From Darwin and Einstein to the origins of life, consciousness and the universe itself, Carroll combines cosmos-sprawling science and profound thought in a quest to explain our world. Destined to sit alongside the works of our greatest thinkers, The Big Picture demonstrates that while our lives may be forever dwarfed by the immensity of the universe, they can be redeemed by our capacity to comprehend it and give it meaning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind. In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind.    </p>
<p>                    In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and how it evolved. With deft use of examples of humor and wordplay, Steven Pinker weaves our vast knowledge of language into a compelling story: language is a human instinct, wired into our brains by evolution. The Language Instinct received the William James Book Prize from the American Psychological Association and the Public Interest Award from the Linguistics Society of America. This edition includes an update on advances in the science of language since The Language Instinct was first published.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agnosticism & Atheism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eclectic & Esoteric Religions & Belief Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom ___ For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom<br />
                    ___    </p>
<p>                    For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and psychology.    </p>
<p>                     Throughout the book, Harris argues that there are important truths to be found in the experience of contemplatives such as Jesus, Buddha and other saints and sages of history-and, therefore, that there is more to understanding reality than science and secular culture generally allow.    </p>
<p>                    Waking Up is part seeker&#8217;s memoir and part exploration of the scientific underpinnings of spirituality. No other book marries contemplative wisdom and modern science in this way, and no author other than Sam Harris-a scientist, philosopher, and famous sceptic-could write it.<br />
                     ___    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A demanding, illusion-shattering book.&#8217; Kirkus Reviews<br />
                    &#8216;A pleasure to read.&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tao of Physics : An Exploration of the Parallels between Modern Physics and Eastern Mysticism &#8211; Fritjof Capra (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-tao-of-physics-an-exploration-of-the-parallels-between-modern-physics-and-eastern-mysticism-fritjof-capra-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mysticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tao-of-physics-an-exploration-of-the-parallels-between-modern-physics-and-eastern-mysticism-fritjof-capra-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A special edition of the &#8220;brilliant&#8221; best-selling classic on the paradoxes of modern physics and their relationship to concepts of Eastern mysticism (New York Magazine) The Tao of Physics brought the mystical implications of subatomic physics to popular consciousness for the very first time. Many books have been written in the ensuing years about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tao-of-physics-an-exploration-of-the-parallels-between-modern-physics-and-eastern-mysticism-fritjof-capra-abridged/">The Tao of Physics : An Exploration of the Parallels between Modern Physics and Eastern Mysticism &#8211; Fritjof Capra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A special edition of the &#8220;brilliant&#8221; best-selling classic on the paradoxes of modern physics and their relationship to concepts of Eastern mysticism (New York Magazine)    </p>
<p>                    The Tao of Physics brought the mystical implications of subatomic physics to popular consciousness for the very first time. Many books have been written in the ensuing years about the connections between quantum theory and the ideas of Buddhism, Hinduism, and Taoism, but Fritjof Capra&#8217;s text serves as the foundation on which the others have been built&#8211;and its wisdom has stood the test of time. Its publication in more than twenty-three languages stands as testimony to its universal applicability and its enduring significance.     </p>
<p>                    This special edition celebrates the thirty-fifth anniversary of this early Shambhala best seller that has gone on to become a true classic. It includes a fresh cover design and a new preface by the author reflecting on further discoveries and developments in the years since the book&#8217;s original publication.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Physicists do not need mysticism,&#8221; Dr. Capra says, &#8220;and mystics do not need physics, but humanity needs both.&#8221; It is a message of timeless importance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tao-of-physics-an-exploration-of-the-parallels-between-modern-physics-and-eastern-mysticism-fritjof-capra-abridged/">The Tao of Physics : An Exploration of the Parallels between Modern Physics and Eastern Mysticism &#8211; Fritjof Capra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A prescient warning of a future we now inhabit, where fake news stories and Internet conspiracy theories play to a disaffected American populace &#8220;A glorious book . . . A spirited defense of science . . . From the first page to the last, this book is a manifesto for clear thought.&#8221;&#8211;Los Angeles Times How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/">The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A prescient warning of a future we now inhabit, where fake news stories and Internet conspiracy theories play to a disaffected American populace     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A glorious book . . . A spirited defense of science . . . From the first page to the last, this book is a manifesto for clear thought.&#8221;&#8211;Los Angeles Times     </p>
<p>                     How can we make intelligent decisions about our increasingly technology-driven lives if we don&#8217;t understand the difference between the myths of pseudoscience and the testable hypotheses of science? Pulitzer Prize-winning author and distinguished astronomer Carl Sagan argues that scientific thinking is critical not only to the pursuit of truth but to the very well-being of our democratic institutions.     </p>
<p>                     Casting a wide net through history and culture, Sagan examines and authoritatively debunks such celebrated fallacies of the past as witchcraft, faith healing, demons, and UFOs. And yet, disturbingly, in today&#8217;s so-called information age, pseudoscience is burgeoning with stories of alien abduction, channeling past lives, and communal hallucinations commanding growing attention and respect. As Sagan demonstrates with lucid eloquence, the siren song of unreason is not just a cultural wrong turn but a dangerous plunge into darkness that threatens our most basic freedoms.     </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Demon-Haunted World     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Powerful . . . A stirring defense of informed rationality. . . Rich in surprising information and beautiful writing.&#8221;&#8211;The Washington Post Book World     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Compelling.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A clear vision of what good science means and why it makes a difference. . . . A testimonial to the power of science and a warning of the dangers of unrestrained credulity.&#8221;&#8211;The Sciences     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Passionate.&#8221;&#8211;San Francisco Examiner-Chronicle</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/">The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Optimism Bias : Why we&#8217;re wired to look on the bright side &#8211; Tali Sharot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-optimism-bias-why-were-wired-to-look-on-the-bright-side-tali-sharot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Methodology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-optimism-bias-why-were-wired-to-look-on-the-bright-side-tali-sharot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the British Psychological Society Book Award for Popular Psychology Psychologists have long been aware that most people tend to maintain an irrationally positive outlook on life. In fact, optimism may be crucial to our existence. Tali Sharot&#8217;s original cognitive research demonstrates in surprising ways the biological basis for optimism. In this fascinating exploration, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-optimism-bias-why-were-wired-to-look-on-the-bright-side-tali-sharot-abridged/">The Optimism Bias : Why we&#8217;re wired to look on the bright side &#8211; Tali Sharot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the British Psychological Society Book Award for Popular Psychology    </p>
<p>                    Psychologists have long been aware that most people tend to maintain an irrationally positive outlook on life. In fact, optimism may be crucial to our existence. Tali Sharot&#8217;s original cognitive research demonstrates in surprising ways the biological basis for optimism. In this fascinating exploration, she takes an in-depth, clarifying look at how the brain generates hope and what happens when it fails; how the brains of optimists and pessimists differ; why we are terrible at predicting what will make us happy; how anticipation and dread affect us; and how our optimistic illusions affect our financial, professional, and emotional decisions.    </p>
<p>                    With its cutting-edge science and its wide-ranging and accessible narrative, The Optimism Bias provides us with startling new insight into how the workings of the brain create our hopes and dreams.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-optimism-bias-why-were-wired-to-look-on-the-bright-side-tali-sharot-abridged/">The Optimism Bias : Why we&#8217;re wired to look on the bright side &#8211; Tali Sharot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The companion book to COURSERA(R)&#8217;s wildly popular massive open online course Learning How to Learn Whether you are a student struggling to fulfill a math or science requirement, or you are embarking on a career change that requires a new skill set, A Mind for Numbers offers the tools you need to get a better [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/">A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The companion book to COURSERA(R)&#8217;s wildly popular massive open online course Learning How to Learn     </p>
<p>                    Whether you are a student struggling to fulfill a math or science requirement, or you are embarking on a career change that requires a new skill set, A Mind for Numbers offers the tools you need to get a better grasp of that intimidating material. Engineering professor Barbara Oakley knows firsthand how it feels to struggle with math. She flunked her way through high school math and science courses, before enlisting in the army immediately after graduation. When she saw how her lack of mathematical and technical savvy severely limited her options&#8211;both to rise in the military and to explore other careers&#8211;she returned to school with a newfound determination to re-tool her brain to master the very subjects that had given her so much trouble throughout her entire life.     </p>
<p>                     In A Mind for Numbers, Dr. Oakley lets us in on the secrets to learning effectively&#8211;secrets that even dedicated and successful students wish they&#8217;d known earlier. Contrary to popular belief, math requires creative, as well as analytical, thinking. Most people think that there&#8217;s only one way to do a problem, when in actuality, there are often a number of different solutions&#8211;you just need the creativity to see them. For example, there are more than three hundred different known proofs of the Pythagorean Theorem. In short, studying a problem in a laser-focused way until you reach a solution is not an effective way to learn. Rather, it involves taking the time to step away from a problem and allow the more relaxed and creative part of the brain to take over. The learning strategies in this book apply not only to math and science, but to any subject in which we struggle. We all have what it takes to excel in areas that don&#8217;t seem to come naturally to us at first, and learning them does not have to be as painful as we might think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/">A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans. Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests? By studying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans.      </p>
<p>                    Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests?     </p>
<p>                    By studying social behaviors in animals, such as bonding, the herd instinct, the forming of trusting alliances, expressions of consolation, and conflict resolution, Frans de Waal demonstrates that animals-and humans-are preprogrammed to reach out. He has found that chimpanzees care for mates that are wounded by leopards, elephants offer reassuring rumbles to youngsters in distress, and dolphins support sick companions near the water&#8217;s surface to prevent them from drowning. From day one humans have innate sensitivities to faces, bodies, and voices; we&#8217;ve been designed to feel for one another.     </p>
<p>                    De Waal&#8217;s theory runs counter to the assumption that humans are inherently selfish, which can be seen in the fields of politics, law, and finance. But he cites the public&#8217;s outrage at the U.S. government&#8217;s lack of empathy in the wake of Hurricane Katrina as a significant shift in perspective-one that helped Barack Obama become elected and ushered in what perhaps could become an Age of Empathy. Through a better understanding of empathy&#8217;s survival value in evolution, de Waal suggests, we can work together toward a more just society based on a more generous and accurate view of human nature.     </p>
<p>                    Written in layman&#8217;s prose with a wealth of anecdotes, wry humor, and incisive intelligence, The Age of Empathy is essential reading for our embattled times.     </p>
<p>                    An important and timely message about the biological roots of human kindness.&#8211;Desmond Morris, author of The Naked Ape</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simply Complexity : A Clear Guide to Complexity Theory &#8211; Neil Johnson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/simply-complexity-a-clear-guide-to-complexity-theory-neil-johnson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chaos Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybernetics & Systems Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/simply-complexity-a-clear-guide-to-complexity-theory-neil-johnson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What do traffic jams, stock market crashes, and wars have in common? They are all explained using complexity, an unsolved puzzle that many researchers believe is the key to predicting &#8211; and ultimately solving-everything from terrorist attacks and pandemic viruses right down to rush hour traffic congestion. Complexity is considered by many to be the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simply-complexity-a-clear-guide-to-complexity-theory-neil-johnson-abridged/">Simply Complexity : A Clear Guide to Complexity Theory &#8211; Neil Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What do traffic jams, stock market crashes, and wars have in common? They are all explained using complexity, an unsolved puzzle that many researchers believe is the key to predicting &#8211; and ultimately solving-everything from terrorist attacks and pandemic viruses right down to rush hour traffic congestion.    </p>
<p>                    Complexity is considered by many to be the single most important scientific development since general relativity and it promises to make sense of no less than the very heart of the Universe. Using it, scientists can find order emerging from seemingly random interactions of all kinds, from something as simple as flipping coins through to more challenging problems such as the patterns in modern jazz, the growth of cancer tumours, and predicting shopping habits.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simply-complexity-a-clear-guide-to-complexity-theory-neil-johnson-abridged/">Simply Complexity : A Clear Guide to Complexity Theory &#8211; Neil Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Merchants of Doubt : How a Handful of Scientists Obscured the Truth on Issues from Tobacco Smoke to Global Warming &#8211; Erik M. Conway, Naomi Oreskes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. scientific community has long led the world in research on such areas as public health, environmental science, and issues affecting quality of life. Our scientists have produced landmark studies on the dangers of DDT, tobacco smoke, acid rain, and global warming. But at the same time, a small yet potent subset of this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/">Merchants of Doubt : How a Handful of Scientists Obscured the Truth on Issues from Tobacco Smoke to Global Warming &#8211; Erik M. Conway, Naomi Oreskes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. scientific community has long led the world in research on such areas as public health, environmental science, and issues affecting quality of life. Our scientists have produced landmark studies on the dangers of DDT, tobacco smoke, acid rain, and global warming. But at the same time, a small yet potent subset of this community leads the world in vehement denial of these dangers.    </p>
<p>                    Merchants of Doubt tells the story of how a loose-knit group of high-level scientists and scientific advisers, with deep connections in politics and industry, ran effective campaigns to mislead the public and deny well-established scientific knowledge over four decades. Remarkably, the same individuals surface repeatedly &#8211; some of the same figures who have claimed that the science of global warming is &#8220;not settled&#8221; denied the truth of studies linking smoking to lung cancer, coal smoke to acid rain, and CFCs to the ozone hole. &#8220;Doubt is our product,&#8221; wrote one tobacco executive. These &#8216;experts&#8217; supplied it.     </p>
<p>                    Naomi Oreskes and Erik M. Conway, historians of science, roll back the rug on this dark corner of the American scientific community, showing how ideology and corporate interests, aided by a too-compliant media, have skewed public understanding of some of the most pressing issues of our era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/">Merchants of Doubt : How a Handful of Scientists Obscured the Truth on Issues from Tobacco Smoke to Global Warming &#8211; Erik M. Conway, Naomi Oreskes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Information: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT    </p>
<p>                    We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need to be late.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master class &#8230; As a guide for perplexed Westerners, this book is very hard to beat &#8230; an honest, cohesive explanation for why the world is the way it is, without miracle cures or scapegoats&#8217; John Micklethwait, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; admirably honest &#8230; injects a badly needed dose of optimism into the modern debate&#8217; Gillian Tett, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;His main piece of advice for individuals, corporations, and countries is clear: Take a deep breath and adapt. This world isn&#8217;t going to wait for you&#8217; Fortune    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A humane and empathetic book&#8217; David Henkin, The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable. We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable.    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the time of Columbus, Copernicus, Gutenberg and others, redrew all maps of the world, liberated information and shifted Western civilization from the medieval to the early modern era. Such change came at a price: social division, political extremism, economic shocks, pandemics and other unintended consequences of human endeavour.    </p>
<p>                    Now is our second Renaissance. In the face of terrorism, Brexit, refugee crises and the global impact of a Trump presidency, we can flourish-if we heed the urgent lessons of history. Age of Discovery, revised and updated for this paperback edition, shows us how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The physiologist Benjamin Libet famously demonstrated that activity in the brain&#8217;s motor regions can be detected some 300 milliseconds before a person feels that he has decided to move. Another lab recently used fMRI data to show that some &#8220;conscious&#8221; decisions can be predicted up to 10 seconds before they enter awareness (long before the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/">Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The physiologist Benjamin Libet famously demonstrated that activity in the brain&#8217;s motor regions can be detected some 300 milliseconds before a person feels that he has decided to move. Another lab recently used fMRI data to show that some &#8220;conscious&#8221; decisions can be predicted up to 10 seconds before they enter awareness (long before the preparatory motor activity detected by Libet). Clearly, findings of this kind are difficult to reconcile with the sense that one is the conscious source of one&#8217;s actions.     </p>
<p>                    The question of free will is no mere curio of philosophy seminars. A belief in free will underwrites both the religious notion of &#8220;sin&#8221; and our enduring commitment to retributive justice. The Supreme Court has called free will a &#8220;universal and persistent&#8221; foundation for our system of law. Any scientific developments that threatened our notion of free will would seem to put the ethics of punishing people for their bad behaviour in question.In Free Will Harris debates these ideas and asks whether or not, given what brain science is telling us, we actually have free will?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/">Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The as If Principle : The Radically New Approach to Changing Your Life &#8211; Dr Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-as-if-principle-the-radically-new-approach-to-changing-your-life-dr-richard-wiseman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-as-if-principle-the-radically-new-approach-to-changing-your-life-dr-richard-wiseman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a bestselling author and the most-followed psychologist on Twitter, this &#8220;intriguing new slant to personal transformation&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews) shows you how to take control of your life in an instant. Victorian philosopher William James had a theory about emotion and behavior: It isn&#8217;t that our feelings guide our actions (feel happy and you will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-as-if-principle-the-radically-new-approach-to-changing-your-life-dr-richard-wiseman-abridged/">The as If Principle : The Radically New Approach to Changing Your Life &#8211; Dr Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a bestselling author and the most-followed psychologist on Twitter, this &#8220;intriguing new slant to personal transformation&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews) shows you how to take control of your life in an instant.  Victorian philosopher William James had a theory about emotion and behavior: It isn&#8217;t that our feelings guide our actions (feel happy and you will laugh). On the contrary, it is our actions that guide our emotions (laugh and you will feel happy). This led James to a remarkable conclusion: &#8220;If you want a quality, act as if you already have it.&#8221; Roused by James&#8217;s astonishing discovery, renowned psychologist and bestselling author Richard Wiseman confirms James&#8217;s principle and shows how the self-help genre has for too long put the cart before the horse in trying to help us take control of our lives. Bringing to the table a dazzling array of firsthand experiments, surprising histories, and psychological case studies, Wiseman illustrates in brilliant detail how we can apply this principle in our daily lives:  Smile to become measurably happier Wash your hands to drive away guilt Clench your fist to increase your willpower Eat with your nondominant hand to lose weight Nod while speaking to become more persuasive Act like a newlywed to rekindle your marriage  Lively, engaging, and truly mind-changing, The As If Principle is that rare gem that offers real, workable solutions for your day-to-day goals while helping you to instantly take control of your emotions. Whether it&#8217;s quitting a bad habit, persevering through a difficult task, or achieving your dream self, The As If Principle can help. Don&#8217;t just think about changing your life. Do it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-as-if-principle-the-radically-new-approach-to-changing-your-life-dr-richard-wiseman-abridged/">The as If Principle : The Radically New Approach to Changing Your Life &#8211; Dr Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Beginning of Infinity: Explanations that Transform The World : Explanations that Transform The World &#8211; David Deutsch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-beginning-of-infinity-explanations-that-transform-the-world-explanations-that-transform-the-world-david-deutsch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematical Foundations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematical Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-beginning-of-infinity-explanations-that-transform-the-world-explanations-that-transform-the-world-david-deutsch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In our search for truth, how far have we advanced? This uniquely human quest for good explanations has driven amazing improvements in everything from scientific understanding and technology to politics, moral values and human welfare. But will progress end, either in catastrophe or completion &#8211; or will it continue indefinitely? In this profound and seminal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-beginning-of-infinity-explanations-that-transform-the-world-explanations-that-transform-the-world-david-deutsch-abridged/">The Beginning of Infinity: Explanations that Transform The World : Explanations that Transform The World &#8211; David Deutsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In our search for truth, how far have we advanced? This uniquely human quest for good explanations has driven amazing improvements in everything from scientific understanding and technology to politics, moral values and human welfare. But will progress end, either in catastrophe or completion &#8211; or will it continue indefinitely? In this profound and seminal book, David Deutsch explores the furthest reaches of our current understanding, taking in the Infinity Hotel, supernovae and the nature of optimism, to instill in all of us a wonder at what we have achieved &#8211; and the fact that this is only the beginning of humanity&#8217;s infinite possibility.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-beginning-of-infinity-explanations-that-transform-the-world-explanations-that-transform-the-world-david-deutsch-abridged/">The Beginning of Infinity: Explanations that Transform The World : Explanations that Transform The World &#8211; David Deutsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Master Algorithm : How the Quest for the Ultimate Learning Machine Will Remake Our World &#8211; Pedro Domingos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pedro Domingos demystifies machine learning and shows how wondrous and exciting the future will be&#8217; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs Society is changing, one learning algorithm at a time, from search engines to online dating, personalized medicine to predicting the stock market. But learning algorithms are not just about Big Data &#8211; these algorithms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/">The Master Algorithm : How the Quest for the Ultimate Learning Machine Will Remake Our World &#8211; Pedro Domingos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pedro Domingos demystifies machine learning and shows how wondrous and exciting the future will be&#8217; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs    </p>
<p>                    Society is changing, one learning algorithm at a time, from search engines to online dating, personalized medicine to predicting the stock market. But learning algorithms are not just about Big Data &#8211; these algorithms take raw data and make it useful by creating more algorithms. This is something new under the sun: a technology that builds itself. In The Master Algorithm, Pedro Domingos reveals how machine learning is remaking business, politics, science and war. And he takes us on an awe-inspiring quest to find &#8216;The Master Algorithm&#8217; &#8211; a universal learner capable of deriving all knowledge from data.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/">The Master Algorithm : How the Quest for the Ultimate Learning Machine Will Remake Our World &#8211; Pedro Domingos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control  chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Create a Mind : The Secret of Human Thought Revealed &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the best person I know at predicting the future of artificial intelligence.&#8217; Bill Gates In How to Create a Mind, Ray Kurzweil offers a provocative exploration of the most important project in human-machine civilisation: reverse engineering the brain to understand precisely how it works and using that knowledge to create even more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">How to Create a Mind : The Secret of Human Thought Revealed &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the best person I know at predicting the future of artificial intelligence.&#8217; Bill Gates    </p>
<p>                    In How to Create a Mind, Ray Kurzweil offers a provocative exploration of the most important project in human-machine civilisation: reverse engineering the brain to understand precisely how it works and using that knowledge to create even more intelligent machines. Kurzweil explores how the brain functions, how the mind emerges from the brain, and the implications of vastly increasing the powers of our intelligence in addressing the world&#8217;s problems. He thoughtfully examines emotional and moral intelligence and the origins of consciousness and envisions the radical &#8211; arguably inevitable &#8211; future of our merging with the intelligent technology we are creating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">How to Create a Mind : The Secret of Human Thought Revealed &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger : Heretics, Activists, and One Scholar&#8217;s Search for Justice &#8211; Alice Dreger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues & Debates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Smart, delightful . . . a splendidly entertaining education in ethics, activism, and science.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review (Editor&#8217;s Choice) An impassioned defense of intellectual freedom and a clarion call to intellectual responsibility, Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger is one American&#8217;s eye-opening story of life in the trenches of scientific controversy. For two decades, historian [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/">Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger : Heretics, Activists, and One Scholar&#8217;s Search for Justice &#8211; Alice Dreger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Smart, delightful . . . a splendidly entertaining education in ethics, activism, and science.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review (Editor&#8217;s Choice)    </p>
<p>                     An impassioned defense of intellectual freedom and a clarion call to intellectual responsibility, Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger is one American&#8217;s eye-opening story of life in the trenches of scientific controversy. For two decades, historian Alice Dreger has led a life of extraordinary engagement, combining activist service to victims of unethical medical research with defense of scientists whose work has outraged identity politics activists. With spirit and wit, Dreger offers in Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger an unforgettable vision of the importance of rigorous truth seeking in today&#8217;s America, where both the free press and free scholarly inquiry struggle under dire economic and political threats.    </p>
<p>                     This illuminating chronicle begins with Dreger&#8217;s own research into the treatment of people born intersex (once called hermaphrodites). Realization of the shocking surgical and ethical abuses conducted in the name of &#8220;normalizing&#8221; intersex children&#8217;s gender identities moved Dreger to become an internationally recognized patient rights activist. But even as the intersex rights movement succeeded, Dreger began to realize how some fellow progressive activists were employing lies and personal attacks to silence scientists whose data revealed uncomfortable truths about humans. In researching one such case, Dreger suddenly became the target of just these kinds of attacks.    </p>
<p>                     Troubled, she decided to try to understand more-to travel the country to ferret out the truth behind various controversies, to obtain a global view of the nature and costs of these battles. Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger describes Dreger&#8217;s long and harrowing journeys between the two camps for which she felt equal empathy: social justice activists determined to win and researchers determined to put hard truths before comfort. Ultimately what emerges is a lesson about the intertwining of justice and of truth-and a lesson of the importance of responsible scholars and journalists to our fragile democracy.    </p>
<p>                     Praise for Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger:<br />
                     &#8220;An engrossing volume that is sure to undo any lingering notions that academic debate is the province of empiricists who pledge allegiance to the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth . . . Dreger&#8217;s clear and well-paced prose makes for compelling . . . reading.&#8221; -The Chicago Tribune</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/">Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger : Heretics, Activists, and One Scholar&#8217;s Search for Justice &#8211; Alice Dreger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
