<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Nationalism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/nationalism/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/nationalism/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Nationalism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/nationalism/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Imagined Communities : Reflections on the Origin and Spread of Nationalism &#8211; Benedict Anderson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nationalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What are the imagined communities that compel men to kill or to die for an idea of a nation? This notion of nationhood had its origins in the founding of the Americas, but was then adopted and transformed by populist movements in nineteenth-century Europe. It became the rallying cry for anti-Imperialism as well as the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/">Imagined Communities : Reflections on the Origin and Spread of Nationalism &#8211; Benedict Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are the imagined communities that compel men to kill or to die for an idea of a nation? This notion of nationhood had its origins in the founding of the Americas, but was then adopted and transformed by populist movements in nineteenth-century Europe. It became the rallying cry for anti-Imperialism as well as the abiding explanation for colonialism. In this scintillating, groundbreaking work of intellectual history Anderson explores how ideas are formed and reformulated at every level, from high politics to popular culture, and the way that they can make people do extraordinary things. In the twenty-first century, these debates on the nature of the nation state are even more urgent. As new nations rise, vying for influence, and old empires decline, we must understand who we are as a community in the face of history, and change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/">Imagined Communities : Reflections on the Origin and Spread of Nationalism &#8211; Benedict Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who Built That : Awe-Inspiring Stories of American Tinkerpreneurs &#8211; Michelle Malkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-built-that-awe-inspiring-stories-of-american-tinkerpreneurs-michelle-malkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nationalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-built-that-awe-inspiring-stories-of-american-tinkerpreneurs-michelle-malkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Firebrand conservative columnist, commentator, Internet entrepreneur, and #1 New York Times bestselling author Michelle Malkin tells the fascinating, little-known stories of the inventors who have contributed to American exceptionalism and technological progress. Call them America&#8217;s &#8220;tinkerpreneurs&#8221;&#8211;unsung innovators who commercialized their &#8220;little&#8221; ideas to create products, companies, wealth, and opportunities that thrive today. Tireless, self-made, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-built-that-awe-inspiring-stories-of-american-tinkerpreneurs-michelle-malkin-abridged/">Who Built That : Awe-Inspiring Stories of American Tinkerpreneurs &#8211; Michelle Malkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Firebrand conservative columnist, commentator, Internet entrepreneur, and #1 New York Times bestselling author Michelle Malkin tells the fascinating, little-known stories of the inventors who have contributed to American exceptionalism and technological progress.     </p>
<p>                    Call them America&#8217;s &#8220;tinkerpreneurs&#8221;&#8211;unsung innovators who commercialized their &#8220;little&#8221; ideas to create products, companies, wealth, and opportunities that thrive today. Tireless, self-made, and largely self-taught, they raised our standard of living with the creation of items we daily take for granted, from razors to bottle caps, flashlights to bridge cables.     </p>
<p>                    This entertaining and enlightening treasury is, in part, Michelle Malkin&#8217;s response to President Obama&#8217;s infamous assertion that &#8220;if you&#8217;ve got a business, you didn&#8217;t build that.&#8221; She examines how factors such as profit motive, intellectual property rights, patriotism, faith, family, and an unwavering belief in American exceptionalism set the stage for the creation of toilet paper, glass bottles, the hydroelectric power plant, and more.     </p>
<p>                    Demonized by the left as greedy villains and selfish barons, these visionaries have nurtured job-creating powerhouses used today by &#8220;progressive&#8221; propagandists who can&#8217;t comprehend how much comfort and convenience they enjoy as a result of the ingenious contributions by these original American dreamers. Are they rich? You bet. They earned their private rewards for the public good. Find out Who Built That&#8211;and the next time you turn on your air conditioner, say thank you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-built-that-awe-inspiring-stories-of-american-tinkerpreneurs-michelle-malkin-abridged/">Who Built That : Awe-Inspiring Stories of American Tinkerpreneurs &#8211; Michelle Malkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nationalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism. Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections. In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism.    </p>
<p>                    Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections.    </p>
<p>                    In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist and commentator Rick Wilson delivers &#8220;a searingly honest, bitingly funny, comprehensive answer to the question we find ourselves asking most mornings: &#8216;What the hell is going on?&#8217; (Chicago Tribune). The Guardian hails Everything Trump Touches Dies, saying it gives, &#8220;more unvarnished truths about Donald Trump than anyone else in the American political establishment has offered. Wilson never holds back.&#8221; Rick mercilessly exposes the damage Trump has done to the country, to the Republican Party, and to the conservative movement that has abandoned its principles for the worst President in American history.    </p>
<p>                    Wilson unblinkingly dismantles Trump&#8217;s deceptions and the illusions to which his supporters cling, shedding light on the guilty parties who empower and enable Trump in Washington and in the media. He calls out the race-war dead-enders who hitched a ride with Trump, the alt-right basement dwellers who worship him, and the social conservatives who looked the other way. Publishers Weekly calls it, &#8220;a scathing, profane, unflinching, and laugh-out-loud funny rebuke of Donald Trump and his presidency.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    No left-winger, Wilson is a lifelong conservative who delivers his withering critique of Trump from the right. A leader of the Never Trump movement, he warned from the start that Trump would destroy the lives and reputations of everyone in his orbit, and Everything Trump Touches Dies is a deft chronicle the tragicomic political story of our time. From the early campaign days through the shock of election night, to the inconceivable train-wreck of Trump&#8217;s first year. Rick Wilson provides not only an insightful analysis of the Trump administration, but also an optimistic path forward for the GOP, the conservative movement, and the country.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hilarious, smartly written, and usually spot-on&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews), Everything Trump Touches Dies is perfect for those on either side of the aisle who need a dose of unvarnished reality, a good laugh, a strong cocktail, and a return to sanity in American politics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
