<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Project Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/project-management/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/project-management/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Project Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/project-management/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Team Genius : The New Science of High-Performing Organizations &#8211; Rich Karlgaard, Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/team-genius-the-new-science-of-high-performing-organizations-rich-karlgaard-michael-s-malone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/team-genius-the-new-science-of-high-performing-organizations-rich-karlgaard-michael-s-malone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking book that sheds new light on the vital importance of teams as the fundamental unit of organization and competition in the global economy. Teams-we depend on them for both our professional success and our personal happiness. But isn&#8217;t it odd how little scrutiny we give them? The teams that make up our lives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-genius-the-new-science-of-high-performing-organizations-rich-karlgaard-michael-s-malone-abridged/">Team Genius : The New Science of High-Performing Organizations &#8211; Rich Karlgaard, Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking book that sheds new light on the vital importance of teams as the fundamental unit of organization and competition in the global economy.  Teams-we depend on them for both our professional success and our personal happiness. But isn&#8217;t it odd how little scrutiny we give them? The teams that make up our lives are created mostly by luck, happenstance, or circumstance-but rarely by design. In trivial matters-say, a bowling team, the leadership of a neighborhood group, or a holiday party committee-success by serendipity is already risky enough. But when it comes to actions by fast-moving start-ups, major corporations, nonprofit institutions, and governments, leaving things to chance can be downright dangerous.  Offering vivid reports of the latest scientific research, compelling case studies, and great storytelling, Team Genius shows managers and executives that the planning, design, and management of great teams no longer have to be a black art. It explores solutions to essential questions that could spell the difference between success and obsolescence. Do you know how to reorganize your subpar teams to turn them into top performers?<br />
                    Can you identify which of the top-performing teams in your company are reaching the end of their life span? Do you have the courage to shut them down? Do you know how to create a replacement team that will be just as effective-without losing time or damaging morale? And, most important, are your teams the right size for the job?  Throughout, Rich Karlgaard and Michael S. Malone share insights and real-life examples gleaned from their careers as journalists, analysts, investors, and globetrotting entrepreneurs, meeting successful teams and team leaders to reveal some &#8220;new truths&#8221;:  *  The right team size is usually one fewer person than what managers think they need. *  The greatest question facing good teams is not how to succeed, but how to die. *  Good &#8220;chemistry&#8221; often makes for the least effective teams. *  Cognitive diversity yields the highest performance gains-but only if you understand what it is. *  How to find the &#8220;bliss point&#8221; in team intimacy-and become three times more productive. *  How to identify destructive team members before they do harm. *  Why small teams are 40 percent more likely to create a successful breakthrough than a solo genius is.<br />
                    *  Why groups of 7 (+- 2), 150, and 1,500 are magic sizes for teams. Eye-opening, grounded, and essential, Team Genius is the next big idea to revolutionize business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-genius-the-new-science-of-high-performing-organizations-rich-karlgaard-michael-s-malone-abridged/">Team Genius : The New Science of High-Performing Organizations &#8211; Rich Karlgaard, Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FIRE : How Fast, Inexpensive, Restrained, and Elegant Methods Ignite Innovation &#8211; Dan Ward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Noted military technology expert Dan Ward&#8217;s manifesto for creating great products and projects using the methods of rapid innovation. Why do some programs deliver their product under cost, while others bust their budget? Why do some deliver ahead of schedule, while others experience endless delays? Which products work better-the quick and thrifty or the slow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/">FIRE : How Fast, Inexpensive, Restrained, and Elegant Methods Ignite Innovation &#8211; Dan Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Noted military technology expert Dan Ward&#8217;s manifesto for creating great products and projects using the methods of rapid innovation.  Why do some programs deliver their product under cost, while others bust their budget? Why do some deliver ahead of schedule, while others experience endless delays? Which products work better-the quick and thrifty or the slow and expensive? Which situation leads to superior equipment?  With nearly two decades as an engineering officer in the U. S. Air Force, Dan Ward explored these questions during tours of duty at military research laboratories, the Air Force Institute of Technology, an intelligence agency, the Pentagon and Afghanistan. The pattern he noticed revealed that the most successful project leaders in both the public and private sectors delivered top-shelf products with a skeleton crew, a shoestring budget, and a cannonball schedule. Excessive investment of time, money, or complexity actually reduced innovation. He concluded the secret to innovation is to be fast, inexpensive, simple, and small.  FIRE presents an entertaining and practical framework for pursuing rapid, frugal innovation.<br />
                    A story-filled blend of pop culture and engineering insight, FIRE has something for everyone: strategic concepts leaders can use as they cast a vision, actionable principles for managers as they make business decisions, and practical tools for workers as they design, build, assess and test new products.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/">FIRE : How Fast, Inexpensive, Restrained, and Elegant Methods Ignite Innovation &#8211; Dan Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emotional Intelligence for Project Managers : The People Skills You Need to Achieve Outstanding Results &#8211; Anthony Mersino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/emotional-intelligence-for-project-managers-the-people-skills-you-need-to-achieve-outstanding-results-anthony-mersino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/emotional-intelligence-for-project-managers-the-people-skills-you-need-to-achieve-outstanding-results-anthony-mersino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As if the project manager&#8217;s job was not hard enough&#8211;having to be not a jack of all trades but a master of them!&#8211;all the technical expertise he has learned can be completely nullified if he doesn&#8217;t have good people skills to navigate appropriately through all the obstacles each project is certain to bring. As recent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-intelligence-for-project-managers-the-people-skills-you-need-to-achieve-outstanding-results-anthony-mersino-abridged/">Emotional Intelligence for Project Managers : The People Skills You Need to Achieve Outstanding Results &#8211; Anthony Mersino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As if the project manager&#8217;s job was not hard enough&#8211;having to be not a jack of all trades but a master of them!&#8211;all the technical expertise he has learned can be completely nullified if he doesn&#8217;t have good people skills to navigate appropriately through all the obstacles each project is certain to bring. As recent research has indicated that emotional intelligence (EI) now accounts for an astonishing 70 to 80 percent of management success, there is no doubt that today&#8217;s successful project manager needs strong interpersonal skills and the ability to recognize emotional cues in order to lead their teams to success&#8211;the technical expertise the position depended on so greatly in the past simply isn&#8217;t enough anymore!Emotional Intelligence for Project Managers introduces readers to all facets of EI and shows how emotions can be leveraged to meet project goals. Project managers strong in technical skills but needing help in the EI department will learn how to: * Set the tone and direction for the project * Communicate effectively * Motivate, inspire, and engage their team * Encourage flexibility and collaboration * Deal productively with stress, criticism, and change * Establish the kind of high morale that attracts top performers * And moreNow in its second edition, this unique and invaluable resource for project managers in every industry includes several expanded sections on self-awareness and self-management, as well as a new chapter on using EI to lead Agile Teams and a close look at Servant Leadership. You&#8217;ve spent years gathering the technical intelligence you need for this challenging career&#8211;now separate yourself from the pack by increasing your emotional intelligence!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-intelligence-for-project-managers-the-people-skills-you-need-to-achieve-outstanding-results-anthony-mersino-abridged/">Emotional Intelligence for Project Managers : The People Skills You Need to Achieve Outstanding Results &#8211; Anthony Mersino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Third Wave : An Entrepreneur&#8217;s Vision of the Future &#8211; Steve Case (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-wave-an-entrepreneurs-vision-of-the-future-steve-case-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-wave-an-entrepreneurs-vision-of-the-future-steve-case-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Case&#8217;s career began when he cofounded America Online (AOL) in 1985. At the time, only three percent of Americans were online. It took a decade for AOL to achieve mainstream success. AOL became the top performing company of the 1990s, and at its peak more than half of all consumer Internet traffic in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-wave-an-entrepreneurs-vision-of-the-future-steve-case-abridged/">The Third Wave : An Entrepreneur&#8217;s Vision of the Future &#8211; Steve Case (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steve Case&#8217;s career began when he cofounded America Online (AOL) in 1985. At the time, only three percent of Americans were online. It took a decade for AOL to achieve mainstream success. AOL became the top performing company of the 1990s, and at its peak more than half of all consumer Internet traffic in the United States ran through the service. After Case engineered AOL&#8217;s merger with Time Warner and he became Chairman of the combined business, Case oversaw the biggest media and communications empire in the world.<br />
                         In The Third Wave, which pays homage to the work of the futurist Alvin Toffler, Case takes us behind the scenes of some of the most consequential and riveting business decisions of our time while offering illuminating insights from decades of working as an entrepreneur, an investor, a philanthropist, and an advocate for sensible bipartisan policies.<br />
                         We are entering, as Case explains, a new paradigm called the &#8220;Third Wave&#8221; of the Internet. The first wave saw AOL and other companies lay the foundation for consumers to connect to the Internet. The second wave saw companies like Google and Facebook build on top of the Internet to create search and social networking capabilities, while apps like Snapchat and Instagram leverage the smartphone revolution. Now, Case argues, we&#8217;re entering the Third Wave: a period in which entrepreneurs will vastly transform major &#8220;real world&#8221; sectors like health, education, transportation, energy, and food-and in the process change the way we live our daily lives.<br />
                         The Third Wave is part memoir, part manifesto, and part playbook for the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-wave-an-entrepreneurs-vision-of-the-future-steve-case-abridged/">The Third Wave : An Entrepreneur&#8217;s Vision of the Future &#8211; Steve Case (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good Strategy/Bad Strategy : The difference and why it matters &#8211; Richard Rumelt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-strategy-bad-strategy-the-difference-and-why-it-matters-richard-rumelt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-strategy-bad-strategy-the-difference-and-why-it-matters-richard-rumelt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Richard Rumelt&#8217;s Good Strategy/Bad Strategy was published in 2011, it immediately struck a chord, calling out as bad strategy the mish-mash of pop culture, motivational slogans and business buzz speak so often and misleadingly masquerading as the real thing. Since then, his original and pragmatic ideas have won fans around the world and continue [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-strategy-bad-strategy-the-difference-and-why-it-matters-richard-rumelt-abridged/">Good Strategy/Bad Strategy : The difference and why it matters &#8211; Richard Rumelt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Richard Rumelt&#8217;s Good Strategy/Bad Strategy was published in 2011, it immediately struck a chord, calling out as bad strategy the mish-mash of pop culture, motivational slogans and business buzz speak so often and misleadingly masquerading as the real thing.    </p>
<p>                    Since then, his original and pragmatic ideas have won fans around the world and continue to help readers to recognise and avoid the elements of bad strategy and adopt good, action-oriented strategies that honestly acknowledge the challenges being faced and offer straightforward approaches to overcoming them. Strategy should not be equated with ambition, leadership, vision or planning; rather, it is coherent action backed by an argument.    </p>
<p>                    For Rumelt, the heart of good strategy is insight into the hidden power in any situation, and into an appropriate response &#8211; whether launching a new product, fighting a war or putting a man on the moon. Drawing on examples of the good and the bad from across all sectors and all ages, he shows how this insight can be cultivated with a wide variety of tools that lead to better thinking and better strategy, strategy that cuts through the hype and gets results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-strategy-bad-strategy-the-difference-and-why-it-matters-richard-rumelt-abridged/">Good Strategy/Bad Strategy : The difference and why it matters &#8211; Richard Rumelt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Eight Essential People Skills for Project Management : Solving the Most Common People Problems for Team Leaders &#8211; Zachary Wong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-eight-essential-people-skills-for-project-management-solving-the-most-common-people-problems-for-team-leaders-zachary-wong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-eight-essential-people-skills-for-project-management-solving-the-most-common-people-problems-for-team-leaders-zachary-wong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Veteran project manager and University of California professor Zachary Wong identifies the eight most common people problems in managing projects and offers a flexible, customizable approach to solving them, based on a lifetime of research. Zachary Wong offers practical strategies, skills, and tools to help project managers diagnose and solve their toughest people problems. Based [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-eight-essential-people-skills-for-project-management-solving-the-most-common-people-problems-for-team-leaders-zachary-wong-abridged/">The Eight Essential People Skills for Project Management : Solving the Most Common People Problems for Team Leaders &#8211; Zachary Wong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Veteran project manager and University of California professor Zachary Wong identifies the eight most common people problems in managing projects and offers a flexible, customizable approach to solving them, based on a lifetime of research. Zachary Wong offers practical strategies, skills, and tools to help project managers diagnose and solve their toughest people problems. Based on decades in the trenches, the book shows how to confront and correct bad behavior, increase team performance and inclusion, turn around difficult people and poor performers, get people to do what you want them to do, boost employee motivation and attitude, reduce change resistance and risk aversion, and manage difficult bosses. Wong believes that the best team leaders are problem-solvers and facilitators, so this book provides problem-solving models and tools to diagnose people problems, and facilitative methods, processes, and techniques to correct them. It&#8217;s an approach that can be personalized to fit any person or situation. Each skill is explained with a well-balanced mix of case stories, examples, strategies, processes, tools, and techniques along with illustrations, graphics, tables, and other visuals to clarify key concepts and their workplace application. To reinforce the most important learnings, Wong includes a Memory Card and Skill Summary at the end of each chapter. Nothing is harder than leading people and managing project teams. Being successful takes a combination of knowing human psychology, organizational behaviors, and human factors; having supervisory, process, and communication skills; ensuring good teamwork, high integrity, and strong leadership; and having the ability to integrate and apply these skills to a diverse work team. The Eight Essential People Skills for Project Management is designed for individuals, team leaders, and managers who oversee and coordinate the daily performance of others and who are seeking solutions that they can apply immediately.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-eight-essential-people-skills-for-project-management-solving-the-most-common-people-problems-for-team-leaders-zachary-wong-abridged/">The Eight Essential People Skills for Project Management : Solving the Most Common People Problems for Team Leaders &#8211; Zachary Wong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myth of Multitasking &#8211; Dave Crenshaw (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-myth-of-multitasking-dave-crenshaw-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myth-of-multitasking-dave-crenshaw-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Multitasking Doesn&#8217;t Work-Learn What Does! &#8220;&#8230;multitasking is, in fact, a lie that actually wastes time, energy, and money. Most of all, it robs us of life and our relationships with others.&#8221; -Chuck Norris, world-renowned actor and martial artist Through anecdotal and real-world examples, The Myth of Multitasking proves that multitasking hurts your focus and productivity. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-of-multitasking-dave-crenshaw-abridged/">The Myth of Multitasking &#8211; Dave Crenshaw (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Multitasking Doesn&#8217;t Work-Learn What Does!<br />
                    &#8220;&#8230;multitasking is, in fact, a lie that actually wastes time, energy, and money. Most of all, it robs us of life and our relationships with others.&#8221; -Chuck Norris, world-renowned actor and martial artist     </p>
<p>                    Through anecdotal and real-world examples, The Myth of Multitasking proves that multitasking hurts your focus and productivity. Instead, learn how to be more effective by doing one thing at a time.    </p>
<p>                    Productivity and effective time management end with multitasking. The false idea that multitasking is productive has become even more prevalent and damaging to our productivity and well-being since the first edition of The Myth of Multitasking was published in 2008. In this revised and updated second edition, author and productivity expert Dave Crenshaw provides a solution for the chaos of distraction that multitasking creates-and a way to combat the temptation to constantly switch between tasks.    </p>
<p>                    Learn how to actually get things done. Dave Crenshaw takes the idea of multitasking as a productivity tool and smashes it to smithereens. But rather than leaving you with the burden of wading through the wreckage all by yourself, he shows you how to focus, move forward, and free up more time for what you value the most.    </p>
<p>                    In this new edition of The Myth of Multitasking, discover:    </p>
<p>                    Updated research on how and why multitasking doesn&#8217;t work<br />
                    Worksheets to help you figure out how to manage your day effectively<br />
                    Easy, actionable steps to manage your life well and accomplish your dreams and goals    </p>
<p>                    Readers of self-improvement books and time management books like Indistractable, Free to Focus, or It Doesn&#8217;t Have to Be Crazy at Work will love increasing productivity and personal success with The Myth of Multitasking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-of-multitasking-dave-crenshaw-abridged/">The Myth of Multitasking &#8211; Dave Crenshaw (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Effective HR Communication : A Framework for Communicating HR Programmes with Impact &#8211; Debra Corey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/effective-hr-communication-a-framework-for-communicating-hr-programmes-with-impact-debra-corey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/effective-hr-communication-a-framework-for-communicating-hr-programmes-with-impact-debra-corey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s competitive environment where we are doing everything we can to compete for talent, effective communication ensures we are showcasing our HR programmes in a way which will help us attract, retain and engage talent. Effective HR Communication is a practical guide to develop and deliver effective communication campaigns, ensuring that teams have the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/effective-hr-communication-a-framework-for-communicating-hr-programmes-with-impact-debra-corey-abridged/">Effective HR Communication : A Framework for Communicating HR Programmes with Impact &#8211; Debra Corey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s competitive environment where we are doing everything we can to compete for talent, effective communication ensures we are showcasing our HR programmes in a way which will help us attract, retain and engage talent. Effective HR Communication is a practical guide to develop and deliver effective communication campaigns, ensuring that teams have the knowledge, skills and tools to achieve the desired objectives.     </p>
<p>                    Whether introducing new HR programmes or re-launching existing ones, communications help us deliver the key messages so that employees understand, appreciate and action them to meet our HR and business objectives.     </p>
<p>                    Effective HR Communication introduces a six-step &#8216;IMPACT&#8217; model to explain and demonstrate the critical steps to be followed when developing a communications campaign.  This includes steps such as understanding the communication needs and requirements of employees, developing the most robust objectives, selecting and developing the appropriate medium, planning a campaign in an effective manner, leveraging the support of business partners, developing effective communications content, and measuring the success of the campaign.      </p>
<p>                    Using a combination of theory, examples, tips and tools from leading experts, this book provides practical information which can easily be used to create effective and impactful communications.  Case studies from leading organizations such as BT, LV=, Merlin Entertainments and Reward Gateway are included to further illustrate how communication has been done effectively.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/effective-hr-communication-a-framework-for-communicating-hr-programmes-with-impact-debra-corey-abridged/">Effective HR Communication : A Framework for Communicating HR Programmes with Impact &#8211; Debra Corey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
