<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Higher &amp; Further Education, Tertiary Education Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/higher-further-education-tertiary-education/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/higher-further-education-tertiary-education/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Higher &amp; Further Education, Tertiary Education Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/higher-further-education-tertiary-education/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>U Thrive : How to Succeed in College (and Life) &#8211; Daniel Lerner, Alan Daniel Schlechter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/u-thrive-how-to-succeed-in-college-and-life-daniel-lerner-alan-daniel-schlechter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Students & Student Organisations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/u-thrive-how-to-succeed-in-college-and-life-daniel-lerner-alan-daniel-schlechter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every year, almost 4,000,000 students begin their freshman year at colleges and universities nationwide. Most of them will sleep less and stress out a whole lot more. By the end of the year, 30% of those freshmen will have dropped out. For many, the unforeseen demands of college life are so overwhelming that &#8220;the best [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-thrive-how-to-succeed-in-college-and-life-daniel-lerner-alan-daniel-schlechter-abridged/">U Thrive : How to Succeed in College (and Life) &#8211; Daniel Lerner, Alan Daniel Schlechter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every year, almost 4,000,000 students begin their freshman year at colleges and universities nationwide. Most of them will sleep less and stress out a whole lot more. By the end of the year, 30% of those freshmen will have dropped out. For many, the unforeseen demands of college life are so overwhelming that &#8220;the best four years of your life&#8221; can start to feel like the worst.    </p>
<p>                    Enter Daniel Lerner and Dr. Alan Schlechter, ready to teach students how to not only survive college, but flourish in it. Filled with fascinating science, real-life stories, and tips for building positive lifelong habits, U Thrive addresses the opportunities and challenges every undergrad will face-from finding a passion to dealing with nightmarish roommates and surviving finals week. Engaging and hilarious, U Thrive will help students grow into the happy, successful alums they all deserve to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-thrive-how-to-succeed-in-college-and-life-daniel-lerner-alan-daniel-schlechter-abridged/">U Thrive : How to Succeed in College (and Life) &#8211; Daniel Lerner, Alan Daniel Schlechter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Redesigning Leadership &#8211; John Maeda, Contributions by Rebecca J Bermont (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/redesigning-leadership-john-maeda-contributions-by-rebecca-j-bermont-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/redesigning-leadership-john-maeda-contributions-by-rebecca-j-bermont-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lessons for a new generation of leaders on teamwork, meetings, conversations, free food, social media, apologizing, and other topics. When designer and computer scientist John Maeda was tapped to be president of the celebrated Rhode Island School of Design in 2008, he had to learn how to be a leader quickly. He had to transform [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/redesigning-leadership-john-maeda-contributions-by-rebecca-j-bermont-abridged/">Redesigning Leadership &#8211; John Maeda, Contributions by Rebecca J Bermont (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lessons for a new generation of leaders on teamwork, meetings, conversations, free food, social media, apologizing, and other topics.    </p>
<p>                    When designer and computer scientist John Maeda was tapped to be president of the celebrated Rhode Island School of Design in 2008, he had to learn how to be a leader quickly. He had to transform himself from a tenured professor&#8211;with a love of argument for argument&#8217;s sake and the freedom to experiment&#8211;into the head of a hierarchical organization. The professor is free to speak his mind against &#8220;the man.&#8221; The college president is &#8220;the man.&#8221; Maeda has had to teach himself, through trial and error, about leadership. In Redesigning Leadership, he shares his learning process.     </p>
<p>                    Maeda, writing as an artist and designer, a technologist, and a professor, discusses intuition and risk-taking, &#8220;transparency,&#8221; and all the things that a conversation can do that an email can&#8217;t. In his transition from MIT to RISD he finds that the most effective way to pull people together is not social networking but free food. Leading a team? The best way for a leader to leverage the collective power of a team is to reveal his or her own humanity.     </p>
<p>                    Asked if he has stopped designing, Maeda replied (via Twitter) &#8220;I&#8217;m designing how to talk about/with/for our #RISD community.&#8221; Maeda&#8217;s creative nature makes him a different sort of leader&#8211;one who prizes experimentation, honest critique, and learning as you go. With Redesigning Leadership, he uses his experience to reveal a new model of leadership for the next generation of leaders.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/redesigning-leadership-john-maeda-contributions-by-rebecca-j-bermont-abridged/">Redesigning Leadership &#8211; John Maeda, Contributions by Rebecca J Bermont (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where You Go Is Not Who You&#8217;ll Be : An Antidote to the College Admissions Mania &#8211; Frank Bruni (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/where-you-go-is-not-who-youll-be-an-antidote-to-the-college-admissions-mania-frank-bruni-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/where-you-go-is-not-who-youll-be-an-antidote-to-the-college-admissions-mania-frank-bruni-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Read award-winning journalist Frank Bruni&#8217;s New York Times bestseller: an inspiring manifesto about everything wrong with today&#8217;s frenzied college admissions process and how to make the most of your college years. Over the last few decades, Americans have turned college admissions into a terrifying and occasionally devastating process, preceded by test prep, tutors, all sorts [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/where-you-go-is-not-who-youll-be-an-antidote-to-the-college-admissions-mania-frank-bruni-abridged/">Where You Go Is Not Who You&#8217;ll Be : An Antidote to the College Admissions Mania &#8211; Frank Bruni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read award-winning journalist Frank Bruni&#8217;s New York Times bestseller: an inspiring manifesto about everything wrong with today&#8217;s frenzied college admissions process and how to make the most of your college years.     </p>
<p>                     Over the last few decades, Americans have turned college admissions into a terrifying and occasionally devastating process, preceded by test prep, tutors, all sorts of stratagems, all kinds of rankings, and a conviction among too many young people that their futures will be determined and their worth established by which schools say yes and which say no.     </p>
<p>                     In Where You Go is Not Who You&#8217;ll Be, Frank Bruni explains why this mindset is wrong, giving students and their parents a new perspective on this brutal, deeply flawed competition and a path out of the anxiety that it provokes.     </p>
<p>                     Bruni, a bestselling author and a columnist for the New York Times, shows that the Ivy League has no monopoly on corner offices, governors&#8217; mansions, or the most prestigious academic and scientific grants. Through statistics, surveys, and the stories of hugely successful people, he demonstrates that many kinds of colleges serve as ideal springboards. And he illuminates how to make the most of them. What matters in the end are students&#8217; efforts in and out of the classroom, not the name on their diploma.     </p>
<p>                     Where you go isn&#8217;t who you&#8217;ll be. Americans need to hear that&#8211;and this indispensable manifesto says it with eloquence and respect for the real promise of higher education.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/where-you-go-is-not-who-youll-be-an-antidote-to-the-college-admissions-mania-frank-bruni-abridged/">Where You Go Is Not Who You&#8217;ll Be : An Antidote to the College Admissions Mania &#8211; Frank Bruni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Exegesis & Hermeneutics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Earliest Times To Present Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This rich and magisterial work traces Palestine&#8217;s millennia-old heritage, uncovering cultures and societies of astounding depth and complexity that stretch back to the very beginnings of recorded history. Starting with the earliest references in Egyptian and Assyrian texts, Nur Masalha explores how Palestine and its Palestinian identity have evolved over thousands of years, from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/">Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This rich and magisterial work traces Palestine&#8217;s millennia-old heritage, uncovering cultures and societies of astounding depth and complexity that stretch back to the very beginnings of recorded history.    </p>
<p>                    Starting with the earliest references in Egyptian and Assyrian texts, Nur Masalha explores how Palestine and its Palestinian identity have evolved over thousands of years, from the Bronze Age to the present day. Drawing on a rich body of sources and the latest archaeological evidence, Masalha shows how Palestine&#8217;s multicultural past has been distorted and mythologised by Biblical lore and the Israel-Palestinian conflict.    </p>
<p>                    In the process, Masalha reveals that the concept of Palestine, contrary to accepted belief, is not a modern invention or one constructed in opposition to Israel, but rooted firmly in ancient past. Palestine represents the authoritative account of the country&#8217;s history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/">Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Learning, Home Learning, Distance Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned education writer comes a fascinating examination of the rapidly shifting world of college that every parent, student and educator needs to understand. In 2011-2012, some of the world&#8217;s most famous universities and technology entrepreneurs began a revolution in higher education. College courses that had been kept from all but an elite few [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/">The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned education writer comes a fascinating examination of the rapidly shifting world of college that every parent, student and educator needs to understand.    </p>
<p>                    In 2011-2012, some of the world&#8217;s most famous universities and technology entrepreneurs began a revolution in higher education. College courses that had been kept from all but an elite few were released to students around the world &#8212; for free. And thanks to exploding tuition prices, a volatile global economy and some high-tech innovations, we&#8217;re now poised for a total rethinking of what college is and should be. In the NEW YORK TIMES-bestselling THE END OF COLLEGE, Kevin Carey draws on new research to paint an exciting portrait of the near future of education. He explains how the college experience is being radically altered now and how it will emancipate millions of people around the world. Insightful and readable, THE END OF COLLEGE is an innovative roadmap to understanding tomorrow&#8217;s higher education today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/">The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
