<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Rap &amp; Hip-Hop Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/rap-hip-hop/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/rap-hip-hop/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Rap &amp; Hip-Hop Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/rap-hip-hop/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD &#8211; Russ (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/its-all-in-your-head-russ-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rap & Hip-Hop]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/its-all-in-your-head-russ-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Instant National Bestseller! Wall Street Journal bestseller; USA Today bestseller; Publishers Weekly bestseller; international bestseller. An inspirational book by self-made musical superstar, Russ, reminding you that it starts with YOU, to believe in yourself, and to get out of your own way. Twenty-seven-year-old rapper, songwriter, and producer Russ walks his own path, at his own [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-all-in-your-head-russ-abridged/">IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD &#8211; Russ (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Instant National Bestseller! Wall Street Journal bestseller; USA Today bestseller; Publishers Weekly bestseller; international bestseller.    </p>
<p>                    An inspirational book by self-made musical superstar, Russ, reminding you that it starts with YOU, to believe in yourself, and to get out of your own way.     </p>
<p>                      Twenty-seven-year-old rapper, songwriter, and producer Russ walks his own path, at his own pace. By doing so, he proved that he didn&#8217;t need a major label to surpass over a billion streams on Spotify/Apple Music, get on Forbes&#8217; 2019 &#8220;30 Under 30,&#8221; make the Forbes&#8217; &#8220;30 Under 30 Cash Kings&#8221; at number 20 for most earned, sell out arenas across the U.S. and around the globe, and become one of the most popular and engaged rappers right now. His method was simple: love and believe in yourself absolutely and work hard no matter what. In this memoir, Russ inspires readers to walk to their individual rhythms and beat their biggest obstacles: themselves.    </p>
<p>                      With chapters named after his most powerful and popular songs, IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD will reflect on the lessons he&#8217;s learned from his career, family, and relationships. He&#8217;ll push readers to bet on themselves, take those leaps of faith, and recognize struggles as opportunities. With illustrations throughout consistent with the brand Russ has built and his fan base loves, IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD will give readers an inside-look at the man and the motivation behind the music. A lover of books like The Alchemist and The Seven Spiritual Laws of Success, Russ delivers a short, potent, inspirational, raw, and honest book that gives readers a way to find self-belief and unlock their potential. Fans already rely on Russ as an inspiration of confidence; now, he is taking it to the next level with this book, which will contain lyrics from his music and visuals that reflect his inimitable style.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-all-in-your-head-russ-abridged/">IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD &#8211; Russ (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jay-Z : Made in America &#8211; Michael Eric Dyson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/jay-z-made-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians, Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rap & Hip-Hop]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/jay-z-made-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dyson&#8217;s incisive analysis of JAY-Z&#8217;s brilliance not only offers a brief history of hip-hop&#8217;s critical place in American culture, but also hints at how we can best move forward.&#8221; &#8211;Questlove JAY-Z: Made in America is the fruit of Michael Eric Dyson&#8217;s decade of teaching the work of one of the greatest poets this nation has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jay-z-made-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/">Jay-Z : Made in America &#8211; Michael Eric Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dyson&#8217;s incisive analysis of JAY-Z&#8217;s brilliance not only offers a brief history of hip-hop&#8217;s critical place in American culture, but also hints at how we can best move forward.&#8221; &#8211;Questlove    </p>
<p>                    JAY-Z: Made in America is the fruit of Michael Eric Dyson&#8217;s decade of teaching the work of one of the greatest poets this nation has produced, as gifted a wordsmith as Walt Whitman, Robert Frost and Rita Dove. But as a rapper, he&#8217;s sometimes not given the credit he deserves for just how great an artist he&#8217;s been for so long.<br />
                    This book wrestles with the biggest themes of JAY-Z&#8217;s career, including hustling, and it recognizes the way that he&#8217;s always weaved politics into his music, making important statements about race, criminal justice, black wealth and social injustice. As he enters his fifties, and to mark his thirty years as a recording artist, this is the perfect time to take a look at JAY-Z&#8217;s career and his role in making this nation what it is today. In many ways, this is JAY-Z&#8217;s America as much as it&#8217;s Pelosi&#8217;s America, or Trump&#8217;s America, or Martin Luther King&#8217;s America. JAY-Z has given this country a language to think with and words to live by.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jay-z-made-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/">Jay-Z : Made in America &#8211; Michael Eric Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
