<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Communication Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/communication-studies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/communication-studies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Communication Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/communication-studies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Empire of Illusion : The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle &#8211; Chris Hedges</title>
		<link>/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We now live in two Americas. One,now the minority,functions in a print-based, literate world that can cope with complexity and can separate illusion from truth. The other,the majority,is retreating from a reality-based world into one of false certainty and magic. To this majority,which crosses social class lines, though the poor are overwhelmingly affected,presidential debate and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/">Empire of Illusion : The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle &#8211; Chris Hedges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We now live in two Americas. One,now the minority,functions in a print-based, literate world that can cope with complexity and can separate illusion from truth. The other,the majority,is retreating from a reality-based world into one of false certainty and magic. To this majority,which crosses social class lines, though the poor are overwhelmingly affected,presidential debate and political rhetoric is pitched at a sixth-grade reading level. In this  other America,&#8221; serious film and theatre, as well as newspapers and books, are being pushed to the margins of society. In the tradition of Christopher Lasch&#8217;s  The Culture of Narcissism  and Neil Postman&#8217;s  Amusing Ourselves to Death , Pulitzer Prize-winner Chris Hedges navigates this culture,attending WWF contests, the Adult Video News Awards in Las Vegas, and Ivy League graduation ceremonies,to expose an age of terrifying decline and heightened self-delusion.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/">Empire of Illusion : The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle &#8211; Chris Hedges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In a time in which the ways we communicate and connect are constantly changing, and not always for the better, Sherry Turkle provides a much needed voice of caution and reason to help explain what the f*** is going on.&#8221; &#8211;Aziz Ansari, author of Modern Romance Renowned media scholar Sherry Turkle investigates how a flight [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In a time in which the ways we communicate and connect are constantly changing, and not always for the better, Sherry Turkle provides a much needed voice of caution and reason to help explain what the f*** is going on.&#8221; &#8211;Aziz Ansari,  author of Modern Romance     </p>
<p>                    Renowned media scholar Sherry Turkle investigates how a flight from conversation undermines our relationships, creativity, and productivity&#8211;and why reclaiming face-to-face conversation can help us regain lost ground.    </p>
<p>                    We live in a technological universe in which we are always communicating. And yet we have sacrificed conversation for mere connection.     </p>
<p>                     Preeminent author and researcher Sherry Turkle has been studying digital culture for over thirty years. Long an enthusiast for its possibilities, here she investigates a troubling consequence: at work, at home, in politics, and in love, we find ways around conversation, tempted by the possibilities of a text or an email in which we don&#8217;t have to look, listen, or reveal ourselves.     </p>
<p>                     We develop a taste for what mere connection offers. The dinner table falls silent as children compete with phones for their parents&#8217; attention. Friends learn strategies to keep conversations going when only a few people are looking up from their phones. At work, we retreat to our screens although it is conversation at the water cooler that increases not only productivity but commitment to work. Online, we only want to share opinions that our followers will agree with &#8211; a politics that shies away from the real conflicts and solutions of the public square.     </p>
<p>                     The case for conversation begins with the necessary conversations of solitude and self-reflection. They are endangered: these days, always connected, we see loneliness as a problem that technology should solve. Afraid of being alone, we rely on other people to give us a sense of ourselves, and our capacity for empathy and relationship suffers. We see the costs of the flight from conversation everywhere: conversation is the cornerstone for democracy and in business it is good for the bottom line. In the private sphere, it builds empathy, friendship, love, learning, and productivity.     </p>
<p>                     But there is good news: we are resilient. Conversation cures.     </p>
<p>                     Based on five years of research and interviews in homes, schools, and the workplace, Turkle argues that we have come to a better understanding of where our technology can and cannot take us and that the time is right to reclaim conversation. The most human&#8211;and humanizing&#8211;thing that we do.     </p>
<p>                     The virtues of person-to-person conversation are timeless, and our most basic technology, talk, responds to our modern challenges. We have everything we need to start, we have each other.     </p>
<p>                    Turkle&#8217;s latest book, The Empathy Diaries (3/2/21) is available now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Campaigns that Shook the World : The Evolution of Public Relations &#8211; Danny Rogers, Foreword by Sir Martin Sorrell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/campaigns-that-shook-the-world-the-evolution-of-public-relations-danny-rogers-foreword-by-sir-martin-sorrell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/campaigns-that-shook-the-world-the-evolution-of-public-relations-danny-rogers-foreword-by-sir-martin-sorrell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Campaigns that Shook the World provides the inside story on a selection of the greatest campaigns of the last four decades, while narrating the development of the PR and communications business. The book provides the definitive case studies of nine campaigns &#8211; political, corporate and entertainment &#8211; from the 1970s to the present day. It [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/campaigns-that-shook-the-world-the-evolution-of-public-relations-danny-rogers-foreword-by-sir-martin-sorrell-abridged/">Campaigns that Shook the World : The Evolution of Public Relations &#8211; Danny Rogers, Foreword by Sir Martin Sorrell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Campaigns that Shook the World provides the inside story on a selection of the greatest campaigns of the last four decades, while narrating the development of the PR and communications business. The book provides the definitive case studies of nine campaigns &#8211; political, corporate and entertainment &#8211; from the 1970s to the present day. It explains their strategies and tactics, looks at the imagery and icons they created and interviews the powerful, flamboyant personalities who crafted and executed these seminal projects.    </p>
<p>                    The book examines Thatcherism, New Labour, Britain&#8217;s royal family, the Rolling Stones, David Beckham, the London 2012 Olympics, Product (RED), Obama for America and Dove&#8217;s Campaign for Real Beauty. In addition, Campaigns that Shook the World:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; contains exclusive interviews with campaign gurus such as Alastair Campbell, Matthew Freud, Simon Fuller and Lord Tim Bell<br />
                    &#8211; investigates the relationship between communication techniques, the media and evolving public opinion, using real-world examples<br />
                    &#8211; features campaigns by Saatchi &#038; Saatchi, Edelman, Bell Pottinger, Ogilvy, Freuds and other well-known marketing consultancies    </p>
<p>                    Campaigns that Shook the World grapples with PR&#8217;s uneasy place at the nexus of politics and celebrity, holding the best campaigns up to scrutiny and showcasing just how powerful PR can be as an instrument of change. It contains insights from Alan Edwards, Paddy Harverson and many others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/campaigns-that-shook-the-world-the-evolution-of-public-relations-danny-rogers-foreword-by-sir-martin-sorrell-abridged/">Campaigns that Shook the World : The Evolution of Public Relations &#8211; Danny Rogers, Foreword by Sir Martin Sorrell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider. After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry. From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider.    </p>
<p>                    After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry.     </p>
<p>                    From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that routinely rejected stories due to racial bias, to the number of papers that accepted cash bribes. Gripping, thought-provoking and revelatory, this is an insider&#8217;s look at one of the most tainted professions.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Meticulous, fair-minded and utterly gripping&#8217; Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Powerful and timely&#8230;his analysis is fair, meticulously researched and fascinating&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Culture &#8211; Edward T. Hall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned American anthropologist comes a proud celebration of human capacities. For too long, people have taken their own ways of life for granted, ignoring the vast, international cultural community that srrounds them. Humankind must now embark on the difficult journey beyond culture, to the discovery of a lost self a sense of perspective. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/">Beyond Culture &#8211; Edward T. Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned American anthropologist comes a proud celebration of human capacities. For too long, people have taken their own ways of life for granted, ignoring the vast, international cultural community that srrounds them. Humankind must now embark on the difficult journey beyond culture, to the discovery of a lost self a sense of perspective. By holding up a mirror, Hall permits us to see the awesome grip of unconscious culture. With concrete examples ranging from James Joyce&#8217;s Finnegans Wake to the mating habits of the bowerbird of New Guinea, Hall shows us ourselves. Beyond Culture is a book about self-discovery; it is a voyage we all must embark on if mankind is to survive.     </p>
<p>                    Fascinating and emotionally challenging. . . . The book&#8217;s graceful, non-technical style and the many illuminating, real-life illustrations make it a delight to read. &#8211;Library Journal    </p>
<p>                    Hall&#8217;s book helps us to rethink our values. . . . We come away from it exhilarated. &#8211;Ashley Montagu     </p>
<p>                    In this penetrating analysis of the culturally determined yet &#8216;unconscious&#8217; attitudes that mold our thought, feeling, communication and behavior. . . . Hall makes explicit taken-for-granted linguistic patterns, body rhythms, personality dynamics, educational goals. . . . Many of Hall&#8217;s ideas are original and incisive . . . [and] should reward careful readers with new ways of thinking about themselves and others. &#8211;Publishers Weekly    </p>
<p>                    A fascintaing book which stands beside The Hidden Dimension and The Silent Language to prove Hall one of the most original anthropologists of our era. &#8211;Paul Bohannan</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/">Beyond Culture &#8211; Edward T. Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution. For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers. Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution.    For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers.       Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created.       They are using blogs, Twitter, and Facebook to share stories, and selecting their sources to create their own &#8216;front page&#8217;.   In this lively, biting critique, media commentator Tim Dunlop explores the rise of the audience, and how unprepared the mainstream media has been for this changing balance of power.       Drawing on his experiences as prominent political blogger, he argues that the future of meaningful journalism &#8211; the sort we need in order to be informed citizens &#8211; will increasingly rely on journalists and editors taking the audience into their confidence and working with them, rather than against them.   The New Front Page is a passionate plea on behalf of those tired of being talked down to by the fourth estate.       Perceptive and illuminating, it asks audiences and media to work together to hold the powerful to account, and to produce the sort of news and analysis that enriches public debate.   &#8216;A fascinating account of how digital technology has changed Australian media forever.&#8217;       Katharine Viner, editor-in-chief of The Guardian Australia   &#8216;An essential guide to understanding our insurgent new media.&#8217;       Lindsay Tanner, author of Sideshow   &#8216;Dunlop writes with humour, passion, and insight.&#8217;       Gay Alcorn, journalist</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes, it makes more sense to lose today in order to win tomorrow. What do you do when you know what you want, but you have no idea how to get it? &#8216;The greatest negotiation book of all time.&#8217; Inc. Magazine ________________ Never walk away. Learn to listen, then learn to understand, then learn to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/">Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes, it makes more sense to lose today in order to win tomorrow. What do you do when you know what you want, but you have no idea how to get it?    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The greatest negotiation book of all time.&#8217; Inc. Magazine<br />
                     ________________                           </p>
<p>                     Never walk away. Learn to listen, then learn to understand, then learn to win.    </p>
<p>                    Negotiation is part of every human encounter, and most of us do it badly. Whether dealing with family, a business, or diplomacy, people often fail to meet their goals in every country and context. They focus on power and &#8220;win-win&#8221; instead of relationships and perceptions. They don&#8217;t find enough things to trade. They think others should be rational when they should be dealing with emotions. They get distracted from their goals.    </p>
<p>                    In this revolutionary and seminal bestselling book, leading negotiation practitioner, coach and professor Stuart Diamond shows how emotional intelligence, perceptions, cultural diversity and collaboration produce four times as much value as old-school, conflictive, power, leverage and logic. Drawing on thirty-plus years of research involving 30,000 people across 45 countries &#8211; ranging from political and corporate leaders to administrative assistants, lawyers, housewives, students, and labourers &#8211; he outlines specific, practical and better ways to deal with others. To this, he adds his 40-year experience as a corporate executive, Harvard-trained attorney, and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist.    </p>
<p>                    Getting More is based on Professor Diamond&#8217;s award-winning negotiations course at The Wharton Business School, where it has been the most sought-after course by students for almost two decades. It contains a powerful toolkit that can be used in any situation: with kids and jobs, travel and shopping, business, politics, relationships, cultures, partners and competitors. His advice is brought to life in an accessible and entertaining manner through the stories of hundreds of people who have used the toolkit with great success.<br />
                    ________________    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;From advising on how to negotiate with terrorists, to industrial disputes, to children, Diamond&#8217;s twelve rules of negotiation promise to open new doors every day.&#8217; Radio One    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Practical, immediately applicable and highly effective.&#8217; Evan Wittenberg, co-founder of TRUE and former Head of Global Leadership Development at Google    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I rely on Stuart Diamond&#8217;s negotiation tools every day.&#8217; Christian Hernandez, venture capitalist and former Head of International Business Development at Facebook</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-more-how-you-can-negotiate-to-succeed-in-work-and-life-stuart-diamond-abridged/">Getting More : How You Can Negotiate to Succeed in Work and Life &#8211; Stuart Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind. In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic book on the development of human language by the world&#8217;s leading expert on language and the mind.    </p>
<p>                    In this classic, the world&#8217;s expert on language and mind lucidly explains everything you always wanted to know about language: how it works, how children learn it, how it changes, how the brain computes it, and how it evolved. With deft use of examples of humor and wordplay, Steven Pinker weaves our vast knowledge of language into a compelling story: language is a human instinct, wired into our brains by evolution. The Language Instinct received the William James Book Prize from the American Psychological Association and the Public Interest Award from the Linguistics Society of America. This edition includes an update on advances in the science of language since The Language Instinct was first published.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-language-instinct-how-the-mind-creates-language-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Language Instinct : How the Mind Creates Language &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Find out Anything from Anyone, Anytime : Secrets of Calculated Questioning from a Veteran Interrogator &#8211; James O. Pyle, Maryann Karinch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/find-out-anything-from-anyone-anytime-secrets-of-calculated-questioning-from-a-veteran-interrogator-james-o-pyle-maryann-karinch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/find-out-anything-from-anyone-anytime-secrets-of-calculated-questioning-from-a-veteran-interrogator-james-o-pyle-maryann-karinch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The secret to finding out anything you want to know is amazingly simple: Ask good questions. Most people trip through life asking bad questions&#8211;of teachers, friends, coworkers, clients, prospects, experts, and suspects. Even people trained in questioning, such as journalists and lawyers, commonly ask questions that get partial or misleading answers. People in any profession [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/find-out-anything-from-anyone-anytime-secrets-of-calculated-questioning-from-a-veteran-interrogator-james-o-pyle-maryann-karinch-abridged/">Find out Anything from Anyone, Anytime : Secrets of Calculated Questioning from a Veteran Interrogator &#8211; James O. Pyle, Maryann Karinch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The secret to finding out anything you want to know is amazingly simple: Ask good questions. Most people trip through life asking bad questions&#8211;of teachers, friends, coworkers, clients, prospects, experts, and suspects. Even people trained in questioning, such as journalists and lawyers, commonly ask questions that get partial or misleading answers.     </p>
<p>                    People in any profession will immediately benefit by developing the skill and art of good questioning. Find Out Anything From Anyone, Anytime will give you the power to:     </p>
<p>                    Identify and practice good questioning techniques<br />
                    Recognize types of questions to avoid<br />
                    Know the questions required when hearing unconfirmed reports or gossip<br />
                    Practice good listening techniques and exploit all leads<br />
                    Determine when and how to control the conversation<br />
                    Gain real expertise fast     </p>
<p>                    Within professional interrogation circles, author James Pyle is known as a strategic debriefer&#8211;meaning there is no one around him more skilled at asking questions and getting answers. He has been training other interrogators in questioning techniques since 1989.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/find-out-anything-from-anyone-anytime-secrets-of-calculated-questioning-from-a-veteran-interrogator-james-o-pyle-maryann-karinch-abridged/">Find out Anything from Anyone, Anytime : Secrets of Calculated Questioning from a Veteran Interrogator &#8211; James O. Pyle, Maryann Karinch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities. In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities.     </p>
<p>                    In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our language carries secrets about our feelings, our self-concept, and our social intelligence. Our most forgettable words, such as pronouns and prepositions, can be the most revealing: their patterns are as distinctive as fingerprints.     </p>
<p>                    Using innovative analytic techniques, Pennebaker X-rays everything from John McCain&#8217;s tweets to the Federalist Papers. Who would have predicted that the high school student who uses too many verbs in her college admissions essay is likely to make lower grades in college? Or that a world leader&#8217;s use of pronouns could reliably presage whether he will lead his country into war? You&#8217;ll learn what Lady Gaga and William Butler Yeats have in common, and how Ebenezer Scrooge&#8217;s syntax hints at his self-deception and repressed emotion in this sprightly, surprising tour of what our words are saying-whether we mean them to or not.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Difficult Conversations : How to Discuss What Matters Most &#8211; Douglas Stone, Bruce Patton, Sheila Heen, Foreword by Roger Fisher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/difficult-conversations-how-to-discuss-what-matters-most-douglas-stone-bruce-patton-sheila-heen-foreword-by-roger-fisher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/difficult-conversations-how-to-discuss-what-matters-most-douglas-stone-bruce-patton-sheila-heen-foreword-by-roger-fisher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The 10th-anniversary edition of the New York Times business bestseller-now updated with Answers to Ten Questions People Ask We attempt or avoid difficult conversations every day-whether dealing with an underperforming employee, disagreeing with a spouse, or negotiating with a client. From the Harvard Negotiation Project, the organization that brought you Getting to Yes, Difficult Conversations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/difficult-conversations-how-to-discuss-what-matters-most-douglas-stone-bruce-patton-sheila-heen-foreword-by-roger-fisher-abridged/">Difficult Conversations : How to Discuss What Matters Most &#8211; Douglas Stone, Bruce Patton, Sheila Heen, Foreword by Roger Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 10th-anniversary edition of the New York Times business bestseller-now updated with Answers to Ten Questions People Ask      </p>
<p>                     We attempt or avoid difficult conversations every day-whether dealing with an underperforming employee, disagreeing with a spouse, or negotiating with a client. From the Harvard Negotiation Project, the organization that brought you Getting to Yes, Difficult Conversations provides a step-by-step approach to having those tough conversations with less stress and more success. you&#8217;ll learn how to:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Decipher the underlying structure of every difficult conversation<br />
                     &#8211; Start a conversation without defensiveness<br />
                     &#8211; Listen for the meaning of what is not said<br />
                    &#8211; Stay balanced in the face of attacks and accusations<br />
                    &#8211; Move from emotion to productive problem solving</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/difficult-conversations-how-to-discuss-what-matters-most-douglas-stone-bruce-patton-sheila-heen-foreword-by-roger-fisher-abridged/">Difficult Conversations : How to Discuss What Matters Most &#8211; Douglas Stone, Bruce Patton, Sheila Heen, Foreword by Roger Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After everything that&#8217;s happened, how is it possible that conservatives still win debates about the economy? Time and again the right wins over voters by claiming that their solutions are only common sense, even as their tired policies of budgetary sacrifice and corporate plunder both create and prolong economic disaster. Why does the electorate keep [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After everything that&#8217;s happened, how is it possible that conservatives still win debates about the economy? Time and again the right wins over voters by claiming that their solutions are only common sense, even as their tired policies of budgetary sacrifice and corporate plunder both create and prolong economic disaster. Why does the electorate keep buying what they&#8217;re selling? According to political communications expert Anat Shenker-Osorio, it&#8217;s all about language,and not just theirs, but ours.In  Don&#8217;t Buy It  Shenker-Osorio diagnoses our economic discourse as stricken with faulty messages, deceptive personification, and, worst of all, a barely coherent concept of what the economy actually is. Opening up the business section of most newspapers or flipping on cable news unleashes an onslaught of economic doomsaying that treats the economy as an ungovernable force of nature. Alternately, by calling the economy  unhealthy&#8221; or  recovering&#8221; as we so often do, we unconsciously give it the status of a living being. No wonder Americans become willing to submit to any indignity required to keep the economy happy. Tread lightly, we can&#8217;t risk irritating the economy!Cutting through conservative myth-making, messaging muddles, and destructive misinformation, Shenker-Osorio suggests a new way to win the most important arguments of our day. The left doesn&#8217;t have to self-destruct every time matters economic come to the fore,there are metaphors and frames that can win, and Shenker-Osorio shows what they are and how to use them. Don&#8217;t Buy It  is a vital handbook for seizing victory in the economic debate. In the end, it convincingly shows that radically altering our politics and policies for the better is a matter of first changing the conversation,literally.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Thinking : Upgrade Your Reasoning and Make Better Decisions with Mental Models &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Lauren McCann (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An invaluable resource for making sense of the world, making good decisions, and placing smart bets. A fast-paced and fun read jam-packed with useful information on every page.&#8217; Annie Duke, author of Thinking in Bets ________________ Turn yourself into a superthinker and make the right decisions every time. You want to make better decisions. You [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/">Super Thinking : Upgrade Your Reasoning and Make Better Decisions with Mental Models &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Lauren McCann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An invaluable resource for making sense of the world, making good decisions, and placing smart bets. A fast-paced and fun read jam-packed with useful information on every page.&#8217; Annie Duke, author of Thinking in Bets<br />
                     ________________                           </p>
<p>                     Turn yourself into a superthinker and make the right decisions every time.    </p>
<p>                     You want to make better decisions. You want to be right more of the time professionally and personally. However, being more right consistently is a hard problem because the world is such a complex, evolving place. How do you navigate this complexity?    </p>
<p>                     Mental models are decision-making tools that guide our perception of the world and our behaviour in it. They help us understand life, make decisions and solve problems. The best models help us make intelligent investments, develop ground-breaking technologies and even travel to outer space.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Note your frame of reference before debating someone with different political views. If you understand how your perspective contrasts with someone else&#8217;s you can prevent the conversation from getting hostile.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Apply the sunk cost fallacy to the end of a doomed project. Just because you&#8217;ve put a lot of hours into it doesn&#8217;t mean that you have to keep going.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Before blaming someone, consider Hanlon&#8217;s Razor, &#8216;Never attribute to malice that which is adequately explained by carelessness&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Try to solve mysteries with Occam&#8217;s Razor, &#8216;Among competing hypotheses, the one with the fewest assumptions should be selected&#8217;. When you hear hoof beats, think of horses not zebras.    </p>
<p>                     Building on our knowledge of well-known models such as the Bandwagon Effect or Paradigm Shift and introducing us to the lesser known like the Eisenhower Matrix or the Boiling Frog Symbol, this indispensable book distils the most effective mental models into a single, digestible volume. It will make even the most complex models accessible and engaging to enable you to make better, more informed decisions in every part of your life.<br />
                     ________________    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Internalizing these mental models will help you understand the world around you. Once you can spot them, you can change your own behavior to avoid common traps, adjust how you interact with people to get better results, and maybe even articulate new mental models of the world that have yet to be discovered.&#8217; Brian Armstrong, co-founder and CEO, Coinbase    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;You can&#8217;t really know anything if you just remember isolated facts. If the facts don&#8217;t hang together on a latticework of theory, you don&#8217;t have them in a usable form. You&#8217;ve got to have models in your head.&#8217; Charlie Munger, vice chairman, Berkshire Hathaway</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-thinking-upgrade-your-reasoning-and-make-better-decisions-with-mental-models-gabriel-weinberg-lauren-mccann-abridged/">Super Thinking : Upgrade Your Reasoning and Make Better Decisions with Mental Models &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Lauren McCann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Budget Airlines in India leverage on Online Marketing to increase the Competitiveness : A Study &#8211; Srinivas Rao Yemula (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-budget-airlines-in-india-leverage-on-online-marketing-to-increase-the-competitiveness-a-study-srinivas-rao-yemula-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-budget-airlines-in-india-leverage-on-online-marketing-to-increase-the-competitiveness-a-study-srinivas-rao-yemula-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Master&#8217;s Thesis from the year 2015 in the subject Communications &#8211; Public Relations, Advertising, Marketing, Social Media, grade: Distinction, University of Sunderland (Management Development Institute of Singapore.), course: Masters in Business Administration., language: English, abstract: Online marketing techniques have become the popular trend that helps organization to promote products and services globally. Budget airlines industry [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-budget-airlines-in-india-leverage-on-online-marketing-to-increase-the-competitiveness-a-study-srinivas-rao-yemula-abridged/">How Budget Airlines in India leverage on Online Marketing to increase the Competitiveness : A Study &#8211; Srinivas Rao Yemula (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Master&#8217;s Thesis from the year 2015 in the subject Communications &#8211; Public Relations, Advertising, Marketing, Social Media, grade: Distinction, University of Sunderland (Management Development Institute of Singapore.), course: Masters in Business Administration., language: English, abstract: Online marketing techniques have become the popular trend that helps organization to promote products and services globally. Budget airlines industry in India can leverage on the online marketing in order to increase the competitiveness in the market as most of the people choose to fly budget airlines. This research paper identifies and analyses various online marketing techniques and factors that contribute to the success of online marketing. Both primary and secondary data gathering techniques are used in this research study. The primary instruments for this research study is questionnaires with the sample sizes 381 of working adults and students of Indian community in India and overseas. The secondary sources used for this study are books, newspapers, magazines, journals, articles, and previous research papers. Both qualitative and quantitative research methods are used to analyse the data. IBM SPSS version 22 application software is used to analyse the data and generate the graphical output in pie chart diagram. From the research study, the researcher has found several success factors that play an important role in the successful execution of online marketing campaign such as quality content of the website, regular updates of the social media website, blogging on the popular blogs website to increase the website traffic, online video marketing, email marketing and paid search marketing. Lastly, there are six critical success factors identified in this research study.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-budget-airlines-in-india-leverage-on-online-marketing-to-increase-the-competitiveness-a-study-srinivas-rao-yemula-abridged/">How Budget Airlines in India leverage on Online Marketing to increase the Competitiveness : A Study &#8211; Srinivas Rao Yemula (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Gathering : How We Meet and Why It Matters &#8211; Priya Parker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to create the most transformative meetings and moments &#8216;Priya Parker has created both an art and a science to gathering in ways that can bring joy and fulfilment to any meeting&#8217; Deepak Chopra &#8216;Hosts of all kinds, this is a must-read!&#8217; Chris Anderson, creator of TED &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; Being deprived of gathering has revealed just [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/">The Art of Gathering : How We Meet and Why It Matters &#8211; Priya Parker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to create the most transformative meetings and moments    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Priya Parker has created both an art and a science to gathering in ways that can bring joy and fulfilment to any meeting&#8217; Deepak Chopra     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hosts of all kinds, this is a must-read!&#8217; Chris Anderson, creator of TED    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;     </p>
<p>                    Being deprived of gathering has revealed just how important it is to us; to connect with others, collaborate, share ideas and create moving, life-affirming experiences.    </p>
<p>                    At a time when coming together is more crucial than ever, Priya Parker sets forth a human-centered approach to gathering that can help everyone create meaningful, memorable experiences in their lives, large and small, for work and for play.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on her wide expertise as a facilitator of high-powered gatherings around the world, Parker takes us inside events of all kinds to show what works, what doesn&#8217;t, and why. She investigates a wide array of gatherings &#8211; a court hearing, a flash-mob party, an Arab-Israeli summer camp &#8211; and explains how simple changes can invigorate any group experience. The result is a book full of exciting ideas of real-world applications and one that will forever alter the way you look at your next business meeting, dinner party and garden barbecue.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A long overdue and urgent manifesto&#8217; Seth Godin, New York Times bestselling author of This is Marketing</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-gathering-how-we-meet-and-why-it-matters-priya-parker-abridged/">The Art of Gathering : How We Meet and Why It Matters &#8211; Priya Parker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do I Make Myself Clear? : Why Writing Well Matters &#8211; Harold Evans (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-i-make-myself-clear-why-writing-well-matters-harold-evans-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-i-make-myself-clear-why-writing-well-matters-harold-evans-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Harry Evans has edited everything from the urgent files of battlefield reporters to the complex thought processes of Henry Kissinger, and he has been knighted for his services to journalism. In Do I Make Myself Clear?,his definitive guide to writing well, Evans brings his indispensable insight to the art of clear communication. The right words [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-i-make-myself-clear-why-writing-well-matters-harold-evans-abridged/">Do I Make Myself Clear? : Why Writing Well Matters &#8211; Harold Evans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Harry Evans has edited everything from the urgent files of battlefield reporters to the complex thought processes of Henry Kissinger, and he has been knighted for his services to journalism. In Do I Make Myself Clear?,his definitive guide to writing well, Evans brings his indispensable insight to the art of clear communication.    </p>
<p>                    The right words are oxygen to our ideas, but the digital era, with all of its TTYL, LMK and WTF, has been cutting off that oxygen flow. The compulsion to be precise has vanished from our culture, and in writing of all kinds we see a trend towards more &#8211; more speed and more information, but far less clarity. Evans provides practical examples of how editing and rewriting can make for better communication, even in the digital age.    </p>
<p>                    DO I MAKE MYSELF CLEAR? is an essential text, and one that will provide every reader an editor at their shoulder.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-i-make-myself-clear-why-writing-well-matters-harold-evans-abridged/">Do I Make Myself Clear? : Why Writing Well Matters &#8211; Harold Evans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seventh Million : The Israelis and the Holocaust &#8211; Tom Segev, Translated by Professor Haim Watzman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holocaust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Seventh Million is the first book to show the decisive impact of the Holocaust on the identity, ideology, and politics of Israel. Drawing on diaries, interviews, and thousands of declassified documents, Segev reconsiders the major struggles and personalities of Israel&#8217;s past, including Ben-Gurion, Begin, and Nahum Goldmann, and argues that the nation&#8217;s legacy has, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/">The Seventh Million : The Israelis and the Holocaust &#8211; Tom Segev, Translated by Professor Haim Watzman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Seventh Million is the first book to show the decisive impact of the Holocaust on the identity, ideology, and politics of Israel. Drawing on diaries, interviews, and thousands of declassified documents, Segev reconsiders the major struggles and personalities of Israel&#8217;s past, including Ben-Gurion, Begin, and Nahum Goldmann, and argues that the nation&#8217;s legacy has, at critical moments&#8211;the Exodus affair, the Eichmann trial, the case of John Demjanjuk&#8211;have been molded and manipulated in accordance with the ideological requirements of the state. The Seventh Million uncovers a vast and complex story and reveals how the bitter events of decades past continue to shape the experiences not just of individuals but of a nation. Translated by Haim Watzman.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/">The Seventh Million : The Israelis and the Holocaust &#8211; Tom Segev, Translated by Professor Haim Watzman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secrets of Dynamic Communication : Preparing and Delivering Powerful Speeches &#8211; Ken Davis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/secrets-of-dynamic-communication-preparing-and-delivering-powerful-speeches-ken-davis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Sermons]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/secrets-of-dynamic-communication-preparing-and-delivering-powerful-speeches-ken-davis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive study targeted for both beginning and veteran speakers in the art of public speaking and communication. Students are taught the SCORRE system &#8211; a creative and relevant communication model used by leaders to effectively penetrate today&#8217;s culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-dynamic-communication-preparing-and-delivering-powerful-speeches-ken-davis-abridged/">Secrets of Dynamic Communication : Preparing and Delivering Powerful Speeches &#8211; Ken Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive study targeted for both beginning and veteran speakers in the art of public speaking and communication. Students are taught the SCORRE system &#8211; a creative and relevant communication model used by leaders to effectively penetrate today&#8217;s culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-dynamic-communication-preparing-and-delivering-powerful-speeches-ken-davis-abridged/">Secrets of Dynamic Communication : Preparing and Delivering Powerful Speeches &#8211; Ken Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Listening Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you? This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever. At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation. On social media, we shape our personal narratives. At parties, we talk over one another. So do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show    </p>
<p>                    When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you?     </p>
<p>                    This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever.    </p>
<p>                     At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation.    </p>
<p>                     On social media, we shape our personal narratives.    </p>
<p>                     At parties, we talk over one another. So do our politicians.    </p>
<p>                     We&#8217;re not listening.    </p>
<p>                     And no one is listening to us.    </p>
<p>                    Now more than ever, we need to listen to those around us. New York Times contributor Kate Murphy draws on countless conversations she has had with everyone from priests to CIA interrogators, focus group moderators to bartenders, her great-great aunt to her friend&#8217;s toddler, to show how only by listening well can we truly connect with others.    </p>
<p>                     Listening has the potential to transform our relationships and our working lives, improve our self-knowledge, and increase our creativity and happiness. While it may take some effort, it&#8217;s a skill that can be learnt and perfected.    </p>
<p>                     When all we crave is to understand and be understood, You&#8217;re Not Listening shows us how.    </p>
<p>                    * With a new afterword by the author *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book couldn&#8217;t be more timely. Inspiringly profound&#8230;smart and playful&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ll be adopting Murphy&#8217;s advice&#8217; Sunday Times, Style</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semiotics / Semiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They reveal how issues are framed and topics chosen, and contrast the double standards underlying accounts of free elections, a free press, and governmental repression between Nicaragua and El Salvador; between the Russian invasion of Afghanistan and the American invasion of Vietnam; between the genocide in Cambodia under a pro-American government and genocide under Pol Pot. What emerges from this groundbreaking work is an account of just how propagandistic our mass media are, and how we can learn to read them and see their function in a radically new way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Language Intelligence : Lessons on persuasion from Jesus, Shakespeare, Lincoln, and Lady Gaga &#8211; Joseph J Romm (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Romm, one of Rolling Stone magazine&#8217;s top &#8220;100 Agents of Change,&#8221; has focused his talents on helping us all to increase our Language Intelligence and to better understand the art of persuasion. Romm demonstrates that you don&#8217;t have to be an expert to vastly improve your ability to communicate. He has pulled together the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/">Language Intelligence : Lessons on persuasion from Jesus, Shakespeare, Lincoln, and Lady Gaga &#8211; Joseph J Romm (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Romm, one of Rolling Stone magazine&#8217;s top &#8220;100 Agents of Change,&#8221; has focused his talents on helping us all to increase our Language Intelligence and to better understand the art of persuasion.     </p>
<p>                     Romm demonstrates that you don&#8217;t have to be an expert to vastly improve your ability to communicate. He has pulled together the secrets of the greatest communicators in history to show how you can apply these tools to your writing, speaking, blogging &#8211; even your Tweeting. The book also looks at the language intelligence of President Obama and Governor Romney.     </p>
<p>                     Nothing could be more relevant in 2012 as Americans prepare to make vital choices in the upcoming elections. Language Intelligence not only will prepare you to be a much more memorable and persuasive communicator, it will also help you to understand the tricks of the trade used &#8212; and misused &#8212; by candidates on the stump.     </p>
<p>                     With a few easily digestible and memorable concepts, Language Intelligence also offers readers an indispensible roadmap for today&#8217;s political and pop culture landscape. &#8220;For anyone who seeks to understand why Lady Gaga&#8217;s music has become a global phenomena or how to avoid &#8216;Etch-a-Sketch&#8217; moments, this book is for you,&#8221; said Romm.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/">Language Intelligence : Lessons on persuasion from Jesus, Shakespeare, Lincoln, and Lady Gaga &#8211; Joseph J Romm (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>User Research : Improve Product and Service Design and Enhance Your UX Research &#8211; Stephanie Marsh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many businesses are based on creating desirable experiences, products and services for users. However, companies often fail to consider the end user &#8211; the consumer &#8211; in their planning and development processes. How can marketing practitioners effectively understand their customers and create products and services that work for them? This book has the answers. User [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/">User Research : Improve Product and Service Design and Enhance Your UX Research &#8211; Stephanie Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many businesses are based on creating desirable experiences, products and services for users. However, companies often fail to consider the end user &#8211; the consumer &#8211; in their planning and development processes. How can marketing practitioners effectively understand their customers and create products and services that work for them? This book has the answers.    </p>
<p>                    User experience research, also known as UX research, focuses on understanding user behaviours, needs and motivations through a range of observational techniques, task analysis and other methodologies. User Research is a practical guide that shows readers how to use the vast array of user research methods available. Written by one of the UK&#8217;s leading UX research professionals, readers can benefit from in-depth knowledge that explores the fundamentals of user research.    </p>
<p>                    Covering all the key research methods including face-to-face user testing, card sorting, surveys, A/B testing and many more, the book gives expert insight into the nuances, advantages and disadvantages of each, while also providing guidance on how to interpret, analyze and share the data once it has been obtained. Now in its second edition, User Research provides a new chapter on research operations and infrastructure as well as new material on combining user research methodologies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/">User Research : Improve Product and Service Design and Enhance Your UX Research &#8211; Stephanie Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Culture Code : The Secrets of Highly Successful Groups &#8211; Daniel Coyle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-culture-code-the-secrets-of-highly-successful-groups-daniel-coyle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-culture-code-the-secrets-of-highly-successful-groups-daniel-coyle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;A marvel of insight and practicality&#8217; Charles Duhigg, author of The Power of Habit ____________________________ How do you build and sustain a great team? The Culture Code reveals the secrets of some of the best teams in the world &#8211; from Pixar to Google to US Navy SEALs &#8211; explaining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-culture-code-the-secrets-of-highly-successful-groups-daniel-coyle-abridged/">The Culture Code : The Secrets of Highly Successful Groups &#8211; Daniel Coyle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A marvel of insight and practicality&#8217; Charles Duhigg, author of The Power of Habit<br />
                    ____________________________    </p>
<p>                    How do you build and sustain a great team?    </p>
<p>                    The Culture Code reveals the secrets of some of the best teams in the world &#8211; from Pixar to Google to US Navy SEALs &#8211; explaining the three skills such groups have mastered in order to generate trust and a willingness to collaborate. Combining cutting-edge science, on-the-ground insight and practical ideas for action, it offers a roadmap for creating an environment where innovation flourishes, problems get solved, and expectations are exceeded.    </p>
<p>                    ____________________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;There are profound ideas on every single page, stories that will change the way you work, the way you lead, and the impact you have on the world. Highly recommended, an urgent read.&#8217; Seth Godin, author of Linchpin    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Truly brilliant . . . Read it immediately&#8217; Adam Grant, author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Well told stories, with actionable lessons&#8217; Financial Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-culture-code-the-secrets-of-highly-successful-groups-daniel-coyle-abridged/">The Culture Code : The Secrets of Highly Successful Groups &#8211; Daniel Coyle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Almost everyone swears, or worries about not swearing, from the two year-old who has just discovered the power of potty mouth to the grandma who wonders why every other word she hears is obscene. Whether they express anger or exhilaration, are meant to insult or to commend, swear words perform a crucial role in language. But swearing is also a uniquely well-suited lens through which to look at history, offering a fascinating record of what people care about on the<br />
                    deepest levels of a culture-what&#8217;s divine, what&#8217;s terrifying, and what&#8217;s taboo.     </p>
<p>                    Holy Sh*t tells the story of two kinds of swearing-obscenities and oaths-from ancient Rome and the Bible to today. With humor and insight, Melissa Mohr takes readers on a journey to discover how &#8220;swearing&#8221; has come to include both testifying with your hand on the Bible and calling someone a *#$&#038;!* when they cut you off on the highway. She explores obscenities in ancient Rome-which were remarkably similar to our own-and unearths the history of religious oaths in the Middle Ages,<br />
                    when swearing (or not swearing) an oath was often a matter of life and death. Holy Sh*t also explains the advancement of civility and corresponding censorship of language in the 18th century, considers the rise of racial slurs after World War II, examines the physiological effects of swearing (increased heart<br />
                    rate and greater pain tolerance), and answers a question that preoccupies the FCC, the US Senate, and anyone who has recently overheard little kids at a playground: are we swearing more now than people did in the past?     </p>
<p>                    A gem of lexicography and cultural history, Holy Sh*t is a serious exploration of obscenity-and it also just might expand your repertoire of words to choose from the next time you shut your finger in the car door.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-sht-a-brief-history-of-swearing-melissa-mohr-abridged/">Holy Sh*t : A Brief History of Swearing &#8211; Melissa Mohr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Messengers : 8 Ways to Get Heard &#8211; Stephen Martin, Joseph Marks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/messengers-8-ways-to-get-heard-stephen-martin-joseph-marks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/messengers-8-ways-to-get-heard-stephen-martin-joseph-marks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>____________________________ Why can some people effortlessly command the attention of everyone in the room? What makes some individuals seem immediately credible and others appear inherently untrustworthy? And how is it that precisely the same idea can be enthusiastically embraced or roundly rejected depending on who has put it forward? When we talk to others, we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/messengers-8-ways-to-get-heard-stephen-martin-joseph-marks-abridged/">Messengers : 8 Ways to Get Heard &#8211; Stephen Martin, Joseph Marks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>____________________________<br />
                    Why can some people effortlessly command the attention of everyone in the room?    </p>
<p>                    What makes some individuals seem immediately credible and others appear inherently untrustworthy?    </p>
<p>                    And how is it that precisely the same idea can be enthusiastically embraced or roundly rejected depending on who has put it forward?    </p>
<p>                    When we talk to others, we assume that they are carefully weighing our words and arguments. But these are far from  being the only factors that hold sway.    </p>
<p>                    In this groundbreaking new book, bestselling behavioural scientists Stephen Martin and Joseph Marks explore the eight powerful human traits that help determine whether what we have to say gets heard or lands on deaf ears. They show how seemingly irrelevant details about our demeanour influence others&#8217; responses. They explain how trust is won, even when it may not be deserved. They show how the most trivial of signals &#8211; like the shape of our face, the shoes we wear or the car we drive &#8211; can influence how people respond to us.    </p>
<p>                    And in a world of uncertainty and fake news they demonstrate how, increasingly, the Messenger is the Message.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Some books make us better citizens. Others make us better at our jobs. This amazing book does both!&#8217;<br />
                    Dan Pink, author of When, Drive and To Sell is Human<br />
                    ____________________________<br />
                    &#8216;A tour de force. Timely and thoroughly researched.&#8217;<br />
                    Professor Robert Cialdini, author of Influence and Pre-suasion    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Messengers is engaging, informative and entertaining. It will change the way you think about who you follow and take advice from. But why would you listen to me? Read their book to find out.&#8217;<br />
                    Professor Tali Sharot, author of The Optimism Bias and The Influential Mind    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A powerful, profoundly illuminating exploration of one of the most important subjects of our time. Martin and Marks have a terrific talent for combining evidence and research with lively and vivid writing. Trust these messengers!&#8217;<br />
                    Cass R. Sunstein, Robert Walmsley University Professor, Harvard University, and author of Conformity    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating&#8217;<br />
                    The Economist    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Zeitgeisty&#8217;<br />
                    Financial Times, Business Book of the Month    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Messengers is a crucial reminder that the messenger is as important as the message. Superficial indicators count.&#8217;<br />
                    PR Week</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/messengers-8-ways-to-get-heard-stephen-martin-joseph-marks-abridged/">Messengers : 8 Ways to Get Heard &#8211; Stephen Martin, Joseph Marks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Enhance your copywriting skills with psychology-driven techniques to create stand out copy that taps into consumer decision making and sells, using this second edition of the ultimate copywriting survival guide for the 21st century &#8211; essential to every marketing or creative professional&#8217;s bookshelf. With many professionals now developing their skills on the job, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/">Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enhance your copywriting skills with psychology-driven techniques to create stand out copy that taps into consumer decision making and sells, using this second edition of the ultimate copywriting survival guide for the 21st century &#8211; essential to every marketing or creative professional&#8217;s bookshelf.    </p>
<p>                    With many professionals now developing their skills on the job, it is notoriously difficult to benchmark successful copy. This book provides a step up for those who already know the basics of writing copy, and are seeking more advanced, psychology-driven techniques to gain the competitive edge. With practical insight into human decision making and consumer engagement, it will inspire the clear-cut confidence needed to create, quantify, and sell stand out copy in a cluttered marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    Complementing the &#8216;how to&#8217; perspective of copywriting, with impressive interviews from leading ad agencies and copywriters across the globe, this second edition addresses the everyday issues faced in a multitude of roles, including:    </p>
<p>                    -Practical advice to measure and benchmark effective copy<br />
                    -Guidance on creating and critiquing briefs<br />
                    -New chapters on how to weave copywriting skills into the wider industry<br />
                    -Storytelling and content marketing<br />
                    -The impact of evolving channels like mobile and social media    </p>
<p>                    Practical, inspiring and extremely digestible, Persuasive Copywriting is the only vibrant, all-encompassing guide to copywriting that you need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/">Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What We Say Matters : Practicing Nonviolent Communication &#8211; Ike Lasater, Judith Hanson Lasater (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-we-say-matters-practicing-nonviolent-communication-ike-lasater-judith-hanson-lasater-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chakras, Auras & Spiritual Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-we-say-matters-practicing-nonviolent-communication-ike-lasater-judith-hanson-lasater-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Drawing from Buddhist and yogic precepts, this practical guide offers tools for becoming a better, more compassionate communicator at home, at work, and in the world Have you ever tried to tell someone what you want only to feel misunderstood and frustrated? Or hesitated to ask for what you needed because you didn&#8217;t want to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-we-say-matters-practicing-nonviolent-communication-ike-lasater-judith-hanson-lasater-abridged/">What We Say Matters : Practicing Nonviolent Communication &#8211; Ike Lasater, Judith Hanson Lasater (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Drawing from Buddhist and yogic precepts, this practical guide offers tools for becoming a better, more compassionate communicator at home, at work, and in the world     </p>
<p>                     Have you ever tried to tell someone what you want only to feel misunderstood and frustrated? Or hesitated to ask for what you needed because you didn&#8217;t want to burden the other person? Or been stuck in blame or anger that wouldn&#8217;t go away?     </p>
<p>                     Judith and Ike Lasater, long-term students of yoga and Buddhism, experienced dilemmas like these, too. Even though they had studied the yoga principle of satya (truth) and the Buddhist precept of right speech, it was not until they began practicing Marshall Rosenberg&#8217;s techniques of Nonviolent Communication (NVC) that they understood how to live satya and right speech.     </p>
<p>                     In What We Say Matters, Judith and Ike describe their journey through NVC and how speech becomes a spiritual practice based on giving and receiving with compassion&#8211;everywhere, all the time&#8211;whether at home, at work, or in the world. Their writing is deeply personal, punctuated by their recounts of trial and error, success and failure, laughter and challenge&#8211;even in writing this book! They guide you through an introduction to NVC with clear explanations, poignant examples, suggested exercises, and helpful resources. With practice, you&#8217;ll learn new ways to:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Extend empathy to yourself and others<br />
                    &#8211; Distinguish between feelings and needs<br />
                    &#8211; Make requests rather than demands<br />
                    &#8211; Choose connection over conflict<br />
                    &#8211; Create mutually satisfying outcomes</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-we-say-matters-practicing-nonviolent-communication-ike-lasater-judith-hanson-lasater-abridged/">What We Say Matters : Practicing Nonviolent Communication &#8211; Ike Lasater, Judith Hanson Lasater (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
