<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Genetic Engineering Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/genetic-engineering/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/genetic-engineering/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Genetic Engineering Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/genetic-engineering/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized  the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much more besides. In it, Dawkins extended the gene&#8217;s eye view to argue that the genes that sit within an organism have an<br />
                    influence that reaches out beyond the visible traits in that body &#8211; the phenotype &#8211; to the wider environment, which can include other individuals. So, for instance, the genes of the beaver drive it to gather twigs to produce the substantial physical structure of a dam; and the genes of the cuckoo chick produce effects that<br />
                    manipulate the behaviour of the host bird, making it nurture the intruder as one of its own. This notion of the extended phenotype has proved to be highly influential in the way we understand evolution and the natural world. It represents a key scientific contribution to evolutionary biology, and it continues to play an important role in research in the life sciences.    </p>
<p>                    The Extended Phenotype is a conceptually deep book that forms important reading for biologists and students. But Dawkins&#8217; clear exposition is accessible to all who are prepared to put in a little effort.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene<br />
                    Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the future of our species for fans of Homo Deus and The Gene.<br />
                    After 3.8 billion years humankind is about to start evolving by new rules&#8230;<br />
                    From leading geopolitical expert and technology futurist Jamie Metzl comes a groundbreaking exploration of the many ways genetic-engineering is shaking the core foundations of our lives-sex, war, love, and death.<br />
                    At the dawn of the genetics revolution, our DNA is becoming as readable, writable, and hackable as our information technology. But as humanity starts retooling our own genetic code, the choices we make today will be the difference between realizing breathtaking advances in human well-being and descending into a dangerous and potentially deadly genetic arms race.<br />
                    Enter the laboratories where scientists are turning science fiction into reality. Look towards a future where our deepest beliefs, morals, religions, and politics are challenged like never before and the very essence of what it means to be human is at play. When we can engineer our future children, massively extend our lifespans, build life from scratch, and recreate the plant and animal world, should we?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages. As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages.    </p>
<p>                    As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene  has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and in which organisms can be seen as vehicles for their replication. This imaginative, powerful, and stylistically brilliant work not only brought the insights of Neo-Darwinism to a wide audience, but galvanized the biology<br />
                    community, generating much debate and stimulating whole new areas of research. Forty years later, its insights remain as relevant today as on the day it was published.     </p>
<p>                    This 40th anniversary edition includes a new epilogue from the author discussing the continuing relevance of these ideas in evolutionary biology today, as well as the original prefaces and foreword, and extracts from early reviews.     </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
