<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Romance Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/romance-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/romance-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Romance Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/romance-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Captivated By You &#8211; Sylvia Day</title>
		<link>/captivated-by-you-sylvia-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/captivated-by-you-sylvia-day/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fourth novel in the #1 New York Times and #1 USA Today bestselling Crossfire series. Gideon calls me his angel, but he&#8217;s the miracle in my life. My gorgeous, wounded warrior, so determined to slay my demons while refusing to face his own. The vows we&#8217;d exchanged should have bound us tighter than blood [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/captivated-by-you-sylvia-day/">Captivated By You &#8211; Sylvia Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fourth novel in the #1 New York Times and #1 USA Today bestselling Crossfire series.     </p>
<p>                    Gideon calls me his angel, but he&#8217;s the miracle in my life. My gorgeous, wounded warrior, so determined to slay my demons while refusing to face his own.     </p>
<p>                     The vows we&#8217;d exchanged should have bound us tighter than blood and flesh. Instead they opened old wounds, exposed pain and insecurities, and lured bitter enemies out of the shadows. I felt him slipping from my grasp, my greatest fears becoming my reality, my love tested in ways I wasn&#8217;t sure I was strong enough to bear.     </p>
<p>                     At the brightest time in our lives, the darkness of his past encroached and threatened everything we&#8217;d worked so hard for. We faced a terrible choice: the familiar safety of the lives we&#8217;d had before each other or the fight for a future that suddenly seemed an impossible and hopeless dream&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/captivated-by-you-sylvia-day/">Captivated By You &#8211; Sylvia Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Angel Fire (Immortal Legacy Book 1) &#8211; Ella Sumers</title>
		<link>/angel-fire-immortal-legacy-book-1-ella-sumers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/angel-fire-immortal-legacy-book-1-ella-sumers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cadence Lightbringer, daughter of an archangel, has trained from birth to one day drink the Nectar of the gods and ascend to the angels’ ranks. She’s always been the perfect soldier. She’s always known exactly where her life is headed. Until she is assigned to a mission with Damiel Dragonsire, Master Interrogator of the Legion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/angel-fire-immortal-legacy-book-1-ella-sumers/">Angel Fire (Immortal Legacy Book 1) &#8211; Ella Sumers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cadence Lightbringer, daughter of an archangel, has trained from birth to one day drink the Nectar of the gods and ascend to the angels’ ranks. She’s always been the perfect soldier. She’s always known exactly where her life is headed.</p>
<p>Until she is assigned to a mission with Damiel Dragonsire, Master Interrogator of the Legion of Angels.</p>
<p>Powerful, paranoid, and brutally intelligent, Damiel has built up a reputation for hunting down each and every traitor hiding within the Legion’s ranks. And his latest suspect is Cadence. Convinced she is not the perfect soldier everyone believes her to be, he will stop at nothing to expose her.</p>
<p>Angel Fire is the first book in the Immortal Legacy series.</p>
<p>The Immortal Legacy series:<br />
Angel Fire<br />
Angel Fury<br />
Angel Fever</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/angel-fire-immortal-legacy-book-1-ella-sumers/">Angel Fire (Immortal Legacy Book 1) &#8211; Ella Sumers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vendetta in Death : An Eve Dallas Novel &#8211; J D Robb</title>
		<link>/vendetta-in-death-an-eve-dallas-novel-j-d-robb/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/vendetta-in-death-an-eve-dallas-novel-j-d-robb/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lieutenant Eve Dallas must keep the predator from becoming the prey in Vendetta in Death, the newest thriller from the #1 New York Times bestselling author J.D. Robb. She calls herself Lady Justice. And once she has chosen a man as her target, she turns herself into a tall blonde or a curvaceous redhead, makes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vendetta-in-death-an-eve-dallas-novel-j-d-robb/">Vendetta in Death : An Eve Dallas Novel &#8211; J D Robb</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lieutenant Eve Dallas must keep the predator from becoming the prey in Vendetta in Death, the newest thriller from the #1 New York Times bestselling author J.D. Robb.  </p>
<p>                    She calls herself Lady Justice. And once she has chosen a man as her target, she turns herself into a tall blonde or a curvaceous redhead, makes herself as alluring and seductive as possible to them. Once they are in her grasp, they are powerless. </p>
<p>                    The first victim is wealthy businessman Nigel McEnroy. His company&#8217;s human resources department has already paid out settlements to a couple of his young victims&#8211;but they don&#8217;t know that his crimes go far beyond workplace harassment. Lady Justice knows. And in one shocking night of brutality, she makes him pay a much steeper price. </p>
<p>                    Now Eve Dallas and her husband, Roarke, are combing through the evidence of McEnroy&#8217;s secret life. His compulsive need to record his misdeeds provides them with a wide range of suspects, but the true identity of Lady Justice remains elusive. It&#8217;s a challenging case, made even more difficult by McEnroy&#8217;s widow, who reacts to the investigation with fury, denial, and threats. Meanwhile, Lady Justice&#8217;s criminal crusade is escalating rapidly, and if Eve can&#8217;t stop this vigilante, there&#8217;s no telling how much blood may be spilled&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vendetta-in-death-an-eve-dallas-novel-j-d-robb/">Vendetta in Death : An Eve Dallas Novel &#8211; J D Robb</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</title>
		<link>/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD *************************** Memphis, Tennessee, 1939 Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story </p>
<p>                    OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD</p>
<p>                    THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD</p>
<p>                    ***************************</p>
<p>                    Memphis, Tennessee, 1939</p>
<p>                    Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. But when their father must rush their mother to the hospital one stormy night, Rill is left in charge, until strangers arrive in force. Wrenched from all that is familiar and thrown into a Tennessee Children&#8217;s Home Society orphanage, the Foss children are assured that they will soon be returned to their parents &#8211; but they quickly realize the dark truth&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Aiken, South Carolina, present day</p>
<p>                    Born into wealth and privilege, Avery Stafford seems to have it all: a successful career, a handsome fiance, and a lavish wedding on the horizon. But when Avery returns home to help her father weather a health crisis, a chance encounter leaves her with uncomfortable questions and compels her to take a journey through her family&#8217;s long-hidden history, on a path that will ultimately lead either to devastation or to redemption.</p>
<p>                    *********************</p>
<p>                    Based on one of America&#8217;s most notorious real-life scandals, in which Georgia Tann, director of a Memphis-based adoption organization, kidnapped and sold poor children to wealthy families all over the country, Before We Were Yours is a riveting, wrenching and ultimately uplifting global bestseller. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A tale of enduring power&#8217; Paula McLain</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is impossible not to get swept up in this near-perfect novel&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bared to You : A Crossfire Novel &#8211; Sylvia Day</title>
		<link>/bared-to-you-a-crossfire-novel-sylvia-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bared-to-you-a-crossfire-novel-sylvia-day/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bared to You by Sylvia Day is the first in the Crossfire trilogy featuring Gideon and Eva, two wounded souls who come together in an explosion of lust and passion as intoxicating as it is devastating &#8211; the perfect read for fans of bestselling erotic romance Fifty Shades of Grey by E.L. James. Our journey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bared-to-you-a-crossfire-novel-sylvia-day/">Bared to You : A Crossfire Novel &#8211; Sylvia Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bared to You by Sylvia Day is the first in the Crossfire trilogy featuring Gideon and Eva, two wounded souls who come together in an explosion of lust and passion as intoxicating as it is devastating &#8211; the perfect read for fans of bestselling erotic romance Fifty Shades of Grey by E.L. James. Our journey began in fire&#8230;Gideon Cross came into my life like lightning in the darkness &#8211; beautiful and brilliant, jagged and white hot. I was drawn to him as I&#8217;d never been to anything or anyone in my life. I craved his touch like a drug, even knowing it would weaken me. I was flawed and damaged, and he opened those cracks in me so easily&#8230;Gideon knew. He had demons of his own. And we would become the mirrors that reflected each other&#8217;s most private wounds &#8230;and desires. The bonds of his love transformed me, even as I prayed that the torment of our pasts didn&#8217;t tear us apart&#8230;Intensely romantic, darkly sensual and completely addictive, Bared to You will take you to the very limits of obsession &#8211; and beyond.<br />
                    Sylvia Day is the number one New York Times and number one international bestselling author of more than a dozen award-winning novels, which have been translated into thirty eight languages. She has been nominated for the Goodreads Choice Award for Best Author and her work has been honoured as Amazon&#8217;s Best of the Year in Romance. She has won the RT Book Reviews Reviewers&#8217; Choice Award and been nominated for the Romance Writers of America&#8217;s prestigious RITA award twice. The second novel in the series Reflected in You is available from Penguin in october. `Bared to You has an emotional feel similar to Fifty Shades of Grey&#8230;It is full of emotional angst, scorching love scenes, and a compelling story line.` (Dear Author). `While it is true that Bared to You has much in common with Fifty Shades of Grey, Bared to You is a more complete story, one that is better written. The characters are better developed and the story is far sexier. This is an erotic romance that should not be missed. It will make readers fall in love.` (Romance Novel News).<br />
                    `The secondary characters are just as flawed as Eva and Gideon, which makes Bared to You richer and more real to me than many of the contemporary books I&#8217;ve read in a while.` (Romance Junkies). `This is a sophisticated, provocative, titillating, highly erotic, sexually driven read and is extremely well done. I enjoyed Fifty Shades of Grey, but I loved Bared to You.` (Swept Away by Romance). `This book was just incredible. I couldn&#8217;t put it down! The sex was so hot and the relationship was so juicy that I just had to know what was coming next!` (Read Our Lips). `It literally blew my mind and after finishing it, I wasn&#8217;t able to stop thinking about it! &#8230;Bared to You is an intense novel full of hardships, heartbreak, overcoming obstacles, trust, and most of all &#8230;trying to find love in a relationship that may seem hopeless. I truly and wholeheartedly was amazed by this book.` (Happy Ever After). `Bared to You obliterates the competition with its real, emotionally intense characters that deal with pain and pleasure with honesty`. (Joyfully Reviewed).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bared-to-you-a-crossfire-novel-sylvia-day/">Bared to You : A Crossfire Novel &#8211; Sylvia Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Faefever : Fever Series Book 3 &#8211; Karen Marie Moning</title>
		<link>/faefever-fever-series-book-3-karen-marie-moning/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/faefever-fever-series-book-3-karen-marie-moning/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER He calls me his Queen of the Night. I&#8217;d die for him. I&#8217;d kill for him, too. When MacKayla Lane receives a page torn from her dead sister&#8217;s journal, she is stunned by Alina&#8217;s desperate words. And now MacKayla knows that her sister&#8217;s killer is close. But evil is closer. And [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/faefever-fever-series-book-3-karen-marie-moning/">Faefever : Fever Series Book 3 &#8211; Karen Marie Moning</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    He calls me his Queen of the Night. I&#8217;d die for him. I&#8217;d kill for him, too. </p>
<p>                    When MacKayla Lane receives a page torn from her dead sister&#8217;s journal, she is stunned by Alina&#8217;s desperate words. And now MacKayla knows that her sister&#8217;s killer is close. But evil is closer. And suddenly the sidhe-seer is on the hunt: For answers. For revenge. And for an ancient book of dark magic so evil that it corrupts anyone who touches it. </p>
<p>                    Mac&#8217;s quest for the Sinsar Dubh takes her into the mean, shapeshifting streets of Dublin, with a suspicious cop on her tail. Forced into a dangerous triangle of alliance with V&#8217;lane, a lethal Fae prince, and Jericho Barrons, a man of deadly secrets, Mac is soon locked in a battle for her body, mind, and soul. </p>
<p>                    Look for all of Karen Marie Moning&#8217;s sensational Fever novels:<br />
                     DARKFEVER BLOODFEVER FAEFEVER DREAMFEVER SHADOWFEVER ICED BURNED FEVERBORN FEVERSONG</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/faefever-fever-series-book-3-karen-marie-moning/">Faefever : Fever Series Book 3 &#8211; Karen Marie Moning</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Collector &#8211; Nora Roberts</title>
		<link>/the-collector-nora-roberts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-collector-nora-roberts/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A thrilling novel of crime and passion from Nora Roberts &#8211; the world&#8217;s greatest storyteller Lila Emerson is fascinated by other people&#8217;s lives. As a house-sitter, she loves looking after the glamorous homes she could never afford herself. And as a writer, she enjoys dreaming up stories for the people she sees from her window. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-collector-nora-roberts/">The Collector &#8211; Nora Roberts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A thrilling novel of crime and passion from Nora Roberts &#8211; the world&#8217;s greatest storyteller    </p>
<p>                    Lila Emerson is fascinated by other people&#8217;s lives. As a house-sitter, she loves looking after the glamorous homes she could never afford herself. And as a writer, she enjoys dreaming up stories for the people she sees from her window. But then one day she witnesses something only too real &#8211; the shocking murder of a young woman living across the street in New York. Now Lila is in mortal danger from an audacious, single-minded assassin who kills for profit and for pleasure.    </p>
<p>                    With the police following a false lead, Lila&#8217;s only hope is to team up with Ashton Archer, an artist with his own complicated reasons for getting involved. Lila wants to trust the passionate, quick-witted Ash &#8211; but is she letting her feelings blind her to his motives? Either way, she will never watch from the sidelines again&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-collector-nora-roberts/">The Collector &#8211; Nora Roberts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Max &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/max-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/max-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The ice is a cold mistress. As the league&#8217;s most eligible goalie, Max Fournier has access to his fair share of willing puck bunnies, but right now he&#8217;s more interested in bringing home another championship than a one-night stand. A romantic at heart, Max believes in love; he&#8217;s just not great at relationships. So when [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/max-sawyer-bennett/">Max &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ice is a cold mistress. As the league&#8217;s most eligible goalie, Max Fournier has access to his fair share of willing puck bunnies, but right now he&#8217;s more interested in bringing home another championship than a one-night stand. A romantic at heart, Max believes in love; he&#8217;s just not great at relationships. So when he finally meets a nice girl who&#8217;s not blinded by his celebrity, he&#8217;s feeling the heat&#8211;and the pressure to save her from herself. Between working two jobs and raising her sister&#8217;s kids, Julianne Bradley doesn&#8217;t have time for sports&#8211;or men. All she knows about Max is that he&#8217;s the sexiest customer to ever grace her gas-station counter. And he sees past her tired eyes and makes Jules yearn for things she can&#8217;t have: a glamorous fling, a passionate lover, and the time to enjoy both. Max makes her feel like Cinderella, even though Jules has enough baggage to crush a glass slipper. Luckily, he&#8217;s no prince&#8211;only a fierce competitor determined to win her heart.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/max-sawyer-bennett/">Max &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mortal Instruments 4: City of Fallen Angels &#8211; Cassandra Clare</title>
		<link>/the-mortal-instruments-4-city-of-fallen-angels-cassandra-clare/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's General Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sci Fi Books for Kids]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mortal-instruments-4-city-of-fallen-angels-cassandra-clare/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fourth in Cassandra Clare&#8217;s internationally bestselling Mortal Instruments series about the Shadowhunters. Discover more secrets about the Shadowhunters as they fight to protect the world from demons in the fourth book in the internationally bestselling series. To love is to destroy&#8230; The Mortal War is over, and Clary Fray is home in New York, excited [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mortal-instruments-4-city-of-fallen-angels-cassandra-clare/">The Mortal Instruments 4: City of Fallen Angels &#8211; Cassandra Clare</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fourth in Cassandra Clare&#8217;s internationally bestselling Mortal Instruments series about the Shadowhunters.    </p>
<p>                    Discover more secrets about the Shadowhunters as they fight to protect the world from demons in the fourth book in the internationally bestselling series. To love is to destroy&#8230; The Mortal War is over, and Clary Fray is home in New York, excited about all the possibilities before her. She&#8217;s training to become a Shadowhunter and &#8211; most importantly of all &#8211; she can finally call Jace her boyfriend. But her happiness has come at a price&#8230; This edition contains a map and a new foreword by Cassandra Clare. Read all the sensational books in The Shadowhunter Chronicles: The Mortal Instruments, The Infernal Devices, Tales from the Shadowhunter Academy, The Bane Chronicles, The Dark Artifices, The Last Hours and The Shadowhunter&#8217;s Codex.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mortal-instruments-4-city-of-fallen-angels-cassandra-clare/">The Mortal Instruments 4: City of Fallen Angels &#8211; Cassandra Clare</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strange Fascination : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</title>
		<link>/strange-fascination-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Witchcraft & Wicca]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/strange-fascination-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s summer in Adders Fork. The sun is out, the sky is blue and things are going swimmingly for Rosie Strange, thank you very much. The Essex Witch Museum has been relaunched with a new Ursula Cadence wing and picnic grounds. Then developers roll into the sleepy village to widen the road. When the centuries-old [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strange-fascination-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/">Strange Fascination : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s summer in Adders Fork. The sun is out, the sky is blue and things are going swimmingly for Rosie Strange, thank you very much. The Essex Witch Museum has been relaunched with a new Ursula Cadence wing and picnic grounds.     </p>
<p>                    Then developers roll into the sleepy village to widen the road. When the centuries-old Blackly Be boulder, said to mark the grave of a notorious witch but now in the car park of the Seven Stars, is moved, all hell breaks out. Within hours a slew of peculiar phenomena descends and, when a severed head is discovered atop the boulder, the locals can take no more and storm the Museum to demand someone take action.    </p>
<p>                    Can Rosie and Sam unravel the mystery? And what of the ancient treasure that could drastically change someone&#8217;s fortunes and offer a motive for murder?    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strange-fascination-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/">Strange Fascination : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marek &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/marek-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/marek-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Marek Fabritis is used to delivering blows, not receiving them. But when he gets tipped off by an anonymous email about his ex-girlfriend, the news leaves him ice cold-and it&#8217;s not because Gracen Moore is getting married to a total jerk. It&#8217;s the fact that Marek has a three-year-old daughter he never knew about. Now [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/marek-sawyer-bennett/">Marek &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Marek Fabritis is used to delivering blows, not receiving them. But when he gets tipped off by an anonymous email about his ex-girlfriend, the news leaves him ice cold-and it&#8217;s not because Gracen Moore is getting married to a total jerk. It&#8217;s the fact that Marek has a three-year-old daughter he never knew about. Now he&#8217;s going back home, not to play knight in shining armor but to make damn sure that no man takes what&#8217;s his. For the first time, there might be something more important than hockey. Gracen Moore has always loved Marek. That&#8217;s why she let him go, so he could pursue a career in the NHL. And that&#8217;s why she never told him about Lilly. Only now does Gracen realize that she made an unforgivable mistake. But is that any reason for Marek to crash her wedding and make an epic scene? If the spark that still smolders between them is to be trusted, maybe. Still, Gracen&#8217;s not getting her hopes up. Because she knows better than anyone that appearances aren&#8217;t always what they seem . . . Contains mature themes.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/marek-sawyer-bennett/">Marek &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Roman &#8211; Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/roman-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/roman-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a league full of troublemakers, Cold Fury defenseman Roman Sýkora stands out&#8211;at least when it comes to negative publicity. When he&#8217;s not chilling in the penalty box, the sizzling Czech skate demon is racking up tabloid headlines for his scandalous behavior with the ladies. But now Roman&#8217;s feeling the burn from management to clean [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/roman-sawyer-bennett/">Roman &#8211; Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a league full of troublemakers, Cold Fury defenseman Roman Sýkora stands out&#8211;at least when it comes to negative publicity. When he&#8217;s not chilling in the penalty box, the sizzling Czech skate demon is racking up tabloid headlines for his scandalous behavior with the ladies. But now Roman&#8217;s feeling the burn from management to clean up his act, or else. Luckily he&#8217;s got an enticing distraction: a fun-loving barista who plays the ukulele and brings out a side of Roman he didn&#8217;t know he had. Lexi Robertson came to Raleigh, North Carolina, to finally meet her father, Brian Brannon, and her half sister, Gray, both of whom work in the Cold Fury&#8217;s front office. That&#8217;s where she first meets sexy, intimidating Roman&#8211;who&#8217;s really a big softie at heart. As one relationship takes off, another begins: Brian seems to be clicking with Lexi&#8217;s boss at the coffee shop. But when the friction between Roman and her new family heats up, Lexi wonders whether she&#8217;s a pawn in their game. Feeling hurt and foolish, Lexi&#8217;s ready to quit while she&#8217;s ahead. Trouble is, Roman&#8217;s not ready to quit on her.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/roman-sawyer-bennett/">Roman &#8211; Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Garrett : A Cold Fury Hockey Novel &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/garrett-a-cold-fury-hockey-novel-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/garrett-a-cold-fury-hockey-novel-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Carolina Cold Fury star Garrett Samuelson never wants to miss out on a single minute of fun. Whether he&#8217;s playing hockey, hanging out with friends, or walking the red carpet with a new date on his arm, he lives every day to the fullest. When he meets Olivia Case, he sees someone who&#8217;s exactly his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/garrett-a-cold-fury-hockey-novel-sawyer-bennett/">Garrett : A Cold Fury Hockey Novel &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Carolina Cold Fury star Garrett Samuelson never wants to miss out on a single minute of fun. Whether he&#8217;s playing hockey, hanging out with friends, or walking the red carpet with a new date on his arm, he lives every day to the fullest. When he meets Olivia Case, he sees someone who&#8217;s exactly his type&#8211;confident, sexy, and smart. But the more he pursues her, the more Garrett shares a side of himself that other women don&#8217;t normally get to see. Olivia has been keeping a secret. She&#8217;s undergoing treatment for some serious medical issues, and she doesn&#8217;t have time for a relationship with no guarantees&#8211;especially one with a hot-as-sin womanizer who won&#8217;t take no for an answer. But as she gets to know the real Garrett, Olivia can&#8217;t help falling for him . . . hard. To reveal the truth would mean risking everything&#8211;but you can&#8217;t score without taking the tough shots.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/garrett-a-cold-fury-hockey-novel-sawyer-bennett/">Garrett : A Cold Fury Hockey Novel &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shadow Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/shadow-game-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shadow-game-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan plunges readers into the darkest recesses of the mind as a man and a woman discover the terrifying power-and the forbidden passion-that could destroy them both in the first novel in the GhostWalker series. The brainchild of renowned scientist Peter Whitney and his brilliant daughter, Lily, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shadow-game-christine-feehan/">Shadow Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan plunges readers into the darkest recesses of the mind as a man and a woman discover the terrifying power-and the forbidden passion-that could destroy them both in the first novel in the GhostWalker series.    </p>
<p>                    The brainchild of renowned scientist Peter Whitney and his brilliant daughter, Lily, the GhostWalker experiment was created to enhance the psychic abilities of an elite squadron, transforming their natural telekenetic powers into a unique military weapon. But something has gone wrong&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    In the isolated underground, the men have been dying, victims of bizarre accidents. Captain Ryland Miller knows he is next. When Dr. Whitney himself is murdered, Ryland has only one person left to trust: the beautiful Lily. Possessed of an uncanny sixth sense herself, Lily shares Ryland&#8217;s every new fear, every betrayal, every growing suspicion, and every passionate beat of the heart.     </p>
<p>                    Together, they will be drawn deeper into the labyrinth of her father&#8217;s past&#8230;and closer to a secret that someone would kill to keep hidden.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shadow-game-christine-feehan/">Shadow Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Hills &#8211; Nora Roberts</title>
		<link>/black-hills-nora-roberts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-hills-nora-roberts/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this #1 New York Times bestseller, Nora Roberts takes readers deep into the rugged hills of South Dakota, where the shadows keep secrets, hunters stalk the land, and a friendship matures into something more&#8230;. Cooper Sullivan spent the summers of his youth on his grandparents&#8217; South Dakota ranch, sharing innocent games and stolen kisses [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-hills-nora-roberts/">Black Hills &#8211; Nora Roberts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this #1 New York Times bestseller, Nora Roberts takes readers deep into the rugged hills of South Dakota, where the shadows keep secrets, hunters stalk the land, and a friendship matures into something more&#8230;.    </p>
<p>                    Cooper Sullivan spent the summers of his youth on his grandparents&#8217; South Dakota ranch, sharing innocent games and stolen kisses with the neighbor girl, Lil Chance. Now, twelve years after they last walked together hand in hand, fate has brought them back to the Black Hills.    </p>
<p>                    Though the memory of Coop&#8217;s touch still haunts her, Lil has let nothing stop her dream of opening the Chance Wildlife Refuge, but something-or someone-has been keeping a close watch. When small pranks and acts of destruction escalate into a heartless attack on Lil&#8217;s beloved cougar, memories of an unsolved murder have Coop springing to action to keep Lil safe.     </p>
<p>                    Both of them know the natural dangers that lurk in the wild landscape of the Black Hills. But a killer of twisted and unnatural instincts has singled them out as prey&#8230;.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-hills-nora-roberts/">Black Hills &#8211; Nora Roberts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hawke &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/hawke-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hawke-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Off the ice, elite defenseman Hawke Therrien enjoys his fair share of booze and good times. And why shouldn&#8217;t he? He&#8217;s worked his way up from the minor leagues and made himself a star. The only thing Hawke misses from that life is the pierced, tattooed free spirit who broke his heart without so much [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hawke-sawyer-bennett/">Hawke &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Off the ice, elite defenseman Hawke Therrien enjoys his fair share of booze and good times. And why shouldn&#8217;t he? He&#8217;s worked his way up from the minor leagues and made himself a star. The only thing Hawke misses from that life is the pierced, tattooed free spirit who broke his heart without so much as an explanation. She&#8217;s almost unrecognizable when she walks back into his life seven years later, except for the look in her eyes that feels like a punch to the gut. Vale Campbell isn&#8217;t the same girl she was at twenty. As crazy as she was about Hawke, her reckless behavior and out-of-control drinking were starting to scare her. She had to clean up her act, and that would never happen with Hawke around. Cutting him loose was the hardest thing Vale ever had to do&#8211;until now. Because she&#8217;s still crazy about Hawke, and if he could ever learn to forgive her, they just might have a future together.Contains mature themes.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hawke-sawyer-bennett/">Hawke &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mortal Instruments 6: City of Heavenly Fire &#8211; Cassandra Clare</title>
		<link>/the-mortal-instruments-6-city-of-heavenly-fire-cassandra-clare/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's General Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books for Teenagers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mortal-instruments-6-city-of-heavenly-fire-cassandra-clare/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shadowhunters and demons square off for the sixth and final book in the internationally bestselling Mortal Instruments series from Cassandra Clare. Discover more secrets about the Shadowhunters as they fight to protect the world from demons in the final book in the internationally bestselling series. Darkness has descended on the Shadowhunter world. Clary, Jace, Simon, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mortal-instruments-6-city-of-heavenly-fire-cassandra-clare/">The Mortal Instruments 6: City of Heavenly Fire &#8211; Cassandra Clare</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shadowhunters and demons square off for the sixth and final book in the internationally bestselling Mortal Instruments series from Cassandra Clare.    </p>
<p>                    Discover more secrets about the Shadowhunters as they fight to protect the world from demons in the final book in the internationally bestselling series. Darkness has descended on the Shadowhunter world. Clary, Jace, Simon, and their friends band together to fight the greatest evil they have ever faced&#8230; This edition contains a map and a new foreword by Cassandra Clare. Read all the sensational books in The Shadowhunter Chronicles: The Mortal Instruments, The Infernal Devices, Tales from the Shadowhunter Academy, The Bane Chronicles, The Dark Artifices, The Last Hours and The Shadowhunter&#8217;s Codex.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mortal-instruments-6-city-of-heavenly-fire-cassandra-clare/">The Mortal Instruments 6: City of Heavenly Fire &#8211; Cassandra Clare</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Grave on the Right &#8211; Darynda Jones</title>
		<link>/first-grave-on-the-right-darynda-jones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-grave-on-the-right-darynda-jones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>First Grave on the Right is the smashing, award-winning debut novel that introduces Charley Davidson: part-time private investigator and full-time Grim Reaper. Charley sees dead people. That&#8217;s right, she sees dead people. And it&#8217;s her job to convince them to go into the light. But when these very dead people have died under less than [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-grave-on-the-right-darynda-jones/">First Grave on the Right &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First Grave on the Right is the smashing, award-winning debut novel that introduces Charley Davidson: part-time private investigator and full-time Grim Reaper.     </p>
<p>                    Charley sees dead people. That&#8217;s right, she sees dead people. And it&#8217;s her job to convince them to go into the light. But when these very dead people have died under less than ideal circumstances (i.e., murder), sometimes they want Charley to bring the bad guys to justice. Complicating matters are the intensely hot dreams she&#8217;s been having about an Entity who has been following her all her life&#8230;and it turns out he might not be dead after all. In fact, he might be something else entirely.     </p>
<p>                    This is a thrilling debut novel from Darynda Jones, an exciting newcomer to the world of paranormal romantic suspense.     </p>
<p>                    First Grave on the Right is the winner of the 2012 Rita Award for Best First Book.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-grave-on-the-right-darynda-jones/">First Grave on the Right &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Street Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/street-game-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/street-game-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan goes beyond the boundaries of paranormal romance as two lovers take to the streets to play the most dangerous game of all. For Mack McKinley and his team of GhostWalker killing machines, urban warfare is an art. But despite a hard-won knowledge of the San Francisco streets, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/street-game-christine-feehan/">Street Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan goes beyond the boundaries of paranormal romance as two lovers take to the streets to play the most dangerous game of all.     </p>
<p>                    For Mack McKinley and his team of GhostWalker killing machines, urban warfare is an art. But despite a hard-won knowledge of the San Francisco streets, Mack knows from experience that too many things can still go wrong. Danger is just another part of the game-and now he&#8217;s come face-to-face with a woman who can play just as tough.     </p>
<p>                    Jaimie is a woman with a sapphire stare so potent it can destroy a man. Years ago she and Mack had a history-volatile, erotic, and electric. Then she vanished. Now she&#8217;s walked back into Mack&#8217;s life as a spy with too many secrets for her own good. Against all odds, she&#8217;s hooking up with Mack one more time to take on an enemy that could destroy them both, or bring them back together in one hot, no-holds-barred adrenaline rush.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/street-game-christine-feehan/">Street Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brighter Than The Sun : A KGI Novel &#8211; Maya Banks</title>
		<link>/brighter-than-the-sun-a-kgi-novel-maya-banks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brighter-than-the-sun-a-kgi-novel-maya-banks/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Searing action and passion ignite the latest New York Times bestselling KGI novel from the author of Darkest Before Dawn. The Kelly Group International (KGI): A super-elite, top secret, family-run business. Qualifications: High intelligence, rock-hard body, military background. Mission: Hostage/kidnap victim recovery. Intelligence gathering. Handling jobs the U.S. government can&#8217;t&#8230; As the last unattached member [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brighter-than-the-sun-a-kgi-novel-maya-banks/">Brighter Than The Sun : A KGI Novel &#8211; Maya Banks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Searing action and passion ignite the latest New York Times bestselling KGI novel from the author of Darkest Before Dawn.  </p>
<p>                     The Kelly Group International (KGI):  A super-elite, top secret, family-run business.<br />
                     Qualifications:  High intelligence, rock-hard body, military background.<br />
                     Mission:  Hostage/kidnap victim recovery. Intelligence gathering.<br />
                     Handling jobs the U.S. government can&#8217;t&#8230; </p>
<p>                     As the last unattached member of the Kelly clan, Joe is more than ready to risk life and limb on any mission he&#8217;s assigned to, but when it comes to love, he&#8217;ll keep his distance. He&#8217;s content to watch his brothers become thoroughly domesticated. </p>
<p>                     Zoe&#8217;s had nothing but heartbreak in her life, and she&#8217;s determined to start over with a completely new identity, thanks to her college friend, Rusty Kelly. But it&#8217;s the gorgeous smile and tender words of Joe Kelly that begin to weaken her resolve to never risk her heart again. And Joe will have to put everything on the line to save Zoe, when secrets of her past resurface&#8211;and threaten to tear them apart&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brighter-than-the-sun-a-kgi-novel-maya-banks/">Brighter Than The Sun : A KGI Novel &#8211; Maya Banks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Night Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/night-game-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/night-game-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this &#8220;suspenseful&#8230;captivating&#8221; (Publishers Weekly) novel in GhostWalker series, #1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan tracks the desperate steps of a wanted woman-betrayed, avenging, and dangerously irresistible&#8230; Gator Fontenot of the Special Forces paranormal squad can&#8217;t refuse an urgent request to save the elusive Iris &#8220;Flame&#8221; Johnson, a victim of the same horrific [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/night-game-christine-feehan/">Night Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this &#8220;suspenseful&#8230;captivating&#8221; (Publishers Weekly) novel in GhostWalker series, #1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan tracks the desperate steps of a wanted woman-betrayed, avenging, and dangerously irresistible&#8230;    </p>
<p>                     Gator Fontenot of the Special Forces paranormal squad can&#8217;t refuse an urgent request to save the elusive Iris &#8220;Flame&#8221; Johnson, a victim of the same horrific experiments that warped Gator. Now unleashed, she&#8217;s a red-haired weapon of unimaginable destructive powers, a walking time bomb bent on revenge in the sultry bayous of New Orleans, and hunted by a shadowy assassin. It&#8217;s Gator&#8217;s job to reel Flame in. But can two people haunted by violent betrayals trust the passion that soon ignites between them? Or is one of them just playing another seductive and deadly night game?    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/night-game-christine-feehan/">Night Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eleventh Grave in Moonlight &#8211; Darynda Jones</title>
		<link>/eleventh-grave-in-moonlight-darynda-jones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eleventh-grave-in-moonlight-darynda-jones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An absolute must read.&#8217; J.R. Ward, No.1 New York Times bestselling author of the Black Dagger Brotherhood series. &#8216;The grim reaper gets a shiny cook makeover in Jones&#8217;s blazing hot debut&#8230; will appeal to fans of MaryJanice Davidson and Janet Evanovich.&#8217; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly &#8216;What&#8217;s better than a bad-ass girl grim reaper who keeps us safe [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eleventh-grave-in-moonlight-darynda-jones/">Eleventh Grave in Moonlight &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An absolute must read.&#8217; J.R. Ward, No.1 New York Times bestselling author of the Black Dagger Brotherhood series. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The grim reaper gets a shiny cook makeover in Jones&#8217;s blazing hot debut&#8230; will appeal to fans of MaryJanice Davidson and Janet Evanovich.&#8217; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly </p>
<p>                    &#8216;What&#8217;s better than a bad-ass girl grim reaper who keeps us safe from hell hounds and demons? (The answer is obviously nothing.)&#8217; RT Book Reviews </p>
<p>                    A typical day in the life of Charley Davidson involves cheating husbands, missing people, errant wives, philandering business owners, and oh yeah . . . demons, hell hounds, evil gods, and dead people. Lots and lots of dead people. </p>
<p>                    As a part time Private Investigator and full-time Grim Reaper, Charley has to balance the good, the bad, the undead, and those who want her dead. </p>
<p>                    Now Charley is learning to make peace with the fact that she is a goddess with all kinds of power and that her own daughter has been born to save the world from total destruction. The forces of hell are determined to see Charley banished forever to the darkest corners of another dimension but with the son of Satan himself as her husband, maybe Charley can find a way to have her happily ever after after all.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I am furiously envious of Darynda Jones and rue the day she came up with this concept, damn her eyes. First Grave On The Right kidnapped me from the first paragraph, and didn&#8217;t let go until the exceedingly yummy conclusion.&#8217; MaryJanice Davidson, New York Times bestselling author of the Undead series</p>
<p>                    &#8216;First Grave on the Right is smart, sharp and wickedly entertaining. Grab this one.&#8217; Jayne Ann Krentz, New York Times besselling author of Fires Up</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eleventh-grave-in-moonlight-darynda-jones/">Eleventh Grave in Moonlight &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Every Breath : A captivating story of enduring love from the author of The Notebook &#8211; Nicholas Sparks</title>
		<link>/every-breath-a-captivating-story-of-enduring-love-from-the-author-of-the-notebook-nicholas-sparks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/every-breath-a-captivating-story-of-enduring-love-from-the-author-of-the-notebook-nicholas-sparks/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are times when destiny and love collide. This story is one of them. From the number one bestselling author of The Notebook and Two by Two comes an unforgettable tale of enduring love . . . Hope Anderson is at a crossroads. After six years with her boyfriend, she is no longer sure what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-breath-a-captivating-story-of-enduring-love-from-the-author-of-the-notebook-nicholas-sparks/">Every Breath : A captivating story of enduring love from the author of The Notebook &#8211; Nicholas Sparks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are times when destiny and love collide. This story is one of them.</p>
<p>                    From the number one bestselling author of The Notebook and Two by Two comes an unforgettable tale of enduring love . . .</p>
<p>                    Hope Anderson is at a crossroads. After six years with her boyfriend, she is no longer sure what she wants, and when her father becomes ill she heads to her family&#8217;s cottage at Sunset Beach in North Carolina to make some difficult decisions.</p>
<p>                    Tru Walls has been summoned across an ocean from where he was born and raised in Zimbabwe by a letter from a man claiming to be his father. In journeying to Sunset Beach, Tru hopes to unravel the mystery surrounding his mother&#8217;s life, but the letter will lead him in an unexpected direction. </p>
<p>                    When these two strangers&#8217; paths cross, their chance encounter sets in motion a heart-breaking story &#8211; one that will transcend decades, continents and the workings of fate. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A new Nicholas Sparks novel is a major event . . . [Every Breath] is deeply moving and I was captivated . . . fans are going to adore this latest, beautifully written tale&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[Every Breath is a] powerful read that tugs at the heartstrings&#8217; OK! Magazine </p>
<p>                    Praise for multi-million-copy bestseller phenomenon, Nicholas Sparks:</p>
<p>                    &#8216;When it comes to tales about love, Nicholas Sparks is one of the undisputed kings&#8217; Heat</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An absorbing page-turner&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fiercely romantic and touching tale&#8217; Heat on The Longest Ride</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An A-grade romantic read&#8217; OK! on Safe Haven</p>
<p>                    &#8216;This one won&#8217;t leave a dry eye&#8217; Daily Mirror on The Lucky One</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-breath-a-captivating-story-of-enduring-love-from-the-author-of-the-notebook-nicholas-sparks/">Every Breath : A captivating story of enduring love from the author of The Notebook &#8211; Nicholas Sparks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cowboys Like Us &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</title>
		<link>/cowboys-like-us-vicki-lewis-thompson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Westerns]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cowboys-like-us-vicki-lewis-thompson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When love means saying goodbye&#8230; After a career ending sports injury, Logan Carswell retreats to a small Wyoming town to heal mind and body. But his short-term solution hits a snag when he meets sexy bartender Caro Davis. She&#8217;s everything he&#8217;s ever wanted. A generous lover. A loyal friend. But she&#8217;s firmly planted in a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cowboys-like-us-vicki-lewis-thompson/">Cowboys Like Us &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When love means saying goodbye&#8230;</p>
<p>                    After a career ending sports injury, Logan Carswell retreats to a small Wyoming town to heal mind and body. But his short-term solution hits a snag when he meets sexy bartender Caro Davis. She&#8217;s everything he&#8217;s ever wanted. A generous lover. A loyal friend. But she&#8217;s firmly planted in a place he&#8217;ll never call home.</p>
<p>                    Tending bar at the Spirits and Spurs suits Caro just fine. She&#8217;s a small-town girl who isn&#8217;t about to leave Shoshone or her ailing grandmother. Not even for the kindest, hottest man she&#8217;s ever met. He&#8217;s ditched his big-city clothes for cowboy duds, but the change is temporary. And every moment they share brings her closer to heartbreak&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Saddle up for the sixth book in the Sons of Chance series! Steamy western romances from the NYT bestselling author who brought you The McGavin Brothers of Eagles Nest, Montana. If you like sexy cowboys, charming small towns, and laugh-out-loud adventures, you&#8217;ll love the Sons of Chance. Pick up your copy of Cowboys Like Us today!</p>
<p>                    Sons of Chance</p>
<p>                    WHAT A COWBOY WANTS (Book 1)</p>
<p>                    A COWBOY&#8217;S TEMPTATION (Book 2)</p>
<p>                    CLAIMED BY THE COWBOY (Book 3)</p>
<p>                    SHOULD&#8217;VE BEEN A COWBOY (Book 4)</p>
<p>                    COWBOY UP (Book 5)</p>
<p>                    COWBOYS LIKE US (Book 6)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cowboys-like-us-vicki-lewis-thompson/">Cowboys Like Us &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finale : Caraval Series Book 3 &#8211; Stephanie Garber</title>
		<link>/finale-caraval-series-book-3-stephanie-garber/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/finale-caraval-series-book-3-stephanie-garber/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sunday Times and #1 New York Times bestselling author Stephanie Garber takes us back to the magical world of Caraval, where Scarlett and Tella Dragna must fight for their happy endings . . . Caraval is over, but perhaps the greatest game of all has begun &#8211; with lives, empires, and hearts all at stake. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finale-caraval-series-book-3-stephanie-garber/">Finale : Caraval Series Book 3 &#8211; Stephanie Garber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sunday Times and #1 New York Times bestselling author Stephanie Garber takes us back to the magical world of Caraval, where Scarlett and Tella Dragna must fight for their happy endings . . .</p>
<p>                    Caraval is over, but perhaps the greatest game of all has begun &#8211; with lives, empires, and hearts all at stake.</p>
<p>                    There are no spectators this time: only those who will win, and those who will lose everything. Welcome, welcome to the Caraval&#8217;s Finale.</p>
<p>                    All games must come to an end . . .</p>
<p>                    *** Pre-order Stephanie Garber&#8217;s magical new fantasy Once Upon A Broken Heart, now! ***</p>
<p>                    Further praise for the Caraval Series:</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Enchanting . . . [I] never wanted to come out&#8217; Sabaa Tahir</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Immersive and engaging . . . destined to capture imaginations&#8217; Kirkus</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Extravagantly imaginative and enchanting . . . Pure magic and escapism&#8217; Cecelia Ahern</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An enchanting carnival of dreams and nightmares . . . beautifully and vividly written&#8217; SciFi Now</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finale-caraval-series-book-3-stephanie-garber/">Finale : Caraval Series Book 3 &#8211; Stephanie Garber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reed &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/reed-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reed-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No one plays like Reed Olson, whether it&#8217;s hockey season or not. After back-to-back NHL championships, he&#8217;s craving a little R&#038;R. Reed leans to a specific type&#8211;blond, busty, and interested&#8211;and fortunately he has a little black book full of options. So why is it he can&#8217;t stop dreaming about the new girl who just moved [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reed-sawyer-bennett/">Reed &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No one plays like Reed Olson, whether it&#8217;s hockey season or not. After back-to-back NHL championships, he&#8217;s craving a little R&#038;R. Reed leans to a specific type&#8211;blond, busty, and interested&#8211;and fortunately he has a little black book full of options. So why is it he can&#8217;t stop dreaming about the new girl who just moved in next door? A certified brainiac, she seems to want nothing to do with the hard-bodied athlete. Josie Ives desperately needs something her celebrity neighbor obviously doesn&#8217;t: solitude. Reed is everything she imagined&#8211;a little too good-looking, with a body that puts Greek gods to shame. But she didn&#8217;t expect he would also be funny and charming. Josie knows she&#8217;s the opposite of his type, and that&#8217;s fine with her. Still, the chemistry between them is undeniable. Their newfound friendship certainly has its benefits, but she&#8217;s starting to wonder if opposites really do attract. Contains mature themes.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reed-sawyer-bennett/">Reed &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ryker &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/ryker-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ryker-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The stakes have never been higher for Carolina Cold Fury goalie Ryker Evans. With his contract running out, he&#8217;s got a year left to prove that he&#8217;s still at the top of his game. And since his wife left him, Ryker has been balancing life as a pro hockey star and a single parent to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ryker-sawyer-bennett/">Ryker &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The stakes have never been higher for Carolina Cold Fury goalie Ryker Evans. With his contract running out, he&#8217;s got a year left to prove that he&#8217;s still at the top of his game. And since his wife left him, Ryker has been balancing life as a pro hockey star and a single parent to two daughters. Management is waiting for him to screw up. The fans are ready to pounce. Everybody&#8217;s taking dirty shots-except for the fiery redhead whose faith in Ryker gives him a fresh start. As the league&#8217;s only female general manager, Gray Brannon has learned not to mix business with pleasure. And yet even this tough, talented career woman can&#8217;t help breaking her own rules as she gives Ryker everything she&#8217;s got. She hopes that their hot streak will last forever, but with Ryker&#8217;s conniving ex plotting to reclaim her man, the pressure&#8217;s on Gray to step up and save a tender new love before it&#8217;s too late.Contains mature themes.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ryker-sawyer-bennett/">Ryker &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rich People Problems : A Novel &#8211; Kevin Kwan</title>
		<link>/rich-people-problems-a-novel-kevin-kwan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rich-people-problems-a-novel-kevin-kwan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of Crazy Rich Asians (the basis for the acclaimed major motion picture) and China Rich Girlfriend, here is the uproarious conclusion to the Crazy Rich Asians trilogy. Book Three of the Crazy Rich Asians Trilogy When Nicholas Young hears that his grandmother, Su Yi, is on her deathbed, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rich-people-problems-a-novel-kevin-kwan/">Rich People Problems : A Novel &#8211; Kevin Kwan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of Crazy Rich Asians (the basis for the acclaimed major motion picture) and China Rich Girlfriend, here is the uproarious conclusion to the Crazy Rich Asians trilogy.</p>
<p>                    Book Three of the Crazy Rich Asians Trilogy </p>
<p>                    When Nicholas Young hears that his grandmother, Su Yi, is on her deathbed, he rushes to be by her bedside&#8211;but he&#8217;s not alone. The entire Shang-Young clan has convened from all corners of the globe to stake claim on their matriarch&#8217;s massive fortune. With each family member vying to inherit Tyersall Park&#8211;a trophy estate on 64 prime acres in the heart of Singapore&#8211;Nicholas&#8217;s childhood home turns into a hotbed of speculation and sabotage. </p>
<p>                    As her relatives fight over heirlooms, Astrid Leong is at the center of her own storm, desperately in love with her old sweetheart Charlie Wu, but tormented by her ex-husband&#8211;a man hell bent on destroying Astrid&#8217;s reputation and relationship. Meanwhile Kitty Pong, married to China&#8217;s second richest man, billionaire Jack Bing, still feels second best next to her new step-daughter, famous fashionista Colette Bing. </p>
<p>                    A sweeping novel that takes us from the elegantly appointed mansions of Manila to the secluded private islands in the Sulu Sea, from a kidnapping at Hong Kong&#8217;s most elite private school to a surprise marriage proposal at an Indian palace, caught on camera by the telephoto lenses of paparazzi, Kevin Kwan&#8217;s hilarious, gloriously wicked new novel reveals the long-buried secrets of Asia&#8217;s most privileged families and their rich people problems. </p>
<p>                    Look for Kevin Kwan&#8217;s latest novel, Sex &#038; Vanity!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rich-people-problems-a-novel-kevin-kwan/">Rich People Problems : A Novel &#8211; Kevin Kwan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zack &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/zack-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zack-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rising star Zack Grantham has been stuck in a downward spiral of grief that has put his career on hold. Back on the road with the Carolina Cold Fury, still crippled by emotional baggage, and now a single dad, he&#8217;s in need of some serious help with his son. But while the nerdy new nanny [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zack-sawyer-bennett/">Zack &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rising star Zack Grantham has been stuck in a downward spiral of grief that has put his career on hold. Back on the road with the Carolina Cold Fury, still crippled by emotional baggage, and now a single dad, he&#8217;s in need of some serious help with his son. But while the nerdy new nanny wins his son&#8217;s heart, Zack isn&#8217;t sure that he&#8217;s ready for a woman&#8217;s touch&#8211;even after getting a glimpse of the killer curves she&#8217;s hiding under those baggy clothes. Kate Francis usually keeps men like Zack at a distance. Though his athlete&#8217;s body is honed to perfection, he refuses to move on with his life&#8211;and besides, he&#8217;s her boss. Still, the sparks between them are undeniable, tempting Kate to turn their professional relationship into a personal one. But before she makes a power play for Zack&#8217;s wounded heart, Kate will have to open him up again and show him that love is worth the fight.Contains mature themes.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zack-sawyer-bennett/">Zack &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Murder Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/murder-game-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/murder-game-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Be seduced by the world of the GhostWalkers as #1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan raises the stakes in the ultimate game of love and death&#8230; Games should be fun, but for two expert teams across the country, they&#8217;re murder-because the winning team is the one that gets the most kills. The participants [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/murder-game-christine-feehan/">Murder Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Be seduced by the world of the GhostWalkers as #1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan raises the stakes in the ultimate game of love and death&#8230;    </p>
<p>                     Games should be fun, but for two expert teams across the country, they&#8217;re murder-because the winning team is the one that gets the most kills. The participants in this violent challenge are rumored to be GhostWalkers. And Kaden Montague isn&#8217;t happy about it.    </p>
<p>                     Kaden is a GhostWalker and he&#8217;s determined to clear the GhostWalker name of the rumors. And he&#8217;s going to need the help of psychic Tansy Meadows to do it. But as soon as he sees her, he knows his mission will be more complicated than he imagined-and the &#8220;murder game&#8221; may not be at all what it seems.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/murder-game-christine-feehan/">Murder Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mind Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/mind-game-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mind-game-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan returns to a world of terrifying power and forbidden passion in the second novel in her breathtaking GhostWalker series. Possessed of an extraordinary telekinetic gift, Dahlia LeBlanc has spent her life isolated from other people. And just when she thinks she&#8217;s finally achieved some semblance of peace, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-game-christine-feehan/">Mind Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan returns to a world of terrifying power and forbidden passion in the second novel in her breathtaking GhostWalker series.    </p>
<p>                    Possessed of an extraordinary telekinetic gift, Dahlia LeBlanc has spent her life isolated from other people. And just when she thinks she&#8217;s finally achieved some semblance of peace, her well-orchestrated world comes crashing down&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    For a reason she cannot guess, she has become the target of deadly assassins. Suddenly no place is safe-not even the secret refuge she&#8217;d established long ago. Now she must rely on Nicolas Trevane-a dangerous warrior sent to track her down and protect her. Together, they generate a scorching heat Dahlia never imagined was possible. But can she trust this man with her secrets-especially when some people would kill to get their hands on them?    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-game-christine-feehan/">Mind Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Van &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/van-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/van-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As one of the league&#8217;s toughest enforcers, Van Turner is ruthless on the ice. He plays hard because it&#8217;s the only way to channel the rage boiling inside, and a reputation as an A-hole is better than everyone knowing the truth. Van has spent his entire life running from a secret that&#8217;s kept him from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/van-sawyer-bennett/">Van &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As one of the league&#8217;s toughest enforcers, Van Turner is ruthless on the ice. He plays hard because it&#8217;s the only way to channel the rage boiling inside, and a reputation as an A-hole is better than everyone knowing the truth. Van has spent his entire life running from a secret that&#8217;s kept him from getting involved in relationships-or accepting lucrative deals with East Coast teams. Then the Carolina Cold Fury makes him an offer he can&#8217;t refuse . . . and Van meets a woman he can&#8217;t resist. Simone Fournier is the stubborn one in her family-and that&#8217;s saying something, considering her brothers are two of the Cold Fury&#8217;s biggest stars. Simone gets what she wants, and what she wants is Van. Still, there&#8217;s a part of him Simone can&#8217;t reach, no matter how hard she tries. In private, he&#8217;s all fire and passion. In public, he freezes her out. Van may want to push her away, but Simone won&#8217;t let him go that easily. Because this time, she&#8217;s playing for keeps. Contains mature themes.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/van-sawyer-bennett/">Van &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lucas &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/lucas-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lucas-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Carolina Cold Fury hockey team is stacked with hotshots. But when a new player joins their ranks, he learns that even superstars can&#8217;t go it alone when it comes to love. Lucas Fournier is only serious about one thing: hockey. The league&#8217;s fun-loving charmer, Luc is always up for a good prank or a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lucas-sawyer-bennett/">Lucas &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Carolina Cold Fury hockey team is stacked with hotshots. But when a new player joins their ranks, he learns that even superstars can&#8217;t go it alone when it comes to love. Lucas Fournier is only serious about one thing: hockey. The league&#8217;s fun-loving charmer, Luc is always up for a good prank or a great lay, and he has no intention of settling down. But being traded to the Carolina Cold Fury&#8211;and to play alongside his big brother, Max&#8211;is no joke. With another title in sight, the last thing Luc wants is to let his new teammates down. To succeed, Luc will need to keep his head in the game and the most . . . er, demanding member of his anatomy in check. But when temptation hits, Luc hits back harder. Museum curator Stephanie Frazier has always put business before pleasure, which just about explains her nonexistent sex life. But when Stephanie meets Luc at a champagne-fueled gala, she finds herself flirting like crazy&#8211;and going home with the uninhibited athlete. For one night, she learns what passion is all about. She just never counted on the little surprise Luc leaves behind. And that&#8217;s when things really start to get interesting.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lucas-sawyer-bennett/">Lucas &#8211;  Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China Rich Girlfriend &#8211; Kevin Kwan</title>
		<link>/china-rich-girlfriend-kevin-kwan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/china-rich-girlfriend-kevin-kwan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of Crazy Rich Asians, now a MAJOR MOTION PICTURE starring Constance Wu, Henry Golding, Michelle Yeoh and Gemma Chan, comes a deliciously fun story of family, fortune, and fame in Mainland China. It&#8217;s the eve of Rachel Chu&#8217;s wedding, and she should be over the moon. She has a flawless oval-cut [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/china-rich-girlfriend-kevin-kwan/">China Rich Girlfriend &#8211; Kevin Kwan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of Crazy Rich Asians, now a MAJOR MOTION PICTURE starring Constance Wu, Henry Golding, Michelle Yeoh and Gemma Chan, comes a deliciously fun story of family, fortune, and fame in Mainland China.    </p>
<p>                     It&#8217;s the eve of Rachel Chu&#8217;s wedding, and she should be over the moon. She has a flawless oval-cut diamond, a wedding dress she loves, and a fiance willing to give up one of the biggest fortunes in Asia in order to marry her. Still, Rachel mourns the fact that her birth father, a man she never knew, won&#8217;t be there to walk her down the aisle.    </p>
<p>                    Then a chance accident reveals his identity. Suddenly, Rachel is drawn into a dizzying world of Shanghai splendor, a world where people attend church in a penthouse, where exotic cars race down the boulevard, and where people aren&#8217;t just crazy rich&#8230; they&#8217;re China rich.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/china-rich-girlfriend-kevin-kwan/">China Rich Girlfriend &#8211; Kevin Kwan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strange Sight : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</title>
		<link>/strange-sight-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Witchcraft & Wicca]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/strange-sight-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The La Fleur restaurant has a slew of unusual phenomena. Bonnet-clad apparitions pass through walls, blood leaks from ceilings and rats besiege the dining room. Experts from the Great Essex Witch Museum are called in to quell these strange sights. But before Rosie Strange and Sam Stone can do their thing events turn darker. For [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strange-sight-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/">Strange Sight : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The La Fleur restaurant has a slew of unusual phenomena. Bonnet-clad apparitions pass through walls, blood leaks from ceilings and rats besiege the dining room. Experts from the Great Essex Witch Museum are called in to quell these strange sights. But before Rosie Strange and Sam Stone can do their thing events turn darker. For La Fleur&#8217;s chef has been strung up and slaughtered like a pig. More oddly, the only witness, the owner&#8217;s daughter Mary, swears blind a ghost did it.       </p>
<p>                    Rosie and Sam must find out what&#8217;s happening before Mary takes the fall. But intuitions and tip-offs lead them stumbling into the dark waters of the past, exposing secrets of a wider conspiracy, as well as secrets all Rosie&#8217;s own. With strange chills Rosie and Sam learn that seeing isn&#8217;t always believing, while thoughts of truth may be just as illusory.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strange-sight-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/">Strange Sight : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alex &#8211; Sawyer Bennett</title>
		<link>/alex-sawyer-bennett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alex-sawyer-bennett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hockey star Alexander Crossman has a reputation as a cold-hearted player on and off the ice. Pushed into the sport by his alcoholic father, Alex isn&#8217;t afraid to give fans the proverbial middle finger, relishing his role as the MVP they love to hate. Management, however, isn&#8217;t so amused. Now Alex has a choice: fix [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alex-sawyer-bennett/">Alex &#8211; Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hockey star Alexander Crossman has a reputation as a cold-hearted player on and off the ice. Pushed into the sport by his alcoholic father, Alex isn&#8217;t afraid to give fans the proverbial middle finger, relishing his role as the MVP they love to hate. Management, however, isn&#8217;t so amused. Now Alex has a choice: fix his public image through community service or ride the bench. But Alex refuses to be molded into the Carolina Cold Fury poster boy . . . not even by a tempting redhead with killer curves. As a social worker, Sutton Price is accustomed to difficult people like Alex, who&#8217;s been assigned to help her create a drug-abuse awareness program for at-risk youth as part of the Fury&#8217;s effort to clean up his image. What she doesn&#8217;t expect is the arrogant smirk from his perfect lips stirring her most heated fantasies. But Sutton isn&#8217;t one to cross professional boundaries-and besides, Alex doesn&#8217;t do relationships . . . or does he? The more she sees behind Alex&#8217;s bad-boy fa�ade, the more Sutton craves the man she uncovers.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alex-sawyer-bennett/">Alex &#8211; Sawyer Bennett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deadly Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/deadly-game-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deadly-game-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan explores the limits of endurance and the boundaries of passion in a life-and-death struggle to survive in this GhostWalker novel&#8230; It begins as a mission to protect a politician from an assassination threat. But the operation takes an unexpected turn when Mari, a mysteriously beautiful GhostWalker, is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deadly-game-christine-feehan/">Deadly Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan explores the limits of endurance and the boundaries of passion in a life-and-death struggle to survive in this GhostWalker novel&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    It begins as a mission to protect a politician from an assassination threat. But the operation takes an unexpected turn when Mari, a mysteriously beautiful GhostWalker, is taken hostage. At the same time, Ken Norton, expert assassin and himself a GhostWalker warrior, is on a mission of his own-one that reaches into Mari&#8217;s own past. No stranger to the ways of violent warfare, Mari must join forces with Ken and trust his every move-each one more intimate than the last.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deadly-game-christine-feehan/">Deadly Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conspiracy Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/conspiracy-game-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conspiracy-game-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fourth novel in #1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan&#8217;s GhostWalker series plunges two lovers into a game where danger and passion lurk in the darkest shadows of the mind&#8230; Jack Norton is a GhostWalker, a genetically enhanced sniper with a merciless sense of justice, a phantom welcomed by the anonymity of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-game-christine-feehan/">Conspiracy Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fourth novel in #1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan&#8217;s GhostWalker series plunges two lovers into a game where danger and passion lurk in the darkest shadows of the mind&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    Jack Norton is a GhostWalker, a genetically enhanced sniper with a merciless sense of justice, a phantom welcomed by the anonymity of the night. But a mission to rescue his brother in the jungle has left him vulnerable to rebel forces. His only salvation is his power of telepathy. Then he meets Briony, an unusual beauty on a mission of her own. But they share more than the sweltering heat&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    Briony shares the GhostWalker powers. Yet she&#8217;s different. She doesn&#8217;t know what she is, or what she&#8217;s capable of. But her enemies do. And Jack and Briony&#8217;s flight will take them into a frightening conspiracy of mind and body&#8211;across the globe, and into the heart of darkness where the shocking truth is something neither of them could have foreseen&#8211;or can escape.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-game-christine-feehan/">Conspiracy Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Summoned to Thirteenth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</title>
		<link>/summoned-to-thirteenth-grave-darynda-jones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/summoned-to-thirteenth-grave-darynda-jones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s lucky number thirteen . . . this is the epic finale for our favourite Grim Reaper and her sinfully sexy son-of-the-devil husband, Reyes. Charley Davidson, Grim Reaper extraordinaire, is pissed. She&#8217;s been kicked off the earthly plane for eternity &#8211; which is exactly the amount of time it takes to make a person stark, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summoned-to-thirteenth-grave-darynda-jones/">Summoned to Thirteenth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s lucky number thirteen . . . this is the epic finale for our favourite Grim Reaper and her sinfully sexy son-of-the-devil husband, Reyes.</p>
<p>                    Charley Davidson, Grim Reaper extraordinaire, is pissed. She&#8217;s been kicked off the earthly plane for eternity &#8211; which is exactly the amount of time it takes to make a person stark, raving mad. But someone&#8217;s looking out for her, and she&#8217;s allowed to return after a mere hundred years in exile. Is it too much to hope for that not much has changed? Apparently it is. Bummer.</p>
<p>                    She&#8217;s missed her daughter. She&#8217;s missed Reyes. She&#8217;s missed Cookie and Garrett and Uncle Bob. But now that she&#8217;s back on earth, it&#8217;s time to put to rest burning questions that need answers. What happened to her mother? How did she really die? Who killed her? And are cupcakes or coffee the best medicine for a broken heart? It all comes to a head in an epic showdown between good and evil in this final smart and hilarious novel.</p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s Charley&#8217;s last adventure, and the one thing we know for sure is that it&#8217;s going to be one wild ride . . .</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An absolute must read&#8217; J.R. Ward, No.1 New York Times bestselling author of the Black Dagger Brotherhood series.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The grim reaper gets a shiny cook makeover in Jones&#8217;s blazing hot debut&#8230; will appeal to fans of MaryJanice Davidson and Janet Evanovich.&#8217; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly</p>
<p>                    &#8216;What&#8217;s better than a bad-ass girl grim reaper who keeps us safe from hell hounds and demons? (The answer is obviously nothing.)&#8217; RT Book Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summoned-to-thirteenth-grave-darynda-jones/">Summoned to Thirteenth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yvonne Goes to York &#8211; M. C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/yvonne-goes-to-york-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/yvonne-goes-to-york-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The sixth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. A damsel in distress and a confirmed bachelor &#8211; surely a match made in heaven! No coach journey is ever dull with Miss Hannah Pym aboard, and this one proves no exception as she meets the young and beautiful Miss Yvonne Grenier, who is fleeing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/yvonne-goes-to-york-m-c-beaton/">Yvonne Goes to York &#8211; M. C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The sixth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. </p>
<p>                    A damsel in distress and a confirmed bachelor &#8211; surely a match made in heaven!</p>
<p>                    No coach journey is ever dull with Miss Hannah Pym aboard, and this one proves no exception as she meets the young and beautiful Miss Yvonne Grenier, who is fleeing the Terror in France.</p>
<p>                    Charming but shy, Yvonne becomes quite frightened when a dangerous enemy also boards the stagecoach to York. Luckily Miss Pym is on hand to propose a plan which will save Yvonne &#8211; and throw her into the arms of the wealthy and unattached Marquis of Ware! </p>
<p>                    Handsome and tailored to perfection, the marquis&#8217;s birth and fortune are armour enough to defend Yvonne. Although the girl is of the French bourgeoisie and below him, Miss Pym is a certain that Yvonne&#8217;s Gallic graces and quick-witted tongue have more than piqued his interest. After all, a maiden in distress is irresistible &#8211; even to a confirmed bachelor!</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/yvonne-goes-to-york-m-c-beaton/">Yvonne Goes to York &#8211; M. C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Curse of Tenth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</title>
		<link>/the-curse-of-tenth-grave-darynda-jones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-curse-of-tenth-grave-darynda-jones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Part-time PI and full-time grim reaper, Charley Davidson has asked a lot of questions throughout her life: Why can I see dead people? Who is the hot supernatural entity following me? How do I get gum out of my sister&#8217;s hair before she wakes up? But, &#8220;How do I trap not one god, but three?&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curse-of-tenth-grave-darynda-jones/">The Curse of Tenth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Part-time PI and full-time grim reaper, Charley Davidson has asked a lot of questions throughout her life: Why can I see dead people? Who is the hot supernatural entity following me? How do I get gum out of my sister&#8217;s hair before she wakes up? But, &#8220;How do I trap not one god, but three?&#8221; was never among them. Until now. And since those gods are on earth to kill her daughter, she has little choice but to track them down, trap them, and cast them from this dimension.  But one of them stole her heart a very long time ago. Can a god of absolute death and destruction change his omniscient spots, or will his allegiance lie with his brothers?  Those are just some of the questions Charley must answer, and quick. Add to that a homeless girl on the run for her life, a man who&#8217;s been framed for murdering a woman who is still very much alive, and a pendant made from god glass that has the entire supernatural world in an uproar, Charley has her hands full. If she can manage to take care of the whole world-destroying-gods thing, we&#8217;re saved. If not, well&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curse-of-tenth-grave-darynda-jones/">The Curse of Tenth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should&#8217;ve Been a Cowboy &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</title>
		<link>/shouldve-been-a-cowboy-vicki-lewis-thompson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Westerns]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shouldve-been-a-cowboy-vicki-lewis-thompson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Addicted to her cowboy&#8217;s kisses&#8230; Tyler O&#8217;Connelli kissed Alex Keller goodbye and figured that was that. Tyler&#8217;s career takes her all over the globe, while Alex settles in the little town of Shoshone, Wyoming. But when Tyler makes a quick visit to see family, her reunion with Alex rekindles a fire that never died. Tyler [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shouldve-been-a-cowboy-vicki-lewis-thompson/">Should&#8217;ve Been a Cowboy &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Addicted to her cowboy&#8217;s kisses&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Tyler O&#8217;Connelli kissed Alex Keller goodbye and figured that was that. Tyler&#8217;s career takes her all over the globe, while Alex settles in the little town of Shoshone, Wyoming. But when Tyler makes a quick visit to see family, her reunion with Alex rekindles a fire that never died.</p>
<p>                    Tyler is blindsided by Alex&#8217;s transformation. Who knew a Stetson, snug jeans and a pair of boots would rocket him from cute to smokin&#8217; hot? Leaving him the first time was tough. Leaving him now is unthinkable.</p>
<p>                    But she&#8217;s just been offered the biggest promotion of her career&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Saddle up for the fourth book in the Sons of Chance series! Steamy western romances from the NYT bestselling author who brought you The McGavin Brothers of Eagles Nest, Montana. If you like sexy cowboys, charming small towns, and laugh-out-loud adventures, you&#8217;ll love the Sons of Chance. Pick up your copy of Should&#8217;ve Been a Cowboy today!</p>
<p>                    Sons of Chance</p>
<p>                    WHAT A COWBOY WANTS (Book 1)</p>
<p>                    A COWBOY&#8217;S TEMPTATION (Book 2)</p>
<p>                    CLAIMED BY THE COWBOY (Book 3)</p>
<p>                    SHOULD&#8217;VE BEEN A COWBOY (Book 4)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shouldve-been-a-cowboy-vicki-lewis-thompson/">Should&#8217;ve Been a Cowboy &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shifting Sands Resort Omnibus Volume 1 &#8211; Zoe Chant</title>
		<link>/shifting-sands-resort-omnibus-volume-1-zoe-chant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shifting-sands-resort-omnibus-volume-1-zoe-chant/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Adventure, romance, and laughter: escape to Shifting Sands Resort! Set at a tropical luxury resort for shifters only, this quirky, fan-favorite series is a romance thrill ride with humor and heart. Each book weaves into a compelling mystery about the island and the secrets that it&#8217;s hiding&#8230; An undercover spy, a wounded warrior, and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shifting-sands-resort-omnibus-volume-1-zoe-chant/">Shifting Sands Resort Omnibus Volume 1 &#8211; Zoe Chant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Adventure, romance, and laughter: escape to Shifting Sands Resort!</p>
<p>                    Set at a tropical luxury resort for shifters only, this quirky, fan-favorite series is a romance thrill ride with humor and heart. Each book weaves into a compelling mystery about the island and the secrets that it&#8217;s hiding&#8230;</p>
<p>                    An undercover spy, a wounded warrior, and a bartender wearing a cowboy hat all find their fated mates in these three standalone novels of healing and finding family. Come for the hot sand and cold drinks, stay for the love and laughs.</p>
<p>                    This volume includes the novels</p>
<p>                    Tropical Tiger Spy</p>
<p>                    Tropical Wounded Wolf</p>
<p>                    Tropical Bartender Bear</p>
<p>                    and three short stories, two of which are exclusive to this collection. This omnibus edition is in the author&#8217;s preferred reading order.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shifting-sands-resort-omnibus-volume-1-zoe-chant/">Shifting Sands Resort Omnibus Volume 1 &#8211; Zoe Chant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exile&#8217;s Valor &#8211; Mercedes Lackey</title>
		<link>/exiles-valor-mercedes-lackey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/exiles-valor-mercedes-lackey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This stand-alone novel in the Valdemar series continues the story of prickly weapons-master Alberich. Once a heroic Captain in the army of Karse, a kingdom at war with Valdemar, Alberich becomes one of Valdemar&#8217;s Heralds. Despite prejudice against him, he becomes the personal protector of young Queen Selenay. But can he protect her from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exiles-valor-mercedes-lackey/">Exile&#8217;s Valor &#8211; Mercedes Lackey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This stand-alone novel in the Valdemar series continues the story of prickly weapons-master Alberich. Once a heroic Captain in the army of Karse, a kingdom at war with Valdemar, Alberich becomes one of Valdemar&#8217;s Heralds. Despite prejudice against him, he becomes the personal protector of young Queen Selenay. But can he protect her from the dangers of her own heart?    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exiles-valor-mercedes-lackey/">Exile&#8217;s Valor &#8211; Mercedes Lackey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deborah Goes to Dover &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/deborah-goes-to-dover-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deborah-goes-to-dover-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fifth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. The engaging Miss Hannah Pym delights all as she resumes her matchmaking adventures aboard the English stage &#8211; when lonely hearts chance across her intrepid path they&#8217;re sure to find themselves en route for romance! Destined for Dover, Miss Pym has her matchmaking work cut [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deborah-goes-to-dover-m-c-beaton/">Deborah Goes to Dover &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fifth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. </p>
<p>                    The engaging Miss Hannah Pym delights all as she resumes her matchmaking adventures aboard the English stage &#8211; when lonely hearts chance across her intrepid path they&#8217;re sure to find themselves en route for romance!</p>
<p>                    Destined for Dover, Miss Pym has her matchmaking work cut out for her when she encounters the pretty but hoydenish Lady Deborah Western! Encouraged by an unruly twin brother, the spirited, golden-haired Deborah seems set on dressing and acting the tomboy, much to the dismay of her handsome neighbor, the Earl of Ashton&#8230;</p>
<p>                    To Deb, the earl is a dull stick, always lecturing on the behavior of a proper lady. But her desire to fish, hunt, and ride astride is quickly replaced with more romantic notions when the tall, green-eyed earl challenges her to a horse race and wins himself an unforgettable kiss. </p>
<p>                    Miss Pym can&#8217;t resist the opportunity to match-make, and with the help of her clever maneuverings, Lady Deborah will soon be well and truly matched &#8211; perhaps even to the earl himself!</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deborah-goes-to-dover-m-c-beaton/">Deborah Goes to Dover &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book of Life : A Novel &#8211; Deborah Harkness</title>
		<link>/the-book-of-life-a-novel-deborah-harkness/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-of-life-a-novel-deborah-harkness/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling series finale and sequel to A Discovery of Witches and Shadow of Night. Look for the hit series &#8220;A Discovery of Witches&#8221; streaming on Sundance Now and Shudder, and coming to television this April on AMC and BBC America. Fans of the All Souls Trilogy sent this highly anticipated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-life-a-novel-deborah-harkness/">The Book of Life : A Novel &#8211; Deborah Harkness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling series finale and sequel to A Discovery of Witches and Shadow of Night.     </p>
<p>                     Look for the hit series &#8220;A Discovery of Witches&#8221; streaming on Sundance Now and Shudder, and coming to television this April on AMC and BBC America.    </p>
<p>                    Fans of the All Souls Trilogy sent this highly anticipated finale straight to #1 on the New York Times hardcover bestseller list. Bringing the series&#8217; magic and suspense to a deeply satisfying conclusion, The Book of Life is poised to become an even bigger phenomenon in paperback.    </p>
<p>                    Diana and Matthew time-travel back from Elizabethan London to make a dramatic return to the present-facing new crises and old enemies. At Matthew&#8217;s ancestral home, Sept-Tours, they reunite with the beloved cast of characters from A Discovery of Witches-with one significant exception. But the real threat to their future has yet to be revealed, and when it is, the search for Ashmole 782 and its missing pages takes on even more urgency.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-life-a-novel-deborah-harkness/">The Book of Life : A Novel &#8211; Deborah Harkness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Storm Cursed &#8211; Patricia Briggs</title>
		<link>/storm-cursed-patricia-briggs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monsters & Legendary Beings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/storm-cursed-patricia-briggs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful entry in the #1 New York Times bestselling series, Mercy Thompson must face a deadly enemy to defend all she loves&#8230; My name is Mercedes Athena Thompson Hauptman, and I am a car mechanic. And a coyote shapeshifter. And the mate of the Alpha of the Columbia Basin werewolf pack. Even so, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/storm-cursed-patricia-briggs/">Storm Cursed &#8211; Patricia Briggs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful entry in the #1 New York Times bestselling series, Mercy Thompson must face a deadly enemy to defend all she loves&#8230; </p>
<p>                     My name is Mercedes Athena Thompson Hauptman, and I am a car mechanic.<br />
                    And a coyote shapeshifter.<br />
                    And the mate of the Alpha of the Columbia Basin werewolf pack. </p>
<p>                     Even so, none of that would have gotten me into trouble if, a few months ago, I hadn&#8217;t stood upon a bridge and taken responsibility for the safety of the citizens who lived in our territory. It seemed like the thing to do at the time. It should have only involved hunting down killer goblins, zombie goats, and an occasional troll. Instead, our home was viewed as neutral ground, a place where humans would feel safe to come and treat with the fae. </p>
<p>                     The reality is that nothing and no one is safe. As generals and politicians face off with the Gray Lords of the fae, a storm is coming and her name is Death. </p>
<p>                     But we are pack, and we have given our word. </p>
<p>                     We will die to keep it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/storm-cursed-patricia-briggs/">Storm Cursed &#8211; Patricia Briggs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Flirt &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-flirt-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-flirt-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If I could have foreseen the future, I would have married the first man who asked me! Tongues were set wagging when Elizabeth Markham&#8217;s glamorous young parents were killed, sinking their only child to the unspeakable class of poor relation. Forced to live with her cruel, miserly uncle Julius, Elizabeth is forbidden to partake in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-flirt-m-c-beaton/">The Flirt &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If I could have foreseen the future, I would have married the first man who asked me!    </p>
<p>                    Tongues were set wagging when Elizabeth Markham&#8217;s glamorous young parents were killed, sinking their only child to the unspeakable class of poor relation. Forced to live with her cruel, miserly uncle Julius, Elizabeth is forbidden to partake in the season&#8217;s festivities. Marriage is her only escape, and she enacts a daring plan to trick her way into the Duke of Dunster&#8217;s exclusive house party, to snare one of the eligible dandies sure to dance attendance on her.    </p>
<p>                    Her plan proceeds swimmingly, as Elizabeth flirts with all but the arrogant Lord Charles Lufford, considered to be quite a catch. She ignores him thoroughly until her uncle discovers her deception and Charles saves her&#8211;by announcing their engagement!    </p>
<p>                    But Elizabeth&#8217;s troubles are far from over, for in her absence she had come into an inheritance. And her uncle, along with one other sinister party would rather see her perish than receive it.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-flirt-m-c-beaton/">The Flirt &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strange Magic : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</title>
		<link>/strange-magic-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/strange-magic-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rosie Strange doesn&#8217;t believe in ghosts or witches or magic. No, not at all. It&#8217;s no surprise therefore when she inherits the ramshackle Essex Witch Museum, her first thought is to take the money and run. Still, the museum exerts a curious pull over Rosie. There&#8217;s the eccentric academic who bustles in to demand she [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strange-magic-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/">Strange Magic : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rosie Strange doesn&#8217;t believe in ghosts or witches or magic. No, not at all. It&#8217;s no surprise therefore when she inherits the ramshackle Essex Witch Museum, her first thought is to take the money and run.</p>
<p>                    Still, the museum exerts a curious pull over Rosie. There&#8217;s the eccentric academic who bustles in to demand she help in a hunt for old bones, those of the notorious Ursula Cadence, a witch long since put to death. And there&#8217;s curator Sam Stone, a man about whom Rosie can&#8217;t decide if he&#8217;s tiresomely annoying or extremely captivating. It all adds up to looking like her plans to sell the museum might need to be delayed, just for a while.</p>
<p>                    Finding herself and Sam embroiled in a most peculiar centuries-old mystery, Rosie is quickly expelled from her comfort zone, where to her horror, the secrets of the past come with their own real, and all too present, danger as a strange magic threatens to envelope them all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strange-magic-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/">Strange Magic : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Murder at Sunrise Lake &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/murder-at-sunrise-lake-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/murder-at-sunrise-lake-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan reaches new heights of passion and suspense in this thrilling novel that takes readers deep into the California backcountry, where a woman is tormented by visions of a killer. It starts in her dreams. Hideous flashes from a nightmare only she can stop. Images of a murderer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/murder-at-sunrise-lake-christine-feehan/">Murder at Sunrise Lake &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan reaches new heights of passion and suspense in this thrilling novel that takes readers deep into the California backcountry, where a woman is tormented by visions of a killer.  </p>
<p>                    It starts in her dreams. Hideous flashes from a nightmare only she can stop. Images of a murderer stalking the ones she cares about most&#8230;  </p>
<p>                    Stella Harrison thought she got away from the traumas of her past. Running the Sunrise Lake resort high in the Sierra Nevada mountains has brought her peace, even though she doesn&#8217;t truly share her quiet life with anyone. Not even Sam, the hired handyman that notices everything and always seems to know exactly what she needs. </p>
<p>                    Stella doesn&#8217;t know anything about Sam&#8217;s past, but somehow over the last two years his slow, steady presence has slipped past her defenses. Still, she knows she can&#8217;t tell him about her recent premonitions. So far there&#8217;s been no murder. No body. No way to prove what&#8217;s about to happen without destroying the life she&#8217;s built for herself. </p>
<p>                    But a killer is out there. And Stella knows that this time she&#8217;ll do whatever it takes to stop him.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/murder-at-sunrise-lake-christine-feehan/">Murder at Sunrise Lake &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emily Goes to Exeter &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/emily-goes-to-exeter-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/emily-goes-to-exeter-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. A dead employer&#8217;s legacy of five thousand pounds allows spinster Hannah Pym to resign from housekeeping and find adventure travelling the English countryside by stagecoach. But adventure soon finds Miss Pym in the form of Miss Emily Freemantle, a spoilt violet-eyed beauty fleeing an arranged [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emily-goes-to-exeter-m-c-beaton/">Emily Goes to Exeter &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. </p>
<p>                    A dead employer&#8217;s legacy of five thousand pounds allows spinster Hannah Pym to resign from housekeeping and find adventure travelling the English countryside by stagecoach. But adventure soon finds Miss Pym in the form of Miss Emily Freemantle, a spoilt violet-eyed beauty fleeing an arranged marriage to a rake she has never met.</p>
<p>                    When the girl&#8217;s darkly handsome betrothed boards their stage, Miss Pym is certain Emily was rash to bolt from this aristocratic catch!  And so as soon as the travellers repair to an inn, Miss Pym begins her matchmaking&#8230; and although Lord Ranger Harley complains he&#8217;ll not marry an ungrateful minx, Miss Pym suspects once she&#8217;s marshalled the couple into sharing intimate household chores, all romantic knots will be untangled!</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emily-goes-to-exeter-m-c-beaton/">Emily Goes to Exeter &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Education of Miss Patterson Lib/E &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-education-of-miss-patterson-lib-e-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-education-of-miss-patterson-lib-e-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For lovely young Miss Patricia Patterson, life seemed a delightful dream until the specter of her guardian, Lord Charles Gaunt, cast a shadow over her carefree days of idleness and enchanting evenings of dazzling balls and delicious flirtations. Lord Charles demanded she act the part of a proper and perfectly boring young miss. Even worse, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-miss-patterson-lib-e-m-c-beaton/">The Education of Miss Patterson Lib/E &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For lovely young Miss Patricia Patterson, life seemed a delightful dream until the specter of her guardian, Lord Charles Gaunt, cast a shadow over her carefree days of idleness and enchanting evenings of dazzling balls and delicious flirtations. Lord Charles demanded she act the part of a proper and perfectly boring young miss. Even worse, he insisted she devote her waking hours to cultivating her mind rather than captivating her swarm of admirers. Thus, the battle was joined between the handsome, arrogant aristocrat who had Patricia in his lawful power, and Patricia, who vowed to turn this hateful tyrant into her lovelorn slave.&#8221;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-miss-patterson-lib-e-m-c-beaton/">The Education of Miss Patterson Lib/E &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deirdre and Desire &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/deirdre-and-desire-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deirdre-and-desire-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Red-haired, jade-eyed Deirdre is determined to marry for Love &#8211; nothing else will do. So the fact her father&#8217;s candidate for her hand, Lord Harry Desire, is well bred and good looking, interests her not a jot! But the feelings he arouses in her are truly distracting. Deirdre&#8217;s discovery of what desire can mean and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deirdre-and-desire-m-c-beaton/">Deirdre and Desire &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Red-haired, jade-eyed Deirdre is determined to marry for Love &#8211; nothing else will do.  So the fact her father&#8217;s candidate for her hand, Lord Harry Desire, is well bred and good looking, interests her not a jot! But the feelings he arouses in her are truly distracting.    </p>
<p>                    Deirdre&#8217;s discovery of what desire can mean and where her heart really lies brings about a delicious climax to this adventure of intrigue, misunderstanding &#8211; and love!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deirdre-and-desire-m-c-beaton/">Deirdre and Desire &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miss Tonks Turns to Crime &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/miss-tonks-turns-to-crime-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/miss-tonks-turns-to-crime-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One cannot live of dignity alone! The poor relations banded together some time ago to run The Poor Relation Hotel in the hope their embarrassed relatives would buy them out, but as the hotel prospered, so they began to enjoy the fruit of their labour. But once again they need money to go on and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/miss-tonks-turns-to-crime-m-c-beaton/">Miss Tonks Turns to Crime &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One cannot live of dignity alone!    </p>
<p>                    The poor relations banded together some time ago to run The Poor Relation Hotel in the hope their embarrassed relatives would buy them out, but as the hotel prospered, so they began to enjoy the fruit of their labour.    </p>
<p>                    But once again they need money to go on and so poor, faded Miss Tonks is dispatched to her rich sister to steal something valuable from her in order to keep the hotel on its feet.  All the other poor relations have their doubts about Miss Tonks&#8217; chances for success, but the shy spinster as more than a few surprises up her sleeve!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/miss-tonks-turns-to-crime-m-c-beaton/">Miss Tonks Turns to Crime &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Belinda Goes to Bath &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/belinda-goes-to-bath-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/belinda-goes-to-bath-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The second book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. The delightful Miss Hannah Pym returns to the English countryside in search of adventure and romance in distress. No sooner does Miss Pym board her next stagecoach than she finds herself embroiled in the plight of Miss Belinda Earle, a spirited heiress banished to Bath [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/belinda-goes-to-bath-m-c-beaton/">Belinda Goes to Bath &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The second book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. </p>
<p>                    The delightful Miss Hannah Pym returns to the English countryside in search of adventure and romance in distress.</p>
<p>                    No sooner does Miss Pym board her next stagecoach than she finds herself embroiled in the plight of Miss Belinda Earle, a spirited heiress banished to Bath after swearing off the marriage market.</p>
<p>                    When the coach founders near Baddell Castle, and the dashing Marquis of Frenton comes to the rescue, Miss Pym decides to give Fate a hand.  Although the austere bachelor disdains romance, his furtive glances towards Belinda prove to Miss Pym that her expert matchmaking will soon turn this star-crossed couple into a heavenly match!</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/belinda-goes-to-bath-m-c-beaton/">Belinda Goes to Bath &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What a Cowboy Wants &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</title>
		<link>/what-a-cowboy-wants-vicki-lewis-thompson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Westerns]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-a-cowboy-wants-vicki-lewis-thompson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>He&#8217;s her perfect cowboy fantasy&#8230; Photographer Dominique Jeffries escaped to Wyoming after a bad breakup from her stifling ex. The last thing she&#8217;s looking for is commitment. And snapping pictures of a shirtless, sweaty cowhand leads to the perfect diversion. Nick Chance isn&#8217;t exactly a cowhand on the Last Chance Ranch but, hey, he&#8217;ll be [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-a-cowboy-wants-vicki-lewis-thompson/">What a Cowboy Wants &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>He&#8217;s her perfect cowboy fantasy&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Photographer Dominique Jeffries escaped to Wyoming after a bad breakup from her stifling ex. The last thing she&#8217;s looking for is commitment. And snapping pictures of a shirtless, sweaty cowhand leads to the perfect diversion.</p>
<p>                    Nick Chance isn&#8217;t exactly a cowhand on the Last Chance Ranch but, hey, he&#8217;ll be whatever the lady needs! Too bad all she wants is a quick roll in the hay.</p>
<p>                    Saddle up for the first book in the Sons of Chance series! Steamy western romances from the NYT bestselling author who brought you The McGavin Brothers of Eagles Nest, Montana. If you like sexy cowboys, charming small towns, and laugh-out-loud adventures, you&#8217;ll love the Sons of Chance. Pick up your copy of What a Cowboy Wants today!</p>
<p>                    * Note* This title was originally released in 2010 as Wanted!</p>
<p>                    Sons of Chance</p>
<p>                    WHAT A COWBOY WANTS (Book 1)</p>
<p>                    A COWBOY&#8217;S TEMPTATION (Book 2)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-a-cowboy-wants-vicki-lewis-thompson/">What a Cowboy Wants &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deadly Secrets &#8211; Kate Udall, Jen Talty</title>
		<link>/deadly-secrets-kate-udall-jen-talty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deadly-secrets-kate-udall-jen-talty/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After staring down the wrong end of a gun, not once, but twice, all Patty Harmon had wanted was to have a little fun. She&#8217;d spent most of her life taking care of everyone else but herself. While she had a plan for her life, she hadn&#8217;t yet started to live her life. So, when [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deadly-secrets-kate-udall-jen-talty/">Deadly Secrets &#8211; Kate Udall, Jen Talty</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After staring down the wrong end of a gun, not once, but twice, all Patty Harmon had wanted was to have a little fun. She&#8217;d spent most of her life taking care of everyone else but herself. While she had a plan for her life, she hadn&#8217;t yet started to live her life. So, when the aloof, distant, and emotionally unavailable New York State Trooper Reese McGinn takes an interest in her, she&#8217;s all in&#8230;for the moment.     </p>
<p>                    When the moment is over, they go their separate ways, and Patty can get back to her life plan. But once again, that plan is interrupted when Patty finds herself pregnant. She&#8217;ll let Reese back in for the sake of the child, but can she keep Reese from stealing her heart?     </p>
<p>                    New York State Trooper Reese McGinn has been haunted by his late mother&#8217;s confession and the secret she took to her grave. For the last seven years, he&#8217;s done nothing but move from job to job and town to town, vowing to never put down roots. But when his summer fling with Patty Harmon ends with a child on the way, he decides it&#8217;s time to forget the past.     </p>
<p>                    Only, the past doesn&#8217;t want to forget him, and a deadly secret rises from the grave, threatening to take away everything he thought he never wanted.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deadly-secrets-kate-udall-jen-talty/">Deadly Secrets &#8211; Kate Udall, Jen Talty</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vicious &#8211; Savannah Peachwood, Christian Rummel, L. J. Shen</title>
		<link>/vicious-savannah-peachwood-christian-rummel-l-j-shen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/vicious-savannah-peachwood-christian-rummel-l-j-shen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NOW A TOP TEN AMAZON BESTSELLER Emilia They say love and hate are the same feelings experienced under different circumstances, and it&#8217;s true. The man who comes to me in my dreams also haunts me in my nightmares. He is a brilliant lawyer. A skilled criminal. A beautiful liar. A bully and a savior, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vicious-savannah-peachwood-christian-rummel-l-j-shen/">Vicious &#8211; Savannah Peachwood, Christian Rummel, L. J. Shen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NOW A TOP TEN AMAZON BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    Emilia<br />
                    They say love and hate are the same feelings experienced under different circumstances, and it&#8217;s true.<br />
                    The man who comes to me in my dreams also haunts me in my nightmares.<br />
                    He is a brilliant lawyer.<br />
                    A skilled criminal.<br />
                    A beautiful liar.<br />
                    A bully and a savior, a monster and a lover.<br />
                    Ten years ago, he made me run away from the small town where we lived. Now, he came for me in New York, and he isn&#8217;t leaving until he takes me with him.     </p>
<p>                    Vicious<br />
                    She is a starving artist.<br />
                    Pretty and evasive like cherry blossom.<br />
                    Ten years ago, she barged into my life unannounced and turned everything upside down.<br />
                    She paid the price.<br />
                    Emilia LeBlanc is completely off-limits, my best friend&#8217;s ex-girlfriend. The woman who knows my darkest secret, and the daughter of the cheap Help we hired to take care of our estate.<br />
                    That should deter me from chasing her, but it doesn&#8217;t.<br />
                    So she hates me. Big fucking deal.<br />
                    She better get used to me.     </p>
<p>                    Vicious is a complete standalone and a part of the Sinners of Saint series</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vicious-savannah-peachwood-christian-rummel-l-j-shen/">Vicious &#8211; Savannah Peachwood, Christian Rummel, L. J. Shen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Somehow, Some Way : A Billionaire Builders Novella &#8211; Madeleine Maby, Lance Greenfield, Jennifer Probst</title>
		<link>/somehow-some-way-a-billionaire-builders-novella-madeleine-maby-lance-greenfield-jennifer-probst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/somehow-some-way-a-billionaire-builders-novella-madeleine-maby-lance-greenfield-jennifer-probst/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bolivar Randy Heart (a.k.a. Brady) knows exactly what he wants next in life: the perfect wife. Raised in a strict traditional family household, he seeks a woman who is sweet, conservative, and eager to settle down. With his well-known protective and dominant streak, he needs a woman to offer him balance in a world where [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/somehow-some-way-a-billionaire-builders-novella-madeleine-maby-lance-greenfield-jennifer-probst/">Somehow, Some Way : A Billionaire Builders Novella &#8211; Madeleine Maby, Lance Greenfield, Jennifer Probst</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bolivar Randy Heart (a.k.a. Brady) knows exactly what he wants next in life: the perfect wife. Raised in a strict traditional family household, he seeks a woman who is sweet, conservative, and eager to settle down. With his well-known protective and dominant streak, he needs a woman to offer him balance in a world where he relishes control.     </p>
<p>                    Too bad the newly hired, gorgeous, rehab addict is blasting through all his preconceptions and wrecking his ideals&#8230;one nail at a time&#8230;.     </p>
<p>                    Charlotte Grayson knows who she is and refuses to apologize. Growing up poor made her appreciate the simple things in life, and her new job at Pierce Brothers Construction is perfect to help her carve out a career in renovating houses. When an opportunity to transform a dilapidated house in a dangerous neighborhood pops up, she goes in full throttle. Unfortunately, she&#8217;s forced to work with the firm&#8217;s sexy architect who&#8217;s driving her crazy with his archaic views on women. Too bad he&#8217;s beginning to tempt her to take a chance on more than just work&#8230;one stroke at a time&#8230;.     </p>
<p>                    Somehow, some way, they need to work together to renovate a house without killing each other&#8230;or surrendering to the white-hot chemistry knocking at the front door.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/somehow-some-way-a-billionaire-builders-novella-madeleine-maby-lance-greenfield-jennifer-probst/">Somehow, Some Way : A Billionaire Builders Novella &#8211; Madeleine Maby, Lance Greenfield, Jennifer Probst</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lure of Oblivion &#8211; Jill Redfield, Suzanne Wright</title>
		<link>/lure-of-oblivion-jill-redfield-suzanne-wright/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lure-of-oblivion-jill-redfield-suzanne-wright/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gwen Miller may be a human, but she has no problem taking a stand against her own kind. She&#8217;s going to testify against the teenage boy she saw viciously assault a lone shifter female&#8211;and no amount of pressure from the boy&#8217;s wealthy family will make her back down. But when the harassment turns violent, help [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lure-of-oblivion-jill-redfield-suzanne-wright/">Lure of Oblivion &#8211; Jill Redfield, Suzanne Wright</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gwen Miller may be a human, but she has no problem taking a stand against her own kind. She&#8217;s going to testify against the teenage boy she saw viciously assault a lone shifter female&#8211;and no amount of pressure from the boy&#8217;s wealthy family will make her back down. But when the harassment turns violent, help comes in the form of a lean, toned wolf with winter-gray eyes.    </p>
<p>                    As a guest at Gwen&#8217;s inn, shifter enforcer Zander Devlin can&#8217;t help but notice that the fierce and leggy brunette is in serious trouble. Since she&#8217;s putting herself at risk for one of his kind, keeping her safe is the least he can do. That&#8217;s not the only reason Zander wants her close. He desires her, even as the wolf inside him backs away from her. But his feral instincts are hard to keep down, and as they take shape, they&#8217;re harder for Gwen to resist. Then again, embracing them could be the only thing that could save her life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lure-of-oblivion-jill-redfield-suzanne-wright/">Lure of Oblivion &#8211; Jill Redfield, Suzanne Wright</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wicked Dirty &#8211; Paula Hoffman, J. Kenner</title>
		<link>/wicked-dirty-paula-hoffman-j-kenner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wicked-dirty-paula-hoffman-j-kenner/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes bad isn&#8217;t good enough&#8230;. On the outside, Lyle Tarpin is a clean-cut Hollywood actor whose star is on the rise. Inside, he&#8217;s battling his own demons, shunning relationships, and finding solace in the arms of a string of anonymous women paid very well for their discretion. But when he&#8217;s photographed in a compromising position [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wicked-dirty-paula-hoffman-j-kenner/">Wicked Dirty &#8211; Paula Hoffman, J. Kenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes bad isn&#8217;t good enough&#8230;.     </p>
<p>                    On the outside, Lyle Tarpin is a clean-cut Hollywood actor whose star is on the rise. Inside, he&#8217;s battling his own demons, shunning relationships, and finding solace in the arms of a string of anonymous women paid very well for their discretion. But when he&#8217;s photographed in a compromising position by an over-eager reporter, the only way to save his career is to say that the woman he was with is his fianc&#8217;e. And now Lyle has to play a very public game with the only woman who&#8217;s ever managed to get under his skin.     </p>
<p>                    Struggling waitress Sugar Laine agrees to spend one night with Lyle &#8211; but only because she&#8217;s desperate to save her family home. She never expects that a night of passion will turn into a pretend engagement&#8230;or that the heat between them will blossom into love.     </p>
<p>                    But sometimes love has a price.     </p>
<p>                    And now the only question is &#8211; can Lyle and Sugar afford to pay it?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wicked-dirty-paula-hoffman-j-kenner/">Wicked Dirty &#8211; Paula Hoffman, J. Kenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mrs Budley Falls from Grace &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/mrs-budley-falls-from-grace-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mrs-budley-falls-from-grace-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Another Poor Relation has to resort to genteel thievery to make end meet &#8211; but she gets much more than she bargains for! Cut off by her own relations, pretty, dainty widow Eliza Budley must visit some other family manor to purloin expensive baubles. Happily, the rich Marquess of Peterhouse is in his dotage and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mrs-budley-falls-from-grace-m-c-beaton/">Mrs Budley Falls from Grace &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Another Poor Relation has to resort to genteel thievery to make end meet &#8211; but she gets much more than she bargains for!    </p>
<p>                    Cut off by her own relations, pretty, dainty widow Eliza Budley must visit some other family manor to purloin expensive baubles.  Happily, the rich Marquess of Peterhouse is in his dotage and wouldn&#8217;t know a relative from a bedpost, so Eliza is sent to play the imposter.    </p>
<p>                    But things do not go as planned and Eliza is met by the new Marquess &#8211; wickedly handsome, and with all his wits about him.  And somehow Eliza finds herself confessing her bluff to him and he in turn is much taken with her daring and charm  &#8211; but can he fall in love with such a scheming  widow from the world of trade? Time for the other Poor Relations to get involved and help these confused lovers!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mrs-budley-falls-from-grace-m-c-beaton/">Mrs Budley Falls from Grace &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Poet &#8211; A M Johnson</title>
		<link>/poet-a-m-johnson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/poet-a-m-johnson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Melissa Trujillo knows suffering. She&#8217;s tasted it, touched it, injected it. Sobriety is a gift, but it isn&#8217;t enough to wash away her secrets. Kieran O&#8217;Connell knows sacrifice. He&#8217;s owned it, held it between his fingers, and felt it in his knees. Words are his freedom, and they&#8217;ve begun to fade.Two different worlds, one moment [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/poet-a-m-johnson/">Poet &#8211; A M Johnson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Melissa Trujillo knows suffering. She&#8217;s tasted it, touched it, injected it. Sobriety is a gift, but it isn&#8217;t enough to wash away her secrets. Kieran O&#8217;Connell knows sacrifice. He&#8217;s owned it, held it between his fingers, and felt it in his knees. Words are his freedom, and they&#8217;ve begun to fade.Two different worlds, one moment and the Earth shifts-granting them a path.His eyes meet hers. Her hand fits his. Kieran finds his muse. Melissa finds her new addiction. But, when sin meets virtue, angels fall, and the truth, it becomes a blade. Together they&#8217;ll walk the sharp edge, and if her lies cut too deep, not even his words could save her&#8230; save them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/poet-a-m-johnson/">Poet &#8211; A M Johnson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Storm Gathering &#8211; Rebecca Zanetti</title>
		<link>/storm-gathering-rebecca-zanetti/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/storm-gathering-rebecca-zanetti/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Even before surviving the Scorpius bacterium, Greyson Storm was a lone wolf navigating minefields. As a kid, he learned to take a hit and find safety. As an adult, he joined the military and quickly learned how to protect and defend. When the world ended, he created a mercenary camp with military precision, no entanglements, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/storm-gathering-rebecca-zanetti/">Storm Gathering &#8211; Rebecca Zanetti</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even before surviving the Scorpius bacterium, Greyson Storm was a lone wolf navigating minefields. As a kid, he learned to take a hit and find safety. As an adult, he joined the military and quickly learned how to protect and defend. When the world ended, he created a mercenary camp with military precision, no entanglements, and a promise to avenge a fallen friend. As part of that vow, he kidnapped Maureen Shadow, but now that he has let her go, her blue eyes and intriguing mind keep haunting him&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    As possibly the only Biotechnology Engineer still living, Maureen Shadow might be humanity&#8217;s one hope to survive the aftermath of Scorpius, making her frighteningly valuable to both allies and enemies. Even after sexual tension explodes between her and Greyson, she&#8217;s not sure which camp he belongs to&#8211;friend or foe? Worse yet, survival may mean thwarting his prime mission, putting her in even more peril. When danger and seduction collide, there is no safety in this new world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/storm-gathering-rebecca-zanetti/">Storm Gathering &#8211; Rebecca Zanetti</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mist in the Mirror &#8211; Susan Hill</title>
		<link>/the-mist-in-the-mirror-susan-hill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mist-in-the-mirror-susan-hill/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A terrifying ghost story by the bestselling author of The Woman in Black. One dark and rainy night, Sir James Monmouth returns to London after years spent travelling alone. Intent on uncovering the secrets of his childhood hero, the mysterious Conrad Vane, he begins to investigate Vane&#8217;s life, but he finds himself warned off at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mist-in-the-mirror-susan-hill/">The Mist in the Mirror &#8211; Susan Hill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A terrifying ghost story by the bestselling author of The Woman in Black.</p>
<p>                    One dark and rainy night, Sir James Monmouth returns to London after years spent travelling alone. </p>
<p>                    Intent on uncovering the secrets of his childhood hero, the mysterious Conrad Vane, he begins to investigate Vane&#8217;s life, but he finds himself warned off at every turn. </p>
<p>                    Before long he realises he is being followed too. A pale, thin boy is haunting his every step but every time he tries to confront the boy he disappears. And what of the chilling scream and desperate sobbing only he can hear? </p>
<p>                    His quest leads him eventually to the old lady of Kittiscar Hall, where he discovers something far more terrible at work than he could ever have imagined.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thoroughly frightening&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Chills the blood&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mist-in-the-mirror-susan-hill/">The Mist in the Mirror &#8211; Susan Hill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Roman : Florentine Series, Book 3 &#8211; Sylvain Reynard</title>
		<link>/the-roman-florentine-series-book-3-sylvain-reynard/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-roman-florentine-series-book-3-sylvain-reynard/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Paperback edition includes bonus content. Raven and her sister, Cara, are at the mercy of a small detachment of Florentine vampyres who are delivering them as a peace offering to the feared Curia in Rome. Though she&#8217;s unsure William survived the coup that toppled his principality, Raven is determined to protect her sister at all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-roman-florentine-series-book-3-sylvain-reynard/">The Roman : Florentine Series, Book 3 &#8211; Sylvain Reynard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paperback edition includes bonus content.    </p>
<p>                    Raven and her sister, Cara, are at the mercy of a small detachment of Florentine vampyres who are delivering them as a peace offering to the feared Curia in Rome.    </p>
<p>                    Though she&#8217;s unsure William survived the coup that toppled his principality, Raven is determined to protect her sister at all costs, even if it means challenging Borek, the commander of the detachment.    </p>
<p>                    In an effort to keep Raven from falling into the hands of his enemies, William puts himself at the mercy of the Roman, the dangerous and mysterious vampyre king of Italy. But the Roman is not what he expects &#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Alliances and enmities will shift and merge as William struggles to save the woman he loves and his principality, without plunging the vampyre population into a world war.    </p>
<p>                    This stunning conclusion to the Florentine series will take readers across Italy and beyond as the lovers fight to remain together.  Forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-roman-florentine-series-book-3-sylvain-reynard/">The Roman : Florentine Series, Book 3 &#8211; Sylvain Reynard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dragonsworn &#8211; Holter Graham, Sherrilyn Kenyon</title>
		<link>/dragonsworn-holter-graham-sherrilyn-kenyon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dragonsworn-holter-graham-sherrilyn-kenyon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There is nothing in the universe the cursed dragon, Falcyn, hates more than humanity . . . except Greek humans. In a war he wanted no part of, they systematically destroyed everything he&#8217;d ever cared for. Now he waits for the day when evolution will finally rid him of the human vermin. Medea was born [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dragonsworn-holter-graham-sherrilyn-kenyon/">Dragonsworn &#8211; Holter Graham, Sherrilyn Kenyon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is nothing in the universe the cursed dragon, Falcyn, hates more than humanity . . . except Greek humans. In a war he wanted no part of, they systematically destroyed everything he&#8217;d ever cared for. Now he waits for the day when evolution will finally rid him of the human vermin.    </p>
<p>                    Medea was born the granddaughter of the Greek god Apollo, and among the first of his people that he cursed to die. But she will not let anyone rule her life. Not even her notorious grandfather. And when Apollo sends a new plague to destroy what remains of her people, she refuses to stand by and watch him take everything she loves from her again.    </p>
<p>                    This time, she knows of a secret weapon that can stop the ancient god and his army of demons. Once and for all. However, said device is in the hands of a dragon who wants nothing to do with politics, the gods, humanity, demons or Apollites. And especially not her. He is the immovable object.    </p>
<p>                    She is the unstoppable force . . .    </p>
<p>                    When Apollo makes a strategic move that backfires, he forces Falcyn back into play. Now Medea either has the weapon she needs to save her people, or she&#8217;s unleashed total Armageddon. If she can&#8217;t find some way to control the dragon before it&#8217;s too late, Falcyn will be an even worse plague on the world than the one Apollo has set loose. But how can anyone control a demonic dragon whose sole birthright is world annihilation?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dragonsworn-holter-graham-sherrilyn-kenyon/">Dragonsworn &#8211; Holter Graham, Sherrilyn Kenyon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Claimed by the Mountain Man &#8211; Eric London, Lillian Claire, Frankie Love</title>
		<link>/claimed-by-the-mountain-man-eric-london-lillian-claire-frankie-love/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/claimed-by-the-mountain-man-eric-london-lillian-claire-frankie-love/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Everly,&#8221; he growls. &#8220;I&#8217;m claiming you as mine, right here, right now.&#8221; Silas I want a wife who knows what it means to live off the grid, cook my food, and keep my bed warm. In exchange, I&#8217;ll give her a lifetime of happiness in the form of my cock. But damn, Everly&#8217;s more than [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/claimed-by-the-mountain-man-eric-london-lillian-claire-frankie-love/">Claimed by the Mountain Man &#8211; Eric London, Lillian Claire, Frankie Love</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Everly,&#8221; he growls. &#8220;I&#8217;m claiming you as mine, right here, right now.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Silas     </p>
<p>                    I want a wife who knows what it means to live off the grid, cook my food, and keep my bed warm. In exchange, I&#8217;ll give her a lifetime of happiness in the form of my cock. But damn, Everly&#8217;s more than I bargained for, and I don&#8217;t think she has any idea what it means to be mine. Hell, I wanted a wife, but I&#8217;m not sure I know how to live with a woman.     </p>
<p>                    Everly     </p>
<p>                    Did I expect to be a mail-order bride at 22? No. But honestly, my life could be a helluva lot worse. The agency says this Alaskan mountain man is rich, hot as heck, and willing to pay off my student loans. I&#8217;m crossing my fingers he&#8217;s everything I signed up for. But I may be a little over my head. Mostly because I&#8217;m marrying a stranger, and also because I&#8217;ve never dated. Period. Clearly I have no clue how to be a wife, but it&#8217;s too late to back out now.     </p>
<p>                    *WARNING: This story features a mountain man who knows exactly what he wants. And how he wants it. Don&#8217;t one-click if you want a tame mail order bride story; this is a classic Frankie Love romance, steamy as hell with a HEA.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/claimed-by-the-mountain-man-eric-london-lillian-claire-frankie-love/">Claimed by the Mountain Man &#8211; Eric London, Lillian Claire, Frankie Love</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dirty Sexy Player &#8211; Elena Wolfe, Jacob Morgan, Laurelin Paige</title>
		<link>/dirty-sexy-player-elena-wolfe-jacob-morgan-laurelin-paige/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dirty-sexy-player-elena-wolfe-jacob-morgan-laurelin-paige/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Available in audio first, New York Times best-selling author Laurelin Paige&#8217;s newest red-hot romance! Weston King knows how to play. But wild nights and owning an extensive collection of women&#8217;s panties don&#8217;t carry the thrill they once did, so when his business partner, Donovan, suggests an outrageous plan to allow them to take over their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dirty-sexy-player-elena-wolfe-jacob-morgan-laurelin-paige/">Dirty Sexy Player &#8211; Elena Wolfe, Jacob Morgan, Laurelin Paige</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Available in audio first, New York Times best-selling author Laurelin Paige&#8217;s newest red-hot romance!     </p>
<p>                    Weston King knows how to play. But wild nights and owning an extensive collection of women&#8217;s panties don&#8217;t carry the thrill they once did, so when his business partner, Donovan, suggests an outrageous plan to allow them to take over their competition, Wes takes him up on the offer. The crazy idea? Marry the competitor.     </p>
<p>                    Elizabeth Dyson, the bride-to-be in question, is on board with the plan. She wants access to her trust fund and can only get it once she marries. Each has something the other wants &#8211; all they have to do is pretend to like each other well enough to tie the knot.     </p>
<p>                    Only trouble is, playing fiancé to Elizabeth isn&#8217;t quite that simple. Wes finds her sexy and brilliant&#8230;and soon wishes their engagement wasn&#8217;t fake at all. Not that he&#8217;d ever tell her that.     </p>
<p>                    But a lover boy like Wes can stand an empty bed only for so long&#8230;and even the best of players has to put down his cards eventually.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dirty-sexy-player-elena-wolfe-jacob-morgan-laurelin-paige/">Dirty Sexy Player &#8211; Elena Wolfe, Jacob Morgan, Laurelin Paige</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Never, Part Three &#8211; Colleen Hoover, Tarryn Fisher</title>
		<link>/never-never-part-three-colleen-hoover-tarryn-fisher/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books for Teenagers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/never-never-part-three-colleen-hoover-tarryn-fisher/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling authors Colleen Hoover and Tarryn Fisher are back with the much-anticipated final installment in the Never Never novella series. Together, Silas Nash and Charlie Wynwood must look deeper into the past to find out who they were and who they want to be. With time ticking down, the couple are in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-never-part-three-colleen-hoover-tarryn-fisher/">Never Never, Part Three &#8211; Colleen Hoover, Tarryn Fisher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling authors Colleen Hoover and Tarryn Fisher are back with the much-anticipated final installment in the Never Never novella series. Together, Silas Nash and Charlie Wynwood must look deeper into the past to find out who they were and who they want to be. With time ticking down, the couple are in a race to find the answers they need before they lose everything. Can they regain what they once had? And will it restore who they once were?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-never-part-three-colleen-hoover-tarryn-fisher/">Never Never, Part Three &#8211; Colleen Hoover, Tarryn Fisher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Kiss Quotient &#8211; Carly Robins, Helen Hoang</title>
		<link>/the-kiss-quotient-carly-robins-helen-hoang/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-kiss-quotient-carly-robins-helen-hoang/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stella Lane thinks math is the only thing that unites the universe. She comes up with algorithms to predict customer purchases&#8211;a job that has given her more money than she knows what to do with as well as way less experience in the dating department than the average thirty-year-old. It doesn&#8217;t help that she has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-kiss-quotient-carly-robins-helen-hoang/">The Kiss Quotient &#8211; Carly Robins, Helen Hoang</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stella Lane thinks math is the only thing that unites the universe. She comes up with algorithms to predict customer purchases&#8211;a job that has given her more money than she knows what to do with as well as way less experience in the dating department than the average thirty-year-old. It doesn&#8217;t help that she has Asperger&#8217;s and that French kissing reminds her of a shark getting its teeth cleaned by pilot fish. She decides that she needs lots of practice&#8211;with a professional&#8211;which is why she hires escort Michael Phan. The Vietnamese-Swedish stunner can&#8217;t afford to turn down Stella&#8217;s offer, and he agrees to help her check off all the boxes on her lesson plan&#8211;from foreplay to more-than-missionary position&#8230; Before long, Stella not only learns to appreciate his kisses but also to crave all of the other things he&#8217;s making her feel. Their no-nonsense partnership starts making a strange kind of sense. And the pattern that emerges convinces Stella that love is the best kind of logic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-kiss-quotient-carly-robins-helen-hoang/">The Kiss Quotient &#8211; Carly Robins, Helen Hoang</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fire Touched &#8211; Patricia Briggs</title>
		<link>/fire-touched-patricia-briggs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monsters & Legendary Beings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fire-touched-patricia-briggs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mercy Thompson has been hailed as &#8220;a heroine who&#8230;always remains true to herself&#8221; (Library Journal). Now she&#8217;s back, and she&#8217;ll soon discover that when the fae stalk the human world, it&#8217;s the children who suffer&#8230; Tensions between the fae and humans are coming to a head. And when coyote shapeshifter Mercy and her Alpha werewolf [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-touched-patricia-briggs/">Fire Touched &#8211; Patricia Briggs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mercy Thompson has been hailed as &#8220;a heroine who&#8230;always remains true to herself&#8221; (Library Journal). Now she&#8217;s back, and she&#8217;ll soon discover that when the fae stalk the human world, it&#8217;s the children who suffer&#8230;     </p>
<p>                     Tensions between the fae and humans are coming to a head. And when coyote shapeshifter Mercy and her Alpha werewolf mate, Adam, are called upon to stop a rampaging troll, they find themselves with something that could be used to make the fae back down and forestall out-and-out war: a human child stolen long ago by the fae.     </p>
<p>                     Defying the most powerful werewolf in the country, the humans, and the fae, Mercy, Adam, and their pack choose to protect the boy no matter what the cost. But who will protect them from a boy who is fire touched?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-touched-patricia-briggs/">Fire Touched &#8211; Patricia Briggs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wicked and the Wallflower : The Bareknuckle Bastards Book I &#8211; Sarah MacLean, Read by Justine Eyre</title>
		<link>/wicked-and-the-wallflower-the-bareknuckle-bastards-book-i-sarah-maclean-read-by-justine-eyre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wicked-and-the-wallflower-the-bareknuckle-bastards-book-i-sarah-maclean-read-by-justine-eyre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Wicked Comes Calling . . . When a mysterious stranger finds his way into her bedchamber and offers his help in landing a duke, Lady Felicity Faircloth agrees&#8211;on one condition. She&#8217;s seen enough of the world to believe in passion, and won&#8217;t accept a marriage without it. The Wallflower Makes a Dangerous Bargain . [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wicked-and-the-wallflower-the-bareknuckle-bastards-book-i-sarah-maclean-read-by-justine-eyre/">Wicked and the Wallflower : The Bareknuckle Bastards Book I &#8211; Sarah MacLean, Read by Justine Eyre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Wicked Comes Calling . . .    </p>
<p>                    When a mysterious stranger finds his way into her bedchamber and offers his help in landing a duke, Lady Felicity Faircloth agrees&#8211;on one condition. She&#8217;s seen enough of the world to believe in passion, and won&#8217;t accept a marriage without it.    </p>
<p>                    The Wallflower Makes a Dangerous Bargain . . .    </p>
<p>                    Bastard son of a duke and king of London&#8217;s dark streets, Devil has spent a lifetime wielding power and seizing opportunity, and the spinster wallflower is everything he needs to exact a revenge years in the making. All he must do is turn the plain little mouse into an irresistible temptress, set his trap, and destroy his enemy.    </p>
<p>                    For the Promise of Passion . . .    </p>
<p>                    But there&#8217;s nothing plain about Felicity Faircloth, who quickly decides she&#8217;d rather have Devil than another. Soon, Devil&#8217;s carefully laid plans are in chaos and he must choose between everything he&#8217;s ever wanted . . . and the only thing he&#8217;s ever desired.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wicked-and-the-wallflower-the-bareknuckle-bastards-book-i-sarah-maclean-read-by-justine-eyre/">Wicked and the Wallflower : The Bareknuckle Bastards Book I &#8211; Sarah MacLean, Read by Justine Eyre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unlikeable Demon Hunter Collection : Books 1-3 &#8211; Deborah Wilde</title>
		<link>/the-unlikeable-demon-hunter-collection-books-1-3-deborah-wilde/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unlikeable-demon-hunter-collection-books-1-3-deborah-wilde/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meet Nava Katz. Punches like a girl. Kicks demon butt. When Nava half-drunkenly interrupts her twin brother&#8217;s induction ceremony, she expects to be chastised. What she doesn&#8217;t expect is to take his place among the previously all-male demon hunters. It&#8217;s the story of a foul-mouthed, romance-impaired heroine with no edit button, faced with her worst [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unlikeable-demon-hunter-collection-books-1-3-deborah-wilde/">The Unlikeable Demon Hunter Collection : Books 1-3 &#8211; Deborah Wilde</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meet Nava Katz.     </p>
<p>                    Punches like a girl.     </p>
<p>                    Kicks demon butt.    </p>
<p>                    When Nava half-drunkenly interrupts her twin brother&#8217;s induction ceremony, she expects to be chastised. What she doesn&#8217;t expect is to take his place among the previously all-male demon hunters.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s the story of a foul-mouthed, romance-impaired heroine with no edit button, faced with her worst nightmare-a purpose.    </p>
<p>                    The Unlikeable Demon Hunter Collection: Books 1-3 includes the first three novels in this fast-paced urban fantasy series that readers describe as &#8220;fun, funny, and unapologetically raunchy&#8230; a clever guilty pleasure at its best.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Get it now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unlikeable-demon-hunter-collection-books-1-3-deborah-wilde/">The Unlikeable Demon Hunter Collection : Books 1-3 &#8211; Deborah Wilde</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worth the Risk &#8211; Scott Merriman, Jamie Beck</title>
		<link>/worth-the-risk-scott-merriman-jamie-beck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/worth-the-risk-scott-merriman-jamie-beck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Woman&#8217;s World Book Club pick. When Jackson St. James decided that six weeks in Vermont&#8217;s Green Mountains would help him get his life together, he didn&#8217;t anticipate replacing his craving for whiskey with a craving for his alluring new landlord, Gabby. Now, instead of prioritizing his sobriety and the resolution of the lawsuit threatening [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/worth-the-risk-scott-merriman-jamie-beck/">Worth the Risk &#8211; Scott Merriman, Jamie Beck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Woman&#8217;s World Book Club pick.    </p>
<p>                    When Jackson St. James decided that six weeks in Vermont&#8217;s Green Mountains would help him get his life together, he didn&#8217;t anticipate replacing his craving for whiskey with a craving for his alluring new landlord, Gabby. Now, instead of prioritizing his sobriety and the resolution of the lawsuit threatening his business, he&#8217;s making excuses to spend time with the spunky young landscaper whose candor is more than a little addictive.    </p>
<p>                    Gabby Decouteau refuses to let her pill-popping mother and unreliable baby daddy turn her into a cynic, so she doesn&#8217;t fight her attraction to her enigmatic new tenant. Although Jackson&#8217;s smile rarely reaches his eyes, his generosity and dependability make her willing to overlook his demons. But once she convinces Jackson to give in to temptation, Gabby&#8217;s jealous ex threatens to disrupt the life Gabby has built for herself and her son.    </p>
<p>                    With so much at stake, Gabby and Jackson must decide if love is worth the risk.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/worth-the-risk-scott-merriman-jamie-beck/">Worth the Risk &#8211; Scott Merriman, Jamie Beck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Neanderthal Marries Human : A Smarter Romance &#8211; Penny Reid</title>
		<link>/neanderthal-marries-human-a-smarter-romance-penny-reid/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/neanderthal-marries-human-a-smarter-romance-penny-reid/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are three things you should know about Quinn Sullivan: 1) He is madly in love with Janie Morris, 2) He&#8217;s not above playing dirty to get what (or who) he wants, and 3) He doesn&#8217;t know how to knit. After just five months of dating Janie, Quinn&#8211;former Wendell and unapologetic autocrat&#8211;is ready to propose [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/neanderthal-marries-human-a-smarter-romance-penny-reid/">Neanderthal Marries Human : A Smarter Romance &#8211; Penny Reid</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are three things you should know about Quinn Sullivan: 1) He is madly in love with Janie Morris, 2) He&#8217;s not above playing dirty to get what (or who) he wants, and 3) He doesn&#8217;t know how to knit.    </p>
<p>                    After just five months of dating Janie, Quinn&#8211;former Wendell and unapologetic autocrat&#8211;is ready to propose marriage. In fact, he&#8217;s more than ready. If it were up to Quinn, he would efficiently propose, marry, and beget Janie with child all in the same day&#8211;thereby avoiding the drama and angst that accompanies the four stages of pre-matrimony: engagement, meeting the parents, bachelor/bachelorette party, and overblown, superfluous wedding day traditions.    </p>
<p>                    But Janie, much to Quinn&#8217;s dismay, tosses a wrench in his efficacious endeavors and challenges him to prove his devotion by going through the matrimonial motions, no matter how minute and mundane.    </p>
<p>                    Will Quinn last until the wedding day? Or will he yield to his tyrant impulses?    </p>
<p>                    This book is not a standalone. It is the sequel to &#8216;Neanderthal Seeks Human, &#8216; and is book #1.5 in the Knitting in the City series.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/neanderthal-marries-human-a-smarter-romance-penny-reid/">Neanderthal Marries Human : A Smarter Romance &#8211; Penny Reid</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man Candy &#8211; Christian Rummel, Savannah Richards, Jessica Lemmon</title>
		<link>/man-candy-christian-rummel-savannah-richards-jessica-lemmon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/man-candy-christian-rummel-savannah-richards-jessica-lemmon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is there room for two in that sleeping bag? When it comes to love, a chiseled loner takes the scenic route in this irresistible stand-alone from the author of Eye Candy (&#8220;Truly the perfect romantic comedy.&#8221; &#8211;Lauren Layne). Dax After spending months buried up to my eyeballs in my family&#8217;s affairs, I&#8217;m ready for a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-candy-christian-rummel-savannah-richards-jessica-lemmon/">Man Candy &#8211; Christian Rummel, Savannah Richards, Jessica Lemmon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is there room for two in that sleeping bag?     </p>
<p>                    When it comes to love, a chiseled loner takes the scenic route in this irresistible stand-alone from the author of Eye Candy (&#8220;Truly the perfect romantic comedy.&#8221; &#8211;Lauren Layne).     </p>
<p>                    Dax After spending months buried up to my eyeballs in my family&#8217;s affairs, I&#8217;m ready for a break. The kind of break where I can spend two solid weeks camping and fishing in the company of absolutely no one. Then I find myself directly in the path of a drop-dead gorgeous tornado by the name of Becca Stone. Who can resist a night with a damsel in distress? Especially when she happens to be a leggy blonde? The last thing I expect is for Becca to show up on my cabin doorstep the next night, shivering in the rain and ready for seconds.     </p>
<p>                    Becca One minute I&#8217;m admiring the rock-hard jaw of the Magic Mike lookalike who walks into my bar, and the next I&#8217;m getting fired by my own brother. Loudly. In front of everyone. Luckily Dax Vaughn is a gentleman who aims his white-hot smile at me. Oh, it&#8217;s on. Wham, bam, thank you ma&#8217;am. Then a torrential storm washes out the main road and causes a massive power outage, giving us two whole weeks to enjoy each other&#8217;s company. At which point Dax will go back home, leaving &#8220;us&#8221; in the rearview mirror. That&#8217;s the plan. Or it was&#8230;until I started falling for him.     </p>
<p>                    Look for Jessica Lemmon&#8217;s stand-alone romances with heartfelt HEAs:     </p>
<p>                    Fighting for Devlin<br />
                    Forgotten Promises<br />
                    Shut Up and Kiss Me<br />
                    Eye Candy<br />
                    Arm Candy<br />
                    Man Candy</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-candy-christian-rummel-savannah-richards-jessica-lemmon/">Man Candy &#8211; Christian Rummel, Savannah Richards, Jessica Lemmon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Silver Silence : Book 1 &#8211; Nalini Singh</title>
		<link>/silver-silence-book-1-nalini-singh/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/silver-silence-book-1-nalini-singh/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author Nalini Singh returns to her extraordinary Psy-Changeling world with a story of wild passion and darkest betrayal . . . Control. Precision. Family. These are the principles that drive Silver Mercant. At a time when the fledgling Trinity Accord seeks to unite a divided world, with Silver playing a crucial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/silver-silence-book-1-nalini-singh/">Silver Silence : Book 1 &#8211; Nalini Singh</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author Nalini Singh returns to her extraordinary Psy-Changeling world with a story of wild passion and darkest betrayal . . .     </p>
<p>                    Control. Precision. Family. These are the principles that drive Silver Mercant. At a time when the fledgling Trinity Accord seeks to unite a divided world, with Silver playing a crucial role as director of a worldwide emergency response network, wildness and chaos are the last things she needs in her life. But that&#8217;s exactly what Valentin Nikolaev, alpha of the StoneWater bears, brings with him.    </p>
<p>                    Valentin has never met a more fascinating woman. Though Silver is ruled by Silence &#8211; her mind clear of all emotion &#8211; Valentin senses a whisper of fire around her. That&#8217;s what keeps him climbing apartment buildings to be near her. But when a shadow assassin almost succeeds in poisoning Silver, the stakes become deadly serious . . . and Silver finds herself in the heart of a powerful bear clan. Her would-be assassin has no idea what their poison has unleashed . . .</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/silver-silence-book-1-nalini-singh/">Silver Silence : Book 1 &#8211; Nalini Singh</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fight for You &#8211; Lili Valente</title>
		<link>/fight-for-you-lili-valente/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fight-for-you-lili-valente/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Warning: A dark, sexy, boundary-pushing read.They destroyed the woman I love. Now I&#8217;m going to make them wish they had never been born.The frat boys who hurt Sam will pay the price for what they did. And the price is everything. I will have their pain, their suffering, and then their lives. I am not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fight-for-you-lili-valente/">Fight for You &#8211; Lili Valente</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Warning: A dark, sexy, boundary-pushing read.They destroyed the woman I love. Now I&#8217;m going to make them wish they had never been born.The frat boys who hurt Sam will pay the price for what they did. And the price is everything. I will have their pain, their suffering, and then their lives. I am not the man I was last summer; I&#8217;m a stone cold bastard with a lump of ice where my heart used to be.They drove Sam away from me and now there is nothing left to lose. And then I see her&#8230;walking through the airport in Costa Rica.It&#8217;s Sam. She&#8217;s alive and here for the same reason I am&#8211;to take vengeance.It doesn&#8217;t take long to figure out we&#8217;re as perfect together as we&#8217;ve always been. Now we just have to decide&#8211;carry through with our dark plans, or get out before it&#8217;s too late.READER ALERT: This is the second half of Danny and Sam&#8217;s story and should be read after Run With Me.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fight-for-you-lili-valente/">Fight for You &#8211; Lili Valente</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pestilence (The Four Horsemen Book #1) &#8211; Laura Thalassa</title>
		<link>/pestilence-the-four-horsemen-book-1-laura-thalassa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pestilence-the-four-horsemen-book-1-laura-thalassa/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>They came to earth-Pestilence, War, Famine, Death-four horsemen riding their screaming steeds, racing to the corners of the world. Four horsemen with the power to destroy all of humanity. They came to earth, and they came to end us all. When Pestilence comes for Sara Burn&#8217;s town, one thing is certain: everyone she knows and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pestilence-the-four-horsemen-book-1-laura-thalassa/">Pestilence (The Four Horsemen Book #1) &#8211; Laura Thalassa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>They came to earth-Pestilence, War, Famine, Death-four horsemen riding their screaming steeds, racing to the corners of the world. Four horsemen with the power to destroy all of humanity. They came to earth, and they came to end us all.    </p>
<p>                    When Pestilence comes for Sara Burn&#8217;s town, one thing is certain: everyone she knows and loves is marked for death. Unless, of course, the angelic-looking horseman is stopped, which is exactly what Sara has in mind when she shoots the unholy beast off his steed.    </p>
<p>                    Too bad no one told her Pestilence can&#8217;t be killed.    </p>
<p>                    Now the horseman, very much alive and very pissed off, has taken her prisoner, and he&#8217;s eager to make her suffer. Only, the longer she&#8217;s with him, the more uncertain she is about his true feelings towards her &#8230; and hers towards him.    </p>
<p>                    And now, well, Sara might still be able to save the world, but in order to do so, she&#8217;ll have to sacrifice her heart in the process.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pestilence-the-four-horsemen-book-1-laura-thalassa/">Pestilence (The Four Horsemen Book #1) &#8211; Laura Thalassa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Accidental Mermaid &#8211; Hollie Jackson, Dakota Cassidy</title>
		<link>/the-accidental-mermaid-hollie-jackson-dakota-cassidy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-accidental-mermaid-hollie-jackson-dakota-cassidy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Esther Williams Sanchez is busy living her life the way she&#8217;s always done. Spending time with her pets, working as a divorce mediator, and enjoying her newly renovated cottage on the beach. She&#8217;s also decided it&#8217;s high time she learn how to swim to prepare for an upcoming cruise. It&#8217;s time to let go of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-mermaid-hollie-jackson-dakota-cassidy/">The Accidental Mermaid &#8211; Hollie Jackson, Dakota Cassidy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Esther Williams Sanchez is busy living her life the way she&#8217;s always done. Spending time with her pets, working as a divorce mediator, and enjoying her newly renovated cottage on the beach. She&#8217;s also decided it&#8217;s high time she learn how to swim to prepare for an upcoming cruise. It&#8217;s time to let go of a horrible past experience and take some lessons. So at thirty-two, Esther enrolls in the only class at the Y with a spot left. A Mommy and Me class-which seems quite tame, considering her oldest classmate aside from her is three-years-old. Learn to swim with a bunch of babies and toddlers? Easy-squeezy, right? Er, no. As Esther leaves the pool after her very first lesson, she sprouts a magnificent tail and fins. Oh, and hair the color of a rainbow. Lots and lots of luscious hair. Lucky for her, the OOPS girls are on site, and as they set about finding out how this happened to Esther, they run into a hunky Australian merman named Tucker Pearson who happens to be the key to Esther&#8217;s problem. But Tucker has problems of his own, and they include being kicked out of his family&#8217;s bottled water company, booted from his pod, and accused of embezzling over a million bucks. Oh, and killing someone . . . OOPS, here we go again!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-mermaid-hollie-jackson-dakota-cassidy/">The Accidental Mermaid &#8211; Hollie Jackson, Dakota Cassidy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hard to Handle (The Play Hard Series Book 1) &#8211; K Bromberg</title>
		<link>/hard-to-handle-the-play-hard-series-book-1-k-bromberg/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hard-to-handle-the-play-hard-series-book-1-k-bromberg/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author K. Bromberg is back with an all new second-chance, standalone hockey romance. At first, the request seemed simple-sign a new athlete to the agency. Then I found out the new athlete was none other than the most wanted man in hockey today: Hunter Maddox Gifted. Sexy. At the top of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hard-to-handle-the-play-hard-series-book-1-k-bromberg/">Hard to Handle (The Play Hard Series Book 1) &#8211; K Bromberg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author K. Bromberg is back with an all new second-chance, standalone hockey romance.     </p>
<p>                    At first, the request seemed simple-sign a new athlete to the agency.     </p>
<p>                    Then I found out the new athlete was none other than the most wanted man in hockey today: Hunter Maddox     </p>
<p>                    Gifted. Sexy. At the top of his game. And the only man who has ever broken my heart.     </p>
<p>                    If signing him will help save our family business, I&#8217;ll swallow my pride and do what&#8217;s asked.     </p>
<p>                    But when it becomes clear his uncharacteristic antics off the ice are a hint of something deeper, keeping things strictly professional between us becomes more than complicated. But I know better than to cross that line.    </p>
<p>                    I&#8217;ll never date a client. Not even for him.     </p>
<p>                    ***     </p>
<p>                    Win the Stanley Cup and do it before time runs out.     </p>
<p>                    Not a small feat, but it&#8217;s what&#8217;s motivated me since the start of my career.     </p>
<p>                    And time is running out.     </p>
<p>                    Enter Dekker Kincade.     </p>
<p>                    Feisty. Dogged. Damn gorgeous. The one I let get away.     </p>
<p>                    I have no idea why she&#8217;s traveling with the team, but hell if resisting her is going to be easy.     </p>
<p>                    But I have a job to do, and I refuse to lose sight of that end game. Even if she confuses me. Even if she sees parts of me I&#8217;ve hidden from the world.     </p>
<p>                    I can&#8217;t lose focus. Not even for her.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hard-to-handle-the-play-hard-series-book-1-k-bromberg/">Hard to Handle (The Play Hard Series Book 1) &#8211; K Bromberg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Newly Witch Game : Magic and Mayhem Universe: Magic and Mayhem, Book Ten &#8211; Robyn Peterman</title>
		<link>/the-newly-witch-game-magic-and-mayhem-universe-magic-and-mayhem-book-ten-robyn-peterman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-newly-witch-game-magic-and-mayhem-universe-magic-and-mayhem-book-ten-robyn-peterman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s all fun and games until someone throws a dirty jumper rollup and you lose out in the Cornhole tournament of life. According to Baba Yoscarybutt, it&#8217;s time for me to witch up or step back down into the Cornholio minor leagues. While Cornhole is definitely not my beanbag, I can&#8217;t stand to lose. I [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-newly-witch-game-magic-and-mayhem-universe-magic-and-mayhem-book-ten-robyn-peterman/">The Newly Witch Game : Magic and Mayhem Universe: Magic and Mayhem, Book Ten &#8211; Robyn Peterman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s all fun and games until someone throws a dirty jumper rollup and you lose out in the Cornhole tournament of life.    </p>
<p>                    According to Baba Yoscarybutt, it&#8217;s time for me to witch up or step back down into the Cornholio minor leagues. While Cornhole is definitely not my beanbag, I can&#8217;t stand to lose.    </p>
<p>                    I don&#8217;t want to be the next Baba Yaga. I&#8217;m doing just peachy as the Shifter Wanker who heals the clumsy idiots of Assjacket, West Virginia. I love my life. My werewolf mate is hotter than asphalt in August, my twins are adorable, my dad and brother rock, and I have real friends for the first time in my life.    </p>
<p>                    However, when my evil nemesis, Medusa Jones, steps up to throw a floppy bag and steal the title of Future Baba Yaga from me, all bets are off.    </p>
<p>                    I will challenge the nasty piece of work to win back the job I didn&#8217;t want in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    With Sassy and Fuc*ing Derrick by my side, I will finally own my destiny. Of course, Fuc*ing Derrick is prone to meltdowns and Sassy is trying to learn Canadian, but one deals with the floppy bags they&#8217;ve been dealt and tosses them anyway.    </p>
<p>                    It will be dangerous.    </p>
<p>                    It will be cornfusing.    </p>
<p>                    It will be fashionably disastrous.    </p>
<p>                    It will be televised on the magical Charm Channel.    </p>
<p>                    Whatever. A few four baggers, a couple of woodies, a Bigfoot and spell or two should do the trick.    </p>
<p>                    The future of the magical Universe is on the line and I&#8217;m the only one who can save us.    </p>
<p>                    May the Goddess help us all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-newly-witch-game-magic-and-mayhem-universe-magic-and-mayhem-book-ten-robyn-peterman/">The Newly Witch Game : Magic and Mayhem Universe: Magic and Mayhem, Book Ten &#8211; Robyn Peterman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Protector &#8211; Alanea Alder</title>
		<link>/my-protector-alanea-alder/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-protector-alanea-alder/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gavriel Ambrosios has been dreaming of his accident prone mate for weeks. Now that he is nearing the apex of his vampiric transition, she has made her way to Lycaonia, just when he is at his most dangerous. Elizabeth Monroe was planning on staying in Lycaonia while humans forgot about the swan dive she took [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-protector-alanea-alder/">My Protector &#8211; Alanea Alder</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gavriel Ambrosios has been dreaming of his accident prone mate for weeks. Now that he is nearing the apex of his vampiric transition, she has made her way to Lycaonia, just when he is at his most dangerous. Elizabeth Monroe was planning on staying in Lycaonia while humans forgot about the swan dive she took out of her boss&#8217;s office window. Little did she know that this short side trip was about to become permanent. Gavriel is the mate she has always dreamed of. Even as he sweeps her off her feet his need to protect her has him pushing her away. She&#8217;s both concerned with and drawn to his darker nature, but is determined to see him through his transition. In the shadows their enemy has targeted Gavriel when they know he is at his most vulnerable. They creep ever closer to the Alpha estate putting the men on high alert. But as the days get shorter and the nights get longer Elizabeth begins to wonder, which is the bigger threat? The enemy or her mate?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-protector-alanea-alder/">My Protector &#8211; Alanea Alder</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dragon Unleashed &#8211; Eve Langlais</title>
		<link>/dragon-unleashed-eve-langlais/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dragon-unleashed-eve-langlais/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every dragon hoard starts with something&#8230;or someone. Tomas hates scientists, especially since they abused him in such vile ways. And yet, there is something about the doctor that calms his inner beast. Tomas craves her. A treasure for his collection, but how can he convince her to stay? Chandra is frightened by the dragon keeping [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dragon-unleashed-eve-langlais/">Dragon Unleashed &#8211; Eve Langlais</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every dragon hoard starts with something&#8230;or someone.    </p>
<p>                    Tomas hates scientists, especially since they abused him in such vile ways. And yet, there is something about the doctor that calms his inner beast.    </p>
<p>                    Tomas craves her. A treasure for his collection, but how can he convince her to stay?    </p>
<p>                    Chandra is frightened by the dragon keeping her prisoner in his aerie. He&#8217;s been hurt so who can blame him for the madness within? However she sees a glimmer of goodness too. Can he open his heart enough to let her in, or will he unleash his fury upon the world?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dragon-unleashed-eve-langlais/">Dragon Unleashed &#8211; Eve Langlais</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ice Planet Barbarians &#8211; Ruby Dixon</title>
		<link>/ice-planet-barbarians-ruby-dixon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ice-planet-barbarians-ruby-dixon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The international publishing phenomenon Ice Planet Barbarians, now in a special print edition! Fall in love with the out-of-this-world romance between Georgie Carruthers, a human woman, and Vektal, an alien from another planet, in this expanded edition with bonus materials and an exclusive epilogue&#8211;in print only! You&#8217;d think being abducted by aliens would be the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ice-planet-barbarians-ruby-dixon/">Ice Planet Barbarians &#8211; Ruby Dixon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The international publishing phenomenon Ice Planet Barbarians,  now in a special print edition!    </p>
<p>                    Fall in love with the out-of-this-world romance between Georgie Carruthers, a human woman, and Vektal, an alien from another planet, in this expanded edition with bonus materials and an exclusive epilogue&#8211;in print only!     </p>
<p>                    You&#8217;d think being abducted by aliens would be the worst thing that could happen to me. And you&#8217;d be wrong. Because now the aliens are having ship trouble, and they&#8217;ve left their cargo of human women&#8211;including me&#8211;on an ice planet.     </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;re not equipped for life in this desolate winter wasteland. Since I&#8217;m the unofficial leader, I head out into the snow to look for help.     </p>
<p>                    I find help all right. A big blue horned alien introduces himself in a rather . . . startling way. Vektal says that I&#8217;m his mate, his chosen female&#8211;and that the reason his chest is purring is because of my presence. He&#8217;ll help me and my people survive, but this poses a new problem.     </p>
<p>                    If Vektal helps us survive, I&#8217;m not sure he&#8217;s going to want to let me go.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ice-planet-barbarians-ruby-dixon/">Ice Planet Barbarians &#8211; Ruby Dixon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dirt on Ninth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</title>
		<link>/the-dirt-on-ninth-grave-darynda-jones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dirt-on-ninth-grave-darynda-jones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a small village in New York Charley Davidson is living as Jane Doe, a girl with no memory of who she is or where she came from. So when she is working at a diner and slowly begins to realize she can see dead people, she&#8217;s more than a little taken aback. Stranger still [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dirt-on-ninth-grave-darynda-jones/">The Dirt on Ninth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a small village in New York Charley Davidson is living as Jane Doe, a girl with no memory of who she is or where she came from. So when she is working at a diner and slowly begins to realize she can see dead people, she&#8217;s more than a little taken aback. Stranger still are the people entering her life. They seem to know things about her. Things they hide with lies and half-truths. Soon, she senses something far darker. A force that wants to cause her harm, she is sure of it. Her saving grace comes in the form of a new friend she feels she can confide in and the fry cook, a devastatingly handsome man whose smile is breathtaking and touch is scalding. He stays close, and she almost feels safe with him around.  But no one can outrun their past, and the more lies that swirl around her-even from her new and trusted friends-the more disoriented she becomes, until she is confronted by a man who claims to have been sent to kill her. Sent by the darkest force in the universe. A force that absolutely will not stop until she is dead. Thankfully, she has a Rottweiler. But that doesn&#8217;t help in her quest to find her identity and recover what she&#8217;s lost.<br />
                    That will take all her courage and a touch of the power she feels flowing like electricity through her veins. She almost feels sorry for him. The devil in blue jeans. The disarming fry cook who lies with every breath he takes. She will get to the bottom of what he knows if it kills her. Or him. Either way.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dirt-on-ninth-grave-darynda-jones/">The Dirt on Ninth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rescuing Bryn &#8211; Susan Stoker</title>
		<link>/rescuing-bryn-susan-stoker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rescuing-bryn-susan-stoker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When you&#8217;re a Delta Force soldier, you see a lot. Often too much. But nothing can ever prepare you to see your entire team die before your eyes&#8230; The loss of his Delta brothers-and his arm-has Dane &#8220;Fish&#8221; Munroe still struggling months later. He&#8217;s moved to Idaho, where an isolated lifestyle is making things worse, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rescuing-bryn-susan-stoker/">Rescuing Bryn &#8211; Susan Stoker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When you&#8217;re a Delta Force soldier, you see a lot. Often too much. But nothing can ever prepare you to see your entire team die before your eyes&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    The loss of his Delta brothers-and his arm-has Dane &#8220;Fish&#8221; Munroe still struggling months later. He&#8217;s moved to Idaho, where an isolated lifestyle is making things worse, not better. Not that there&#8217;s anyone left to care.    </p>
<p>                    Actually, Bryn Hartwell cares. In fact, she tries to surreptitiously make life just a little easier for the mysterious man who comes into the grocery where she works late at night, only to get a tongue lashing for her trouble. Still, he&#8217;s obviously hurting; someone has to worry about him, spurring Bryn to nurse Dane when he hits a particularly low point.    </p>
<p>                    Intrigued by the quirky, kind, socially awkward woman, Dane allows himself to get close to someone for the first time in ages. A potentially epic mistake-because when her interest in the prepper lifestyle puts Bryn in the hands of a homegrown terrorist, losing her could put Dane&#8217;s mental recovery permanently out of reach.    </p>
<p>                    But once a Delta, always a Delta. And there&#8217;s a team in Texas who are ready to have Dane&#8217;s back at a moment&#8217;s notice.    </p>
<p>                    **Rescuing Bryn is the 6th book in the Delta Force Heroes Series. Each book is a stand-alone, with no cliffhanger endings.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rescuing-bryn-susan-stoker/">Rescuing Bryn &#8211; Susan Stoker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shelter &#8211; Aaron Abano, Paula Hoffman, Jay Crownover</title>
		<link>/shelter-aaron-abano-paula-hoffman-jay-crownover/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Westerns]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shelter-aaron-abano-paula-hoffman-jay-crownover/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>His life is chaos and confusion. It&#8217;s a storm of uncertainty and raging emotion. Sutton Warner is a mess. Everything in his life feels like it&#8217;s unraveling. He&#8217;s let a lot of people down lately, including his daughter. Sutton always promised his little girl he would never disappoint her and that he would always be [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shelter-aaron-abano-paula-hoffman-jay-crownover/">Shelter &#8211; Aaron Abano, Paula Hoffman, Jay Crownover</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>His life is chaos and confusion. It&#8217;s a storm of uncertainty and raging emotion. Sutton Warner is a mess. Everything in his life feels like it&#8217;s unraveling. He&#8217;s let a lot of people down lately, including his daughter. Sutton always promised his little girl he would never disappoint her and that he would always be there when she needed him. Until he wasn&#8217;t. The truth is, he&#8217;s used to disappointing the women in his life. First was his mother who couldn&#8217;t find a reason to stick around when he was growing up. Then there&#8217;s his ex. The woman who takes unbridled delight in making his life incredibly complicated. Luckily, his daughter is still young enough to believe her old man is some kind of hero. But he knows the day is coming when she realizes the truth, that he&#8217;s just a man with some serious flaws and a list of ever-growing weaknesses. Finally, there&#8217;s the woman he&#8217;s desperately trying to forget with every shot tossed back and each pill popped. He more than disappointed Emrys&#8230;. He almost got her killed. Her love is steady and sure. It&#8217;s a shelter shaped by conviction and silent assurance.     </p>
<p>                    Emrys Santos is lost. Everything in her life feels pointless and futile. She&#8217;s been busy running away from her feelings and all the people who love her the most &#8211; including her best friend, the one person who knows exactly what she&#8217;s been through. They promised to always stick together and to lean on one another. It was a promise Em had to break so she could lick her wounds and figure out her next move. For once, there is no easy way out of the tangled web of emotions she&#8217;s caught up in, and right now, she recognizes that all roads lead back to Wyoming&#8230;and back to Sutton. The man she nearly got killed.     </p>
<p>                    Shelter is a standalone novel, the second book in the Getaway series, which features the hardheaded and brokenhearted Warner brothers and the women who dare to love them. These boys are very good at putting the wild in wilderness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shelter-aaron-abano-paula-hoffman-jay-crownover/">Shelter &#8211; Aaron Abano, Paula Hoffman, Jay Crownover</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Cowboy&#8217;s Heart &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</title>
		<link>/a-cowboys-heart-vicki-lewis-thompson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Westerns]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-cowboys-heart-vicki-lewis-thompson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>His muse just strolled in&#8230; Getting left at the altar killed the music in Bryce McGavin&#8217;s soul. But when a guitar-toting redhead with the voice of an angel walks into the Guzzling Grizzly and asks for an audition, his toe starts tapping. Maybe there&#8217;s life in his battered heart after all. Unfortunately, wooing Nicole Williams [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-cowboys-heart-vicki-lewis-thompson/">A Cowboy&#8217;s Heart &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>His muse just strolled in&#8230;<br />
                     Getting left at the altar killed the music in Bryce McGavin&#8217;s soul. But when a guitar-toting redhead with the voice of an angel walks into the Guzzling Grizzly and asks for an audition, his toe starts tapping. Maybe there&#8217;s life in his battered heart after all. Unfortunately, wooing Nicole Williams means dusting off his guitar&#8230;and convincing her attack cat to let him through the front door. A wise man might leave well enough alone. But Bryce never was a wise man&#8230;</p>
<p>                     Saddle up for the fourth book in the popular McGavin Brothers series of steamy western romances from the NYT bestselling author who brought you the Buckskin Brotherhood series. If you like sexy cowboys, charming small towns, and laugh-out-loud adventures, you&#8217;ll love A Cowboy&#8217;s Heart. Pick up your copy today!</p>
<p>                     THE MCGAVIN BROTHERS<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Strength (Book 1)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Honor (Book 2)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Return (Book 3)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Heart (Book 4)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Courage (Book 5)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Christmas (Book 6)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Kiss (Book 7)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Luck (Book 8)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Charm (Book 9)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Challenge (Book 10)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Baby (Book 11)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Holiday (Book 12)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Choice (Book 13)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Worth (Book 14)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Destiny (Book 15)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Secret (Book 16)<br />
                     A Cowboy&#8217;s Homecoming (Book 17)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-cowboys-heart-vicki-lewis-thompson/">A Cowboy&#8217;s Heart &#8211; Vicki Lewis Thompson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark in Death : An Eve Dallas thriller (Book 46) &#8211; J. D. Robb</title>
		<link>/dark-in-death-an-eve-dallas-thriller-book-46-j-d-robb/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-in-death-an-eve-dallas-thriller-book-46-j-d-robb/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s always a reason for murder. But when a young actress is killed in a swift and violent attack at a cinema screening, that reason is hard to fathom &#8211; even for Lieutenant Eve Dallas and her team. It&#8217;s only when bestselling crime writer Blaine DeLano arrives at the precinct that the shocking truth is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-in-death-an-eve-dallas-thriller-book-46-j-d-robb/">Dark in Death : An Eve Dallas thriller (Book 46) &#8211; J. D. Robb</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s always a reason for murder. But when a young actress is killed in a swift and violent attack at a cinema screening, that reason is hard to fathom &#8211; even for Lieutenant Eve Dallas and her team.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s only when bestselling crime writer Blaine DeLano arrives at the precinct that the shocking truth is revealed. Someone is recreating the murder scenes from her latest series, book by book. With six more novels left in the series, Eve now knows how the killer will strike next. But why has DeLano been targeted? Could her abusive husband be involved?    </p>
<p>                    As fiction is transformed into bloody reality, Eve will need all her skill and experience to solve this unique case. Luckily for her, husband Roarke happens to be a fan of Delano&#8217;s work. And he&#8217;s more than happy to work side by side with his brilliant wife &#8211; no matter how dark things become&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-in-death-an-eve-dallas-thriller-book-46-j-d-robb/">Dark in Death : An Eve Dallas thriller (Book 46) &#8211; J. D. Robb</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myth Manifestation &#8211; Johanna Parker, Lisa Shearin</title>
		<link>/the-myth-manifestation-johanna-parker-lisa-shearin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myth-manifestation-johanna-parker-lisa-shearin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The agents of Supernatural Protection &#038; Investigations (SPI) protect people from predatory supernaturals. This time, we&#8217;re the ones who need protection. New York is one of the most popular convention destinations in the world&#8211;for humans and supernaturals. Every hundred years, rulers of the world&#8217;s supernatural races come together to negotiate and renew a peace treaty. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-manifestation-johanna-parker-lisa-shearin/">The Myth Manifestation &#8211; Johanna Parker, Lisa Shearin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The agents of Supernatural Protection &#038; Investigations (SPI) protect people from predatory supernaturals. This time, we&#8217;re the ones who need protection.     </p>
<p>                    New York is one of the most popular convention destinations in the world&#8211;for humans and supernaturals. Every hundred years, rulers of the world&#8217;s supernatural races come together to negotiate and renew a peace treaty. Meeting in the same hotel are the governors of our world&#8217;s goblin and elf colonies. SPI is saddled with the security nightmare of keeping the living delegates alive and the undead delegates from becoming permanently deceased. We&#8217;ve got our work cut out for us.     </p>
<p>                    I&#8217;m Makenna Fraser, seer for SPI. Our security nightmare becomes real when monsters from the delegates&#8217; mythologies begin mysteriously appearing in the flesh to hunt delegates from every side of the debate. And when the hotel gets sucked into another dimension, there&#8217;s no escape. We discover that we&#8217;re all pieces in an elaborate and deadly game. A game about to spill out into the real world. Failing to escape is game over and not an option. We have to save the world&#8211;but first, we have to save ourselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-manifestation-johanna-parker-lisa-shearin/">The Myth Manifestation &#8211; Johanna Parker, Lisa Shearin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Brightest Embers Lib/E &#8211; Jeaniene Frost, Read by Tavia Gilbert</title>
		<link>/the-brightest-embers-lib-e-jeaniene-frost-read-by-tavia-gilbert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-brightest-embers-lib-e-jeaniene-frost-read-by-tavia-gilbert/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You can run from your destiny, but you can&#8217;t hide &#8230; Ivy thought that she and Adrian had conquered their fates. Yet with thousands of innocents still trapped in the demon realms, she&#8217;s determined to locate the final hallowed weapon and harness its unparalleled power to free them. But the last relic nearly put Ivy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brightest-embers-lib-e-jeaniene-frost-read-by-tavia-gilbert/">The Brightest Embers Lib/E &#8211; Jeaniene Frost, Read by Tavia Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You can run from your destiny, but you can&#8217;t hide &#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Ivy thought that she and Adrian had conquered their fates. Yet with thousands of innocents still trapped in the demon realms, she&#8217;s determined to locate the final hallowed weapon and harness its unparalleled power to free them. But the last relic nearly put Ivy in the grave-there&#8217;s probably no coming back from this one.     </p>
<p>                    Adrian&#8217;s dark lineage has made him the most powerful of his kind, yet even his incredible abilities might not be enough now. Instead, the treacherous fate he has fought so hard to escape might be the only way he can save Ivy. Their scintillating bond has been tested before, but never with so much on the line. Now fate will come head-to-head against true love, and nothing they&#8217;ve endured can prepare Ivy and Adrian for the unthinkable choices they&#8217;ll face.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brightest-embers-lib-e-jeaniene-frost-read-by-tavia-gilbert/">The Brightest Embers Lib/E &#8211; Jeaniene Frost, Read by Tavia Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Trouble With Twelfth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</title>
		<link>/the-trouble-with-twelfth-grave-darynda-jones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-trouble-with-twelfth-grave-darynda-jones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ever since Reyes escaped from a hell dimension in which Charley accidently trapped him, the son of Satan has been brimstone &#8211; bent on destroying the world his heavenly Brother created. His volatile tendencies have put Charley in a bit of a pickle. But that&#8217;s not the only briny vegetable on her plate. While trying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-trouble-with-twelfth-grave-darynda-jones/">The Trouble With Twelfth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ever since Reyes escaped from a hell dimension in which Charley accidently trapped him, the son of Satan has been brimstone &#8211; bent on destroying the world his heavenly Brother created. His volatile tendencies have put Charley in a bit of a pickle. But that&#8217;s not the only briny vegetable on her plate. While trying to domesticate the feral being that used to be her husband, she also has to deal with her everyday life of annoying all manner of beings &#8211; some corporeal, some not so much &#8211; as she struggles to right the wrongs of society. Only this time she&#8217;s not uncovering a murder. This time she&#8217;s covering one up.  Add to that her new occupation of keeping a startup PI venture &#8211; the indomitable mystery-solving team of Amber Kowalski and Quentin Rutherford &#8211; out of trouble and dealing with the Vatican&#8217;s inquiries into her beloved daughter, and Charley is on the brink of throwing in the towel and becoming a professional shopper. Or possibly a live mannequin. But when someone starts attacking humans who are sensitive to the supernatural world, Charley knows it&#8217;s time to let loose her razor sharp claws. Then again, her number one suspect is the dark entity she&#8217;s loved for centuries.<br />
                    So the question becomes, can she tame the unruly beast before it destroys everything she&#8217;s worked so hard to protect?    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-trouble-with-twelfth-grave-darynda-jones/">The Trouble With Twelfth Grave &#8211; Darynda Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wifed by the Mountain Man &#8211; Joe Arden, Katie McAble, Frankie Love</title>
		<link>/wifed-by-the-mountain-man-joe-arden-katie-mcable-frankie-love/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wifed-by-the-mountain-man-joe-arden-katie-mcable-frankie-love/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s the sexiest thing I&#8217;ve ever seen.&#8221; She laughs softly. &#8220;Reed, you&#8217;ve been alone far too long if a woman putting a baby to sleep is the thing that gets you hard.&#8221; &#8220;Oh, honey.&#8221; I pull her close. &#8220;Plenty gets me hard.&#8221; &#8220;Show me,&#8221; she whispers. &#8220;Show me how hard you can get.&#8221; Reed When [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wifed-by-the-mountain-man-joe-arden-katie-mcable-frankie-love/">Wifed by the Mountain Man &#8211; Joe Arden, Katie McAble, Frankie Love</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;That&#8217;s the sexiest thing I&#8217;ve ever seen.&#8221; She laughs softly. &#8220;Reed, you&#8217;ve been alone far too long if a woman putting a baby to sleep is the thing that gets you hard.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Oh, honey.&#8221; I pull her close. &#8220;Plenty gets me hard.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Show me,&#8221; she whispers. &#8220;Show me how hard you can get.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Reed     </p>
<p>                    When a social worker dropped a baby girl off at my cabin, saying she was mine, my life changed. I moved to the mountains to live life on my own terms, and having a child doesn&#8217;t fit into that plan. I&#8217;m my own f&#8211;king man and don&#8217;t need anyone busting my balls. I don&#8217;t want a wife. I&#8217;m looking for a mother for my baby. The moment I meet Amelia, I know she isn&#8217;t just any woman. She has ideas of how a relationship should work, and our views sure as hell don&#8217;t align. But our chemistry is off the motherf&#8211;king charts, and that might be enough to change my mind about what makes a marriage.     </p>
<p>                    Amelia     </p>
<p>                    After breaking up with the douchebag of the year, all I want is a real man who knows how to take care of a woman. A mountain man seems perfect; I&#8217;ll tame him and he can protect me. But the moment I walk into Reed&#8217;s luxury cabin in the woods I realize this deal is more than I bargained for. I want to be housewife, but a stay-at-home mom? Um. I don&#8217;t know if I can hack it. And even if I can, do I want to? The answer would be easy if Reed didn&#8217;t turn me on &#8211; and get me off &#8211; so perfectly. I came to the woods to find my happily-ever-after, but I might have found an ending I never expected.     </p>
<p>                    Warning: This book contains all the trappings for a steamy Frankie Love romance. Panty-melting sex, fierce men, and true love. Oh, and there&#8217;s an epilogue with all the girls and their mountain men! Eep!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wifed-by-the-mountain-man-joe-arden-katie-mcable-frankie-love/">Wifed by the Mountain Man &#8211; Joe Arden, Katie McAble, Frankie Love</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moonshadow &#8211; Thea Harrison</title>
		<link>/moonshadow-thea-harrison/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/moonshadow-thea-harrison/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From bestselling author Thea Harrison comes the first in an explosive new trilogy set in the Elder Races world&#8230;. Her past is a blank, her future uncertain&#8230;. Recovering from a shooting, LAPD witch consultant Sophie Ross leaves her job and travels to the U.K. to search for answers about her childhood. When she encounters a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moonshadow-thea-harrison/">Moonshadow &#8211; Thea Harrison</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From bestselling author Thea Harrison comes the first in an explosive new trilogy set in the Elder Races world&#8230;.    </p>
<p>                    Her past is a blank, her future uncertain&#8230;.    </p>
<p>                    Recovering from a shooting, LAPD witch consultant Sophie Ross leaves her job and travels to the U.K. to search for answers about her childhood. When she encounters a Daoine Sidhe knight of the Dark Court, she becomes entangled in an ancient hatred between two arcane forces.    </p>
<p>                    He has given his body and soul to fight for his people&#8230;.    </p>
<p>                    Barred from his homeland along with his surviving brother knights, Nikolas Sevigny is embroiled in a conflict that threatens everything he holds dear. Only by uniting his people&#8217;s resources can they hope to prevail against Isabeau, the deadly Queen of the Light Court. He will do anything and use anyone to return home to Lyonesse.    </p>
<p>                    When Nikolas encounters Sophie, he sees a tool to be used. The insouciant witch might be the key to unlocking every passageway that has been barred to the knights of the Dark Court, even as a fascination for her takes root in what&#8217;s left of his soul.    </p>
<p>                    Sophie has no intention of becoming anyone&#8217;s pawn, yet the fierce Nikolas is so compelling, she can&#8217;t deny the temptation that endangers her guarded heart.    </p>
<p>                    As magic threatens Lyonesse, Queen Isabeau unleashes her merciless Hounds, and Nikolas and Sophie become embroiled in a race for survival. Meanwhile, the passion that ignites between them burns too hot to be denied and quickly turns into obsession.    </p>
<p>                    Thank goodness they both know better than to fall in love&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moonshadow-thea-harrison/">Moonshadow &#8211; Thea Harrison</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ghoul Vendetta : A Spi Files Novel &#8211; Lisa Shearin</title>
		<link>/the-ghoul-vendetta-a-spi-files-novel-lisa-shearin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ghoul-vendetta-a-spi-files-novel-lisa-shearin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Men in Black meets Janet Evanovich&#8217;s Stephanie Plum in the fourth urban fantasy novel in the series starring seer Makenna Fraser and her fellow agents at Supernatural Protection &#038; Investigation. The agents of Supernatural Protection &#038; Investigations (SPI) are paid to keep the peace. But that&#8217;s not so easy when an endless evil threatens to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ghoul-vendetta-a-spi-files-novel-lisa-shearin/">The Ghoul Vendetta : A Spi Files Novel &#8211; Lisa Shearin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Men in Black meets Janet Evanovich&#8217;s Stephanie Plum in the fourth urban fantasy novel in the series starring seer Makenna Fraser and her fellow agents at Supernatural Protection &#038; Investigation.     </p>
<p>                    The agents of Supernatural Protection &#038; Investigations (SPI) are paid to keep the peace. But that&#8217;s not so easy when an endless evil threatens to tear that peace to pieces&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    A vampire gangster&#8217;s nephew is abducted off his yacht by a bunch of low-rent Creatures from the Black Lagoon. A slew of banks are knocked over by what looks like the cast of Night of the Living Dead. All of this may seem like the movies, but, I promise you, it&#8217;s not.     </p>
<p>                    I&#8217;m Makenna Fraser, seer for SPI, and I know the culprits aren&#8217;t wearing disguises or makeup. They&#8217;re real. Deadly real. Especially their leader&#8211;an ancient shapeshifter who leaves a trail of chaos and blood in his wake. Now, he&#8217;s taken my partner, Ian&#8211;and his intentions aren&#8217;t pretty.     </p>
<p>                    The worst part? This is only the beginning&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    The beginning of the end of the human race.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ghoul-vendetta-a-spi-files-novel-lisa-shearin/">The Ghoul Vendetta : A Spi Files Novel &#8211; Lisa Shearin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</title>
		<link>/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER A RICHARD AND JUDY BOOKCLUB PICK &#8216;Utterly engrossing&#8217; Guardian It is wash-day for the housemaids at Longbourn House, and Sarah&#8217;s hands are chapped and raw. Domestic life below stairs, ruled with a tender heart and an iron will by Mrs Hill the housekeeper, is about to be disturbed by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/">Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER<br />
                    A RICHARD AND JUDY BOOKCLUB PICK<br />
                    &#8216;Utterly engrossing&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    It is wash-day for the housemaids at Longbourn House, and Sarah&#8217;s hands are chapped and raw. Domestic life below stairs, ruled with a tender heart and an iron will by Mrs Hill the housekeeper, is about to be disturbed by the arrival of a new footman, bearing secrets and the scent of the sea.    </p>
<p>                    What readers are saying:    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A novel to be savoured&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;Highly recommended&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;Very enjoyable exploration of the background to Pride and Prejudice&#8217;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/">Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
