<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Taxation Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/taxation/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/taxation/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Taxation Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/taxation/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</title>
		<link>/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate. Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate.    </p>
<p>                    Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence to challenge the idea that different economic outcomes can be explained by any one factor, be it discrimination, exploitation, or genetics. This revised and enlarged edition also analyzes the human consequences of the prevailing social vision of these disparities and the policies based on that vision&#8211;from educational disasters to widespread crime and violence.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Economics of Taxation: Principles, Policy and Practice 2012/13 &#8211; Simon R. James</title>
		<link>/the-economics-of-taxation-principles-policy-and-practice-2012-13-simon-r-james/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation & Duties Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-economics-of-taxation-principles-policy-and-practice-2012-13-simon-r-james/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For over 30 years this textbook has been the leader in its field. Now revised and updated annually, the 2012/13 edition continues to provide a clear and authoritative introduction to the economic theory of taxation and to its practical operations. Part 1 of the text examines the principles of taxation, whilst Part 2 gives a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economics-of-taxation-principles-policy-and-practice-2012-13-simon-r-james/">The Economics of Taxation: Principles, Policy and Practice 2012/13 &#8211; Simon R. James</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For over 30 years this textbook has been the leader in its field. Now revised and updated annually, the 2012/13 edition continues to provide a clear and authoritative introduction to the economic theory of taxation and to its practical operations. Part 1 of the text examines the principles of taxation, whilst Part 2 gives a broad-based description and evaluation of the policy and practice of the UK&#8217;s tax system, highlighting international comparisons.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economics-of-taxation-principles-policy-and-practice-2012-13-simon-r-james/">The Economics of Taxation: Principles, Policy and Practice 2012/13 &#8211; Simon R. James</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Hidden Wealth of Nations : The Scourge of Tax Havens &#8211; Gabriel Zucman, Translated by Teresa Lavender Fagan, Foreword by Thomas Piketty (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-hidden-wealth-of-nations-the-scourge-of-tax-havens-gabriel-zucman-translated-by-teresa-lavender-fagan-foreword-by-thomas-piketty-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation & Duties Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-hidden-wealth-of-nations-the-scourge-of-tax-havens-gabriel-zucman-translated-by-teresa-lavender-fagan-foreword-by-thomas-piketty-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are well aware of the rise of the 1% as the rapid growth of economic inequality has put the majority of the world&#8217;s wealth in the pockets of fewer and fewer. One much-discussed solution to this imbalance is to significantly increase the rate at which we tax the wealthy. But with an enormous amount [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hidden-wealth-of-nations-the-scourge-of-tax-havens-gabriel-zucman-translated-by-teresa-lavender-fagan-foreword-by-thomas-piketty-abridged/">The Hidden Wealth of Nations : The Scourge of Tax Havens &#8211; Gabriel Zucman, Translated by Teresa Lavender Fagan, Foreword by Thomas Piketty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are well aware of the rise of the 1% as the rapid growth of economic inequality has put the majority of the world&#8217;s wealth in the pockets of fewer and fewer. One much-discussed solution to this imbalance is to significantly increase the rate at which we tax the wealthy. But with an enormous amount of the world&#8217;s wealth hidden in tax havens in countries like Switzerland, Luxembourg, and the Cayman Islands this wealth cannot be fully accounted for and taxed fairly. No one, from economists to bankers to politicians, has been able to quantify exactly how much of the world&#8217;s assets are currently hidden until now. Gabriel Zucman is the first economist to offer reliable insight into the actual extent of the world&#8217;s money held in tax havens. And it&#8217;s staggering. In The Hidden Wealth of Nations, Zucman offers an inventive and sophisticated approach to quantifying how big the problem is, how tax havens work and are organized, and how we can begin to approach a solution. His research reveals that tax havens are a quickly growing danger to the world economy.<br />
                    In the past five years, the amount of wealth in tax havens has increased over 25% there has never been as much money held offshore as there is today. This hidden wealth accounts for at least $7.6 trillion, equivalent to 8% of the global financial assets of households. Fighting the notion that any attempts to vanquish tax havens are futile, since some countries will always offer more advantageous tax rates than others, as well the counter-argument that since the financial crisis tax havens have disappeared, Zucman shows how both sides are actually very wrong. In The Hidden Wealth of Nations he offers an ambitious agenda for reform, focused on ways in which countries can change the incentives of tax havens. Only by first understanding the enormity of the secret wealth can we begin to estimate the kind of actions that would force tax havens to give up their practices. Zucman&#8217;s work has quickly become the gold standard for quantifying the amount of the world&#8217;s assets held in havens.<br />
                    In this concise book, he lays out in approachable language how the international banking system works and the dangerous extent to which the large-scale evasion of taxes is undermining the global market as a whole. If we are to find a way to solve the problem of increasing inequality, The Hidden Wealth of Nations is essential reading.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hidden-wealth-of-nations-the-scourge-of-tax-havens-gabriel-zucman-translated-by-teresa-lavender-fagan-foreword-by-thomas-piketty-abridged/">The Hidden Wealth of Nations : The Scourge of Tax Havens &#8211; Gabriel Zucman, Translated by Teresa Lavender Fagan, Foreword by Thomas Piketty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, Airbnb, Kickstarter, and other innovators, and that we understand money&#8217;s transition from hard currencies to cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin if we are to access their cooperative potential.  The Evolution of Money illuminates this fascinating reality, focusing on the tension between currency&#8217;s real and abstract properties and advancing a vital theory of money rooted in this dual exchange. It begins with the debt tablets of Mesopotamia and follows with the development of coin money in ancient Greece and Rome, gold-backed currencies in medieval Europe, and monetary economics in Victorian England. The book ends in the digital era, with the cryptocurrencies and service providers that are making the most of money&#8217;s virtual side and that suggest a tectonic shift in what we call money.<br />
                    By building this organic time line, The Evolution of Money helps us anticipate money&#8217;s next, transformative role.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Selected as a Financial Times Best Book of 2013 Governments today in both Europe and the United States have succeeded in casting government spending as reckless wastefulness that has made the economy worse. In contrast, they have advanced a policy of draconian budget cuts-austerity-to solve the financial crisis. We are told that we have all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/">Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Selected as a Financial Times Best Book of 2013    </p>
<p>                    Governments today in both Europe and the United States have succeeded in casting government spending as reckless wastefulness that has made the economy worse. In contrast, they have advanced a policy of draconian budget cuts-austerity-to solve the financial crisis. We are told that we have all lived beyond our means and now need to tighten our belts. This view conveniently forgets where all that debt came from. Not from an orgy of government spending, but as the direct result of bailing out,<br />
                    recapitalizing, and adding liquidity to the broken banking system. Through these actions private debt was rechristened as government debt while those responsible for generating it walked away scot free, placing the blame on the state, and the burden on the taxpayer.     </p>
<p>                    That burden now takes the form of a global turn to austerity, the policy of reducing domestic wages and prices to restore competitiveness and balance the budget. The problem, according to political economist Mark Blyth, is that austerity is a very dangerous idea. First of all, it doesn&#8217;t work. As the past four years and countless historical examples from the last 100 years show, while it makes sense for any one state to try and cut its way to growth, it simply cannot work when all states try it<br />
                    simultaneously: all we do is shrink the economy. In the worst case, austerity policies worsened the Great Depression and created the conditions for seizures of power by the forces responsible for the Second World War: the Nazis and the Japanese military establishment. As Blyth amply demonstrates,<br />
                    the arguments for austerity are tenuous and the evidence thin. Rather than expanding growth and opportunity, the repeated revival of this dead economic idea has almost always led to low growth along with increases in wealth and income inequality. Austerity demolishes the conventional wisdom, marshaling an army of facts to demand that we austerity for what it is, and what it costs us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/">Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Treasure Islands : Tax Havens and the Men who Stole the World &#8211; Nicholas Shaxson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Tax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WITH NEW AND UPDATED MATERIAL Billionaire Warren Buffet, currently the third wealthiest man in the world, paid the lowest rate of tax among his office staff, including his receptionist. In 2006 the world&#8217;s three biggest banana companies did nearly GBP400 million worth of business in Britain but paid just GBP128,000 in tax between them. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/">Treasure Islands : Tax Havens and the Men who Stole the World &#8211; Nicholas Shaxson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WITH NEW AND UPDATED MATERIAL    </p>
<p>                    Billionaire Warren Buffet, currently the third wealthiest man in the world, paid the lowest rate of tax among his office staff, including his receptionist.    </p>
<p>                    In 2006 the world&#8217;s three biggest banana companies did nearly GBP400 million worth of business in Britain but paid just GBP128,000 in tax between them.    </p>
<p>                    In January 2009, US law enforcement fined Lloyds TSB $350 million after it admitted secretly channelling Iranian and Sudanese money into the US banking system.    </p>
<p>                    Tax havens are the most important single reason why poor people and poor countries stay poor. They lie at the very heart of the global economy, with over half the world trade processed through them. They have been instrumental in nearly every major economic event, in every big financial scandal, and in every financial crisis since the 1970s, including the latest global economic downturn.     </p>
<p>                    In Treasure Islands, Nicholas Shaxson shows how this happened, and what this means for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/">Treasure Islands : Tax Havens and the Men who Stole the World &#8211; Nicholas Shaxson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
