<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Adoption Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/adoption/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/adoption/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Adoption Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/adoption/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</title>
		<link>/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD *************************** Memphis, Tennessee, 1939 Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story </p>
<p>                    OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD</p>
<p>                    THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD</p>
<p>                    ***************************</p>
<p>                    Memphis, Tennessee, 1939</p>
<p>                    Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. But when their father must rush their mother to the hospital one stormy night, Rill is left in charge, until strangers arrive in force. Wrenched from all that is familiar and thrown into a Tennessee Children&#8217;s Home Society orphanage, the Foss children are assured that they will soon be returned to their parents &#8211; but they quickly realize the dark truth&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Aiken, South Carolina, present day</p>
<p>                    Born into wealth and privilege, Avery Stafford seems to have it all: a successful career, a handsome fiance, and a lavish wedding on the horizon. But when Avery returns home to help her father weather a health crisis, a chance encounter leaves her with uncomfortable questions and compels her to take a journey through her family&#8217;s long-hidden history, on a path that will ultimately lead either to devastation or to redemption.</p>
<p>                    *********************</p>
<p>                    Based on one of America&#8217;s most notorious real-life scandals, in which Georgia Tann, director of a Memphis-based adoption organization, kidnapped and sold poor children to wealthy families all over the country, Before We Were Yours is a riveting, wrenching and ultimately uplifting global bestseller. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A tale of enduring power&#8217; Paula McLain</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is impossible not to get swept up in this near-perfect novel&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chika Jeune was born three days before the devastating earthquake that decimated Haiti in 2010. She spent her infancy in extreme poverty, and when her mother died giving birth to a baby brother, Chika was brought to the Have Faith Haiti Orphanage that Mitch and his wife, Janine operate. Chika&#8217;s arrival made a quick impression. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/">Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chika Jeune was born three days before the devastating earthquake that decimated Haiti in 2010. She spent her infancy in extreme poverty, and when her mother died giving birth to a baby brother, Chika was brought to the Have Faith Haiti Orphanage that Mitch and his wife, Janine operate.    </p>
<p>                    Chika&#8217;s arrival made a quick impression. Brave and self-assured, even as a three-year-old, she delighted the other kids and teachers. But at age five, Chika was suddenly diagnosed with a terminal disease that no doctor in Haiti could help with.    </p>
<p>                    Mitch and Janine took Chika to America, hoping that treatment there would enable her to go back home.  Instead, Chika became a permanent part of their lives, as they embarked on a two-year, around-the-world journey to find a cure. As Chika&#8217;s boundless optimism and humour taught Mitch the joys of caring for a child, he learnt that a relationship built on love, no matter what blows it takes, can never be lost.    </p>
<p>                    This is Mitch Albom at his most poignant, powerful and personal. Chika is a celebration of a girl, her adoptive guardians, and the incredible bond they formed &#8211; a devastatingly beautiful portrait of what it means to be a family, regardless of how it is made.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/">Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
