<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Reference Works Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/reference-works/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/reference-works/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Reference Works Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/reference-works/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stephen King, American Master : A Creepy Corpus of Facts About Stephen King &#038; His Work &#8211; Stephen Spignesi</title>
		<link>/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Companions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fun and informative compendium for Stephen King fans-interviews, essays, and loads of facts and details about all of his work. Fascinating facts, trivia, and little-known details about the Master of the Macabre&#8217;s life and work, plus interviews, essays, and insights for King fans, from the casual to the fanatical! Did you know&#8230;? In his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/">Stephen King, American Master : A Creepy Corpus of Facts About Stephen King &#038; His Work &#8211; Stephen Spignesi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fun and informative compendium for Stephen King fans-interviews, essays, and loads of facts and details about all of his work.</p>
<p>                    Fascinating facts, trivia, and little-known details about the Master of the Macabre&#8217;s life and work, plus interviews, essays, and insights for King fans, from the casual to the fanatical!</p>
<p>                    Did you know&#8230;?</p>
<p>                    In his early teens, Stephen King sold typed copies of his short stories at school.<br />
                    King originally thought his novel Pet Sematary was too frightening to publish.<br />
                    King&#8217;s legendary Dark Tower series took him more than 30 years to write.<br />
                    Thinner was the novel that revealed his &#8220;Richard Bachman&#8221; pseudonym to the world.<br />
                    King wrote The Eyes of the Dragon for his daughter Naomi.<br />
                    He has never liked Stanley Kubrick&#8217;s film version of his novel The Shining.<br />
                    It took him four years to write what some consider his magnum opus, IT.<br />
                    The 2017 film version of IT has grossed more than $700 million worldwide.<br />
                    In addition to novels, King has written essays, plays, screenplays, and even poetry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/">Stephen King, American Master : A Creepy Corpus of Facts About Stephen King &#038; His Work &#8211; Stephen Spignesi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Word by Word : The Secret Life of Dictionaries &#8211; Kory Stamper (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/word-by-word-the-secret-life-of-dictionaries-kory-stamper-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dictionaries & Dictionary Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ELT Background & Reference Material]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language Teaching & Learning Material & Coursework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lexicography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/word-by-word-the-secret-life-of-dictionaries-kory-stamper-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;We think of English as a fortress to be defended, but a better analogy is to think of English as a child. We love and nurture it into being, and once it gains gross motor skills, it starts going exactly where we don&#8217;t want it to go: it heads right for the goddamned electrical sockets.&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/word-by-word-the-secret-life-of-dictionaries-kory-stamper-abridged/">Word by Word : The Secret Life of Dictionaries &#8211; Kory Stamper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;We think of English as a fortress to be defended, but a better analogy is to think of English as a child. We love and nurture it into being, and once it gains gross motor skills, it starts going exactly where we don&#8217;t want it to go: it heads right for the goddamned electrical sockets.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                     With wit and irreverence, lexicographer Kory Stamper cracks open the obsessive world of dictionary writing, from the agonizing decisions about what to define and how to do it to the knotty questions of ever-changing word usage.     </p>
<p>                     Filled with fun facts&#8211;for example, the first documented usage of &#8220;OMG&#8221; was in a letter to Winston Churchill&#8211;and Stamper&#8217;s own stories from the linguistic front lines (including how she became America&#8217;s foremost &#8220;irregardless&#8221; apologist, despite loathing the word), Word by Word is an endlessly entertaining look at the wonderful complexities and eccentricities of the English language.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/word-by-word-the-secret-life-of-dictionaries-kory-stamper-abridged/">Word by Word : The Secret Life of Dictionaries &#8211; Kory Stamper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook : A Practical Guide to Delivering High-value and Differentiated Services in a Competitive Marketplace &#8211; Samir Parikh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Delivers the essential practical skills needed to consult and make sharp, well prepared interactions in a wide range of business situations This comprehensive handbook covers the fundamental skills and attitudes required by successful consultants from novice to practitioner level, irrespective of their specialist area. It untangles the key variables present in any consulting service and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/">The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook : A Practical Guide to Delivering High-value and Differentiated Services in a Competitive Marketplace &#8211; Samir Parikh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Delivers the essential practical skills needed to consult and make sharp, well prepared interactions in a wide range of business situations This comprehensive handbook covers the fundamental skills and attitudes required by successful consultants from novice to practitioner level, irrespective of their specialist area. It untangles the key variables present in any consulting service and introduces practical ways to improve their effectiveness based upon the author&#8217;s experience of helping consulting organisations to develop and excel in the marketplace. The book explores consulting from the ground up&#8217; steering away from theory and focusing instead on practical application, providing a solid platform upon which to build further domain-specific competence. The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook provides: * An understanding of the key variables that can be addressed in order to improve one&#8217;s own consulting performance * A set of simple practices that can be implemented with immediate benefit to the reader * Practical insight into day-to-day real life consulting interactions * Confidence to implement the new ideas and approaches</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/">The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook : A Practical Guide to Delivering High-value and Differentiated Services in a Competitive Marketplace &#8211; Samir Parikh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now a Netflix series! New York Times Bestseller and Winner of the 2018 James Beard Award for Best General Cookbook and multiple IACP Cookbook Awards Named one of the Best Books of 2017 by: NPR, BuzzFeed, The Atlantic, The Washington Post, Chicago Tribune, Rachel Ray Every Day, San Francisco Chronicle, Vice Munchies, Elle.com, Glamour, Eater, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/">Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now a Netflix series!     </p>
<p>                     New York Times Bestseller and Winner of the 2018 James Beard Award for Best General Cookbook and multiple IACP Cookbook Awards      </p>
<p>                     Named one of the Best Books of 2017 by: NPR, BuzzFeed, The Atlantic, The Washington Post, Chicago Tribune, Rachel Ray Every Day, San Francisco Chronicle, Vice Munchies, Elle.com, Glamour, Eater, Newsday, Minneapolis Star Tribune,  The Seattle Times, Tampa Bay Times, Tasting Table, Modern Farmer, Publishers Weekly,  and more.     </p>
<p>                     A visionary new master class in cooking that distills decades of professional experience into just four simple elements, from the woman declared &#8220;America&#8217;s next great cooking teacher&#8221; by Alice Waters.     </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of The Joy of Cooking and How to Cook Everything comes Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat, an ambitious new approach to cooking by a major new culinary voice. Chef and writer Samin Nosrat has taught everyone from professional chefs to middle school kids to author Michael Pollan to cook using her revolutionary, yet simple, philosophy. Master the use of just four elements&#8211;Salt, which enhances flavor; Fat, which delivers flavor and generates texture; Acid, which balances flavor; and Heat, which ultimately determines the texture of food&#8211;and anything you cook will be delicious. By explaining the hows and whys of good cooking, Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat will teach and inspire a new generation of cooks how to confidently make better decisions in the kitchen and cook delicious meals with any ingredients, anywhere, at any time.     </p>
<p>                    Echoing Samin&#8217;s own journey from culinary novice to award-winning chef, Salt, Fat Acid, Heat immediately bridges the gap between home and professional kitchens. With charming narrative, illustrated walkthroughs, and a lighthearted approach to kitchen science, Samin demystifies the four elements of good cooking for everyone. Refer to the canon of 100 essential recipes&#8211;and dozens of variations&#8211;to put the lessons into practice and make bright, balanced vinaigrettes, perfectly caramelized roast vegetables, tender braised meats, and light, flaky pastry doughs.     </p>
<p>                    Featuring 150 illustrations and infographics that reveal an atlas to the world of flavor by renowned illustrator Wendy MacNaughton, Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat will be your compass in the kitchen. Destined to be a classic, it just might be the last cookbook you&#8217;ll ever need.     </p>
<p>                    With a foreword by Michael Pollan.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/">Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Maps & Atlases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from the foreword     </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s nothing like vagabonding: taking time off from your normal life&#8211;from six weeks to four months to two years&#8211;to discover and experience the world on your own terms. In this one-of-a-kind handbook, veteran travel writer Rolf Potts explains how anyone armed with an independent spirit can achieve the dream of extended overseas travel. Now completely revised and updated, Vagabonding is an accessible and inspiring guide to     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; financing your travel time<br />
                     &#8211; determining your destination<br />
                     &#8211; adjusting to life on the road<br />
                     &#8211; working and volunteering overseas<br />
                     &#8211; handling travel adversity<br />
                     &#8211; re-assimilating back into ordinary life     </p>
<p>                     Praise for Vagabonding    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A crucial reference for any budget wanderer.&#8221;&#8211;Time    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The book is a meditation on the joys of hitting the road. . . . It&#8217;s also a primer for those with a case of pent-up wanderlust seeking to live the dream.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I couldn&#8217;t put this book down. It&#8217;s a whole different ethic of travel. . . . [Potts&#8217;s] practical advice might just convince you to enjoy that open-ended trip of a lifetime.&#8221;&#8211;Rick Steves     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Potts wants us to wander, to explore, to embrace the unknown, and, finally, to take our own damn time about it. I think this is the most sensible book of travel-related advice ever written.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Cahill, founding editor of Outside</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword by Neil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction by Ann Druyan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meteorology & Climatology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>RETURNING TO TELEVISION AS AN ALL-NEW MINISERIES ON FOX Cosmos is one of the bestselling science books of all time. In clear-eyed prose, Sagan reveals a jewel-like blue world inhabited by a life form that is just beginning to discover its own identity and to venture into the vast ocean of space. Featuring a new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/">Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword by Neil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction by Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RETURNING TO TELEVISION AS AN ALL-NEW MINISERIES ON FOX     </p>
<p>                    Cosmos is one of the bestselling science books of all time. In clear-eyed prose, Sagan reveals a jewel-like blue world inhabited by a life form that is just beginning to discover its own identity and to venture into the vast ocean of space. Featuring a new Introduction by Sagan&#8217;s collaborator, Ann Druyan, full color illustrations, and a new Foreword by astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson, Cosmos retraces the fourteen billion years of cosmic evolution that have transformed matter into consciousness, exploring such topics as the origin of life, the human brain, Egyptian hieroglyphics, spacecraft missions, the death of the Sun, the evolution of galaxies, and the forces and individuals who helped to shape modern science.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Cosmos     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Magnificent . . . With a lyrical literary style, and a range that touches almost all aspects of human knowledge, Cosmos often seems too good to be true.&#8221;&#8211;The Plain Dealer     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Sagan is an astronomer with one eye on the stars, another on history, and a third&#8211;his mind&#8217;s&#8211;on the human condition.&#8221;&#8211;Newsday     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Brilliant in its scope and provocative in its suggestions . . . shimmers with a sense of wonder.&#8221;&#8211;The Miami Herald     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Sagan dazzles the mind with the miracle of our survival, framed by the stately galaxies of space.&#8221;&#8211;Cosmopolitan     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Enticing . . . iridescent . . . imaginatively illustrated.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/">Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword by Neil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction by Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A prescient warning of a future we now inhabit, where fake news stories and Internet conspiracy theories play to a disaffected American populace &#8220;A glorious book . . . A spirited defense of science . . . From the first page to the last, this book is a manifesto for clear thought.&#8221;&#8211;Los Angeles Times How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/">The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A prescient warning of a future we now inhabit, where fake news stories and Internet conspiracy theories play to a disaffected American populace     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A glorious book . . . A spirited defense of science . . . From the first page to the last, this book is a manifesto for clear thought.&#8221;&#8211;Los Angeles Times     </p>
<p>                     How can we make intelligent decisions about our increasingly technology-driven lives if we don&#8217;t understand the difference between the myths of pseudoscience and the testable hypotheses of science? Pulitzer Prize-winning author and distinguished astronomer Carl Sagan argues that scientific thinking is critical not only to the pursuit of truth but to the very well-being of our democratic institutions.     </p>
<p>                     Casting a wide net through history and culture, Sagan examines and authoritatively debunks such celebrated fallacies of the past as witchcraft, faith healing, demons, and UFOs. And yet, disturbingly, in today&#8217;s so-called information age, pseudoscience is burgeoning with stories of alien abduction, channeling past lives, and communal hallucinations commanding growing attention and respect. As Sagan demonstrates with lucid eloquence, the siren song of unreason is not just a cultural wrong turn but a dangerous plunge into darkness that threatens our most basic freedoms.     </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Demon-Haunted World     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Powerful . . . A stirring defense of informed rationality. . . Rich in surprising information and beautiful writing.&#8221;&#8211;The Washington Post Book World     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Compelling.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A clear vision of what good science means and why it makes a difference. . . . A testimonial to the power of science and a warning of the dangers of unrestrained credulity.&#8221;&#8211;The Sciences     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Passionate.&#8221;&#8211;San Francisco Examiner-Chronicle</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/">The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flawless Consulting : A Guide to Getting Your Expertise Used &#8211; Peter Block (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This Third Edition to Peter Block&#8217;s Flawless Consulting addresses business changes and new challenges since the second edition was written ten years ago. It tackles the challenges next-generation consultants face, including more guidance on how to ask better questions, dealing with difficult clients, working in an increasingly virtual world, how to cope with complexities in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/">Flawless Consulting : A Guide to Getting Your Expertise Used &#8211; Peter Block (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This Third Edition to Peter Block&#8217;s Flawless Consulting addresses business changes and new challenges since the second edition was written ten years ago. It tackles the challenges next-generation consultants face, including more guidance on how to ask better questions, dealing with difficult clients, working in an increasingly virtual world, how to cope with complexities in international consulting, case studies, and guidelines on implementation. Also included are illustrative examples and exercises to help you cement the guides offered.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/">Flawless Consulting : A Guide to Getting Your Expertise Used &#8211; Peter Block (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Color Is Your Parachute? 2020 : A Practical Manual for Job-Hunters and Career-Changers &#8211; Richard N. Bolles (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-color-is-your-parachute-2020-a-practical-manual-for-job-hunters-and-career-changers-richard-n-bolles-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-color-is-your-parachute-2020-a-practical-manual-for-job-hunters-and-career-changers-richard-n-bolles-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With more than 10 million copies sold in 28 countries, the world&#8217;s most popular job-search book is updated for 2020, tailoring Richard Bolles&#8217;s long-trusted guidance with up-to-the-minute information and advice for today&#8217;s job-hunters and career-changers. NAMED ONE OF THE ALL-TIME 100 BEST NONFICTION BOOKS BY TIME What Color Is Your Parachute? is the world&#8217;s most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-color-is-your-parachute-2020-a-practical-manual-for-job-hunters-and-career-changers-richard-n-bolles-abridged/">What Color Is Your Parachute? 2020 : A Practical Manual for Job-Hunters and Career-Changers &#8211; Richard N. Bolles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With more than 10 million copies sold in 28 countries, the world&#8217;s most popular job-search book is updated for 2020, tailoring Richard Bolles&#8217;s long-trusted guidance with up-to-the-minute information and advice for today&#8217;s job-hunters and career-changers. NAMED ONE OF THE ALL-TIME 100 BEST NONFICTION BOOKS BY TIME What Color Is Your Parachute? is the world&#8217;s most popular job-hunting guide, revised and updated annually with more than ten million copies sold. This newly streamlined edition features the latest resources, case studies, and perspectives on today&#8217;s job market, revealing surprising advice on what works&#8211;and what doesn&#8217;t&#8211;so you can focus your efforts on tactics that yield results.  At its core is Richard N. Bolles&#8217;s famed Flower Exercise, a unique self-inventory that helps you design your career&#8211;and your life&#8211;around your key passions, transferable skills, traits, and more.  This practical manual also provides essential tips for writing impressive resumes and cover letters, networking effectively, interviewing with confidence, and negotiating the best salary possible.  Whether you&#8217;re searching for your first job, were recently laid off, or are dreaming of a career change, What Color Is Your Parachute? will guide you toward a fulfilling and prosperous life&#8217;s work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-color-is-your-parachute-2020-a-practical-manual-for-job-hunters-and-career-changers-richard-n-bolles-abridged/">What Color Is Your Parachute? 2020 : A Practical Manual for Job-Hunters and Career-Changers &#8211; Richard N. Bolles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smartest Kids in the World : And How They Got That Way &#8211; Amanda Ripley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Examinations & Assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secondary Schools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Students & Student Organisations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of Gifted Students]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>America has long compared its students to top-performing kids of other nations. But how do the world&#8217;s education superpowers look through the eyes of an American high school student? Author Amanda Ripley follows three teenagers who chose to spend one school year living and learning in Finland, South Korea, and Poland. Through their adventures, Ripley [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/">The Smartest Kids in the World : And How They Got That Way &#8211; Amanda Ripley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>America has long compared its students to top-performing kids of other nations. But how do the world&#8217;s education superpowers look through the eyes of an American high school student? Author Amanda Ripley follows three teenagers who chose to spend one school year living and learning in Finland, South Korea, and Poland. Through their adventures, Ripley discovers startling truths about how attitudes, parenting, and rigorous teaching have revolutionized these countries&#8217; education results.     </p>
<p>                    In The Smartest Kids in the World, Ripley&#8217;s astonishing new insights reveal that top-performing countries have achieved greatness only in the past several decades; that the kids who live there are learning to think for themselves, partly through failing early and often; and that persistence, hard work, and resilience matter more to our children&#8217;s life chances than self-esteem or sports.     </p>
<p>                    Ripley&#8217;s investigative work seamlessly weaves narrative and research, providing in-depth analysis and gripping details that will keep you turning the pages. Written in a clear and engaging style, The Smartest Kids in the World will enliven public as well as dinner table debates over what makes for brighter and better students.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/">The Smartest Kids in the World : And How They Got That Way &#8211; Amanda Ripley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Training Tips For Your New Dog : What To Do When Your Dog Is Chewing, Tugging, And Biting: Raise The Perfect Dog &#8211; Eloy Dipiero (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/training-tips-for-your-new-dog-what-to-do-when-your-dog-is-chewing-tugging-and-biting-raise-the-perfect-dog-eloy-dipiero-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Animals & Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/training-tips-for-your-new-dog-what-to-do-when-your-dog-is-chewing-tugging-and-biting-raise-the-perfect-dog-eloy-dipiero-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A rewarding part of dog ownership is successfully training your dog. Training is an excellent way to bond with your dog and will help you build a good relationship with them. Whether young or old &#8211; all dogs can benefit from learning some basic commands. If you want to know how to stop your dog [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/training-tips-for-your-new-dog-what-to-do-when-your-dog-is-chewing-tugging-and-biting-raise-the-perfect-dog-eloy-dipiero-abridged/">Training Tips For Your New Dog : What To Do When Your Dog Is Chewing, Tugging, And Biting: Raise The Perfect Dog &#8211; Eloy Dipiero (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A rewarding part of dog ownership is successfully training your dog. Training is an excellent way to bond with your dog and will help you build a good relationship with them. Whether young or old &#8211; all dogs can benefit from learning some basic commands. If you want to know how to stop your dog biting, chewing, tugging, or nipping, this book is for you!     </p>
<p>                    This book will guide you on exactly how to quickly create an atmosphere in which a dog (even the most stubborn) will follow the training. These highly effective puppy aggression and behavioral training methods will then guide you and all involved to reaching fast success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/training-tips-for-your-new-dog-what-to-do-when-your-dog-is-chewing-tugging-and-biting-raise-the-perfect-dog-eloy-dipiero-abridged/">Training Tips For Your New Dog : What To Do When Your Dog Is Chewing, Tugging, And Biting: Raise The Perfect Dog &#8211; Eloy Dipiero (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ten Days to Faster Reading &#8211; Abby Marks-Beale (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of A Specific Subject]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jump-Start Your Reading Skills! Speed reading used to require months of training. Now you can rev up your reading in just a few minutes a day. With quizzes to determine your present reading level and exercises to introduce new skills quickly, 10 Days to Faster Reading will improve your reading comprehension and speed as it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/">Ten Days to Faster Reading &#8211; Abby Marks-Beale (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jump-Start Your Reading Skills! Speed reading used to require months of training. Now you can rev up your reading in just a few minutes a day. With quizzes to determine your present reading level and exercises to introduce new skills quickly, 10 Days to Faster Reading will improve your reading comprehension and speed as it shows you how to:     </p>
<p>                     Break the Bad Habits That Slow You Down<br />
                     Develop Your Powers of Concentration<br />
                     Cut Your Reading Time in Half<br />
                     Use Proven, Specially Designed Reading Techniques<br />
                     Boost the Power of Your Peripheral Vision     </p>
<p>                     Learn How to Scan and Skim a Written Report &#8230;And All in 10 Days!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/">Ten Days to Faster Reading &#8211; Abby Marks-Beale (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No-Drama Discipline : The Whole-Brain Way to Calm the Chaos and Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-drama-discipline-the-whole-brain-way-to-calm-the-chaos-and-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-drama-discipline-the-whole-brain-way-to-calm-the-chaos-and-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The pioneering experts behind The Whole-Brain Child and The Yes Brain tackle the ultimate parenting challenge: discipline. &#8220;A lot of fascinating insights . . . an eye-opener worth reading.&#8221;&#8211;Parents Highlighting the fascinating link between a child&#8217;s neurological development and the way a parent reacts to misbehavior, No-Drama Discipline provides an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-drama-discipline-the-whole-brain-way-to-calm-the-chaos-and-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/">No-Drama Discipline : The Whole-Brain Way to Calm the Chaos and Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The pioneering experts behind The Whole-Brain Child and The Yes Brain tackle the ultimate parenting challenge: discipline.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A lot of fascinating insights . . . an eye-opener worth reading.&#8221;&#8211;Parents     </p>
<p>                    Highlighting the fascinating link between a child&#8217;s neurological development and the way a parent reacts to misbehavior, No-Drama Discipline provides an effective, compassionate road map for dealing with tantrums, tensions, and tears&#8211;without causing a scene.     </p>
<p>                    Defining the true meaning of the &#8220;d&#8221; word (to instruct, not to shout or reprimand), the authors explain how to reach your child, redirect emotions, and turn a meltdown into an opportunity for growth. By doing so, the cycle of negative behavior (and punishment) is essentially brought to a halt, as problem solving becomes a win/win situation. Inside this sanity-saving guide you&#8217;ll discover     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; strategies that help parents identify their own discipline philosophy&#8211;and master the best methods to communicate the lessons they are trying to impart<br />
                     &#8211; facts on child brain development&#8211;and what kind of discipline is most appropriate and constructive at all ages and stages<br />
                     &#8211; the way to calmly and lovingly connect with a child&#8211;no matter how extreme the behavior&#8211;while still setting clear and consistent limits<br />
                     &#8211; tips for navigating your child through a tantrum to achieve insight, empathy, and repair<br />
                     &#8211; twenty discipline mistakes even the best parents make&#8211;and how to stay focused on the principles of whole-brain parenting and discipline techniques     </p>
<p>                     Complete with candid stories and playful illustrations that bring the authors&#8217; suggestions to life, No-Drama Discipline shows you how to work with your child&#8217;s developing mind, peacefully resolve conflicts, and inspire happiness and strengthen resilience in everyone in the family.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for No-Drama Discipline     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;With lucid, engaging prose accompanied by cartoon illustrations, Siegel and Bryson help parents teach and communicate more effectively.&#8221;&#8211;Publishers Weekly     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Wow! This book grabbed me from the very first page and did not let go.&#8221;&#8211;Lawrence J. Cohen, Ph.D., author of The Opposite of Worry</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-drama-discipline-the-whole-brain-way-to-calm-the-chaos-and-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/">No-Drama Discipline : The Whole-Brain Way to Calm the Chaos and Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Triumph of Seeds : How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees, Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We live in a world of seeds. From our morning toast to the cotton in our clothes, they are quite literally the stuff and staff of life: supporting diets, economies, and civilizations around the globe. Just as the search for nutmeg and pepper drove the Age of Discovery, coffee beans fueled the Enlightenment and cottonseed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/">The Triumph of Seeds : How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We live in a world of seeds. From our morning toast to the cotton in our clothes, they are quite literally the stuff and staff of life: supporting diets, economies, and civilizations around the globe. Just as the search for nutmeg and pepper drove the Age of Discovery, coffee beans fueled the Enlightenment and cottonseed sparked the Industrial Revolution. Seeds are fundamental objects of beauty, evolutionary wonders, and simple fascinations. Yet, despite their importance, seeds are often seen as commonplace, their extraordinary natural and human histories overlooked. Thanks to this stunning new book, they can be overlooked no more. This is a book of knowledge, adventure, and wonder, spun by an award-winning writer with both the charm of a fireside story-teller and the hard-won expertise of a field biologist. A fascinating scientific adventure, it is essential reading for anyone who loves to see a plant grow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/">The Triumph of Seeds : How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
