<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Social Welfare &amp; Social Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/social-welfare-social-services/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/social-welfare-social-services/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Social Welfare &amp; Social Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/social-welfare-social-services/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Make Trouble : Stand Up, Speak Out, and Find the Courage to Lead &#8211; Cecile Richards, With Lauren Peterson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pressure Groups & Lobbying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Cecile Richards, the former president of Planned Parenthood for more than a decade, daughter of the late Ann Richards, featured speaker at the Women&#8217;s March on Washington, and &#8220;the heroine of the resistance&#8221; (Vogue), comes &#8220;an enthralling memoir&#8221; (Booklist, starred review) filled with &#8220;practical advice and inspiration for aspiring leaders everywhere&#8221; (Hillary Rodham Clinton). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/">Make Trouble : Stand Up, Speak Out, and Find the Courage to Lead &#8211; Cecile Richards, With Lauren Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Cecile Richards, the former president of Planned Parenthood for more than a decade, daughter of the late Ann Richards, featured speaker at the Women&#8217;s March on Washington, and &#8220;the heroine of the resistance&#8221; (Vogue), comes &#8220;an enthralling memoir&#8221; (Booklist, starred review) filled with &#8220;practical advice and inspiration for aspiring leaders everywhere&#8221; (Hillary Rodham Clinton).    </p>
<p>                    Cecile Richards has been an activist since she was taken to the principal&#8217;s office in seventh grade for wearing an armband in protest of the Vietnam War. Richards had an extraordinary childhood in ultra-conservative Texas, where her civil rights attorney father and activist mother taught their kids to be troublemakers. She had a front-row seat to observe the rise of women in American politics and watched her mother, Ann, transform from a housewife to an electrifying force in the Democratic party.    </p>
<p>                    As a young woman, Richards worked as a labor organizer alongside women earning minimum wage, and learned that those in power don&#8217;t give it up without a fight. She experienced first-hand the misogyny, sexism, fake news, and the ever-looming threat of violence that constantly confront women who challenge authority.    </p>
<p>                    Now, after years of advocacy, resistance, and progressive leadership, she shares her &#8220;truly inspiring&#8221; (Redbook) story for the first time-from the joy and heartbreak of activism to the challenges of raising kids, having a life, and making change, all the while garnering a reputation as &#8220;the most badass feminist EVER&#8221; (Teen Vogue).    </p>
<p>                    In the &#8220;powerful and infinitely readable&#8221; (Gloria Steinem) Make Trouble, Richards reflects on the people and lessons that have gotten her through good times and bad, and encourages the rest of us to take risks, make mistakes, and make trouble along the way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/">Make Trouble : Stand Up, Speak Out, and Find the Courage to Lead &#8211; Cecile Richards, With Lauren Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Writing My Wrongs : Life, Death, and the Redemption in an American Prison &#8211; Shaka Senghor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An &#8220;extraordinary, unforgettable&#8221; (Michelle Alexander, author of The New Jim Crow) memoir of redemption and second chances amidst America&#8217;s mass incarceration epidemic, from a member of Oprah&#8217;s SuperSoul 100 Shaka Senghor was raised in a middle-class neighborhood on Detroit&#8217;s east side during the height of the 1980s crack epidemic. An [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/">Writing My Wrongs : Life, Death, and the Redemption in an American Prison &#8211; Shaka Senghor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An &#8220;extraordinary, unforgettable&#8221; (Michelle Alexander, author of The New Jim Crow) memoir of redemption and second chances amidst America&#8217;s mass incarceration epidemic, from a member of Oprah&#8217;s SuperSoul 100     </p>
<p>                    Shaka Senghor was raised in a middle-class neighborhood on Detroit&#8217;s east side during the height of the 1980s crack epidemic. An honor roll student and a natural leader, he dreamed of becoming a doctor&#8211;but at age eleven, his parents&#8217; marriage began to unravel, and beatings from his mother worsened, which sent him on a downward spiral. He ran away from home, turned to drug dealing to survive, and ended up in prison for murder at the age of nineteen, full of anger and despair.     </p>
<p>                    Writing My Wrongs is the story of what came next. During his nineteen-year incarceration, seven of which were spent in solitary confinement, Senghor discovered literature, meditation, self-examination, and the kindness of others&#8211;tools he used to confront the demons of his past, forgive the people who hurt him, and begin atoning for the wrongs he had committed. Upon his release at age thirty-eight, Senghor became an activist and mentor to young men and women facing circumstances like his. His work in the community and the courage to share his story led him to fellowships at the MIT Media Lab and the Kellogg Foundation and invitations to speak at events like TED and the Aspen Ideas Festival.     </p>
<p>                    In equal turns, Writing My Wrongs is a page-turning portrait of life in the shadow of poverty, violence, and fear; an unforgettable story of redemption; and a compelling witness to our country&#8217;s need for rethinking its approach to crime, prison, and the men and women sent there.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/">Writing My Wrongs : Life, Death, and the Redemption in an American Prison &#8211; Shaka Senghor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get What&#8217;s Yours : The Secrets to Maxing Out Your Social Security &#8211; Professor of Economics Laurence J Kotlikoff, Philip Moeller, Paul Solman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare & Benefit Systems]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Social Security law has changed! Get What&#8217;s Yours has been revised and updated to reflect new regulations that took effect on April 29, 2016. Get What&#8217;s Yours has proven itself to be the definitive book about how to navigate the forbidding maze of Social Security and emerge with the highest possible benefits. It is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/">Get What&#8217;s Yours : The Secrets to Maxing Out Your Social Security &#8211; Professor of Economics Laurence J Kotlikoff, Philip Moeller, Paul Solman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Social Security law has changed! Get What&#8217;s Yours has been revised and updated to reflect new regulations that took effect on April 29, 2016.     </p>
<p>                    Get What&#8217;s Yours has proven itself to be the definitive book about how to navigate the forbidding maze of Social Security and emerge with the highest possible benefits. It is an engaging manual of tactics and strategies written by well-known financial commentators that is unobtainable elsewhere. You could try reading all 2,728 rules of the Social Security system (and the thousands of explanations of these rules), but academia&#8217;s Kotlikoff, the popular press&#8217;s Moeller, and public television&#8217;s Solman explain the Social Security system just as comprehensively, and a lot more comprehensibly. Moreover, they demonstrate that what you don&#8217;t know can seriously hurt you: wrong decisions about which Social Security benefits to apply for cost individual retirees tens of thousands of dollars in lost income every year. (Some of those people are even in the book.)     </p>
<p>                    Changes to Social Security that take effect in 2016 make it more important than ever to wait as long as possible (until age 70, if possible) to claim Social Security benefits. The new law also has significant implications for those who wish to claim divorced spousal benefits (and how many Social Security recipients even know about divorced spousal benefits?). Besides addressing these and other issues, this revised edition contains a chapter explaining how Medicare rules can shape Social Security decisions.     </p>
<p>                    Many other personal-finance books briefly address Social Security, but none offers the full, authoritative, yet conversational analysis of Get What&#8217;s Yours.     </p>
<p>                    Get What&#8217;s Yours explains Social Security benefits through basic strategies and stirring stories. It covers the most frequent benefit scenarios faced by married retired couples; by divorced retirees; by widows and widowers. It explains what to do if you&#8217;re a retired parent of dependent children; disabled; an eligible beneficiary who continues to work. It addresses the tax consequences of your choices, as well as the financial implications for other investments. It does all this and more.     </p>
<p>                    There are more than 52 million Americans aged 54 to 69. Ten thousand of them reach Social Security&#8217;s full retirement age of 66 every day. For all these people&#8211;and for their families and friends&#8211;Get What&#8217;s Yours has proven to be an invaluable, and therefore indispensable, tool.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/">Get What&#8217;s Yours : The Secrets to Maxing Out Your Social Security &#8211; Professor of Economics Laurence J Kotlikoff, Philip Moeller, Paul Solman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insurance & Actuarial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicolegal Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017 &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene At a moment of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene      </p>
<p>                    At a moment of drastic political upheaval, An American Sickness is a shocking investigation into our dysfunctional healthcare system &#8211; and offers practical solutions to its myriad problems.    </p>
<p>                     In these troubled times, perhaps no institution has unraveled more quickly and more completely than American medicine. In only a few decades, the medical system has been overrun by organizations seeking to exploit for profit the trust that vulnerable and sick Americans place in their healthcare. Our politicians have proven themselves either unwilling or incapable of reining in the increasingly outrageous costs faced by patients, and market-based solutions only seem to funnel larger and larger sums of our money into the hands of corporations. Impossibly high insurance premiums and inexplicably large bills have become facts of life; fatalism has set in. Very quickly Americans have been made to accept paying more for less. How did things get so bad so fast?     </p>
<p>                     Breaking down this monolithic business into the individual industries-the hospitals, doctors, insurance companies, and drug manufacturers-that together constitute our healthcare system, Rosenthal exposes the recent evolution of American medicine as never before. How did healthcare, the caring endeavor, become healthcare, the highly profitable industry? Hospital systems, which are managed by business executives, behave like predatory lenders, hounding patients and seizing their homes. Research charities are in bed with big pharmaceutical companies, which surreptitiously profit from the donations made by working people. Patients receive bills in code, from entrepreneurial doctors they never even saw.     </p>
<p>                     The system is in tatters, but we can fight back. Dr. Elisabeth Rosenthal doesn&#8217;t just explain the symptoms, she diagnoses and treats the disease itself. In clear and practical terms, she spells out exactly how to decode medical doublespeak, avoid the pitfalls of the pharmaceuticals racket, and get the care you and your family deserve. She takes you inside the doctor-patient relationship and to hospital C-suites, explaining step-by-step the workings of a system badly lacking transparency. This is about what we can do, as individual patients, both to navigate the maze that is American healthcare and also to demand far-reaching reform. An American Sickness is the frontline defense against a healthcare system that no longer has our well-being at heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he tries to understand so-called European socialism firsthand. Though he first tries France (which has become a rhetorical stand-in for the continent as a whole in many Americans&#8217; minds), he eventually ventures into Germany to see what some call the &#8220;boring&#8221; Europe. There he finds the true &#8220;other&#8221; an economic model with more bottom-up worker control than that of any other country in the world and argues that, while we have to take Germany&#8217;s problems seriously, we also have to look seriously at how much it has achieved. Social democracy may let us live nicer lives; it also may be the only way to be globally competitive. This wry, timely book helps us understand why the European model, contrary to popular neoliberal wisdom, may thrive well into the twenty-first century without compromising its citizens&#8217; ease of living and be the best example for the United States to follow.    </p>
<p>                    Germany is more generous than the U.S.:    </p>
<p>                    The average number of paid vacation days in the U.S. is 13, versus Germany&#8217;s 35<br />
                    New mothers in the U.S. get three months of unpaid job-protected leave and only if they work for a company of 50 or more employees, while Germany mandates four months&#8217; paid leave and will pay parents 67% of their salary to stay home for up to 14 months to care for a newborn.<br />
                    U.S. life expectancy is 50th in the world, compared to Germany&#8217;s 32nd.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crippled : Austerity and the Demonization of Disabled People &#8211; Frances Ryan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In austerity Britain, disabled people have become the favourite target. From social care to the benefits system, politicians and media alike have made the case Britain&#8217;s 12 million disabled people are a drain on the public purse. In Crippled, leading commentator Frances Ryan exposes the disturbing reality, telling the story of those most affected by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/">Crippled : Austerity and the Demonization of Disabled People &#8211; Frances Ryan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In austerity Britain, disabled people have become the favourite target. From social care to the benefits system, politicians and media alike have made the case Britain&#8217;s 12 million disabled people are a drain on the public purse. In Crippled, leading commentator Frances Ryan exposes the disturbing reality, telling the story of those most affected by this devastating regime. This includes a paralyzed man forced to crawl down the stairs because the council wouldn&#8217;t provide accessible housing; the malnourished woman sleeping in her wheelchair; and the young girl with bipolar forced to turn to sex work to survive.     </p>
<p>                    Through these personal stories, Ryan charts how in recent years the public attitude towards disabled people has transformed from compassion to contempt: from society&#8217;s `most vulnerable&#8217; to benefit cheats. Crippled is a damning indictment of a safety net gone wrong, and a passionate demand for an end to austerity measures hitting those most in need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/">Crippled : Austerity and the Demonization of Disabled People &#8211; Frances Ryan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Truth Sounds Like : Robert F. Kennedy, James Baldwin, and Our Unfinished Conversation About Race in America &#8211; Michael Eric Dyson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-truth-sounds-like-robert-f-kennedy-james-baldwin-and-our-unfinished-conversation-about-race-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-truth-sounds-like-robert-f-kennedy-james-baldwin-and-our-unfinished-conversation-about-race-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Named a 2018 Notable Work of Nonfiction by The Washington Post NOW A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Winner, The 2018 Southern Book Prize NAMED A BEST/MOST ANTICIPATED BOOK OF 2018 BY: Chicago Tribune &#8211; Time &#8211; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly A stunning follow up to New York Times bestseller Tears We Cannot Stop The Washington Post: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-truth-sounds-like-robert-f-kennedy-james-baldwin-and-our-unfinished-conversation-about-race-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/">What Truth Sounds Like : Robert F. Kennedy, James Baldwin, and Our Unfinished Conversation About Race in America &#8211; Michael Eric Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Named a 2018 Notable Work of Nonfiction by The Washington Post     </p>
<p>                    NOW A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Winner, The 2018 Southern Book Prize    </p>
<p>                    NAMED A BEST/MOST ANTICIPATED BOOK OF 2018 BY: Chicago Tribune &#8211; Time &#8211; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly     </p>
<p>                    A stunning follow up to New York Times bestseller Tears We Cannot Stop     </p>
<p>                    The Washington Post: Passionately written.<br />
                    Chris Matthews, MSNBC: A beautifully written book.<br />
                    Shaun King: &#8220;I kid you not-I think it&#8217;s the most important book I&#8217;ve read all year&#8230;&#8221;      </p>
<p>                    Harry Belafonte: &#8220;Dyson has finally written the book I always wanted to read&#8230;a tour de force.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Joy-Ann Reid: A work of searing prose and seminal brilliance&#8230; Dyson takes that once in a lifetime conversation between black excellence and pain and the white heroic narrative, and drives it right into the heart of our current politics and culture, leaving the reader reeling and reckoning.     </p>
<p>                    Robin D. G. Kelley: &#8220;Dyson masterfully refracts our present racial conflagration&#8230; he reminds us that Black artists and intellectuals bear an awesome responsibility to speak truth to power.     </p>
<p>                    President Barack Obama:  Everybody who speaks after Michael Eric Dyson pales in comparison.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    In 2015 BLM activist Julius Jones confronted Presidential candidate Hillary Clinton with an urgent query: &#8220;What in your heart has changed that&#8217;s going to change the direction of this country?&#8221; &#8220;I don&#8217;t believe you just change hearts,&#8221; she protested. &#8220;I believe you change laws.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    The fraught conflict between conscience and politics &#8211; between morality and power &#8211; in addressing race hardly began with Clinton. An electrifying and traumatic encounter in the sixties crystallized these furious disputes.     </p>
<p>                    In 1963 Attorney General Robert Kennedy sought out James Baldwin to explain the rage that threatened to engulf black America. Baldwin brought along some friends, including playwright Lorraine Hansberry, psychologist Kenneth Clark, and a valiant activist, Jerome Smith. It was Smith&#8217;s relentless, unfiltered fury that set Kennedy on his heels, reducing him to sullen silence.     </p>
<p>                    Kennedy walked away from the nearly three-hour meeting angry &#8211; that the black folk assembled didn&#8217;t understand politics, and that they weren&#8217;t as easy to talk to as Martin Luther King. But especially that they were more interested in witness than policy. But Kennedy&#8217;s anger quickly gave way to empathy, especially for Smith. &#8220;I guess if I were in his shoes&#8230;I might feel differently about this country.&#8221; Kennedy set about changing policy &#8211; the meeting having transformed his thinking in fundamental ways.     </p>
<p>                    There was more: every big argument about race that persists to this day got a hearing in that room. Smith declaring that he&#8217;d never fight for his country given its racist tendencies, and Kennedy being appalled at such lack of patriotism, tracks the disdain for black dissent in our own time. His belief that black folk were ungrateful for the Kennedys&#8217; efforts to make things better shows up in our day as the charge that black folk wallow in the politics of ingratitude and victimhood. The contributions of black queer folk to racial progress still cause a stir. BLM has been accused of harboring a covert queer agenda. The immigrant experience, like that of Kennedy &#8211; versus the racial experience of Baldwin &#8211; is a cudgel to excoriate black folk for lacking hustle and ingenuity. The questioning of whether folk who are interracially partnered can authentically communicate black interests persists. And we grapple still with the responsibility of black intellectuals and artists to bring about social change.     </p>
<p>                    What Truth Sounds Like exists at the tense intersection of the conflict between politics and prophecy &#8211; of whether we embrace political resolution or moral redemption to fix our fractured racial landscape. The future of race and democracy hang in the balance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-truth-sounds-like-robert-f-kennedy-james-baldwin-and-our-unfinished-conversation-about-race-in-america-michael-eric-dyson-abridged/">What Truth Sounds Like : Robert F. Kennedy, James Baldwin, and Our Unfinished Conversation About Race in America &#8211; Michael Eric Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
