<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism) Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/behavioural-theory-behaviourism/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/behavioural-theory-behaviourism/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism) Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/behavioural-theory-behaviourism/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Humankind : A Hopeful History &#8211; Rutger Bregman</title>
		<link>/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER A Guardian, Daily Telegraph, New Statesman and Daily Express Book of the Year &#8216;Hugely, highly and happily recommended&#8217; Stephen Fry &#8216;You should read Humankind. You&#8217;ll learn a lot (I did) and you&#8217;ll have good reason to feel better about the human race&#8217; Tim Harford &#8216;Made me see humanity from a fresh perspective&#8217; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/">Humankind : A Hopeful History &#8211; Rutger Bregman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER<br />
                    A Guardian, Daily Telegraph, New Statesman and Daily Express Book of the Year</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hugely, highly and happily recommended&#8217; Stephen Fry<br />
                    &#8216;You should read Humankind. You&#8217;ll learn a lot (I did) and you&#8217;ll have good reason to feel better about the human race&#8217; Tim Harford<br />
                    &#8216;Made me see humanity from a fresh perspective&#8217; Yuval Noah Harari</p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s a belief that unites the left and right, psychologists and philosophers, writers and historians. It drives the headlines that surround us and the laws that touch our lives. From Machiavelli to Hobbes, Freud to Dawkins, the roots of this belief have sunk deep into Western thought. Human beings, we&#8217;re taught, are by nature selfish and governed by self-interest.</p>
<p>                    Humankind makes a new argument: that it is realistic, as well as revolutionary, to assume that people are good. By thinking the worst of others, we bring out the worst in our politics and economics too.</p>
<p>                    In this major book, internationally bestselling author Rutger Bregman takes some of the world&#8217;s most famous studies and events and reframes them, providing a new perspective on the last 200,000 years of human history. From the real-life Lord of the Flies to the Blitz, a Siberian fox farm to an infamous New York murder, Stanley Milgram&#8217;s Yale shock machine to the Stanford prison experiment, Bregman shows how believing in human kindness and altruism can be a new way to think &#8211; and act as the foundation for achieving true change in our society.</p>
<p>                    It is time for a new view of human nature.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/">Humankind : A Hopeful History &#8211; Rutger Bregman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The First 20 Hours : How to Learn Anything &#8230; Fast &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-first-20-hours-how-to-learn-anything-fast-josh-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Education, Continuous Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-first-20-hours-how-to-learn-anything-fast-josh-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lots of books promise to change your life. This one actually will&#8217; Seth Godin, bestselling author of Purple Cow Have you always wanted to learn a new language? Play an instrument? Launch a business? What&#8217;s holding you back from getting started? Are you worried about the time it takes to acquire new skills &#8211; time [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-20-hours-how-to-learn-anything-fast-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The First 20 Hours : How to Learn Anything &#8230; Fast &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lots of books promise to change your life. This one actually will&#8217; Seth Godin, bestselling author of Purple Cow    </p>
<p>                    Have you always wanted to learn a new language? Play an instrument? Launch a business? What&#8217;s holding you back from getting started? Are you worried about the time it takes to acquire new skills &#8211; time you can&#8217;t spare?    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;    </p>
<p>                    Pick up this book and set aside twenty hours to go from knowing nothing to performing like a pro. That&#8217;s it.    </p>
<p>                    Josh Kaufman, author of international bestseller The Personal MBA, has developed a unique approach to mastering anything. Fast.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;After reading this book, you&#8217;ll be ready to take on any number of skills and make progress on that big project you&#8217;ve been putting off for years&#8217; Chris Guillebeau, bestselling author of Un-F*ck Yourself     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;All that&#8217;s standing between you and playing the ukulele is your TV time for the next two weeks&#8217; Laura Vanderkam, author of What the Most Successful People Do Before Breakfast</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-20-hours-how-to-learn-anything-fast-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The First 20 Hours : How to Learn Anything &#8230; Fast &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Laws of Wealth : Psychology and the Secret to Investing Success &#8211; Daniel Crosby (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times and USA Today bestselling author, Dr Daniel Crosby, comes the behavioral finance book all investors have been waiting for. In The Laws of Wealth, psychologist and behavioral finance expert Daniel Crosby offers an accessible and applied take on a discipline that has long tended toward theory at the expense of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/">The Laws of Wealth : Psychology and the Secret to Investing Success &#8211; Daniel Crosby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times and USA Today bestselling author, Dr Daniel Crosby, comes the behavioral finance book all investors have been waiting for. In The Laws of Wealth, psychologist and behavioral finance expert Daniel Crosby offers an accessible and applied take on a discipline that has long tended toward theory at the expense of the practical. Readers are treated to real, actionable guidance as the promise of behavioral finance is realised and practical applications for everyday investors are delivered. Crosby presents a framework of timeless principles for managing your behavior and your investing process. He begins by outlining ten rules that are the hallmarks of good investor behavior, including &#8216;Forecasting is for Weathermen&#8217; and &#8216;If You&#8217;re Excited, It&#8217;s Probably a Bad Idea&#8217;. He then goes on to introduce a unique new taxonomy of behavioral investment risk that will enable investors and academics alike to understand behavioral risk in a newly coherent and complete way.From here, attention turns to the four ways in which behavioral risk can be combatted and the five equity selection methods investors should harness to take advantage of behaviorally-induced opportunities in the stock market.<br />
                    Throughout, readers are treated to anecdotes, research and graphics that illustrate the lessons in memorable ways. And in highly valuable &#8216;What now?&#8217; summaries at the end of each chapter, Crosby provides clear, concise direction on what investors should think, ask and do to benefit from the behavioral research. Dr. Crosby&#8217;s training as a clinical psychologist and work as an asset manager provide a unique vantage and result in a book that breaks new ground in behavioral finance. You need to follow the laws of wealth to manage your behavior and improve your investing process!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/">The Laws of Wealth : Psychology and the Secret to Investing Success &#8211; Daniel Crosby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alchemy : The Magic of Original Thinking in a World of Mind-Numbing Conformity &#8211; Rory Sutherland (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alchemy-the-magic-of-original-thinking-in-a-world-of-mind-numbing-conformity-rory-sutherland-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alchemy-the-magic-of-original-thinking-in-a-world-of-mind-numbing-conformity-rory-sutherland-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A breakthrough book. Wonderfully applicable to everything in life, and funny as hell.&#8217; Nassim Nicholas Taleb Why is Red Bull so popular &#8211; even though everyone hates the taste? Why do countdown boards on platforms take away the pain of train delays? And why do we prefer stripy toothpaste? Discover the alchemy behind original thinking, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alchemy-the-magic-of-original-thinking-in-a-world-of-mind-numbing-conformity-rory-sutherland-abridged/">Alchemy : The Magic of Original Thinking in a World of Mind-Numbing Conformity &#8211; Rory Sutherland (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A breakthrough book. Wonderfully applicable to everything in life, and funny as hell.&#8217; Nassim Nicholas Taleb    </p>
<p>                    Why is Red Bull so popular &#8211; even though everyone hates the taste? Why do countdown boards on platforms take away the pain of train delays? And why do we prefer stripy toothpaste?    </p>
<p>                    Discover the alchemy behind original thinking, as TED Talk superstar and Ogilvy advertising legend Rory Sutherland reveals why abandoning logic and casting aside rationality is the best way to solve any problem.     </p>
<p>                    In his first book he blends cutting-edge behavioural science, jaw-dropping stories and a touch of branding magic on his mission to turn us all into idea alchemists. He shows how economists, businesses and governments have got it all wrong: we are not rational creatures who make logical decisions based on evidence. Instead, the big problems we face every day, whether as an individual or in society, could very well be solved by thinking less logically. To be brilliant, you have to be irrational.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alchemy-the-magic-of-original-thinking-in-a-world-of-mind-numbing-conformity-rory-sutherland-abridged/">Alchemy : The Magic of Original Thinking in a World of Mind-Numbing Conformity &#8211; Rory Sutherland (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happiness by Design : Finding Pleasure and Purpose in Everyday Life &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happiness-by-design-finding-pleasure-and-purpose-in-everyday-life-paul-dolan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happiness-by-design-finding-pleasure-and-purpose-in-everyday-life-paul-dolan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER How can we make it easier to be happy? Using the latest cutting-edge research, Professor Paul Dolan reveals that wellbeing isn&#8217;t about how we think &#8211; it&#8217;s about what we do. By making deliberate choices that bring us both pleasure and meaning, we can redesign our lives for maximum happiness &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-by-design-finding-pleasure-and-purpose-in-everyday-life-paul-dolan-abridged/">Happiness by Design : Finding Pleasure and Purpose in Everyday Life &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    How can we make it easier to be happy? Using the latest cutting-edge research, Professor Paul Dolan reveals that wellbeing isn&#8217;t about how we think &#8211; it&#8217;s about what we do. By making deliberate choices that bring us both pleasure and meaning, we can redesign our lives for maximum happiness &#8211; without thinking too hard about it.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Outstanding, cutting-edge, and profound. If you&#8217;re going to read one book on happiness, this is the one&#8217; Nassim Nicholas Taleb    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Bold and original &#8230; what I wish for my grandchildren: a life that is rich in activities both pleasurable and meaningful&#8217; Daniel Kahneman, author of Thinking Fast and Slow</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-by-design-finding-pleasure-and-purpose-in-everyday-life-paul-dolan-abridged/">Happiness by Design : Finding Pleasure and Purpose in Everyday Life &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happy Ever After : A Radical New Approach to Living Well &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happy-ever-after-a-radical-new-approach-to-living-well-paul-dolan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happy-ever-after-a-radical-new-approach-to-living-well-paul-dolan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Smart, engaging and funny. It will make you question everything you think you know about what you want&#8217; Caroline Criado Perez, author of Invisible Women Be ambitious; find everlasting love; look after your health &#8230; There are countless stories about how we ought to live our lives. These narratives can make our lives easier, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-ever-after-a-radical-new-approach-to-living-well-paul-dolan-abridged/">Happy Ever After : A Radical New Approach to Living Well &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Smart, engaging and funny. It will make you question everything you think you know about what you want&#8217; Caroline Criado Perez, author of Invisible Women    </p>
<p>                    Be ambitious; find everlasting love; look after your health &#8230; There are countless stories about how we ought to live our lives. These narratives can make our lives easier, and they might sometimes make us happier too. But they can also trap us and those around us.    </p>
<p>                    In Happy Ever After, bestselling happiness expert Professor Paul Dolan draws on a variety of studies ranging over wellbeing, inequality and discrimination to bust the common myths about our sources of happiness. He shows that there can be many unexpected paths to lasting fulfilment. Some of these might involve not going into higher education, choosing not to marry, rewarding acts rooted in self-interest and caring a little less about living forever.    </p>
<p>                    By freeing ourselves from the myth of the perfect life, we might each find a life worth living.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-ever-after-a-radical-new-approach-to-living-well-paul-dolan-abridged/">Happy Ever After : A Radical New Approach to Living Well &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Driven : How Human Nature Shapes Our Choices &#8211; Paul R. Lawrence, Nitin Nohria (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/driven-how-human-nature-shapes-our-choices-paul-r-lawrence-nitin-nohria-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Methodology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/driven-how-human-nature-shapes-our-choices-paul-r-lawrence-nitin-nohria-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A touchstone for understanding how we behave on the job &#8220;This is a stimulating and provocative book in bringing together important ideas from different fields, and, thereby, giving us a whole new slant on &#8216;human nature. &#8216;&#8221; &#8211;Edgar H. Schein, Sloan Fellows Professor of Management Emeritus and Senior Lecturer, MIT In this astonishing, provocative, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/driven-how-human-nature-shapes-our-choices-paul-r-lawrence-nitin-nohria-abridged/">Driven : How Human Nature Shapes Our Choices &#8211; Paul R. Lawrence, Nitin Nohria (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A touchstone for understanding how we behave on the job &#8220;This is a stimulating and provocative book in bringing together important ideas from different fields, and, thereby, giving us a whole new slant on &#8216;human nature. &#8216;&#8221; &#8211;Edgar H. Schein, Sloan Fellows Professor of Management Emeritus and Senior Lecturer, MIT In this astonishing, provocative, and solidly researched book, two Harvard Business School professors synthesize 200 years of thought along with the latest research drawn from the biological and social sciences to propose a new theory, a unified synthesis of human nature. Paul Lawrence and Nitin Nohria have studied the way people behave in that most fascinating arena of human behavior&#8211;the workplace&#8211;and from their work they produce a book that examines the four separate and distinct emotive drives that guide human behavior and influence the choices people make: the drives to acquire, bond, learn, and defend. They ultimately show that, just as advances in information technology have spurred the New Economy in the last quarter of the twentieth century, current advances in biology will be the key to understanding humans and organizations in the new millennium.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/driven-how-human-nature-shapes-our-choices-paul-r-lawrence-nitin-nohria-abridged/">Driven : How Human Nature Shapes Our Choices &#8211; Paul R. Lawrence, Nitin Nohria (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tiny Habits : Why Starting Small Makes Lasting Change Easy &#8211; BJ Fogg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tiny-habits-why-starting-small-makes-lasting-change-easy-bj-fogg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tiny-habits-why-starting-small-makes-lasting-change-easy-bj-fogg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Improving your life is much easier than you think. Whether it&#8217;s losing weight, sleeping more, or restoring your work/life balance &#8211; the secret is to start small. For years, we&#8217;ve been told that being more healthy and productive is a matter of willpower: that we should follow the latest fad and make constant changes to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tiny-habits-why-starting-small-makes-lasting-change-easy-bj-fogg-abridged/">Tiny Habits : Why Starting Small Makes Lasting Change Easy &#8211; BJ Fogg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Improving your life is much easier than you think. Whether it&#8217;s losing weight, sleeping more, or restoring your work/life balance &#8211; the secret is to start small.    </p>
<p>                    For years, we&#8217;ve been told that being more healthy and productive is a matter of willpower: that we should follow the latest fad and make constant changes to our lifestyles. But whether in our diets, fitness plans or jobs, radical overhauls never work. Instead we should start with quick wins &#8211; and embed new, tiny habits into our everyday routines.    </p>
<p>                    The world expert on this is Silicon Valley legend BJ Fogg, pioneering research psychologist and founder of the iconic Behaviour Design Lab at Stanford. Now anyone can use his science-based approach to make changes that are simple to achieve and sticky enough to last.    </p>
<p>                    In the hugely anticipated Tiny Habits, BJ Fogg shows us how to change our lives for the better, one tiny habit at a time. Based on twenty years research and his experience coaching over 40,000 people, it cracks the code of habit formation. Focus on what is easy to change, not what is hard; focus on what you want to do, not what you should do. At the heart of this is a startling truth &#8211; that creating happier, healthier lives can be easy, and surprisingly fun.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tiny-habits-why-starting-small-makes-lasting-change-easy-bj-fogg-abridged/">Tiny Habits : Why Starting Small Makes Lasting Change Easy &#8211; BJ Fogg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Addiction & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life    </p>
<p>                    We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can we kick bad habits &#8211; and stick with it?    </p>
<p>                    According to psychologist and behaviour researcher Dr Sean Young, the answer is to stop trying to change the person, and instead change the process. In Stick With It, Dr Young draws on his own research and that of other leading experts to explain how the mind often interferes with breaking bad habits, and how we can outsmart it, increasing the likelihood of lasting change by 200%.     </p>
<p>                    Packed with practical exercises and real-life case studies, Stick With It shows that it is possible to control spending, stick to a diet, exercise regularly and overcome problem behaviours &#8211; forever.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Scientifically grounded and personally implementable. It&#8217;s a winner&#8217; &#8211; Robert Cialdini, author of Influence and Pre-Suasion    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A must-read for anyone who&#8217;s been unable to keep a New Year&#8217;s resolution or failed at making a lasting change in any other area of their life or work. &#8211; Jonah Berger, author of Contagious    </p>
<p>                    Dr Sean Young is one of the world&#8217;s leading experts in the field of habit-forming. He is an acclaiedpsychologist and the founder and Executive Director of the UCLA Center for Digital Behavior. His research involves the study of cutting-edge ways of using social media and mobile technologies to change and predict human behaviour.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
