<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Political Economy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/political-economy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/political-economy/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Political Economy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/political-economy/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hillbilly Elegy : A Memoir of a Family and Culture in Crisis &#8211; J. D. Vance</title>
		<link>/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Mobility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER Coming November 2020 as a major motion picture from Netflix starring Amy Adams and Glenn Close &#8216;The political book of the year&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;A frank, unsentimental, harrowing memoir &#8230; A superb book&#8217; New York Post &#8216;I bought this to try to better understand Trump&#8217;s appeal &#8230; but the memoir is so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/">Hillbilly Elegy : A Memoir of a Family and Culture in Crisis &#8211; J. D. Vance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER<br />
Coming November 2020 as a major motion picture from Netflix starring Amy Adams and Glenn Close</p>
<p>&#8216;The political book of the year&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>&#8216;A frank, unsentimental, harrowing memoir &#8230; A superb book&#8217; New York Post</p>
<p>&#8216;I bought this to try to better understand Trump&#8217;s appeal &#8230; but the memoir is so much more than that. A gripping, unputdownable page-turner&#8217; India Knight, Evening Standard</p>
<p>J. D. Vance grew up in the hills of Kentucky. His family and friends were the people most of the world calls rednecks, hillbillies or white trash.</p>
<p>In this deeply moving memoir, Vance tells the story of his family&#8217;s demons and of America &#8216; s problem with generational neglect. How his mother struggled against, but never fully escaped, the legacies of abuse, alcoholism, poverty and trauma. How his grandparents, &#8216;dirt poor and in love&#8217;, gave everything for their children to chase the American dream. How Vance beat the odds to graduate from Yale Law School. And how America came to abandon and then condescend to its white working classes, until they reached breaking point.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/">Hillbilly Elegy : A Memoir of a Family and Culture in Crisis &#8211; J. D. Vance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Economic Facts and Fallacies : Second Edition &#8211; Thomas Sowell</title>
		<link>/economic-facts-and-fallacies-second-edition-thomas-sowell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/economic-facts-and-fallacies-second-edition-thomas-sowell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Economic Facts and Fallacies , Thomas Sowell exposes some of the most popular fallacies about economic issues in a lively manner that does not require any prior knowledge of economics. These fallacies include many beliefs widely disseminated in the media and by politicians, such as fallacies about urban problems, income differences, male-female economic differences, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/economic-facts-and-fallacies-second-edition-thomas-sowell/">Economic Facts and Fallacies : Second Edition &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In  Economic Facts and Fallacies , Thomas Sowell exposes some of the most popular fallacies about economic issues in a lively manner that does not require any prior knowledge of economics. These fallacies include many beliefs widely disseminated in the media and by politicians, such as fallacies about urban problems, income differences, male-female economic differences, as well as economic fallacies about academia, about race, and about Third World countries. Sowell shows that fallacies are not simply crazy ideas but in fact have a certain plausibility that gives them their staying power- and makes careful examination of their flaws both necessary and important.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/economic-facts-and-fallacies-second-edition-thomas-sowell/">Economic Facts and Fallacies : Second Edition &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A LITHUB BOOK OF THE DECADE. The US is one of the largest democracies in the world &#8211; or is it? America is experiencing an age of profound economic inequality. Employee protections have been decimated, and state welfare is virtually non-existent, while hedge fund billionaires are grossly under-taxed and big businesses make astounding profits at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/">Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A LITHUB BOOK OF THE DECADE.    </p>
<p>                    The US is one of the largest democracies in the world &#8211; or is it?    </p>
<p>                    America is experiencing an age of profound economic inequality. Employee protections have been decimated, and state welfare is virtually non-existent, while hedge fund billionaires are grossly under-taxed and big businesses make astounding profits at the expense of the environment and of their workers.    </p>
<p>                    How did this come about, and who were the driving forces behind it?    </p>
<p>                    In this powerful and meticulously researched work of investigative journalism, New Yorker staff writer Jane Mayer exposes the network of billionaires trying to buy the US electoral system &#8211; and succeeding. Led by libertarian industrialists the Koch brothers, they believe that taxes are a form of tyranny and that government oversight of business is an assault on freedom. Together, they have spent hundreds of millions of dollars influencing politicians and voters, and hijacking American democracy for their own ends.    </p>
<p>                    Dark Money brilliantly illuminates a shady corner of US politics. It is essential reading for anybody interested in the future of democracy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/">Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doughnut Economics : Seven Ways to Think Like a 21st-Century Economist &#8211; Kate Raworth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/doughnut-economics-seven-ways-to-think-like-a-21st-century-economist-kate-raworth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/doughnut-economics-seven-ways-to-think-like-a-21st-century-economist-kate-raworth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Economics is broken, and the planet is paying the price. Unforeseen financial crises. Extreme wealth inequality. Relentless pressure on the environment. Can we go on like this? Is there an alternative? In Doughnut Economics, Oxford academic Kate Raworth lays out the seven deadly mistakes of economics and offers a radical re-envisioning of the system that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doughnut-economics-seven-ways-to-think-like-a-21st-century-economist-kate-raworth-abridged/">Doughnut Economics : Seven Ways to Think Like a 21st-Century Economist &#8211; Kate Raworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Economics is broken, and the planet is paying the price.    </p>
<p>                    Unforeseen financial crises. Extreme wealth inequality. Relentless pressure on the environment. Can we go on like this? Is there an alternative?    </p>
<p>                    In Doughnut Economics, Oxford academic Kate Raworth lays out the seven deadly mistakes of economics and offers a radical re-envisioning of the system that has brought us to the point of ruin. Moving beyond the myths of &#8216;rational economic man&#8217; and unlimited growth, Doughnut Economics zeroes in on the sweet spot: a system that meets all our needs without exhausting the planet.    </p>
<p>                    The demands of the 21st century require a new shape of economics. This might just be it.    </p>
<p>                    *The Sunday Times Bestseller*<br />
                     *A Financial Times and Forbes Book of the Year*<br />
                     *Winner of the Transmission Prize 2018*<br />
                     *Longlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2017*    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The John Maynard Keynes of the 21st century.&#8217; George Monbiot, Guardian    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This is sharp, significant scholarship . . . Thrilling.&#8217; Times Higher Education    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Raworth&#8217;s magnum opus . . . A fascinating reminder to business leaders and economists alike to stand back at a distance to examine our modern economics.&#8217; Books of the Year, Forbes    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;There are some really important economic and political thinkers around at the moment &#8211; such as Kate Raworth&#8217;s Doughnut Economics.&#8217; Andrew Marr, Guardian    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An admirable attempt to broaden the horizons of economic thinking.&#8217; Martin Wolf, Books of the Year, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A compelling and timely intervention.&#8217; Caroline Lucas MP, Books of the Year, The Ecologist</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doughnut-economics-seven-ways-to-think-like-a-21st-century-economist-kate-raworth-abridged/">Doughnut Economics : Seven Ways to Think Like a 21st-Century Economist &#8211; Kate Raworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myth of the Rational Voter : Why Democracies Choose Bad Policies &#8211; New Edition &#8211; Bryan Caplan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-myth-of-the-rational-voter-why-democracies-choose-bad-policies-new-edition-bryan-caplan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myth-of-the-rational-voter-why-democracies-choose-bad-policies-new-edition-bryan-caplan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The greatest obstacle to sound economic policy is not entrenched special interests or rampant lobbying, but the popular misconceptions, irrational beliefs, and personal biases held by ordinary voters. This is economist Bryan Caplan&#8217;s sobering assessment in this provocative and eye-opening book. Caplan argues that voters continually elect politicians who either share their biases or else [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-of-the-rational-voter-why-democracies-choose-bad-policies-new-edition-bryan-caplan-abridged/">The Myth of the Rational Voter : Why Democracies Choose Bad Policies &#8211; New Edition &#8211; Bryan Caplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The greatest obstacle to sound economic policy is not entrenched special interests or rampant lobbying, but the popular misconceptions, irrational beliefs, and personal biases held by ordinary voters. This is economist Bryan Caplan&#8217;s sobering assessment in this provocative and eye-opening book. Caplan argues that voters continually elect politicians who either share their biases or else pretend to, resulting in bad policies winning again and again by popular demand. Boldly calling into question our most basic assumptions about American politics, Caplan contends that democracy fails precisely because it does what voters want. Through an analysis of Americans&#8217; voting behavior and opinions on a range of economic issues, he makes the convincing case that noneconomists suffer from four prevailing biases: they underestimate the wisdom of the market mechanism, distrust foreigners, undervalue the benefits of conserving labor, and pessimistically believe the economy is going from bad to worse.<br />
                    Caplan lays out several bold ways to make democratic government work better&#8211;for example, urging economic educators to focus on correcting popular misconceptions and recommending that democracies do less and let markets take up the slack. The Myth of the Rational Voter takes an unflinching look at how people who vote under the influence of false beliefs ultimately end up with government that delivers lousy results. With the upcoming presidential election season drawing nearer, this thought-provoking book is sure to spark a long-overdue reappraisal of our elective system.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-of-the-rational-voter-why-democracies-choose-bad-policies-new-edition-bryan-caplan-abridged/">The Myth of the Rational Voter : Why Democracies Choose Bad Policies &#8211; New Edition &#8211; Bryan Caplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late    </p>
<p>                    A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and living standards. The bottom line of this outrage is the same; people are demanding their governments do more to improve their lives faster, something which policymakers are unable to deliver under conditions of anaemic growth. Rising income inequality and a stagnant economy are threats to both the developed and the developing world, and leaders can no longer afford to ignore this gathering storm.    </p>
<p>                    In Edge of Chaos, Dambisa Moyo sets out the new political and economic challenges facing the world, and the specific, radical solutions needed to resolve these issues and reignite global growth. Dambisa enumerates the four headwinds of demographics, inequality, commodity scarcity and technological innovation that are driving social and economic unrest, and argues for a fundamental retooling of democratic capitalism to address current problems and deliver better outcomes in the future. In the twenty-first century, a crisis in one country can quickly become our own, and fragile economies produce a fragile international community. Edge of Chaos is a warning for advanced and emerging nations alike: we must reverse the dramatic erosion in growth, or face the consequences of a fragmented and unstable global future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the acclaim for The End of the Free Market, Ian Bremmer is back with Every Nation for Itself, now in paperback, where he addresses the next big issue for the shifting world economy. &#8216;Smart and snappy &#8230; provides the most cogent prediction of how the politics of a post-America world will play out&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following the acclaim for The End of the Free Market, Ian Bremmer is back with Every Nation for Itself, now in paperback, where he addresses the next big issue for the shifting world economy.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Smart and snappy &#8230; provides the most cogent prediction of how the politics of a post-America world will play out&#8217;  New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    What happens when nobody&#8217;s running the world?    </p>
<p>                    The United States is in financial crisis and can&#8217;t hold onto the reins of the G-20. But China has no interest in international leadership, Europe is trying to save the euro, and emerging powers like Brazil and India are focused on domestic development. No government has the time, resources or political capital needed to take an international lead. The world power structure is about to have a vacancy&#8230;at the top.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the G-Zero world, in which no single country has the power to shape a truly global agenda. That means we are about to see 20 years of conflict over economics, finance and climate change.    </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author and strategist Ian Bremmer reveals how world powers are rapidly turning into gated communities, locked in competition. Who will prevail?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prodigy in the US global commentariat. Mr Bremmer&#8217;s rehearsal of the consequences should make us all wise up&#8217; Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An author who is always full of insights&#8217; George Osborne    </p>
<p>                    Ian Bremmer is the president of the world&#8217;s leading global political risk research and consulting firm, Eurasia Group. He has written for the Wall Street Journal, Washington Post, Newsweek, and Harvard Business Review. His six books include The J Curve and The End Of The Free Market.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ai Superpowers : China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order &#8211; Kai-Fu Lee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES, USA TODAY, AND WALL STREET JOURNAL BESTSELLER &#8220;Kai-Fu Lee believes China will be the next tech-innovation superpower and in AI Superpowers: China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order, he explains why. Taiwan-born Lee is perfectly positioned for the task.&#8221;-New York Magazine In this thought-provoking book, Lee argues powerfully that because [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/">Ai Superpowers : China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order &#8211; Kai-Fu Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES, USA TODAY, AND WALL STREET JOURNAL BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Kai-Fu Lee believes China will be the next tech-innovation superpower and in AI Superpowers: China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order, he explains why. Taiwan-born Lee is perfectly positioned for the task.&#8221;-New York Magazine     </p>
<p>                    In this thought-provoking book, Lee argues powerfully that because of the unprecedented developments in AI, dramatic changes will be happening much sooner than many of us expected. Indeed, as the US-Sino AI competition begins to heat up, Lee urges the US and China to both accept and to embrace the great responsibilities that come with significant technological power.     </p>
<p>                    Most experts already say that AI will have a devastating impact on blue-collar jobs. But Lee predicts that Chinese and American AI will have a strong impact on white-collar jobs as well. Is universal basic income the solution? In Lee&#8217;s opinion, probably not. But he provides a clear description of which jobs will be affected and how soon, which jobs can be enhanced with AI, and most importantly, how we can provide solutions to some of the most profound changes in the future of human history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/">Ai Superpowers : China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order &#8211; Kai-Fu Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After everything that&#8217;s happened, how is it possible that conservatives still win debates about the economy? Time and again the right wins over voters by claiming that their solutions are only common sense, even as their tired policies of budgetary sacrifice and corporate plunder both create and prolong economic disaster. Why does the electorate keep [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After everything that&#8217;s happened, how is it possible that conservatives still win debates about the economy? Time and again the right wins over voters by claiming that their solutions are only common sense, even as their tired policies of budgetary sacrifice and corporate plunder both create and prolong economic disaster. Why does the electorate keep buying what they&#8217;re selling? According to political communications expert Anat Shenker-Osorio, it&#8217;s all about language,and not just theirs, but ours.In  Don&#8217;t Buy It  Shenker-Osorio diagnoses our economic discourse as stricken with faulty messages, deceptive personification, and, worst of all, a barely coherent concept of what the economy actually is. Opening up the business section of most newspapers or flipping on cable news unleashes an onslaught of economic doomsaying that treats the economy as an ungovernable force of nature. Alternately, by calling the economy  unhealthy&#8221; or  recovering&#8221; as we so often do, we unconsciously give it the status of a living being. No wonder Americans become willing to submit to any indignity required to keep the economy happy. Tread lightly, we can&#8217;t risk irritating the economy!Cutting through conservative myth-making, messaging muddles, and destructive misinformation, Shenker-Osorio suggests a new way to win the most important arguments of our day. The left doesn&#8217;t have to self-destruct every time matters economic come to the fore,there are metaphors and frames that can win, and Shenker-Osorio shows what they are and how to use them. Don&#8217;t Buy It  is a vital handbook for seizing victory in the economic debate. In the end, it convincingly shows that radically altering our politics and policies for the better is a matter of first changing the conversation,literally.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Poverty : Economic Possibilities for Our Time &#8211; Jeffrey D. Sachs, Foreword by Bono (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Book and man are brilliant, passionate, optimistic and impatient . . . Outstanding.&#8221; -The Economist The landmark exploration of economic prosperity and how the world can escape from extreme poverty for the world&#8217;s poorest citizens, from one of the world&#8217;s most renowned economists Hailed by Time as one of the world&#8217;s hundred most influential people, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/">The End of Poverty : Economic Possibilities for Our Time &#8211; Jeffrey D. Sachs, Foreword by Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Book and man are brilliant, passionate, optimistic and impatient . . . Outstanding.&#8221; -The Economist    </p>
<p>                    The landmark exploration of economic prosperity and how the world can escape from extreme poverty for the world&#8217;s poorest citizens, from one  of the world&#8217;s most renowned economists    </p>
<p>                     Hailed by Time as one of the world&#8217;s hundred most influential people, Jeffrey D. Sachs is renowned for his work around the globe advising economies in crisis. Now a classic of its genre, The End of Poverty distills more than thirty years of experience to offer a uniquely informed vision of the steps that can transform impoverished countries into prosperous ones. Marrying vivid storytelling with rigorous analysis, Sachs lays out a clear conceptual map of the world economy. Explaining his own work in Bolivia, Russia, India, China, and Africa, he offers an integrated set of solutions to the interwoven economic, political, environmental, and social problems that challenge the world&#8217;s poorest countries.    </p>
<p>                     Ten years after its initial publication, The End of Poverty remains an indispensible and influential work. In this 10th anniversary edition, Sachs presents an extensive new foreword assessing the progress of the past decade, the work that remains to be done, and how each of us can help. He also looks ahead across the next fifteen years to 2030, the United Nations&#8217; target date for ending extreme poverty, offering new insights and recommendations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/">The End of Poverty : Economic Possibilities for Our Time &#8211; Jeffrey D. Sachs, Foreword by Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Way Back : Restoring the Promise of America &#8211; F. H. Buckley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-way-back-restoring-the-promise-of-america-f-h-buckley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-way-back-restoring-the-promise-of-america-f-h-buckley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The promise of America is that, with ambition and hard work, anyone can rise to the top. But now the promise has been broken, and weve become an aristocracy where rich parents raise rich kids and poor parents raise poor kids. Weve been told that the changes are structural, that theres nothing we can do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-back-restoring-the-promise-of-america-f-h-buckley-abridged/">The Way Back : Restoring the Promise of America &#8211; F. H. Buckley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The promise of America is that, with ambition and hard work, anyone can rise to the top. But now the promise has been broken, and weve become an aristocracy where rich parents raise rich kids and poor parents raise poor kids.     </p>
<p>                    Weve been told that the changes are structural, that theres nothing we can do about this. But that doesnt explain why other First World countries are beating us hands down on the issue of mobility.     </p>
<p>                    What&#8217;s different about America is our politics. An ostensibly progressive New Class of comfortably rich professionals, media leaders, and academics has shaped the contours of American politics and given us a country of fixed economic classes. It is supported by the poorest of Americans, who have little chance to rise, an alliance of both ends against the middle that recalls the Red Tories of parliamentary countries. Because they support an aristocracy, the members of the New Class are Tories, and because of their feigned concern for the poor, they are Red Tories.    </p>
<p>                    The Way Back explains the revolution in American politics, where political insurgents have challenged the complacent establishment of both parties, and shows how we can restore the promise of economic mobility and equality by pursuing socialist ends through capitalist means.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-back-restoring-the-promise-of-america-f-h-buckley-abridged/">The Way Back : Restoring the Promise of America &#8211; F. H. Buckley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners. Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners.    </p>
<p>                              Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond dealer, along with two Nobel prize winners and a floor of Wall Street&#8217;s brightest and best, Long-Term Captial Management was from the beginning hailed as a new gold standard in investing. It was to be the hedge fund to end all other hedge funds: a discreet private investment club limited to those rich enough to pony up millions.    </p>
<p>                              It became the banks&#8217; own favourite fund and from its inception achieved a run of dizzyingly spectacular returns. New investors barged each other aside to get their investment money into LTCM&#8217;s hands. But as competitors began to mimic Meriweather&#8217;s fund, he altered strategy to maintain the fund&#8217;s performance, leveraging capital with credit on a scale not fully understood and never seen before.    </p>
<p>                              When the markets in Indonesia, South America and Russia crashed in 1998 LCTM&#8217;s investments crashed with them and mountainous debts accumulated. The fund was in melt-down, and threatening to bring down into its trillion-dollar black hole a host of financial instiutions from New York to Switzerland. It&#8217;s a tale of vivid characters, overwheening ambition, and perilous drama told, in Roger Lowenstein&#8217;s hands, with brilliant style and panache.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Defence of Selfishness : Why the Code of Self-Sacrifice is Unjust and Destructive &#8211; Peter Schwartz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From childhood, we&#8217;re taught one central, non-controversial idea about morality: self-sacrifice is a virtue. It is universally accepted that serving the needs of others, rather than our own, is the essence of morality. To be ethical &#8211; it is believed &#8211; is to be altruistic. Questioning this belief is regarded as tantamount to questioning the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/">In Defence of Selfishness : Why the Code of Self-Sacrifice is Unjust and Destructive &#8211; Peter Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From childhood, we&#8217;re taught one central, non-controversial idea about morality: self-sacrifice is a virtue. It is universally accepted that serving the needs of others, rather than our own, is the essence of morality. To be ethical &#8211; it is believed &#8211; is to be altruistic. Questioning this belief is regarded as tantamount to questioning the self-evident. Here, Peter Schwartz questions it. In Defense of Selfishness refutes widespread misconceptions about the meaning of selfishness and of altruism. Basing his arguments on Ayn Rand&#8217;s ethics of rational self-interest, Schwartz demonstrates that genuine selfishness is not exemplified by the brutal plundering of an Attila the Hun or the conniving duplicity of a Bernard Madoff. To the contrary, such people are acting against their actual, long-range interests. The truly selfish individual is committed to moral principles and lives an honest, productive, self-respecting life. He does not feed parasitically off other people. Instead, he renounces the unearned, and deals with others &#8211; in both the material and spiritual realms &#8211; by offering value for value, to mutual benefit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/">In Defence of Selfishness : Why the Code of Self-Sacrifice is Unjust and Destructive &#8211; Peter Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Only Game in Town : Central Banks, Instability, and Recovering from Another Collapse &#8211; Mohamed A. El-Erian (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-only-game-in-town-central-banks-instability-and-recovering-from-another-collapse-mohamed-a-el-erian-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-only-game-in-town-central-banks-instability-and-recovering-from-another-collapse-mohamed-a-el-erian-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A roadmap to what lies ahead and the decisions we must make now to stave off the next global economic and financial crisis, from one of the world&#8217;s most influential economic thinkers and the author of When Markets Collide &#8211; Updated, with a new chapter and author&#8217;s note &#8220;The one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-only-game-in-town-central-banks-instability-and-recovering-from-another-collapse-mohamed-a-el-erian-abridged/">The Only Game in Town : Central Banks, Instability, and Recovering from Another Collapse &#8211; Mohamed A. El-Erian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A roadmap to what lies ahead and the decisions we must make now to stave off the next global economic and financial crisis, from one of the world&#8217;s most influential economic thinkers and the author of When Markets Collide &#8211; Updated, with a new chapter and author&#8217;s note     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The one economic book you must read now . . . If you want to understand [our] bifurcated world and where it&#8217;s headed, there is no better interpreter than Mohamed El-Erian.&#8221;&#8211;Time     </p>
<p>                    Our current economic path is coming to an end. The signposts are all around us: sluggish growth, rising inequality, stubbornly high pockets of unemployment, and jittery financial markets, to name a few. Soon we will reach a fork in the road: One path leads to renewed growth, prosperity, and financial stability, the other to recession and market disorder.     </p>
<p>                    In The Only Game in Town,  El-Erian casts his gaze toward the future of the global economy and markets, outlining the choices we face both individually and collectively in an era of economic uncertainty and financial insecurity. Beginning with their response to the 2008 global crisis, El-Erian explains how and why our central banks became the critical policy actors&#8211;and, most important, why they cannot continue is this role alone. They saved the financial system from collapse in 2008 and a multiyear economic depression, but lack the tools to enable a return to high inclusive growth and durable financial stability. The time has come for a policy handoff, from a prolonged period of monetary policy experimentation to a strategy that better targets what ails economies and distorts the financial sector&#8211;before we stumble into another crisis.     </p>
<p>                     The future, critically, is not predestined. It is up to us to decide where we will go from here as households, investors, companies, and governments. Using a mix of insights from economics, finance, and behavioral science, this book gives us the tools we need to properly understand this turning point, prepare for it, and come out of it stronger. A comprehensive, controversial look at the realities of our global economy and markets, The Only Game in Town is required reading for investors, policymakers, and anyone interested in the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-only-game-in-town-central-banks-instability-and-recovering-from-another-collapse-mohamed-a-el-erian-abridged/">The Only Game in Town : Central Banks, Instability, and Recovering from Another Collapse &#8211; Mohamed A. El-Erian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age. Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award    </p>
<p>                    A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age.    </p>
<p>                    Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and engrossing history of Bitcoin, the landmark digital money and financial technology that has spawned a global social movement.    </p>
<p>                    The notion of a new currency, maintained by the computers of users around the world, has been the butt of many jokes, but that has not stopped it from growing into a technology worth billions of dollars, supported by the hordes of followers who have come to view it as the most important new idea since the creation of the Internet. Believers from Beijing to Buenos Aires see the potential for a financial system free from banks and governments. More than just a tech industry fad, Bitcoin has threatened to decentralize some of society&#8217;s most basic institutions.    </p>
<p>                    An unusual tale of group invention, Digital Gold charts the rise of the Bitcoin technology through the eyes of the movement&#8217;s colorful central characters, including an Argentinian millionaire, a Chinese entrepreneur, Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, and Bitcoin&#8217;s elusive creator, Satoshi Nakamoto. Already, Bitcoin has led to untold riches for some, and prison terms for others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First as Tragedy, Then as Farce &#8211; Slavoj Zizek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Phenomenology & Existentialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Billions of dollars were hastily poured into the global banking system in a frantic attempt at financial stabilisation. So why has it not been possible to bring the same forces to bear in addressing world poverty and environmental crisis? In this take-no-prisoners analysis, Slavoj Zizek frames the moral failures of the modern world in terms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/">First as Tragedy, Then as Farce &#8211; Slavoj Zizek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Billions of dollars were hastily poured into the global banking system in a frantic attempt at financial stabilisation. So why has it not been possible to bring the same forces to bear in addressing world poverty and environmental crisis? In this take-no-prisoners analysis, Slavoj Zizek frames the moral failures of the modern world in terms of the epoch-making events of the first decade of this century. What he finds is the old one-two punch of history: the jab of tragedy, the right hook of farce. In the attacks of 9/11 and the global credit crunch, liberalism dies twice: as a political doctrine and as an economic theory. The election of Donald Trump only confirms the bankruptcy of a liberal order on its last legs. First as Tragedy, Then as Farce is a call for the left to reinvent itself in the light of our desperate historical situation. The time for liberal, moralistic blackmail is over.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/">First as Tragedy, Then as Farce &#8211; Slavoj Zizek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, Airbnb, Kickstarter, and other innovators, and that we understand money&#8217;s transition from hard currencies to cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin if we are to access their cooperative potential.  The Evolution of Money illuminates this fascinating reality, focusing on the tension between currency&#8217;s real and abstract properties and advancing a vital theory of money rooted in this dual exchange. It begins with the debt tablets of Mesopotamia and follows with the development of coin money in ancient Greece and Rome, gold-backed currencies in medieval Europe, and monetary economics in Victorian England. The book ends in the digital era, with the cryptocurrencies and service providers that are making the most of money&#8217;s virtual side and that suggest a tectonic shift in what we call money.<br />
                    By building this organic time line, The Evolution of Money helps us anticipate money&#8217;s next, transformative role.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE WINNERS OF THE 2019 NOBEL PRIZE IN ECONOMICS &#8216;Wonderfully refreshing . . . A must read&#8217; Thomas Piketty In this revolutionary book, prize-winning economists Abhijit V. Banerjee and Esther Duflo show how economics, when done right, can help us solve the thorniest social and political problems of our day. From immigration to inequality, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/">Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE WINNERS OF THE 2019 NOBEL PRIZE IN ECONOMICS    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderfully refreshing . . . A must read&#8217; Thomas Piketty     </p>
<p>                    In this revolutionary book, prize-winning economists Abhijit V. Banerjee and Esther Duflo show how economics, when done right, can help us solve the thorniest social and political problems of our day. From immigration to inequality, slowing growth to accelerating climate change, we have the resources to address the challenges we face but we are so often blinded by ideology.    </p>
<p>                    Original, provocative and urgent, Good Economics for Hard Times offers the new thinking that we need. It builds on cutting-edge research in economics &#8211; and years of exploring the most effective solutions to alleviate extreme poverty &#8211; to make a persuasive case for an intelligent interventionism and a society built on compassion and respect. A much-needed antidote to polarized discourse, this book shines a light to help us appreciate and understand our precariously balanced world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/">Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU & European Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crisp, clear and quietly devastating&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Excellent, authoritative, highly readable&#8217; Irish Times A succinct, expert guide to how we got to Brexit After all the debates, manoeuvrings, recriminations and exaltations, Brexit is upon us. But, as Kevin O&#8217;Rourke writes, Brexit did not emerge out of nowhere: it is the culmination of events that have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/">A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crisp, clear and quietly devastating&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;Excellent, authoritative, highly readable&#8217; Irish Times    </p>
<p>                    A succinct, expert guide to how we got to Brexit    </p>
<p>                    After all the debates, manoeuvrings, recriminations and exaltations,  Brexit is upon us. But, as Kevin O&#8217;Rourke writes, Brexit did not emerge  out of nowhere: it is the culmination of events  that have been under  way for decades and have historical roots stretching back well beyond  that. Brexit has a history.    </p>
<p>                    O&#8217;Rourke, one of the leading economic  historians of his generation, explains not only how British attitudes  to Europe have evolved, but also how the EU&#8217;s history explains why it  operates as it does today &#8211; and how that history has shaped the ways in  which it has responded to Brexit. Why are the economics, the politics  and the history so tightly woven together? Crucially, he also explains  why the question of the Irish border is not just one of customs and  trade, but for the EU goes to the heart of what it is about.  The way in  which British, Irish and European histories continue to interact with  each other will shape the future of Brexit &#8211; and of the continent.    </p>
<p>                    Calm and lucid, A Short History of Brexit  rises above the usual fray of discussions to provide fresh perspectives  and understanding of the most momentous political and economic change  in Britain and the EU for decades.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/">A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Information: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT    </p>
<p>                    We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need to be late.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master class &#8230; As a guide for perplexed Westerners, this book is very hard to beat &#8230; an honest, cohesive explanation for why the world is the way it is, without miracle cures or scapegoats&#8217; John Micklethwait, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; admirably honest &#8230; injects a badly needed dose of optimism into the modern debate&#8217; Gillian Tett, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;His main piece of advice for individuals, corporations, and countries is clear: Take a deep breath and adapt. This world isn&#8217;t going to wait for you&#8217; Fortune    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A humane and empathetic book&#8217; David Henkin, The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The shift toward automation is about to create a tsunami of unemployment. Not in the distant future&#8211;now. One recent estimate predicts 13 million American workers will lose their jobs within the next seven years-jobs that won&#8217;t be replaced. In a future marked by restlessness and chronic unemployment, what will happen to American society? In The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/">The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The shift toward automation is about to create a tsunami of unemployment. Not in the distant future&#8211;now. One recent estimate predicts 13 million American workers will lose their jobs within the next seven years-jobs that won&#8217;t be replaced. In a future marked by restlessness and chronic unemployment, what will happen to American society?    </p>
<p>                    In The War on Normal People, Andrew Yang paints a dire portrait of the American economy. Rapidly advancing technologies like artificial intelligence, robotics and automation software are making millions of Americans&#8217; livelihoods irrelevant. The consequences are these trends are already being felt across our communities in the form of political unrest, drug use, and other social ills. The future looks dire-but is it unavoidable?    </p>
<p>                    In The War on Normal People, Yang imagines a different future &#8212; one in which having a job is distinct from the capacity to prosper and seek fulfillment. At this vision&#8217;s core is Universal Basic Income, the concept of providing all citizens with a guaranteed income-and one that is rapidly gaining popularity among forward-thinking politicians and economists. Yang proposes that UBI is an essential step toward a new, more durable kind of economy, one he calls &#8220;human capitalism.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/">The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Selected as a Financial Times Best Book of 2013 Governments today in both Europe and the United States have succeeded in casting government spending as reckless wastefulness that has made the economy worse. In contrast, they have advanced a policy of draconian budget cuts-austerity-to solve the financial crisis. We are told that we have all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/">Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Selected as a Financial Times Best Book of 2013    </p>
<p>                    Governments today in both Europe and the United States have succeeded in casting government spending as reckless wastefulness that has made the economy worse. In contrast, they have advanced a policy of draconian budget cuts-austerity-to solve the financial crisis. We are told that we have all lived beyond our means and now need to tighten our belts. This view conveniently forgets where all that debt came from. Not from an orgy of government spending, but as the direct result of bailing out,<br />
                    recapitalizing, and adding liquidity to the broken banking system. Through these actions private debt was rechristened as government debt while those responsible for generating it walked away scot free, placing the blame on the state, and the burden on the taxpayer.     </p>
<p>                    That burden now takes the form of a global turn to austerity, the policy of reducing domestic wages and prices to restore competitiveness and balance the budget. The problem, according to political economist Mark Blyth, is that austerity is a very dangerous idea. First of all, it doesn&#8217;t work. As the past four years and countless historical examples from the last 100 years show, while it makes sense for any one state to try and cut its way to growth, it simply cannot work when all states try it<br />
                    simultaneously: all we do is shrink the economy. In the worst case, austerity policies worsened the Great Depression and created the conditions for seizures of power by the forces responsible for the Second World War: the Nazis and the Japanese military establishment. As Blyth amply demonstrates,<br />
                    the arguments for austerity are tenuous and the evidence thin. Rather than expanding growth and opportunity, the repeated revival of this dead economic idea has almost always led to low growth along with increases in wealth and income inequality. Austerity demolishes the conventional wisdom, marshaling an army of facts to demand that we austerity for what it is, and what it costs us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/">Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Treasure Islands : Tax Havens and the Men who Stole the World &#8211; Nicholas Shaxson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Tax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WITH NEW AND UPDATED MATERIAL Billionaire Warren Buffet, currently the third wealthiest man in the world, paid the lowest rate of tax among his office staff, including his receptionist. In 2006 the world&#8217;s three biggest banana companies did nearly GBP400 million worth of business in Britain but paid just GBP128,000 in tax between them. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/">Treasure Islands : Tax Havens and the Men who Stole the World &#8211; Nicholas Shaxson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WITH NEW AND UPDATED MATERIAL    </p>
<p>                    Billionaire Warren Buffet, currently the third wealthiest man in the world, paid the lowest rate of tax among his office staff, including his receptionist.    </p>
<p>                    In 2006 the world&#8217;s three biggest banana companies did nearly GBP400 million worth of business in Britain but paid just GBP128,000 in tax between them.    </p>
<p>                    In January 2009, US law enforcement fined Lloyds TSB $350 million after it admitted secretly channelling Iranian and Sudanese money into the US banking system.    </p>
<p>                    Tax havens are the most important single reason why poor people and poor countries stay poor. They lie at the very heart of the global economy, with over half the world trade processed through them. They have been instrumental in nearly every major economic event, in every big financial scandal, and in every financial crisis since the 1970s, including the latest global economic downturn.     </p>
<p>                    In Treasure Islands, Nicholas Shaxson shows how this happened, and what this means for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/">Treasure Islands : Tax Havens and the Men who Stole the World &#8211; Nicholas Shaxson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our Kids : The American Dream in Crisis &#8211; Robert D. Putnam (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/our-kids-the-american-dream-in-crisis-robert-d-putnam-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/our-kids-the-american-dream-in-crisis-robert-d-putnam-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and &#8220;a passionate, urgent&#8221; (The New Yorker) examination of the growing inequality gap from the bestselling author of Bowling Alone: why fewer Americans today have the opportunity for upward mobility. Central to the very idea of America is the principle that we are a nation of opportunity. But over the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-kids-the-american-dream-in-crisis-robert-d-putnam-abridged/">Our Kids : The American Dream in Crisis &#8211; Robert D. Putnam (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and &#8220;a passionate, urgent&#8221; (The New Yorker) examination of the growing inequality gap from the bestselling author of Bowling Alone: why fewer Americans today have the opportunity for upward mobility.<br />
                         Central to the very idea of America is the principle that we are a nation of opportunity. But over the last quarter century we have seen a disturbing &#8220;opportunity gap&#8221; emerge. We Americans have always believed that those who have talent and try hard will succeed, but this central tenet of the American Dream seems no longer true or at the least, much less true than it was.<br />
                         In Our Kids, Robert Putnam offers a personal and authoritative look at this new American crisis, beginning with the example of his high school class of 1959 in Port Clinton, Ohio. The vast majority of those students went on to lives better than those of their parents. But their children and grandchildren have faced diminishing prospects. Putnam tells the tale of lessening opportunity through poignant life stories of rich, middle class, and poor kids from cities and suburbs across the country, brilliantly blended with the latest social-science research.<br />
                         &#8220;A truly masterful volume&#8221; (Financial Times), Our Kids provides a disturbing account of the American dream that is &#8220;thoughtful and persuasive&#8221; (The Economist). Our Kids offers a rare combination of individual testimony and rigorous evidence: &#8220;No one can finish this book and feel complacent about equal opportunity&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-kids-the-american-dream-in-crisis-robert-d-putnam-abridged/">Our Kids : The American Dream in Crisis &#8211; Robert D. Putnam (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job? That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves. The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job?     </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves.     </p>
<p>                    The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even many full-time and professional jobs are experiencing this precarious shift. Within a decade, a near-majority of the 145 million employed Americans will be impacted. Add to that the steamroller of automation, robots and artificial intelligence already replacing millions of workers and projected to obsolesce millions more, and the jobs picture starts looking grim.     </p>
<p>                    Now a weird yet historic mash-up of Silicon Valley technology and Wall Street greed is thrusting upon us the latest economic fraud: the so-called sharing economy, with companies like Uber, Airbnb and TaskRabbit allegedly liberating workers to become independent and their own CEOs, hiring themselves out for ever-smaller jobs and wages while the companies profit.     </p>
<p>                    But this share the crumbs economy is just the tip of a looming iceberg that the middle class is drifting toward. Raw Deal: How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers, by veteran journalist Steven Hill, is an exposé that challenges conventional thinking, and the hype celebrating this new economy, by showing why the vision of the techno sapien leaders and their Ayn Rand libertarianism is a dead end.     </p>
<p>                    In Raw Deal, Steven Hill proposes pragmatic policy solutions to transform the US economy and its safety net and social contract, launching a new kind of deal to restore power back into the hands of American workers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capitalism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; James Fulcher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/capitalism-a-very-short-introduction-james-fulcher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/capitalism-a-very-short-introduction-james-fulcher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is capitalism? Is capitalism the same everywhere? Is there an alternative? The word &#8216;capitalism&#8217; is one that is heard and used frequently, but what is capitalism really all about, and what does it mean? This Very Short Introduction addresses questions such as &#8216;what is capital?&#8217; before discussing the history and development of capitalism through [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-a-very-short-introduction-james-fulcher-abridged/">Capitalism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; James Fulcher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is capitalism? Is capitalism the same everywhere? Is there an alternative?     </p>
<p>                    The word &#8216;capitalism&#8217; is one that is heard and used frequently, but what is capitalism really all about, and what does it mean? This Very Short Introduction addresses questions such as &#8216;what is capital?&#8217; before discussing the history and development of capitalism through several detailed case studies, ranging from the tulipomania of 17th century Holland, the Great Depression of the 1930s, and in this new edition, the impact of the global financial crisis that started in 2007-8.    </p>
<p>                    James Fulcher looks at the different forms that capitalism takes in Britain, Japan, Sweden, and the United States, and explores whether capitalism has escaped the nation-state by going global. It ends by asking whether there is an alternative to capitalism, discussing socialism, communal and cooperative experiments, and the alternatives proposed by environmentalists.    </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books are the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-a-very-short-introduction-james-fulcher-abridged/">Capitalism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; James Fulcher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Necessary Revolution : Working Together to Create a Sustainable World &#8211; Peter M. Senge, Bryan Smith, Nina Kruschwitz, Joe Laur, Sara Schley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-necessary-revolution-working-together-to-create-a-sustainable-world-peter-m-senge-bryan-smith-nina-kruschwitz-joe-laur-sara-schley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-necessary-revolution-working-together-to-create-a-sustainable-world-peter-m-senge-bryan-smith-nina-kruschwitz-joe-laur-sara-schley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world in which the excess energy from one business would be used to heat another. Where buildings need less and less energy around the world, and where &#8220;regenerative&#8221; commercial buildings &#8211; ones that create more energy than they use &#8211; are being designed. A world in which environmentally sound products and processes would [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-necessary-revolution-working-together-to-create-a-sustainable-world-peter-m-senge-bryan-smith-nina-kruschwitz-joe-laur-sara-schley-abridged/">The Necessary Revolution : Working Together to Create a Sustainable World &#8211; Peter M. Senge, Bryan Smith, Nina Kruschwitz, Joe Laur, Sara Schley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world in which the excess energy from one business would be used to heat another. Where buildings need less and less energy around the world, and where &#8220;regenerative&#8221; commercial buildings &#8211; ones that create more energy than they use &#8211; are being designed. A world in which environmentally sound products and processes would be more cost-effective than wasteful ones. A world in which corporations such as Costco, Nike, BP, and countless others are forming partnerships with environmental and social justice organizations to ensure better stewardship of the earth and better livelihoods in the developing world. Now, stop imagining &#8211; that world is already emerging.     </p>
<p>                    A revolution is underway in today&#8217;s organizations. As Peter Senge and his co-authors reveal in The Necessary Revolution, companies around the world are boldly leading the change from dead-end &#8220;business as usual&#8221; tactics to transformative strategies that are essential for creating a flourishing, sustainable world. There is a long way to go, but the era of denial has ended. Today&#8217;s most innovative leaders are recognizing that for the sake of our companies and our world, we must implement revolutionary&#8211;not just incremental&#8211;changes in the way we live and work.     </p>
<p>                    Brimming with inspiring stories from individuals and organizations tackling social and environmental problems around the globe, THE NECESSARY REVOLUTION reveals how ordinary people at every level are transforming their businesses and communities. By working collaboratively across boundaries, they are exploring and putting into place unprecedented solutions that move beyond just being &#8220;less bad&#8221; to creating pathways that will enable us to flourish in an increasingly interdependent world. Among the stories in these pages are the evolution of Sweden&#8217;s &#8220;Green Zone,&#8221; Alcoa&#8217;s water use reduction goals, GE&#8217;s ecoimagination initiative, and Seventh Generation&#8217;s decision to shift some of their advertising to youth-led social change programs.     </p>
<p>                    At its heart, THE NECESSARY REVOLUTION contains a wealth of strategies that individuals and organizations can use &#8212; specific tools and ways of thinking &#8212; to help us build the confidence and competence to respond effectively to the greatest challenge of our time. It is an essential guidebook for all of us who recognize the need to act and work together&#8211;now&#8211;to create a sustainable world, both for ourselves and for the generations to follow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-necessary-revolution-working-together-to-create-a-sustainable-world-peter-m-senge-bryan-smith-nina-kruschwitz-joe-laur-sara-schley-abridged/">The Necessary Revolution : Working Together to Create a Sustainable World &#8211; Peter M. Senge, Bryan Smith, Nina Kruschwitz, Joe Laur, Sara Schley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land *A New York Post Must-Read Book* *A Newsweek Best New Book* *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017* *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017* *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks* The Wall Street Journal: A devastating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land     </p>
<p>                    *A New York Post Must-Read Book*<br />
                    *A Newsweek Best New Book*<br />
                    *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017*<br />
                    *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017*<br />
                    *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks*     </p>
<p>                    The Wall Street Journal: A devastating portrait&#8230;For anyone wondering why swing-state America voted against the establishment in 2016, Mr. Alexander supplies plenty of answers.      </p>
<p>                    Laura Miller, Slate: This book hunts bigger game. Reads like an odd&#8211;and oddly satisfying&#8211;fusion of George Packer&#8217;s The Unwinding and one of Michael Lewis&#8217; real-life financial thrillers.     </p>
<p>                    The New Yorker: Does a remarkable job.     </p>
<p>                    Beth Macy, author of Factory Man: This book should be required reading for people trying to understand Trumpism, inequality, and the sad state of a needlessly wrecked rural America. I wish I had written it.      </p>
<p>                    In 1947, Forbes magazine declared Lancaster, Ohio the epitome of the all-American town. Today it is damaged, discouraged, and fighting for its future. In Glass House, journalist Brian Alexander uses the story of one town to show how seeds sown 35 years ago have sprouted to give us Trumpism, inequality, and an eroding national cohesion.     </p>
<p>                    The Anchor Hocking Glass Company, once the world&#8217;s largest maker of glass tableware, was the base on which Lancaster&#8217;s society was built. As Glass House unfolds, bankruptcy looms. With access to the company and its leaders, and Lancaster&#8217;s citizens, Alexander shows how financial engineering took hold in the 1980s, accelerated in the 21st Century, and wrecked the company. We follow CEO Sam Solomon, an African-American leading the nearly all-white town&#8217;s biggest private employer, as he tries to rescue the company from the New York private equity firm that hired him. Meanwhile, Alexander goes behind the scenes, entwined with the lives of residents as they wrestle with heroin, politics, high-interest lenders, low wage jobs, technology, and the new demands of American life: people like Brian Gossett, the fourth generation to work at Anchor Hocking; Joe Piccolo, first-time director of the annual music festival who discovers the town relies on him, and it, for salvation; Jason Roach, who police believed may have been Lancaster&#8217;s biggest drug dealer; and Eric Brown, a local football hero-turned-cop who comes to realize that he can never arrest Lancaster&#8217;s real problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating investigation combining history, science and ideas, William Davies shows how well-being influences all aspects of our lives: business, finance, marketing and smart technology. This book will make you rethink everything from the way you work, the power of the &#8216;Nudge&#8217;, the ever-expanding definitions of depression, and the commercialization of your most private feelings. The Happiness Industry is a shocking and brilliantly argued warning about the new religion of the age: our emotions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Logo &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-logo-naomi-klein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumerism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-logo-naomi-klein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No Logo&#8217; was a book that defined a generation when it was first published in 1999. For its 10th anniversay Naomi Klein has updated this iconic book. By the time you&#8217;re twenty-one, you&#8217;ll have seen or heard a million advertisements. But you won&#8217;t be happier for it. This is a book about that much-maligned, much-misunderstood [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-logo-naomi-klein-abridged/">No Logo &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No Logo&#8217; was a book that defined a generation when it was first published in 1999. For its 10th anniversay Naomi Klein has updated this iconic book.    </p>
<p>                              By the time you&#8217;re twenty-one, you&#8217;ll have seen or heard a million advertisements. But you won&#8217;t be happier for it.    </p>
<p>                              This is a book about that much-maligned, much-misunderstood generation coming up behind the slackers, who are being intelligent and active about the world in which they find themselves. It is a world in which all that is &#8216;alternative&#8217; is sold, where any innovation or subversion is immediately adopted by un-radical, faceless corporations. But, gradually, tentatively, a new generation is beginning to fight consumerism with its own best weapons; and it is the first skirmishes in this war that this abrasively intelligent book documents brilliantly.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-logo-naomi-klein-abridged/">No Logo &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rift : A New Africa Breaks Free &#8211; Alex Perry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rift-a-new-africa-breaks-free-alex-perry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rift-a-new-africa-breaks-free-alex-perry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Taking the Great Rift Valley &#8211; the geological fault that will eventually tear Africa in two &#8211; as his central metaphor, Alex Perry explores the split between a resurgent Africa and a world at odds with its rise. Africa has long been misunderstood &#8211; and abused &#8211; by outsiders. Perry travelled the continent for most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rift-a-new-africa-breaks-free-alex-perry-abridged/">The Rift : A New Africa Breaks Free &#8211; Alex Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Taking the Great Rift Valley &#8211; the geological fault that will eventually tear Africa in two &#8211; as his central metaphor, Alex Perry explores the split between a resurgent Africa and a world at odds with its rise. Africa has long been misunderstood &#8211; and abused &#8211; by outsiders. Perry travelled the continent for most of a decade, meeting with entrepreneurs and warlords, professors and cocaine smugglers, presidents and jihadis, among many others.    </p>
<p>                    Opening with a devastating investigation into a largely unreported war crime in Somalia in 2011, he finds Africa at a moment of furious self-assertion. This is a remade continent, defiantly rising from centuries of oppression to become an economic and political titan: where cash is becoming a thing of the past, where astronomers are unlocking the origin of life and where, twenty-five years after Live Aid, Ethiopia&#8217;s first yuppies are traders on an electronic food exchange. Yet, as Africa finally wins the substance of its freedom, it must confront the three last false prophets of Islamists, dictators and aid workers, who would keep it in its bonds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rift-a-new-africa-breaks-free-alex-perry-abridged/">The Rift : A New Africa Breaks Free &#8211; Alex Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he tries to understand so-called European socialism firsthand. Though he first tries France (which has become a rhetorical stand-in for the continent as a whole in many Americans&#8217; minds), he eventually ventures into Germany to see what some call the &#8220;boring&#8221; Europe. There he finds the true &#8220;other&#8221; an economic model with more bottom-up worker control than that of any other country in the world and argues that, while we have to take Germany&#8217;s problems seriously, we also have to look seriously at how much it has achieved. Social democracy may let us live nicer lives; it also may be the only way to be globally competitive. This wry, timely book helps us understand why the European model, contrary to popular neoliberal wisdom, may thrive well into the twenty-first century without compromising its citizens&#8217; ease of living and be the best example for the United States to follow.    </p>
<p>                    Germany is more generous than the U.S.:    </p>
<p>                    The average number of paid vacation days in the U.S. is 13, versus Germany&#8217;s 35<br />
                    New mothers in the U.S. get three months of unpaid job-protected leave and only if they work for a company of 50 or more employees, while Germany mandates four months&#8217; paid leave and will pay parents 67% of their salary to stay home for up to 14 months to care for a newborn.<br />
                    U.S. life expectancy is 50th in the world, compared to Germany&#8217;s 32nd.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fixer : My Adventures Saving Startups from Death by Politics &#8211; Bradley Tusk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Service & Public Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The famed political advisor to Uber, FanDuel, Lemonade, Tesla and other startups reveals what really happens at the intersection of politics, tech and business Most new startups today are in highly regulated industries with strong incumbents &#8211; transportation, hotels, drones, energy, gaming, education, health care, cannabis, finance, liquor, insurance. The more startups try to snatch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/">The Fixer : My Adventures Saving Startups from Death by Politics &#8211; Bradley Tusk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The famed political advisor to Uber, FanDuel, Lemonade, Tesla and other startups reveals what really happens at the intersection of politics, tech and business Most new startups today are in highly regulated industries with strong incumbents &#8211; transportation, hotels, drones, energy, gaming, education, health care, cannabis, finance, liquor, insurance. The more startups try to snatch a piece of the establishment&#8217;s pie, the more they risk running into a political wall. That&#8217;s where Bradley Tusk comes in. Described as Silicon Valley&#8217;s Political Savior (Fast Company) Uber&#8217;s Political Genius (Vanity Fair) and Silicon Valley&#8217;s Favorite Fixer (TechCrunch) Tusk deploys the skills and knowledge he developed working with Chuck Schumer, Michael Bloomberg, Rod Blagojevich, and other political and business legends to help startups fight back. This book goes behind the scenes on how he helped stop the taxi industry from killing Uber in its infancy, how he held insurance companies at bay while startup Lemonade launched in each state, and how he helped online sports betting sites FanDuel and Draft Kings escape the regulatory death grip casinos tried to put on them. As Tusk writes, Every new company is essentially a tech startup. And when you disrupt someone in any industry, they don&#8217;t say thank you. They punch you in the nose. These are the lessons startups need to learn to punch back and survive the clutches of politics. Combining a firsthand glimpse behind the curtain with tangible advice for how any new venture can play the political game, THE FIXER is a must-read for aspiring entrepreneurs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/">The Fixer : My Adventures Saving Startups from Death by Politics &#8211; Bradley Tusk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is Wall Street bad for Main Street America? A well-told exploration of why our current economy is leaving too many behind. &#8211;The New York Times In looking at the forces that shaped the 2016 presidential election, one thing is clear: much of the population believes that our economic system is rigged to enrich the privileged [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/">Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is Wall Street bad for Main Street America?     </p>
<p>                    A well-told exploration of why our current economy is leaving too many behind. &#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                     In looking at the forces that shaped the 2016 presidential election, one thing is clear: much of the population believes that our economic system is rigged to enrich the privileged elites at the expense of hard-working Americans. This is a belief held equally on both sides of political spectrum, and it seems only to be gaining momentum.     </p>
<p>                    A key reason, says Financial Times columnist Rana Foroohar, is the fact that Wall Street is no longer supporting Main Street businesses that create the jobs for the middle and working class. She draws on in-depth reporting and interviews at the highest rungs of business and government to show how the &#8220;financialization of America&#8221;&#8211;the phenomenon by which finance and its way of thinking have come to dominate every corner of business&#8211;is threatening the American Dream.     </p>
<p>                     Now updated with new material explaining how our corrupted financial sys­tem propelled Donald Trump to power, Makers and Takers explores the confluence of forces that has led American businesses to favor balance-sheet engineering over the actual kind, greed over growth, and short-term profits over putting people to work. From the cozy relationship between Wall Street and Washington, to a tax code designed to benefit wealthy individuals and corporations, to forty years of bad policy decisions, she shows why so many Americans have lost trust in the sys­tem, and why it matters urgently to us all.     </p>
<p>                     Through colorful stories of both &#8220;Takers,&#8221; those stifling job creation while lining their own pockets, and &#8220;Makers,&#8221; businesses serving the real economy, Foroohar shows how we can reverse these trends for a better path forward.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/">Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drugs Trade / Drug Trafficking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organized Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like Ryanair or Apple. So when the drug cartels start to think like big business, the only way to understand them is using economics.     </p>
<p>                    In Narconomics, Tom Wainwright meets everyone from coca farmers in secret Andean locations, deluded heads of state in presidential palaces, journalists with a price on their head, gang leaders who run their empires from dangerous prisons and teenage hitmen on city streets &#8211; all in search of the economic truth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A tour de force of historical reportage, America&#8217;s Bank illuminates the tumultuous era and remarkable personalities that spurred the unlikely birth of America&#8217;s modern central bank, the Federal Reserve. Today, the Fed is the bedrock of the financial landscape, yet the fight to create it was so protracted and divisive that it seems a small [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A tour de force of historical reportage, America&#8217;s Bank illuminates the tumultuous era and remarkable personalities that spurred the unlikely birth of America&#8217;s modern central bank, the Federal Reserve. Today, the Fed is the bedrock of the financial landscape, yet the fight to create it was so protracted and divisive that it seems a small miracle that it was ever established.     </p>
<p>                    For nearly a century, America, alone among developed nations, refused to consider any central or organizing agency in its financial system. Americans&#8217; mistrust of big government and of big banks-a legacy of the country&#8217;s Jeffersonian, small-government traditions-was so widespread that modernizing reform was deemed impossible. Each bank was left to stand on its own, with no central reserve or lender of last resort. The real-world consequences of this chaotic and provincial system were frequent financial panics, bank runs, money shortages, and depressions. By the first decade of the twentieth century, it had become plain that the outmoded banking system was ill equipped to finance America&#8217;s burgeoning industry. But political will for reform was lacking. It took an economic meltdown, a high-level tour of Europe, and-improbably-a conspiratorial effort by vilified captains of Wall Street to overcome popular resistance. Finally, in 1913, Congress conceived a federalist and quintessentially American solution to the conflict that had divided bankers, farmers, populists, and ordinary Americans, and enacted the landmark Federal Reserve Act.    </p>
<p>                    Roger Lowenstein-acclaimed financial journalist and bestselling author of When Genius Failed and The End of Wall Street-tells the drama-laden story of how America created the Federal Reserve, thereby taking its first steps onto the world stage as a global financial power. America&#8217;s Bank showcases Lowenstein at his very finest: illuminating complex financial and political issues with striking clarity, infusing the debates of our past with all the gripping immediacy of today, and painting unforgettable portraits of Gilded Age bankers, presidents, and politicians.    </p>
<p>                    Lowenstein focuses on the four men at the heart of the struggle to create the Federal Reserve. These were Paul Warburg, a refined, German-born financier, recently relocated to New York, who was horrified by the primitive condition of America&#8217;s finances; Rhode Island&#8217;s Nelson W. Aldrich, the reigning power broker in the U.S. Senate and an archetypal Gilded Age legislator; Carter Glass, the ambitious, if then little-known, Virginia congressman who chaired the House Banking Committee at a crucial moment of political transition; and President Woodrow Wilson, the academician-turned-progressive-politician who forced Glass to reconcile his deep-seated differences with bankers and accept the principle (anathema to southern Democrats) of federal control. Weaving together a raucous era in American politics with a storied financial crisis and intrigue at the highest levels of Washington and Wall Street, Lowenstein brings the beginnings of one of the country&#8217;s most crucial institutions to vivid and unforgettable life. Readers of this gripping historical narrative will wonder whether they&#8217;re reading about one hundred years ago or the still-seething conflicts that mark our discussions of banking and politics today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
