<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Physiological &amp; Neuro-psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/physiological-neuro-psychology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/physiological-neuro-psychology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Physiological &amp; Neuro-psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/physiological-neuro-psychology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Becoming Aware : A 21-Day Mindfulness Program for Reducing Anxiety and Cultivating Calm &#8211; Dr. Daniel Siegel</title>
		<link>/becoming-aware-a-21-day-mindfulness-program-for-reducing-anxiety-and-cultivating-calm-dr-daniel-siegel/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Body]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/becoming-aware-a-21-day-mindfulness-program-for-reducing-anxiety-and-cultivating-calm-dr-daniel-siegel/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This hands-on user&#8217;s guide to the groundbreaking Wheel of Awareness meditation practice featured in the New York Times bestseller Aware takes readers step-by-step through a twenty-one-day journey to discover what it means to be truly present and aware in our daily lives. In today&#8217;s increasingly fast-paced world it can be difficult to find moments to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-aware-a-21-day-mindfulness-program-for-reducing-anxiety-and-cultivating-calm-dr-daniel-siegel/">Becoming Aware : A 21-Day Mindfulness Program for Reducing Anxiety and Cultivating Calm &#8211; Dr. Daniel Siegel</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This hands-on user&#8217;s guide to the groundbreaking Wheel of Awareness meditation practice featured in the New York Times bestseller Aware takes readers step-by-step through a twenty-one-day journey to discover what it means to be truly present and aware in our daily lives.     </p>
<p>                    In today&#8217;s increasingly fast-paced world it can be difficult to find moments to catch your breath, regain inner balance, and just . . . be. This simple yet profound guide shows readers how to strengthen their minds by learning to focus attention, open awareness, and develop a positive state of mind&#8211;the three pillars of mindfulness practice that research shows lead to greater physical and mental well-being.     </p>
<p>                    Psychiatrist and cofounder of the Mindsight Institute, Daniel J. Siegel, M.D., created the science-grounded meditation practice called the Wheel of Awareness to unlock the power of the brain to integrate its many functions and develop internal resources that lead to an enduring sense of calm and quiet. Packed with guided meditation instructions, practical exercises, and everyday tools and techniques, Becoming Aware meets readers where they are and offers a simple program to enhance our inner sense of clarity and even our interpersonal well-being.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-aware-a-21-day-mindfulness-program-for-reducing-anxiety-and-cultivating-calm-dr-daniel-siegel/">Becoming Aware : A 21-Day Mindfulness Program for Reducing Anxiety and Cultivating Calm &#8211; Dr. Daniel Siegel</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mind Time : The Temporal Factor in Consciousness &#8211; Benjamin Libet</title>
		<link>/mind-time-the-temporal-factor-in-consciousness-benjamin-libet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mind-time-the-temporal-factor-in-consciousness-benjamin-libet/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our subjective inner life is what really matters to us as human beings&#8211;and yet we know relatively little about how it arises. Over a long and distinguished career Benjamin Libet has conducted experiments that have helped us see, in clear and concrete ways, how the brain produces conscious awareness. For the first time, Libet gives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-time-the-temporal-factor-in-consciousness-benjamin-libet/">Mind Time : The Temporal Factor in Consciousness &#8211; Benjamin Libet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our subjective inner life is what really matters to us as human beings&#8211;and yet we know relatively little about how it arises. Over a long and distinguished career Benjamin Libet has conducted experiments that have helped us see, in clear and concrete ways, how the brain produces conscious awareness. For the first time, Libet gives his own account of these experiments and their importance for our understanding of consciousness.</p>
<p>                    Most notably, Libet&#8217;s experiments reveal a substantial delay&#8211;the &#8220;mind time&#8221; of the title&#8211;before any awareness affects how we view our mental activities. If all conscious awarenesses are preceded by unconscious processes, as Libet observes, we are forced to conclude that unconscious processes initiate our conscious experiences. Freely voluntary acts are found to be initiated unconsciously before an awareness of wanting to act&#8211;a discovery with profound ramifications for our understanding of free will.</p>
<p>                    How do the physical activities of billions of cerebral nerve cells give rise to an integrated conscious subjective awareness? How can the subjective mind affect or control voluntary actions? Libet considers these questions, as well as the implications of his discoveries for the nature of the soul, the identity of the person, and the relation of the non-physical subjective mind to the physical brain that produces it. Rendered in clear, accessible language, Libet&#8217;s experiments and theories will allow interested amateurs and experts alike to share the experience of the extraordinary discoveries made in the practical study of consciousness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-time-the-temporal-factor-in-consciousness-benjamin-libet/">Mind Time : The Temporal Factor in Consciousness &#8211; Benjamin Libet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Brain That Changes Itself : Stories of Personal Triumph from the Frontiers of Brain Science &#8211; Norman Doidge</title>
		<link>/the-brain-that-changes-itself-stories-of-personal-triumph-from-the-frontiers-of-brain-science-norman-doidge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-brain-that-changes-itself-stories-of-personal-triumph-from-the-frontiers-of-brain-science-norman-doidge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD &#8216;A remarkable and hopeful portrait of the endless adaptability of the human brain&#8217; Oliver Sacks &#8216;Utterly wonderful . . . without question one of the most important books about the brain you will ever read; yet it is beautifully written, immensely approachable, and full of humanity&#8217; Iain McGilchrist MA, author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-that-changes-itself-stories-of-personal-triumph-from-the-frontiers-of-brain-science-norman-doidge/">The Brain That Changes Itself : Stories of Personal Triumph from the Frontiers of Brain Science &#8211; Norman Doidge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A remarkable and hopeful portrait of the endless adaptability of the human brain&#8217; Oliver Sacks</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Utterly wonderful . . . without question one of the most important books about the brain you will ever read; yet it is beautifully written, immensely approachable, and full of humanity&#8217; Iain McGilchrist MA, author of The Master and His Emissary</p>
<p>                    Meet the ninety-year-old doctor who is still practicing medicine, the stroke victim who learned to move and talk again and the woman with half a brain that rewired itself to work as a whole. All these people had their lives transformed by the remarkable discovery that our brains can repair themselves through the power of positive thinking. </p>
<p>                    Here bestselling author, psychiatrist and psychoanalyst Norman Doidge reveals the secrets of the cutting-edge science of &#8216;neuroplasticity&#8217;. He introduces incredible case histories &#8211; blind people helped to see, IQs raised and memories sharpened &#8211; and tells the stories of the maverick scientists who are overturning centuries of assumptions about the brain.   </p>
<p>                    This inspiring book will leave you with a sense of wonder at the capabilities of the mind, and the self-healing power that lies within all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-that-changes-itself-stories-of-personal-triumph-from-the-frontiers-of-brain-science-norman-doidge/">The Brain That Changes Itself : Stories of Personal Triumph from the Frontiers of Brain Science &#8211; Norman Doidge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</title>
		<link>/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michio Kaku, the New York Times bestselling author of Physics of the Impossible and Physics of the Future tackles the most fascinating and complex object in the known universe: the human brain. The Future of the Mind brings a topic that once belonged solely to the province of science fiction into a startling new reality. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/">The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michio Kaku, the New York Times bestselling author of Physics of the Impossible and Physics of the Future tackles the most fascinating and complex object in the known universe: the human brain.     </p>
<p>                    The Future of the Mind brings a topic that once belonged solely to the province of science fiction into a startling new reality. This scientific tour de force unveils the astonishing research being done in top laboratories around the world&#8211;all based on the latest advancements in neuroscience and physics&#8211;including recent experiments in telepathy, mind control, avatars, telekinesis, and recording memories and dreams. The Future of the Mind is an extraordinary, mind-boggling exploration of the frontiers of neuroscience. Dr. Kaku looks toward the day when we may achieve the ability to upload the human brain to a computer, neuron for neuron; project thoughts and emotions around the world on a brain-net; take a &#8220;smart pill&#8221; to enhance cognition; send our consciousness across the universe; and push the very limits of immortality.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/">The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
