<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Non-alcoholic Beverages Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/non-alcoholic-beverages/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/non-alcoholic-beverages/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Non-alcoholic Beverages Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/non-alcoholic-beverages/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-alcoholic Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217; &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217;  &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller      </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice O&#8217;Keeffe, Guardian     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Truthful, modern and real&#8217; &#8211; Stylist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Brave, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober came to me at a time when I much needed it&#8230; The book became my best friend, and got me through, and took me on a journey.&#8217; &#8211; Sadie Frost     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Particularly lovely, because it&#8217;s not a deep and dark dive into someone&#8217;s terrible addiction. It&#8217;s a celebration of everything that she has gained from not drinking&#8217; &#8211; Laura Donnelly     </p>
<p>                    Ever sworn off alcohol for a month and found yourself drinking by the 7th? Think there&#8217;s &#8216;no point&#8217; in just one drink? Welcome! There are millions of us. 64% of Brits want to drink less.    </p>
<p>                    Catherine Gray was stuck in a hellish whirligig of Drink, Make horrible decisions, Hangover, Repeat. She had her fair share of &#8216;drunk tank&#8217; jail cells and topless-in-a-hot-tub misadventures.    </p>
<p>                    But this book goes beyond the binges and blackouts to deep-dive into uncharted territory: What happens after you quit drinking? This gripping, heart-breaking and witty book takes us down the rabbit-hole of an alternative reality. A life with zero hangovers, through sober weddings, sex, Christmases and breakups.     </p>
<p>                    In The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober, Catherine Gray shines a light on society&#8217;s drink-pushing and talks to top neuroscientists and psychologists about why we drink, delving into the science behind what it does to our brains and bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Much more than a tale from the netherworld of addicted drinking, this book is about the escape, and why a sober life can be more intoxicating than you ever imagined. Whether you&#8217;re a hopelessly devoted drinker, merely sober-curious, or you&#8217;ve already ditched the drink, you will love this book.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Haunting, admirable and enlightening&#8217; &#8211; The Pool     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A riveting, raw, yet humorous memoir with actionable advice. A truly unique blend of storytelling and science that holds a universe of hope.&#8217; &#8211; Annie Grace, author of This Naked Mind     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Like listening to your best friend teach you to be sober. Lighthearted but serious, it&#8217;s packed with ideas, tools, tips and, most importantly, reasons for living a sober life. This book is excellent.&#8217;- Eric Zimmer, host of podcast The One You Feed     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s fizzy writing succeeds in making this potentially boring-as-hell subject both engaging and highly seductive&#8217; &#8211; The Bookseller     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray is an exceptional writer. Her exquisitely crafted thoughts on the joys of being sober are not only deeply honest and pragmatic, but she manages to infuse tons of humor. This is a delightful, informative, and compelling read for all those who are sober or seeking sobriety.&#8217; &#8211; Sasha Tozzi, Huffington Post columnist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine&#8217;s writing style and voice captivate me. She has a way of translating her story into an experience I don&#8217;t want to end. I want to drink every drop she produces.&#8217; &#8211; Holly Whitaker, founder of Hip Sobriety School and co-presenter of Home podcast     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book is great. A balanced, informative and entertaining melange of memoir, sociology and psychology. I identified very strongly with huge sections of it.&#8217; &#8211; Jon Stewart, guitarist of Sleeper and Leaving AA, Staying Sober blogger >    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Sober is too often equated with &#8220;sombre&#8221; in our culture. Gray&#8217;s book turns that idea on its head. Her experience of sobriety is joyful and life-affirming. A must-read for anyone who has a nagging suspicion that alcohol may be taking away more than it&#8217;s giving.&#8217; &#8211; Hilda Burke, psychotherapist and couples counsellor     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray really captures the FUN we can have in sobriety. This book challenges the status quo; sobriet sounds as liberating as taking a trip to the jungle. Fun and inspirational. What an important book for our time! A joy to read.&#8217; &#8211; Samantha Moyo, founder of Morning Gloryville     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;No other author writes about sober living with as much warmth or emotional range as Catherine Gray. Her deep insight into the subtle psychologies of drinking, and of life, means that everything she writes is both utterly relatable and stretches our minds. Hers is a rare wisdom.&#8217; &#8211; Dr Richard Piper, CEO, Alcohol Change UK</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
