<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Coping With Drug &amp; Alcohol Abuse Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/coping-with-drug-alcohol-abuse/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/coping-with-drug-alcohol-abuse/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Coping With Drug &amp; Alcohol Abuse Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/coping-with-drug-alcohol-abuse/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dry : A Memoir &#8211; Augusten Burroughs</title>
		<link>/dry-a-memoir-augusten-burroughs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dry-a-memoir-augusten-burroughs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Tenth Anniversary Edition of the New York Times bestselling book that has sold over half a million copies in paperback. I was addicted to Bewitched as a kid. I worshipped Darren Stevens the First. When he&#8217;d come home from work and Samantha would say, &#8216;Darren, would you like me to fix you a drink?&#8217; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dry-a-memoir-augusten-burroughs/">Dry : A Memoir &#8211; Augusten Burroughs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Tenth Anniversary Edition of the New York Times bestselling book that has sold over half a million copies in paperback. </p>
<p>                    I was addicted to Bewitched as a kid. I worshipped Darren Stevens the First. When he&#8217;d come home from work and Samantha would say, &#8216;Darren, would you like me to fix you a drink?&#8217; He&#8217;d always rest his briefcase on the table below the mirror in the foyer, wipe his forehead with a monogrammed handkerchief and say, &#8216;Better make it a double.&#8217; (from Chapter Two) </p>
<p>                    You may not know it, but you&#8217;ve met Augusten Burroughs. You&#8217;ve seen him on the street, in bars, on the subway, at restaurants: a twentysomething guy, nice suit, works in advertising. Regular. Ordinary. But when the ordinary person had two drinks, Augusten was circling the drain by having twelve; when the ordinary person went home at midnight, Augusten never went home at all. Loud, distracting ties, automated wake-up calls and cologne on the tongue could only hide so much for so long. At the request (well, it wasn&#8217;t really a request) of his employers, Augusten lands in rehab, where his dreams of group therapy with Robert Downey Jr. are immediately dashed by grim reality of fluorescent lighting and paper hospital slippers. But when Augusten is forced to examine himself, something actually starts to click and that&#8217;s when he finds himself in the worst trouble of all. Because when his thirty days are up, he has to return to his same drunken Manhattan life&#8211;and live it sober. What follows is a memoir that&#8217;s as moving as it is funny, as heartbreaking as it is true. Dry is the story of love, loss, and Starbucks as a Higher Power.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dry-a-memoir-augusten-burroughs/">Dry : A Memoir &#8211; Augusten Burroughs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chasing the Scream : The inspiration for the feature film The United States vs Billie Holiday &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chasing-the-scream-the-inspiration-for-the-feature-film-the-united-states-vs-billie-holiday-johann-hari-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drugs Trade / Drug Trafficking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chasing-the-scream-the-inspiration-for-the-feature-film-the-united-states-vs-billie-holiday-johann-hari-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* Pre-order Johann Hari&#8217;s new book Stolen Focus now! * THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER THE INSPIRATION FOR THE FEATURE FILM THE UNITED STATES VS. BILLIE HOLIDAY &#8216;Screamingly addictive&#8217; STEPHEN FRY &#8216;Superb &#8230; Thrilling story-telling&#8217; NAOMI KLEIN &#8216;A powerful contribution to an urgent debate&#8217; GUARDIAN What if everything we&#8217;ve been told about addiction is wrong? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chasing-the-scream-the-inspiration-for-the-feature-film-the-united-states-vs-billie-holiday-johann-hari-abridged/">Chasing the Scream : The inspiration for the feature film The United States vs Billie Holiday &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* Pre-order Johann Hari&#8217;s new book Stolen Focus now! *    </p>
<p>                    THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    THE INSPIRATION FOR THE FEATURE FILM THE UNITED STATES VS. BILLIE HOLIDAY    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Screamingly addictive&#8217; STEPHEN FRY<br />
                    &#8216;Superb &#8230; Thrilling story-telling&#8217; NAOMI KLEIN<br />
                    &#8216;A powerful contribution to an urgent debate&#8217; GUARDIAN    </p>
<p>                    What if everything we&#8217;ve been told about addiction is wrong? One of Johann Hari&#8217;s earliest memories is of trying to wake up one of his relatives and not being able to. As he grew older, he realised there was addiction in his family. Confused, he set out on a three-year, thirty-thousand mile journey to discover what really causes addiction &#8211; and how to solve it.     </p>
<p>                    Told through a series of gripping human stories, this book was the basis of a TED talk and animation that have been viewed more than twenty million times. It has transformed the global debate about addiction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chasing-the-scream-the-inspiration-for-the-feature-film-the-united-states-vs-billie-holiday-johann-hari-abridged/">Chasing the Scream : The inspiration for the feature film The United States vs Billie Holiday &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Separation & Divorce]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>_____________________________ Is having &#8216;somebody to love&#8217; the most important thing in your life? Do you constantly believe in Mr Right, and that being with him would guarantee you would no longer feel depressed or lonely? Are you bored with &#8216;nice guys&#8217; who are open, honest and dependable? If being in love means being in pain, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/">Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>_____________________________<br />
                    Is having &#8216;somebody to love&#8217; the most important thing in your life?<br />
                    Do you constantly believe in Mr Right, and that being with him would guarantee you would no longer feel depressed or lonely?<br />
                    Are you bored with &#8216;nice guys&#8217; who are open, honest and dependable?     </p>
<p>                    If being in love means being in pain, this book was written for you. Leading relationship and marriage therapist Robin Norwood describes loving too much as a pattern of thoughts and behaviour, which certain women develop as a response to problems from childhood.     </p>
<p>                    Many women find themselves repeatedly drawn into unhappy and destructive relationships with men. They then struggle to make these doomed relationships work. This bestselling relationship self-help book investigates and reveals how powerfully addictive these unhealthy relationships are &#8211; but also gives a very specific programme for recovery from the disease of loving too much, a problem that plagues women everywhere.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/">Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Enough : the neuroscience and experience of addiction &#8211; Judith Grisel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/never-enough-the-neuroscience-and-experience-of-addiction-judith-grisel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Addiction & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug & Substance Abuse: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/never-enough-the-neuroscience-and-experience-of-addiction-judith-grisel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A former drug addict turned behavioural neuroscientist reveals how drugs work in the brain &#8211; and what we can do to fight addiction. Judith Grisel was a daily drug user when she began to consider that her addiction might have a cure, one that she herself could perhaps discover by studying the brain. Now, after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-enough-the-neuroscience-and-experience-of-addiction-judith-grisel-abridged/">Never Enough : the neuroscience and experience of addiction &#8211; Judith Grisel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A former drug addict turned behavioural neuroscientist reveals how drugs work in the brain &#8211; and what we can do to fight addiction.    </p>
<p>                    Judith Grisel was a daily drug user when she began to consider that her addiction might have a cure, one that she herself could perhaps discover by studying the brain. Now, after twenty-five years as a neuroscientist, she shares what she and other scientists have learned about addiction, enriched by captivating glimpses of her personal journey.    </p>
<p>                    In Never Enough, Grisel reveals the unfortunate bottom line of all regular drug use: there is no such thing as a free lunch. All drugs act on the brain in a way that diminishes their enjoyable effects and creates unpleasant ones with repeated use. Delving into the science of one of the world&#8217;s most pressing health problems, she reveals what is different about the brains of addicts even before they first pick up a drink or drug, and highlights the changes that take place in the brain and behaviour as a result of chronic using.    </p>
<p>                    With compassion and clarity, Grisel describes what drove her to addiction, what helped her recover, and her belief that a &#8216;cure&#8217; for addiction will not be found in our individual brains but in the way we interact with our communities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-enough-the-neuroscience-and-experience-of-addiction-judith-grisel-abridged/">Never Enough : the neuroscience and experience of addiction &#8211; Judith Grisel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-alcoholic Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217; &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217;  &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller      </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice O&#8217;Keeffe, Guardian     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Truthful, modern and real&#8217; &#8211; Stylist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Brave, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober came to me at a time when I much needed it&#8230; The book became my best friend, and got me through, and took me on a journey.&#8217; &#8211; Sadie Frost     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Particularly lovely, because it&#8217;s not a deep and dark dive into someone&#8217;s terrible addiction. It&#8217;s a celebration of everything that she has gained from not drinking&#8217; &#8211; Laura Donnelly     </p>
<p>                    Ever sworn off alcohol for a month and found yourself drinking by the 7th? Think there&#8217;s &#8216;no point&#8217; in just one drink? Welcome! There are millions of us. 64% of Brits want to drink less.    </p>
<p>                    Catherine Gray was stuck in a hellish whirligig of Drink, Make horrible decisions, Hangover, Repeat. She had her fair share of &#8216;drunk tank&#8217; jail cells and topless-in-a-hot-tub misadventures.    </p>
<p>                    But this book goes beyond the binges and blackouts to deep-dive into uncharted territory: What happens after you quit drinking? This gripping, heart-breaking and witty book takes us down the rabbit-hole of an alternative reality. A life with zero hangovers, through sober weddings, sex, Christmases and breakups.     </p>
<p>                    In The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober, Catherine Gray shines a light on society&#8217;s drink-pushing and talks to top neuroscientists and psychologists about why we drink, delving into the science behind what it does to our brains and bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Much more than a tale from the netherworld of addicted drinking, this book is about the escape, and why a sober life can be more intoxicating than you ever imagined. Whether you&#8217;re a hopelessly devoted drinker, merely sober-curious, or you&#8217;ve already ditched the drink, you will love this book.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Haunting, admirable and enlightening&#8217; &#8211; The Pool     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A riveting, raw, yet humorous memoir with actionable advice. A truly unique blend of storytelling and science that holds a universe of hope.&#8217; &#8211; Annie Grace, author of This Naked Mind     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Like listening to your best friend teach you to be sober. Lighthearted but serious, it&#8217;s packed with ideas, tools, tips and, most importantly, reasons for living a sober life. This book is excellent.&#8217;- Eric Zimmer, host of podcast The One You Feed     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s fizzy writing succeeds in making this potentially boring-as-hell subject both engaging and highly seductive&#8217; &#8211; The Bookseller     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray is an exceptional writer. Her exquisitely crafted thoughts on the joys of being sober are not only deeply honest and pragmatic, but she manages to infuse tons of humor. This is a delightful, informative, and compelling read for all those who are sober or seeking sobriety.&#8217; &#8211; Sasha Tozzi, Huffington Post columnist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine&#8217;s writing style and voice captivate me. She has a way of translating her story into an experience I don&#8217;t want to end. I want to drink every drop she produces.&#8217; &#8211; Holly Whitaker, founder of Hip Sobriety School and co-presenter of Home podcast     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book is great. A balanced, informative and entertaining melange of memoir, sociology and psychology. I identified very strongly with huge sections of it.&#8217; &#8211; Jon Stewart, guitarist of Sleeper and Leaving AA, Staying Sober blogger >    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Sober is too often equated with &#8220;sombre&#8221; in our culture. Gray&#8217;s book turns that idea on its head. Her experience of sobriety is joyful and life-affirming. A must-read for anyone who has a nagging suspicion that alcohol may be taking away more than it&#8217;s giving.&#8217; &#8211; Hilda Burke, psychotherapist and couples counsellor     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray really captures the FUN we can have in sobriety. This book challenges the status quo; sobriet sounds as liberating as taking a trip to the jungle. Fun and inspirational. What an important book for our time! A joy to read.&#8217; &#8211; Samantha Moyo, founder of Morning Gloryville     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;No other author writes about sober living with as much warmth or emotional range as Catherine Gray. Her deep insight into the subtle psychologies of drinking, and of life, means that everything she writes is both utterly relatable and stretches our minds. Hers is a rare wisdom.&#8217; &#8211; Dr Richard Piper, CEO, Alcohol Change UK</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drugs Trade / Drug Trafficking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organized Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like Ryanair or Apple. So when the drug cartels start to think like big business, the only way to understand them is using economics.     </p>
<p>                    In Narconomics, Tom Wainwright meets everyone from coca farmers in secret Andean locations, deluded heads of state in presidential palaces, journalists with a price on their head, gang leaders who run their empires from dangerous prisons and teenage hitmen on city streets &#8211; all in search of the economic truth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
