<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cellular Biology (cytology) Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/cellular-biology-cytology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/cellular-biology-cytology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Cellular Biology (cytology) Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/cellular-biology-cytology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Scale : The Universal Laws of Life and Death in Organisms, Cities and Companies &#8211; Geoffrey West (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/scale-the-universal-laws-of-life-and-death-in-organisms-cities-and-companies-geoffrey-west-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics Of Industrial Organisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Molecular Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/scale-the-universal-laws-of-life-and-death-in-organisms-cities-and-companies-geoffrey-west-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Geoffrey West&#8217;s research centres on a quest to find unifying principles and patterns connecting everything, from cells and ecosystems to cities, social networks and businesses. Why do organisms and ecosystems scale with size in a remarkably universal and systematic fashion? Is there a maximum size of cities? Of animals and plants? What about companies? Can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scale-the-universal-laws-of-life-and-death-in-organisms-cities-and-companies-geoffrey-west-abridged/">Scale : The Universal Laws of Life and Death in Organisms, Cities and Companies &#8211; Geoffrey West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Geoffrey West&#8217;s research centres on a quest to find unifying principles and patterns connecting everything, from cells and ecosystems to cities, social networks and businesses.    </p>
<p>                    Why do organisms and ecosystems scale with size in a remarkably universal and systematic fashion?    </p>
<p>                    Is there a maximum size of cities? Of animals and plants? What about companies?    </p>
<p>                    Can scale show us how to create a more sustainable future?    </p>
<p>                    By applying the rigour of physics to questions of biology, visionary physicist Geoffrey West found that despite the riotous diversity in the sizes of mammals, they are all, to a large degree, scaled versions of each other. This speaks to everything from how long we can expect to live to how many hours of sleep we need. He then made the even bolder move of exploring his work&#8217;s applicability to cities and to the business world. These investigations have led to powerful insights about the elemental natural laws that bind us together in profound ways, and how all complex systems are dancing to the same simple tune, however diverse and unrelated they may seem.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scale-the-universal-laws-of-life-and-death-in-organisms-cities-and-companies-geoffrey-west-abridged/">Scale : The Universal Laws of Life and Death in Organisms, Cities and Companies &#8211; Geoffrey West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Power, Sex, Suicide : Mitochondria and the meaning of life &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mitochondria are tiny structures located inside our cells that carry out the essential task of producing energy for the cell. They are found in all complex living things, and in that sense, they are fundamental for driving complex life on the planet. But there is much more to them than that. Mitochondria have their own [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/">Power, Sex, Suicide : Mitochondria and the meaning of life &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mitochondria are tiny structures located inside our cells that carry out the essential task of producing energy for the cell. They are found in all complex living things, and in that sense, they are fundamental for driving complex life on the planet. But there is much more to them than that.     </p>
<p>                    Mitochondria have their own DNA, with their own small collection of genes, separate from those in the cell nucleus. It is thought that they were once bacteria living independent lives. Their enslavement within the larger cell was a turning point in the evolution of life, enabling the development of complex organisms and, closely related, the origin of two sexes. Unlike the DNA in the nucleus, mitochondrial DNA is passed down exclusively (or almost exclusively) via the female line. That&#8217;s why it<br />
                    has been used by some researchers to trace human ancestry daughter-to-mother, to &#8216;Mitochondrial Eve&#8217;. Mitochondria give us important information about our evolutionary history. And that&#8217;s not all. Mitochondrial genes mutate much faster than those in the nucleus because of the free radicals produced<br />
                    in their energy-generating role. This high mutation rate lies behind our ageing and certain congenital diseases. The latest research suggests that mitochondria play a key role in degenerative diseases such as cancer, through their involvement in precipitating cell suicide.     </p>
<p>                    Mitochondria, then, are pivotal in power, sex, and suicide. In this fascinating and thought-provoking book, Nick Lane brings together the latest research findings in this exciting field to show how our growing understanding of mitochondria is shedding light on how complex life evolved, why sex arose (why don&#8217;t we just bud?), and why we age and die. This understanding is of fundamental importance, both in understanding how we and all other complex life came to be, but also in order to be able to<br />
                    control our own illnesses, and delay our degeneration and death.     </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/">Power, Sex, Suicide : Mitochondria and the meaning of life &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the revolutionary science behind the power of thought, this book will forever change how you think about your own thinking. This new updated and expanded 10th anniversary edition of The Biology of Belief contains stunning new scientific discoveries about the biochemical effects of the brain&#8217;s functioning that show all the cells of your body [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/">The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the revolutionary science behind the power of thought, this book will forever change how you think about your own thinking.    </p>
<p>                    This new updated and expanded 10th anniversary edition of The Biology of Belief contains stunning new scientific discoveries about the biochemical effects of the brain&#8217;s functioning that show all the cells of your body are affected by your thoughts. Bruce H. Lipton PhD, a renowned cell biologist, describes the precise molecular pathways through which this occurs. Using simple language, illustrations, humour and everyday examples, he demonstrates how the new science of epigenetics is revolutionizing our understanding of the link between mind and matter, and the profound effects it has on our personal lives and the collective life of our species.    </p>
<p>                    It has been 10 years since the publication of The Biology of Belief, Bruce Lipton&#8217;s seminal book on the relationship between mind and body that changed the way we think about our lives, our health and our planet. During that time, research in this field has grown exponentially &#8211; Lipton&#8217;s ground-breaking experiments have now been endorsed by more than a decade of rigorous scientific study.    </p>
<p>                    In this greatly expanded edition, Lipton explores his own experiments and those of other leading-edge scientists that have unravelled in ever greater detail how truly connected the mind, body and spirit are. It is now widely recognized that genes and DNA do not control our biology. Instead, they are controlled by signals from outside the cell, including energetic messages emanating from our thoughts.    </p>
<p>                    This profoundly hopeful synthesis of the latest and best research in cell biology and quantum physics puts the power to create a healthy, joyous life back in our own hands. When we transform our conscious and subconscious thoughts, we transform our lives, and in the process help humanity evolve to a new level of understanding and peace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biology-of-belief-unleashing-the-power-of-consciousness-matter-miracles-bruce-h-lipton-abridged/">The Biology of Belief : Unleashing the Power of Consciousness, Matter &#038; Miracles &#8211; Bruce H. Lipton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bio-ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Ethics & Professional Conduct]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Her name was Henrietta Lacks, but scientists know her as HeLa. Born a poor black tobacco farmer, her cancer cells &#8211; taken without her knowledge &#8211; became a multimillion-dollar industry and one of the most important tools in medicine. Yet Henrietta&#8217;s family did not learn of her &#8216;immortality&#8217; until more than twenty years after her [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/">The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Her name was Henrietta Lacks, but scientists know her as HeLa. Born a poor black tobacco farmer, her cancer cells &#8211; taken without her knowledge &#8211; became a multimillion-dollar industry and one of the most important tools in medicine. Yet Henrietta&#8217;s family did not learn of her &#8216;immortality&#8217; until more than twenty years after her death, with devastating consequences . . .     </p>
<p>                    Rebecca Skloot&#8217;s fascinating account is the story of the life, and afterlife, of one woman who changed the medical world forever. Balancing the beauty and drama of scientific discovery with dark questions about who owns the stuff our bodies are made of, The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks is an extraordinary journey in search of the soul and story of a real woman, whose cells live on today in all four corners of the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/">The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
