<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Agronomy &amp; Crop Production Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/agronomy-crop-production/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/agronomy-crop-production/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Agronomy &amp; Crop Production Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/agronomy-crop-production/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agronomy & Crop Production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Husbandry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animals & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made the most courageous decision of her life: a commitment to change things.    </p>
<p>                     Driven by impulsive will and searing passion, Sonia left behind everything she knew and loved to search the planet for solutions to benefit animals, human health, and the environment. Over the course of living with farmers, hitchhiking with strangers, and risking her life, she developed surprising insights and solutions-both about the food industry and herself.    </p>
<p>                     Lively and heartfelt, Sonia takes readers on an unforgettable adventure from top-secret egg warehouses in Canada to dairy feedlots in the United States, from farm offices in Mexico to lush pastures in Belize, from flocks of village chickens in Indonesia to factory farms in Malaysia.    </p>
<p>                     Revelatory in scope, Project Animal Farm illuminates a hidden world that plays a part in all of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Fed the World &#8211; Leon Hesser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agronomy & Crop Production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Novels: Literary & Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Norman Borlaug was the only person during the twentieth century who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize for work in agriculture and food. There is no Nobel Food Prize, so the Nobel Committee chose Dr. Borlaug as the 1970 recipient of the Peace Prize based on his dramatic scientific breakthroughs and wheat production technology that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/">The Man Who Fed the World &#8211; Leon Hesser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Norman Borlaug was the only person during the twentieth century who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize for work in agriculture and food. There is no Nobel Food Prize, so the Nobel Committee chose Dr. Borlaug as the 1970 recipient of the Peace Prize based on his dramatic scientific breakthroughs and wheat production technology that relieved hunger in much of the world. During the previous decade, many people on the planet Earth, most notably in China and the Asian Subcontinent, were facing starvation, even famine. Borlaug&#8217;s revolutionary achievements relieved widespread human suffering and brought peace.    </p>
<p>                    Dr. Borlaug was hailed as the person who saved the lives of more people&#8211;hundreds of millions&#8211;from starvation than any person in history. He earned the distinction as one of the 100 most influential individuals of the 20th century. His is an inspiring story; he went from an unpretentious Iowa farm boy to scientist-cum-humanist of world acclaim.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/">The Man Who Fed the World &#8211; Leon Hesser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
