<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Psychology: Emotions Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/psychology-emotions/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/psychology-emotions/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Psychology: Emotions Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/psychology-emotions/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David</title>
		<link>/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Body]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ego]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Perfect for lovers of Quiet and The Power of Now, Emotional Agility shares a new way of relating to yourself and the world around you Every day we speak around 16,000 words &#8211; but inside minds we create tens of thousands more. Thoughts such as &#8216;I&#8217;m not spending enough time with my children&#8217; or &#8216;I&#8217;m [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david/">Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Perfect for lovers of Quiet and The Power of Now, Emotional Agility shares a new way of relating to yourself and the world around you</p>
<p>                     Every day we speak around 16,000 words &#8211; but inside minds we create tens of thousands more. </p>
<p>                    Thoughts such as &#8216;I&#8217;m not spending enough time with my children&#8217; or &#8216;I&#8217;m not good enough to present my work&#8217; can seem to be unshakeable facts. In reality, they&#8217;re the judgemental opinions of our inner voice.</p>
<p>                    Drawing on more than twenty years of academic research and her own experiences, Susan David PhD, a psychologist and faculty member at Harvard Medical School, has pioneered a new way to make peace with our inner self, achieve our most valued goals and live life to the fullest.</p>
<p>                     Become aware of your true nature, learn to face your emotions with acceptance and generosity, act according to your deepest values, and flourish.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Essential reading&#8217; Susan Cain, author of Quiet</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A practical, science-backed guide to looking inward and living intentionally&#8217; Arianna Huffington, author of The Sleep Revolution</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An accessible, reader-friendly voyage. Emotional Agility can be helpful to anyone.&#8217; Daniel Goleman, author of Emotional Intelligence</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david/">Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler</title>
		<link>/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Gender]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the better &#8211; and thus we don&#8217;t like to talk or even think about the extent of our selfishness. This is &#8220;the elephant in the brain.&#8221; Such<br />
                    an introspective taboo makes it hard for us to think clearly about our nature and the explanations for our behavior. The aim of this book, then, is to confront our hidden motives directly &#8211; to track down the darker, unexamined corners of our psyches and blast them with floodlights. Then, once<br />
                    everything is clearly visible, we can work to better understand ourselves: Why do we laugh? Why are artists sexy? Why do we brag about travel? Why do we prefer to speak rather than listen?</p>
<p>                    Our unconscious motives drive more than just our private behavior; they also infect our venerated social institutions such as Art, School, Charity, Medicine, Politics, and Religion. In fact, these institutions are in many ways designed to accommodate our hidden motives, to serve covert agendas alongside their &#8220;official&#8221; ones. The existence of big hidden motives can upend the usual political debates, leading one to question the legitimacy of these social institutions, and of standard policies<br />
                    designed to favor or discourage them. You won&#8217;t see yourself &#8211; or the world &#8211; the same after confronting the elephant in the brain.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ask and It is Given : Learning to Manifest Your Desires &#8211; Esther Hicks</title>
		<link>/ask-and-it-is-given-learning-to-manifest-your-desires-esther-hicks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Angels & Channelling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Body]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ask-and-it-is-given-learning-to-manifest-your-desires-esther-hicks/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pairing empowering channelled teachings with practical guidance on the Law of Attraction, this book will help you to manifest a joyful and fulfilling life. This book explains how our relationships, health issues, finances, career concerns and more are influenced by the Universal laws that govern our time/space reality and describes powerful processes that will help [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-and-it-is-given-learning-to-manifest-your-desires-esther-hicks/">Ask and It is Given : Learning to Manifest Your Desires &#8211; Esther Hicks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pairing empowering channelled teachings with practical guidance on the Law of Attraction, this book will help you to manifest a joyful and fulfilling life.    </p>
<p>                    This book explains how our relationships, health issues, finances, career concerns and more are influenced by the Universal laws that govern our time/space reality and describes powerful processes that will help you manifest your desires and live the life you deserve.    </p>
<p>                    Esther and Jerry Hicks&#8217; first book presenting the teachings of the non-physical entity Abraham has drawn an extraordinary collection of endorsements from people keen to draw attention to the message that Abraham has to convey. Endorsements have been received from Neale Donald Walsch, John Gray, Wayne Dyer, Louise L. Hay, Jack Canfield and Christine Northrup.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-and-it-is-given-learning-to-manifest-your-desires-esther-hicks/">Ask and It is Given : Learning to Manifest Your Desires &#8211; Esther Hicks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Power of Vulnerability : Teachings on Authenticity, Connection and Courage &#8211; Brene Brown</title>
		<link>/power-of-vulnerability-teachings-on-authenticity-connection-and-courage-brene-brown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/power-of-vulnerability-teachings-on-authenticity-connection-and-courage-brene-brown/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Show Up and Let Yourself be Seen Is vulnerability the same as weakness? &#8220;In our culture,&#8221; teaches Dr. Brene Brown, &#8220;we associate vulnerability with emotions we want to avoid such as fear, shame, and uncertainty. Yet we too often lose sight of the fact that vulnerability is also the birthplace of joy, belonging, creativity, authenticity, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-of-vulnerability-teachings-on-authenticity-connection-and-courage-brene-brown/">Power of Vulnerability : Teachings on Authenticity, Connection and Courage &#8211; Brene Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Show Up and Let Yourself be Seen</p>
<p>                    Is vulnerability the same as weakness? &#8220;In our culture,&#8221; teaches Dr. Brene Brown, &#8220;we associate vulnerability with emotions we want to avoid such as fear, shame, and uncertainty. Yet we too often lose sight of the fact that vulnerability is also the birthplace of joy, belonging, creativity, authenticity, and love.&#8221; On The Power of Vulnerability, Dr. Brown offers an invitation and a promise-that when we dare to drop the armor that protects us from feeling vulnerable, we open ourselves to the experiences that bring purpose and meaning to our lives. Here she dispels the cultural myth that vulnerability is weakness and reveals that it is, in truth, our most accurate measure of courage.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Power of Vulnerability is a very personal project for me,&#8221; Brene explains. &#8220;This is the first place that all of my work comes together. This audio course draws from all three of my books-it&#8217;s the culmination of everything I&#8217;ve learned over the past 12 years. I&#8217;m very excited to weave it all into a truly comprehensive form that shows what these findings and insights can mean in our lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    Guidance and Insights for Wholehearted Living</p>
<p>                    Over the past 12 years, Dr. Brene Brown has interviewed hundreds of people as part of an ongoing study of vulnerability. &#8220;The research shows that we try to ward disappointment with a shield of cynicism, disarm shame by numbing ourselves against joy, and circumvent grief by shutting off our willingness to love,&#8221; explains Dr. Brown. When we become aware of these patterns, she teaches, we begin to become conscious of how much we sacrifice in the name of self-defense-and how much richer our lives become when we open ourselves to vulnerability.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;In my research,&#8221; Dr. Brown says, &#8220;the word I use to describe people who can live from a place of vulnerability is wholehearted.&#8221; Being wholehearted is a practice-one that we can choose to cultivate through empathy, gratitude, and awareness of our vulnerability armor. Join this engaging and heartfelt teacher on The Power of Vulnerability as she offers profound insights on leaning into the full spectrum of emotions-so we can show up, let ourselves be seen, and truly be all in.</p>
<p>                    Highlights:</p>
<p>                    Cultivating shame resilience-the key to developing a sense of worth and belonging<br />
                    * Vulnerability as the origin point for innovation, adaptability, accountability, and visionary leadership<br />
                    * Our emotional armory-how we use perfectionism, numbing, and other tactics to avoid feeling vulnerable<br />
                    * The myths of vulnerability-common misconceptions about weakness, trust, and self-sufficiency<br />
                    * Discovering your vulnerability armor-recognizing what makes us shut down, and how we can change<br />
                    * The 10 guideposts of wholehearted living-essential skills for becoming fully engaged in life<br />
                    * Six hours of stories, warm humor, and transformative insights for living a life of courage, authenticity, and compassion from Dr. Brene Brown<br />
                    Course objectives:</p>
<p>                    Recognize emotional armory and recognizing what makes us shut down-how we use perfectionism, numbing, and other tactics to avoid feeling vulnerable<br />
                    * Discussing the cultivation of shame resilience&#8211;the key to developing a sense of worth and belonging<br />
                    * Discussing the myths of vulnerability-common misconceptions about weakness, trust, and self-sufficiency<br />
                    * Defining vulnerability as the origin point for innovation, adaptability, accountability, and visionary leadership<br />
                    * Summarizing the 10 guideposts of wholehearted living-essential skills for living a life of courage, authenticity, and compassion</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-of-vulnerability-teachings-on-authenticity-connection-and-courage-brene-brown/">Power of Vulnerability : Teachings on Authenticity, Connection and Courage &#8211; Brene Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Do The Work : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Nicole LePera</title>
		<link>/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;If LePera&#8217;s Instagram feed is full of aha moments illuminating the inner workings of your psyche, the revelations in the book are more like a full firework display.&#8217; Red magazine &#8216;This book is a must-read for anyone on a path of personal growth.&#8217; GABBY BERNSTEIN, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/">How To Do The Work : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Nicole LePera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If LePera&#8217;s Instagram feed is full of aha moments illuminating the inner workings of your psyche, the revelations in the book are more like a full firework display.&#8217; Red magazine    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is a must-read for anyone on a path of personal growth.&#8217; GABBY BERNSTEIN, author of number one New York Times bestsellers Super Attractor and The Universe Has Your Back    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book I wish I had read in my twenties.&#8217; ELIZABETH DAY, author of How to Fail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;How to Do the Work will transform how you see yourself and your ability to change. I believe this book could change lives, if not the world.&#8217;  HOLLY BOURNE, bestselling author of How Do You Like Me Now?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Want more from life? Looking for answers? How to Do the Work will teach you how to find them within yourself. A masterpiece of empowerment &#8211; this book changed my life and, trust me, it&#8217;ll change yours too.&#8217; MEL ROBBINS, author of The 5 Second Rule    </p>
<p>                    As a clinical psychologist, Dr Nicole LePera found herself frustrated by the limitations of traditional psychotherapy. Wanting more for her patients &#8211; and for herself &#8211; she began a journey to develop a united philosophy of mental, physical and spiritual health that equips people with the tools necessary to heal themselves. After experiencing the life-changing results herself, she began to share what she&#8217;d learned with others &#8211; and The Holistic Psychologist was born.    </p>
<p>                    Now Dr LePera is ready to share her much-requested protocol with the world. In How to Do the Work, she offers both a manifesto for self-healing and an essential guide to creating a more vibrant, authentic, and joyful life. Drawing on the latest research from both scientific research and healing modalities, Dr LePera helps us recognise how adverse experiences and trauma in childhood live with us, keeping us stuck engaging in patterns of codependency, emotional immaturity, and trauma bonds. Unless addressed, these self-sabotaging behaviours can quickly become cyclical, leaving people feeling unhappy, unfulfilled, and unwell.    </p>
<p>                    In How to Do the Work, Dr LePera offers readers the support and tools that will allow them to break free from destructive behaviours to reclaim and recreate their lives. Nothing short of a paradigm shift, this is a celebration of empowerment that will forever change the way we approach mental wellness and self-care.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-the-work-the-sunday-times-bestseller-nicole-lepera/">How To Do The Work : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Nicole LePera</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Upside of Your Dark Side : Why Being Your Whole Self&#8211;Not Just Your &#8220;Good&#8221; Self&#8211;Drives Success and Fulfillment &#8211; Todd B. Kashdan, Robert Biswas-Diener (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-upside-of-your-dark-side-why-being-your-whole-self-not-just-your-good-self-drives-success-and-fulfillment-todd-b-kashdan-robert-biswas-diener-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-upside-of-your-dark-side-why-being-your-whole-self-not-just-your-good-self-drives-success-and-fulfillment-todd-b-kashdan-robert-biswas-diener-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Audible Best Seller of 2017 Inc. 11 Great Business Books New York Magazine Best Psychology Books LinkedIn&#8217;s 12 Books on Leadership to Read Two mavericks in the field of positive psychology deliver a timely message Happiness experts have long told us to tune out our negative emotions and focus instead on mindfulness, positivity, and optimism. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upside-of-your-dark-side-why-being-your-whole-self-not-just-your-good-self-drives-success-and-fulfillment-todd-b-kashdan-robert-biswas-diener-abridged/">The Upside of Your Dark Side : Why Being Your Whole Self&#8211;Not Just Your &#8220;Good&#8221; Self&#8211;Drives Success and Fulfillment &#8211; Todd B. Kashdan, Robert Biswas-Diener (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Audible Best Seller of 2017    </p>
<p>                     Inc. 11 Great Business Books     </p>
<p>                     New York Magazine Best Psychology Books    </p>
<p>                     LinkedIn&#8217;s 12 Books on Leadership to Read    </p>
<p>                    Two mavericks in the field of positive psychology deliver a timely message     </p>
<p>                    Happiness experts have long told us to tune out our negative emotions and focus instead on mindfulness, positivity, and optimism. Researchers Todd Kashdan, Ph.D., and Robert Biswas-Diener, Dr. Philos., disagree. Positive emotions alone are not enough. Anger makes us creative, selfishness makes us brave, and guilt is a powerful motivator. The real key to success lies in emotional agility. Drawing upon extensive scientific research and a wide array of real-life examples, The Upside of Your Dark Side will be embraced by business leaders, parents, and everyone else who&#8217;s ready to put their entire psychological tool kit to work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upside-of-your-dark-side-why-being-your-whole-self-not-just-your-good-self-drives-success-and-fulfillment-todd-b-kashdan-robert-biswas-diener-abridged/">The Upside of Your Dark Side : Why Being Your Whole Self&#8211;Not Just Your &#8220;Good&#8221; Self&#8211;Drives Success and Fulfillment &#8211; Todd B. Kashdan, Robert Biswas-Diener (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U Thrive : How to Succeed in College (and Life) &#8211; Daniel Lerner, Alan Daniel Schlechter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/u-thrive-how-to-succeed-in-college-and-life-daniel-lerner-alan-daniel-schlechter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Students & Student Organisations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/u-thrive-how-to-succeed-in-college-and-life-daniel-lerner-alan-daniel-schlechter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every year, almost 4,000,000 students begin their freshman year at colleges and universities nationwide. Most of them will sleep less and stress out a whole lot more. By the end of the year, 30% of those freshmen will have dropped out. For many, the unforeseen demands of college life are so overwhelming that &#8220;the best [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-thrive-how-to-succeed-in-college-and-life-daniel-lerner-alan-daniel-schlechter-abridged/">U Thrive : How to Succeed in College (and Life) &#8211; Daniel Lerner, Alan Daniel Schlechter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every year, almost 4,000,000 students begin their freshman year at colleges and universities nationwide. Most of them will sleep less and stress out a whole lot more. By the end of the year, 30% of those freshmen will have dropped out. For many, the unforeseen demands of college life are so overwhelming that &#8220;the best four years of your life&#8221; can start to feel like the worst.    </p>
<p>                    Enter Daniel Lerner and Dr. Alan Schlechter, ready to teach students how to not only survive college, but flourish in it. Filled with fascinating science, real-life stories, and tips for building positive lifelong habits, U Thrive addresses the opportunities and challenges every undergrad will face-from finding a passion to dealing with nightmarish roommates and surviving finals week. Engaging and hilarious, U Thrive will help students grow into the happy, successful alums they all deserve to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-thrive-how-to-succeed-in-college-and-life-daniel-lerner-alan-daniel-schlechter-abridged/">U Thrive : How to Succeed in College (and Life) &#8211; Daniel Lerner, Alan Daniel Schlechter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Emotions Are Made : The Secret Life of the Brain &#8211; Lisa Feldman Barrett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perception]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How Emotions Are Made did what all great books do. It took a subject I thought I understood and turned my understanding upside down&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell, author of The Tipping Point. When you feel anxious, angry, happy, or surprised, what&#8217;s really going on inside of you? Many scientists believe that emotions come from a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/">How Emotions Are Made : The Secret Life of the Brain &#8211; Lisa Feldman Barrett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How Emotions Are Made did what all great books do. It took a subject I thought I understood and turned my understanding upside down&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell, author of The Tipping Point.    </p>
<p>                    When you feel anxious, angry, happy, or surprised, what&#8217;s really going on inside of you?     </p>
<p>                    Many scientists believe that emotions come from a specific part of the brain, triggered by the world around us. The thrill of seeing an old friend, the fear of losing someone we love &#8211; each of these sensations seems to arise automatically and uncontrollably from within us, finding expression on our faces and in our behaviour, carrying us away with the experience.    </p>
<p>                    This understanding of emotion has been around since Plato. But what if it is wrong? In How Emotions Are Made, pioneering psychologist and neuroscientist Lisa Feldman Barrett draws on the latest scientific evidence to reveal that our common-sense ideas about emotions are dramatically, even dangerously, out of date &#8211; and that we have been paying the price. Emotions aren&#8217;t universally pre-programmed in our brains and bodies; rather they are psychological experiences that each of us constructs based on our unique personal history, physiology and environment.    </p>
<p>                    This new view of emotions has serious implications: when judges issue lesser sentences for crimes of passion, when police officers fire at threatening suspects, or when doctors choose between one diagnosis and another, they&#8217;re all, in some way, relying on the ancient assumption that emotions are hardwired into our brains and bodies. Revising that conception of emotion isn&#8217;t just good science, Barrett shows; it&#8217;s vital to our well-being and the health of society itself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/">How Emotions Are Made : The Secret Life of the Brain &#8211; Lisa Feldman Barrett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raising Cain : Protecting the Emotional Life of Boys &#8211; Dan Kindlon, Michael Thompson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Raising Cain, Dan Kindlon, Ph.D., and Michael Thompson, Ph.D., two of the country&#8217;s leading child psychologists, share what they have learned in more than thirty-five years of combined experience working with boys and their families. They reveal a nation of boys who are hurting&#8211;sad, afraid, angry, and silent. Kindlon and Thompson set out to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/">Raising Cain : Protecting the Emotional Life of Boys &#8211; Dan Kindlon, Michael Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Raising Cain, Dan Kindlon, Ph.D., and Michael Thompson, Ph.D., two of the country&#8217;s leading child psychologists, share what they have learned in more than thirty-five years of combined experience working with boys and their families. They reveal a nation of boys who are hurting&#8211;sad, afraid, angry, and silent. Kindlon and Thompson set out to answer this basic, crucial question: What do boys need that they&#8217;re not getting? They illuminate the forces that threaten our boys, teaching them to believe that &#8220;cool&#8221; equals macho strength and stoicism. Cutting through outdated theories of &#8220;mother blame,&#8221; &#8220;boy biology,&#8221; and &#8220;testosterone,&#8221; the authors shed light on the destructive emotional training our boys receive&#8211;the emotional miseducation of boys. Kindlon and Thompson make a compelling case that emotional literacy is the most valuable gift we can offer our sons, urging parents to recognize the price boys pay when we hold them to an impossible standard of manhood. They identify the social and emotional challenges that boys encounter in school and show how parents can help boys cultivate emotional awareness and empathy&#8211;giving them the vital connections and support they need to navigate the social pressures of youth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/">Raising Cain : Protecting the Emotional Life of Boys &#8211; Dan Kindlon, Michael Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The War for Kindness : Building Empathy in a Fractured World &#8211; Jamil Zaki (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-war-for-kindness-building-empathy-in-a-fractured-world-jamil-zaki-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-war-for-kindness-building-empathy-in-a-fractured-world-jamil-zaki-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this masterpiece, Jamil Zaki weaves together the very latest science with stories that will stay in your heart forever&#8217; &#8211; Angela Duckworth, author of Grit &#8216;Scientific, gripping, groundbreaking and hopeful. The War for Kindness is the message for our times&#8217; &#8211; Carol Dweck, author of Mindset Empathy has been on people&#8217;s mind a lot [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-for-kindness-building-empathy-in-a-fractured-world-jamil-zaki-abridged/">The War for Kindness : Building Empathy in a Fractured World &#8211; Jamil Zaki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this masterpiece, Jamil Zaki weaves together the very latest science with stories that will stay in your heart forever&#8217; &#8211; Angela Duckworth, author of Grit    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Scientific, gripping, groundbreaking and hopeful. The War for Kindness is the message for our times&#8217; &#8211; Carol Dweck, author of Mindset    </p>
<p>                     Empathy has been on people&#8217;s mind a lot lately. Philosophers, evolutionary scientists and indeed former President Obama agree that an increase in empathy could advance us beyond the hatred, violence and polarization in which the world seems caught. Others disagree, arguing it is easiest to empathize with people who look, talk or think like us. As a result, empathy can inspire nepotism, racism and worse.    </p>
<p>                     Having studied the neuroscience and psychology of empathy for over a decade, Jamil Zaki thinks both sides of this debate have a point. Empathy is sometimes an engine for moral progress, and other times for moral failure. But Zaki also thinks that both sides are wrong about how empathy works.      </p>
<p>                     Both scientists and non-scientists commonly argue that empathy is something that happens to you, sort of like an emotional knee-jerk reflex. Second, they believe it happens more to some people than others. This lines people up along a spectrum, with deep empaths on one end and psychopaths on the other. What&#8217;s more, wherever we are on that spectrum, we&#8217;re stuck there.      </p>
<p>                     In The War for Kindness, Zaki lays out a very different view of how empathy works, one that breaks these two assumptions. Empathy is not a reflex; it&#8217;s a choice. We choose empathy (or apathy) constantly: when we read a tragic novel, or cross the street to avoid a homeless person, or ask a distraught friend what&#8217;s the matter. This view has crucial consequences: if empathy is less a trait (like height), and more a skill (like being good at word games), then we can improve at it. By choosing it more often, we can flex our capabilities and grow more empathic over time. We can also &#8220;tune&#8221; empathy, ramping it up in situations where it will help and turning it down when it might backfire.    </p>
<p>                     Zaki takes us from the world of doctors who train medical students to empathise better to social workers who help each other survive empathising too much. From police trainers who help cadets avoid becoming violent cops to political advocates who ask white Americans to literally walk a (dusty) mile in Mexican immigrants&#8217; shoes. This book will give you a deepened understanding of how empathy works, how to control it and how to become the type of empathiser you want to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-for-kindness-building-empathy-in-a-fractured-world-jamil-zaki-abridged/">The War for Kindness : Building Empathy in a Fractured World &#8211; Jamil Zaki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stumbling on Happiness &#8211; Daniel Gilbert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stumbling-on-happiness-daniel-gilbert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stumbling-on-happiness-daniel-gilbert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating and often hilarious work &#8211; winner of the Royal Society of Science Prize 2007 &#8211; pre-eminent psychologist Daniel Gilbert shows how &#8211; and why &#8211; the majority of us have no idea how to make ourselves happy. We all want to be happy, but do we know how? When it comes to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stumbling-on-happiness-daniel-gilbert-abridged/">Stumbling on Happiness &#8211; Daniel Gilbert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating and often hilarious work &#8211; winner of the Royal Society of Science Prize 2007 &#8211; pre-eminent psychologist Daniel Gilbert shows how &#8211; and why &#8211; the majority of us have no idea how to make ourselves happy.    </p>
<p>                              We all want to be happy, but do we know how? When it comes to improving tomorrow at the expense of today, we&#8217;re terrible at predicting how to please our future selves.    </p>
<p>                              In &#8216;Stumbling on Happiness&#8217; Professor Daniel Gilbert combines psychology, neuroscience, economics and philosophy with irrepressible wit to describe how the human brain imagines its future &#8211; and how well (or badly) it predicts what it will enjoy. Revealing some of the amazing secrets of human motivation, he also answers thought-provoking questions &#8211; why do dining companions order different meals instead of getting what they want? Why are shoppers happier when they can&#8217;t get refunds? And why are couples less satisfied after having children while insisting that their kids are a source of joy?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stumbling-on-happiness-daniel-gilbert-abridged/">Stumbling on Happiness &#8211; Daniel Gilbert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A General Theory of Love &#8211; Thomas Lewis, Fari Amini, Richard Lannon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-general-theory-of-love-thomas-lewis-fari-amini-richard-lannon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-general-theory-of-love-thomas-lewis-fari-amini-richard-lannon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This original and lucid account of the complexities of love and its essential role in human well-being draws on the latest scientific research. Three eminent psychiatrists tackle the difficult task of reconciling what artists and thinkers have known for thousands of years about the human heart with what has only recently been learned about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-general-theory-of-love-thomas-lewis-fari-amini-richard-lannon-abridged/">A General Theory of Love &#8211; Thomas Lewis, Fari Amini, Richard Lannon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This original and lucid account of the complexities of love and its essential role in human well-being draws on the latest scientific research. Three eminent psychiatrists tackle the difficult task of reconciling what artists and thinkers have known for thousands of years about the human heart with what has only recently been learned about the primitive functions of the human brain.    </p>
<p>                    A General Theory of Love demonstrates that our nervous systems are not self-contained: from earliest childhood, our brains actually link with those of the people close to us, in a silent rhythm that alters the very structure of our brains, establishes life-long emotional patterns, and makes us, in large part, who we are. Explaining how relationships function, how parents shape their child&#8217;s developing self, how psychotherapy really works, and how our society dangerously flouts essential emotional laws, this is a work of rare passion and eloquence that will forever change the way you think about human intimacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-general-theory-of-love-thomas-lewis-fari-amini-richard-lannon-abridged/">A General Theory of Love &#8211; Thomas Lewis, Fari Amini, Richard Lannon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Courage Habit : How to Accept Your Fears, Release the Past, and Live Your Courageous Life &#8211; Kate Swoboda, Foreword by Bari Tessler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-courage-habit-how-to-accept-your-fears-release-the-past-and-live-your-courageous-life-kate-swoboda-foreword-by-bari-tessler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Growth & Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-courage-habit-how-to-accept-your-fears-release-the-past-and-live-your-courageous-life-kate-swoboda-foreword-by-bari-tessler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What kind of life would you live if you didn&#8217;t allow your fears to hold you back? The Courage Habit offers a powerful program to help you conquer your inner critic, work toward your highest aspirations, and build a courageous community. Are your fears preventing you from living the life you truly want? Do you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-courage-habit-how-to-accept-your-fears-release-the-past-and-live-your-courageous-life-kate-swoboda-foreword-by-bari-tessler-abridged/">The Courage Habit : How to Accept Your Fears, Release the Past, and Live Your Courageous Life &#8211; Kate Swoboda, Foreword by Bari Tessler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What kind of life would you live if you didn&#8217;t allow your fears to hold you back? The Courage Habit offers a powerful program to help you conquer your inner critic, work toward your highest aspirations, and build a courageous community.    </p>
<p>                    Are your fears preventing you from living the life you truly want? Do you ever wish that you had a better job, lived in a different city, or had more authentic and nurturing relationships? Many people believe that they would do more, accomplish more, and feel more fulfilled if only they could rid themselves of that fearful inner voice that constantly whispers, &#8220;you can&#8217;t do it.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    In The Courage Habit, certified life coach Kate Swoboda offers a unique program based in cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) and acceptance and commitment therapy (ACT) to help you act courageously in spite of fear. By identifying your fear triggers, releasing yourself from your past experiences, and acting on what you truly value, you can make courage a daily habit.    </p>
<p>                    Using a practical four-part program, you&#8217;ll learn to understand the emotions that arise when fears are triggered, and to pause and evaluate your emotional state before you act. You&#8217;ll discover how to listen without attachment to the self-defeating messages of your inner critic, understand the critic&#8217;s function, and implement respectful boundaries so that your inner voice no longer controls your behavior. You&#8217;ll reframe self-limiting life narratives that can-without conscious awareness-dictate your day-to-day decisions. And finally, you&#8217;ll nurture more authentic connections with family, friends, and community in order to find support and reinforce the life changes you&#8217;re making.    </p>
<p>                    If you feel like something is holding you back from landing your dream job, moving to a new city, having a satisfying love relationship, or simply taking advantage of all life has to offer &#8211; and if you have a sneaking suspicion that that something is you &#8211; then this one-of-a-kind guide will show you how to finally break free from self-doubt and start living your best life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-courage-habit-how-to-accept-your-fears-release-the-past-and-live-your-courageous-life-kate-swoboda-foreword-by-bari-tessler-abridged/">The Courage Habit : How to Accept Your Fears, Release the Past, and Live Your Courageous Life &#8211; Kate Swoboda, Foreword by Bari Tessler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In private life, we try to induce or suppress love, envy, and anger through deep acting or &#8220;emotion work&#8221;, just as we manage our outer expressions of feeling through surface acting. In trying to bridge a gap between what we feel and what we &#8220;ought&#8221; to feel, we take guidance from &#8220;feeling rules&#8221; about what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In private life, we try to induce or suppress love, envy, and anger through deep acting or &#8220;emotion work&#8221;, just as we manage our outer expressions of feeling through surface acting. In trying to bridge a gap between what we feel and what we &#8220;ought&#8221; to feel, we take guidance from &#8220;feeling rules&#8221; about what is owing to others in a given situation. Based on our private mutual understandings of feeling rules, we make a &#8220;gift exchange&#8221; of acts of emotion management. We bow to each other not simply from the waist, but from the heart. But what occurs when emotion work, feeling rules, and the gift of exchange are introduced into the public world of work? In search of the answer, Arlie Russell Hochschild closely examines two groups of public-contact workers: flight attendants and bill collectors. The flight attendant&#8217;s job is to deliver a service and create further demand for it, to enhance the status of the customer and be &#8220;nicer than natural&#8221;. The bill collector&#8217;s job is to collect on the service, and if necessary, to deflate the status of the customer by being &#8220;nastier than natural.&#8221;<br />
                    Between these extremes, roughly one-third of American men and one-half of American women hold jobs that call for substantial emotional labor. In many of these jobs, they are trained to accept feeling rules and techniques of emotion management that serve the company&#8217;s commercial purpose. Just as we have seldom recognized or understood emotional labor, we have not appreciated its cost to those who do it for a living. Like a physical laborer who becomes estranged from what he or she makes, an emotional laborer, such as a flight attendant, can become estranged not only from her own expressions of feeling (her smile is not &#8220;her&#8221; smile), but also from what she actually feels (her managed friendliness). This estrangement, though a valuable defense against stress, is also an important occupational hazard, because it is through our feelings that we are connected with those around us. On the basis of this book, Hochschild was featured in Key Sociological Thinkers, edited by Rob Stones. This book was also the winner of the Charles Cooley Award in 1983, awarded by the American Sociological Association and received an honorable mention for the C. Wright Mills Award.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler, Robin Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Gender]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler, Robin Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the better &#8211; and thus we don&#8217;t like to talk or even think about the extent of our selfishness. This is &#8220;the elephant in the brain.&#8221; Such<br />
                    an introspective taboo makes it hard for us to think clearly about our nature and the explanations for our behavior. The aim of this book, then, is to confront our hidden motives directly &#8211; to track down the darker, unexamined corners of our psyches and blast them with floodlights. Then, once<br />
                    everything is clearly visible, we can work to better understand ourselves: Why do we laugh? Why are artists sexy? Why do we brag about travel? Why do we prefer to speak rather than listen?    </p>
<p>                    Our unconscious motives drive more than just our private behavior; they also infect our venerated social institutions such as Art, School, Charity, Medicine, Politics, and Religion. In fact, these institutions are in many ways designed to accommodate our hidden motives, to serve covert agendas alongside their &#8220;official&#8221; ones. The existence of big hidden motives can upend the usual political debates, leading one to question the legitimacy of these social institutions, and of standard policies<br />
                    designed to favor or discourage them. You won&#8217;t see yourself &#8211; or the world &#8211; the same after confronting the elephant in the brain.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler, Robin Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Hard Feelings : Emotions at Work and How They Help Us Succeed &#8211; Liz Fosslien, Mollie West Duffy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-hard-feelings-emotions-at-work-and-how-they-help-us-succeed-liz-fosslien-mollie-west-duffy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-hard-feelings-emotions-at-work-and-how-they-help-us-succeed-liz-fosslien-mollie-west-duffy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How do you deal with your emotions at work? &#8216;Full of lively illustrations and practical examples to show how you can harness emotions to become more creative, collaborative and productive&#8217; Adam Grant, author of Originals ________________ We all know what it&#8217;s like to feel overwhelmed with emotions at work &#8211; everything from jealousy to insecurity, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-hard-feelings-emotions-at-work-and-how-they-help-us-succeed-liz-fosslien-mollie-west-duffy-abridged/">No Hard Feelings : Emotions at Work and How They Help Us Succeed &#8211; Liz Fosslien, Mollie West Duffy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do you deal with your emotions at work?     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Full of lively illustrations and practical examples to show how you can harness emotions to become more creative, collaborative and productive&#8217; Adam Grant, author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    ________________                           </p>
<p>                    We all know what it&#8217;s like to feel overwhelmed with emotions at work &#8211;  everything from jealousy to insecurity, anxiety to straight up panic &#8211; and there&#8217;s no field guide to coping with them well.     </p>
<p>                    But we also know that ignoring or suppressing what you feel hurts your health, happiness and productivity.     </p>
<p>                    This book will help you figure out how to express your emotions productively in order to be both happier and more effective at work. Drawing on behavioural economics and psychology, No Hard Feelings will show you how to bring your best self to work every day.    </p>
<p>                    ________________                           </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A must-read&#8217; Susan Cain, author of Quiet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-hard-feelings-emotions-at-work-and-how-they-help-us-succeed-liz-fosslien-mollie-west-duffy-abridged/">No Hard Feelings : Emotions at Work and How They Help Us Succeed &#8211; Liz Fosslien, Mollie West Duffy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fail Fast, Fail Often : How Losing Can Help You Win &#8211; Ryan Babineaux, John Krumboltz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fail-fast-fail-often-how-losing-can-help-you-win-ryan-babineaux-john-krumboltz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fail-fast-fail-often-how-losing-can-help-you-win-ryan-babineaux-john-krumboltz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bold, bossy and bracing, Fail Fast, Fail Often is like a 200-page shot of B12, meant to energize the listless job seeker. &#8211;New York Times What if your biggest mistake is that you never make mistakes? Ryan Babineaux and John Krumboltz, psychologists, career counselors, and creators of the popular Stanford University course &#8220;Fail Fast, Fail [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fail-fast-fail-often-how-losing-can-help-you-win-ryan-babineaux-john-krumboltz-abridged/">Fail Fast, Fail Often : How Losing Can Help You Win &#8211; Ryan Babineaux, John Krumboltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bold, bossy and bracing, Fail Fast, Fail Often is like a 200-page shot of B12, meant to energize the listless job seeker.<br />
                    &#8211;New York Times     </p>
<p>                    What if your biggest mistake is that you never make mistakes?     </p>
<p>                    Ryan Babineaux and John Krumboltz, psychologists, career counselors, and creators of the popular Stanford University course &#8220;Fail Fast, Fail Often,&#8221; have come to a compelling conclusion: happy and successful people tend to spend less time planning and more time acting. They get out into the world, try new things, and make mistakes, and in doing so, they benefit from unexpected experiences and opportunities.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the authors&#8217; research in human development and innovation, Fail Fast, Fail Often shows readers how to allow their enthusiasm to guide them, to act boldly, and to leverage their strengths&#8211;even if they are terrified of failure.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fail-fast-fail-often-how-losing-can-help-you-win-ryan-babineaux-john-krumboltz-abridged/">Fail Fast, Fail Often : How Losing Can Help You Win &#8211; Ryan Babineaux, John Krumboltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crafts & Hobbies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge &#8211; over one million copies sold** Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge  &#8211; over one million copies sold**    </p>
<p>                    Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness    </p>
<p>                    Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. In The Little Book of Lykke, he reveals what he has found.    </p>
<p>                    This captivating read features case studies from Bhutan to Australia, South Korea to Canada, France to Denmark, taking the reader on a happiness treasure hunt. Written in the same warm tone as Meik&#8217;s phenomenal bestseller The Little Book of Hygge, this easy-to-understand book will change the way you think about how you relate to your neighbours, the rituals around cooking and eating dinner, and when to book your next holiday &#8211; and is guaranteed to put a smile on your face.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is a happy book about happiness, written with a twinkle and packaged with Danish style&#8217; (John Helliwell, Economist and Editor of the World Happiness Report)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unmasking the Face : A Guide to Recognizing Emotions from Facial Expressions &#8211; Professor of Psychology Paul Ekman, Wallace V Friesen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unmasking-the-face-a-guide-to-recognizing-emotions-from-facial-expressions-professor-of-psychology-paul-ekman-wallace-v-friesen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unmasking-the-face-a-guide-to-recognizing-emotions-from-facial-expressions-professor-of-psychology-paul-ekman-wallace-v-friesen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ekman and Friesen&#8217;s breakthrough research on the facial expression of emotion uses scores of photographs showing emotions of surprise, fear, disgust, anger, happiness, and sadness. The authors of UNMASKING THE FACE explain how to identify these basic emotions correctly and how to tell when people try to mask, simulate, or neutralize them. It features several [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmasking-the-face-a-guide-to-recognizing-emotions-from-facial-expressions-professor-of-psychology-paul-ekman-wallace-v-friesen-abridged/">Unmasking the Face : A Guide to Recognizing Emotions from Facial Expressions &#8211; Professor of Psychology Paul Ekman, Wallace V Friesen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ekman and Friesen&#8217;s breakthrough research on the facial expression of emotion uses scores of photographs showing emotions of surprise, fear, disgust, anger, happiness, and sadness. The authors of UNMASKING THE FACE explain how to identify these basic emotions correctly and how to tell when people try to mask, simulate, or neutralize them. It features several practical exercises that help actors, teachers, salesmen, counselors, nurses, law-enforcement personnel and physicians &#8212; and everyone else who deals with people &#8212; to become adept, perceptive readers of the facial expressions of emotions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmasking-the-face-a-guide-to-recognizing-emotions-from-facial-expressions-professor-of-psychology-paul-ekman-wallace-v-friesen-abridged/">Unmasking the Face : A Guide to Recognizing Emotions from Facial Expressions &#8211; Professor of Psychology Paul Ekman, Wallace V Friesen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans. Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests? By studying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans.      </p>
<p>                    Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests?     </p>
<p>                    By studying social behaviors in animals, such as bonding, the herd instinct, the forming of trusting alliances, expressions of consolation, and conflict resolution, Frans de Waal demonstrates that animals-and humans-are preprogrammed to reach out. He has found that chimpanzees care for mates that are wounded by leopards, elephants offer reassuring rumbles to youngsters in distress, and dolphins support sick companions near the water&#8217;s surface to prevent them from drowning. From day one humans have innate sensitivities to faces, bodies, and voices; we&#8217;ve been designed to feel for one another.     </p>
<p>                    De Waal&#8217;s theory runs counter to the assumption that humans are inherently selfish, which can be seen in the fields of politics, law, and finance. But he cites the public&#8217;s outrage at the U.S. government&#8217;s lack of empathy in the wake of Hurricane Katrina as a significant shift in perspective-one that helped Barack Obama become elected and ushered in what perhaps could become an Age of Empathy. Through a better understanding of empathy&#8217;s survival value in evolution, de Waal suggests, we can work together toward a more just society based on a more generous and accurate view of human nature.     </p>
<p>                    Written in layman&#8217;s prose with a wealth of anecdotes, wry humor, and incisive intelligence, The Age of Empathy is essential reading for our embattled times.     </p>
<p>                    An important and timely message about the biological roots of human kindness.&#8211;Desmond Morris, author of The Naked Ape</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good Reasons for Bad Feelings : Insights from the Frontier of Evolutionary Psychiatry &#8211; Randolph M. Nesse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Developmental Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new approach to mental disorder. Randolph Nesse&#8217;s insightful book suggests that conditions such as anxiety and depression have a clear evolutionary purpose &#8230; This intriguing book turns some age-old questions about the human condition upside down&#8217; Tim Adams, Observer One of the world&#8217;s most respected psychiatrists provides a much-needed new evolutionary framework for making [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/">Good Reasons for Bad Feelings : Insights from the Frontier of Evolutionary Psychiatry &#8211; Randolph M. Nesse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new approach to mental disorder. Randolph Nesse&#8217;s insightful book  suggests that conditions such as anxiety and depression have a clear  evolutionary purpose &#8230; This intriguing book turns some age-old  questions about the human condition upside down&#8217; Tim Adams, Observer    </p>
<p>                    One of the world&#8217;s most respected psychiatrists provides a much-needed new evolutionary framework for making sense of mental illness    </p>
<p>                    With his classic book Why We Get Sick, Randolph Nesse established the field of evolutionary medicine. Now he returns with a book that transforms our understanding of mental disorders by exploring a fundamentally new question. Instead of asking why certain people suffer from mental illness, Nesse asks why natural selection has left us with fragile minds at all.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on revealing stories from his own clinical practice and insights from evolutionary biology, Nesse shows how negative emotions are useful in certain situations, yet can become excessive. Anxiety protects us from harm in the face of danger, but false alarms are inevitable. Low mood prevents us from wasting effort in pursuit of unreachable goals, but it often escalates into pathological depression. Other mental disorders, such as addiction and anorexia, result from the mismatch between modern environments and our ancient human past. Taken together, these insights and many more help to explain the pervasiveness of human suffering, and show us new paths for relieving it.    </p>
<p>                    Good Reasons for Bad Feelings will fascinate anyone who wonders how our minds can be so powerful, yet so fragile, and how love and goodness came to exist in organisms shaped to maximize Darwinian fitness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/">Good Reasons for Bad Feelings : Insights from the Frontier of Evolutionary Psychiatry &#8211; Randolph M. Nesse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not To Worry : The Remarkable Truth of How a Small Change Can Help You Stress Less and Enjoy Life More &#8211; Paul McGee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-worry-the-remarkable-truth-of-how-a-small-change-can-help-you-stress-less-and-enjoy-life-more-paul-mcgee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-worry-the-remarkable-truth-of-how-a-small-change-can-help-you-stress-less-and-enjoy-life-more-paul-mcgee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to defeat stress, worry, and anxiety to achieve more in business and life. From the international bestselling author of Self-Confidence. Are You A Worrier? Do you seem to worry more than most? Do you find that insignificant things stress you out? Do you sweat the small stuff and the big stuff too? Well, now [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-worry-the-remarkable-truth-of-how-a-small-change-can-help-you-stress-less-and-enjoy-life-more-paul-mcgee-abridged/">How Not To Worry : The Remarkable Truth of How a Small Change Can Help You Stress Less and Enjoy Life More &#8211; Paul McGee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to defeat stress, worry, and anxiety to achieve more in business and life. From the international bestselling author of Self-Confidence. Are You A Worrier? Do you seem to worry more than most? Do you find that insignificant things stress you out? Do you sweat the small stuff and the big stuff too? Well, now s the time to stop worrying and start living. Worry, stress, anxiety whichever label you prefer to use can have consequences that impact not only our lives, but the lives of others around us. When we worry it s like the engine of our mind is constantly being revved up. It doesn t allow us time to switch off and rest. It tires you out. And when you re tired you re less likely to think straight. And when you re not thinking straight it s easy to make stupid mistakes and confuse priorities&#8230;But relax. There is a way forward. In How Not to Worry Paul McGee shows us that there is a way to tackle life s challenges in a calmer and more considered way. It is possible to use a certain degree of worry and anxiety to spur us on towards positive, constructive action, and then leave the rest behind.<br />
                    With down to earth, real life advice, How Not to Worry helps us understand why worrying is such a big deal and the reasons for it, exposing the behavioural traps we fall into when faced with challenges. It then helps us to move on with tools and ideas to deal with our worries in a more constructive way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-worry-the-remarkable-truth-of-how-a-small-change-can-help-you-stress-less-and-enjoy-life-more-paul-mcgee-abridged/">How Not To Worry : The Remarkable Truth of How a Small Change Can Help You Stress Less and Enjoy Life More &#8211; Paul McGee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Fix a Broken Heart &#8211; Dr Guy Winch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-fix-a-broken-heart-dr-guy-winch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-fix-a-broken-heart-dr-guy-winch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>HOW TO FIX A BROKEN HEART PROVIDES THE VALIDATION, COMFORT AND HOPE ANYONE WHO IS HEARTBROKEN DESPERATELY NEEDS.&#8217; ESTHER PEREL, BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STATE OF AFFAIRS AND MATING IN CAPTIVITY Every one of us has or will have our heart broken at some point in our lives. Heartbreak, whether it comes in the form [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fix-a-broken-heart-dr-guy-winch-abridged/">How to Fix a Broken Heart &#8211; Dr Guy Winch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HOW TO FIX A BROKEN HEART PROVIDES THE VALIDATION, COMFORT AND HOPE ANYONE WHO IS HEARTBROKEN DESPERATELY NEEDS.&#8217;<br />
                     ESTHER PEREL, BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STATE OF AFFAIRS AND MATING IN CAPTIVITY     </p>
<p>                     Every one of us has or will have our heart broken at some point in our lives. Heartbreak, whether it comes in the form of romantic love or through loss, is universal, yet we know so little about how to deal with it. Psychologist Dr Guy Winch imagines how different our lives and our society would be if we paid more attention to this unique emotional pain.     </p>
<p>                     Heartbreak can last for days, weeks, months and even years. Yet while we wouldn&#8217;t expect someone to go to work or function well with a broken limb, heartbroken people are expected to function in their lives, despite the emotional pain they feel.     </p>
<p>                    How to Fix a Broken Heart argues that if we don&#8217;t understand how heartbreak works, we won&#8217;t be able to heal it and we are likely to make it worse, which we do, and regularly.     </p>
<p>                     Dr Winch reveals how and why heartbreak impacts our brain and our behaviour in dramatic and unexpected ways, regardless of our age. Emotional pain lowers our ability to reason, to think creatively, to problem solve and to function.    </p>
<p>                    Recovering from heartbreak always starts with a decision, a determination to move on when our mind is fighting to keep us stuck. We can take control of our lives and our minds and put ourselves on the path to healing. Dr Winch offers a toolkit on how to handle and cope with a broken heart and how to, eventually, move on.     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A great read for anyone going through heartbreak, anyone trying to help someone go through heartbreak, or anyone who simply wants to understand humans better&#8217; Tim Urban, creator of Wait But Why?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fix-a-broken-heart-dr-guy-winch-abridged/">How to Fix a Broken Heart &#8211; Dr Guy Winch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>LIFE-CHANGING&#8217; CAROLINE HINNES Learn to harness the strength of mindfulness and positivity to change your life with Eckhart Tolle THE BOOK THAT INSPIRED THE CHART-TOPPING PODCAST OPRAH &#038; ECKHART TOLLE: A NEW EARTH ____________ Are you ready to change your life? In Eckhart Tolle&#8217;s ground-breaking book, he gives you the spiritual framework to: &#8211; Understand [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/">A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LIFE-CHANGING&#8217; CAROLINE HINNES    </p>
<p>                    Learn to harness the strength of mindfulness and positivity to change your life with Eckhart Tolle    </p>
<p>                    THE BOOK THAT INSPIRED THE CHART-TOPPING PODCAST OPRAH &#038; ECKHART TOLLE: A NEW EARTH<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    Are you ready to change your life?    </p>
<p>                    In Eckhart Tolle&#8217;s ground-breaking book, he gives you the spiritual framework to:<br />
                    &#8211; Understand yourself better<br />
                    &#8211; Manage, manifest and achieve your goals<br />
                    &#8211; Reach your full potential<br />
                    &#8211; Channel conflict into something positive<br />
                    &#8211; Change negative habits<br />
                    &#8211; Live in the moment    </p>
<p>                    Open your mind and follow Tolle&#8217;s guidance to happiness and health in the modern world.<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wake up call for the entire planet. A New Earth helps us to stop creating our own suffering and obsessing over the past and what the future might be and to put ourselves in the now&#8217; Oprah Winfrey    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My No. 1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans, Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;m gonna have to listen to [this podcast] several times! Too good!&#8217; Fearne Cotton on the &#8216;Oprah and Eckhart Tolle: A New Earth&#8217; podcast    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book changed my life. It&#8217;s a brilliant and very practical spiritual guide that teaches the way to inner peace: how to live in the moment and get beyond the ego&#8217; Santa Montefiore, bestselling author of The Secret Hours</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/">A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Descartes&#8217; Error : Emotion, Reason and the Human Brain &#8211; Antonio Damasio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/descartes-error-emotion-reason-and-the-human-brain-antonio-damasio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/descartes-error-emotion-reason-and-the-human-brain-antonio-damasio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the centuries since Descartes famously proclaimed, &#8216;I think, therefore I am,&#8217; science has often overlooked emotions as the source of a person&#8217;s true being. Even modern neuroscience has tended until recently to concentrate on the cognitive aspects of brain function, disregarding emotions. This attitude began to change with the publication of Descartes&#8217; Error. Antonio [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/descartes-error-emotion-reason-and-the-human-brain-antonio-damasio-abridged/">Descartes&#8217; Error : Emotion, Reason and the Human Brain &#8211; Antonio Damasio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the centuries since Descartes famously proclaimed, &#8216;I think, therefore I am,&#8217; science has often overlooked emotions as the source of a person&#8217;s true being. Even modern neuroscience has tended until recently to concentrate on the cognitive aspects of brain function, disregarding emotions. This attitude began to change with the publication of Descartes&#8217; Error. Antonio Damasio challenged traditional ideas about the connection between emotions and rationality. In this wonderfully engaging book, Damasio takes the reader on a journey of scientific discovery through a series of case studies, demonstrating what many of us have long suspected: emotions are not a luxury, they are essential to rational thinking and to normal social behaviour.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/descartes-error-emotion-reason-and-the-human-brain-antonio-damasio-abridged/">Descartes&#8217; Error : Emotion, Reason and the Human Brain &#8211; Antonio Damasio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Braving the Wilderness : The quest for true belonging and the courage to stand alone &#8211; Brené Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/braving-the-wilderness-the-quest-for-true-belonging-and-the-courage-to-stand-alone-brene-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/braving-the-wilderness-the-quest-for-true-belonging-and-the-courage-to-stand-alone-brene-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A timely and important new book that challenges everything we think we know about cultivating true belonging in our communities, organizations, and culture, from the #1 bestselling author of Rising Strong, Daring Greatly, and The Gifts of Imperfection. &#8216;True belonging doesn&#8217;t require us to change who we are. It requires us to be who we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/braving-the-wilderness-the-quest-for-true-belonging-and-the-courage-to-stand-alone-brene-brown-abridged/">Braving the Wilderness : The quest for true belonging and the courage to stand alone &#8211; Brené Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A timely and important new book that challenges everything we think we know about cultivating true belonging in our communities, organizations, and culture, from the #1 bestselling author of Rising Strong, Daring Greatly, and The Gifts of Imperfection.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;True belonging doesn&#8217;t require us to change who we are. It requires us to be who we are.&#8217;  Social scientist Brene Brown, PhD, LMSW has sparked a global conversation about the experiences that bring meaning to our lives &#8211; experiences of courage, vulnerability, love, belonging, shame and empathy. In Braving the Wilderness, Brown redefines what it means to truly belong in an age of increased polarisation. With her trademark mix of research, storytelling and honesty, Brown will again change the cultural conversation while mapping out a clear path to true belonging.    </p>
<p>                    Brown argues that what we&#8217;re experiencing today is a spiritual crisis of disconnection, and introduces four practices of true belonging that challenge everything we believe about ourselves and each other. She writes, &#8216;True belonging requires us to believe in and belong to ourselves so fully that we can find sacredness both in both being a part of something, and in standing alone when necessary. But in a culture that&#8217;s rife with perfectionism and pleasing, and with the erosion of civility, it&#8217;s easy to stay quiet, hide in our ideological bunkers, or fit in rather than show up as our true selves and brave the wilderness of uncertainty and criticism. But true belonging is not something we negotiate or accomplish with others; it&#8217;s a daily practice that demands integrity and authenticity. It&#8217;s a personal commitment that we carry in our hearts.&#8217; Brown offers us the clarity and courage we need to find our way back to ourselves and to each other. And that path cuts right through the wilderness. Brown writes, &#8216;The wilderness is an untamed, unpredictable place of solitude and searching. It is a place as dangerous as it is breathtaking, a place as sought after as it is feared. But it turns out to be the place of true belonging, and it&#8217;s the bravest and most sacred place you will ever stand.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/braving-the-wilderness-the-quest-for-true-belonging-and-the-courage-to-stand-alone-brene-brown-abridged/">Braving the Wilderness : The quest for true belonging and the courage to stand alone &#8211; Brené Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happy : Why More or Less Everything is Absolutely Fine &#8211; Derren Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happy-why-more-or-less-everything-is-absolutely-fine-derren-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happy-why-more-or-less-everything-is-absolutely-fine-derren-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8216;Really brilliant and just crammed with wisdom and insight. It will genuinely make a difference to me and the way I think about myself.&#8217; Stephen Fry ___ Everyone says they want to be happy. But that&#8217;s much more easily said than done. What does being happy actually mean? And how do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-why-more-or-less-everything-is-absolutely-fine-derren-brown-abridged/">Happy : Why More or Less Everything is Absolutely Fine &#8211; Derren Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Really brilliant and just crammed with wisdom and insight. It will genuinely make a difference to me and the way I think about myself.&#8217; Stephen Fry    </p>
<p>                    ___    </p>
<p>                    Everyone says they want to be happy. But that&#8217;s much more easily said than done. What does being happy actually mean? And how do you even know when you feel it?    </p>
<p>                    In Happy Derren Brown explores changing concepts of happiness &#8211; from the surprisingly modern wisdom of the Stoics and Epicureans in classical times right up until today, when the self-help industry has attempted to claim happiness as its own. He shows how many of self-help&#8217;s suggested routes to happiness and success &#8211; such as positive thinking, self-belief and setting goals &#8211; can be disastrous to follow and, indeed, actually cause anxiety.    </p>
<p>                    Happy aims to reclaim happiness and to enable us to appreciate the good things in life, in all their transient glory. By taking control of the stories we tell ourselves, by remembering that &#8216;everything&#8217;s fine&#8217; even when it might not feel that way, we can allow ourselves to flourish and to live more happily.    </p>
<p>                    ___    </p>
<p>                    What readers are saying:<br />
                    ***** &#8216;Immensely positive and life-affirming&#8217;<br />
                    ***** &#8216;This is the blue print to a good life&#8217;<br />
                    ***** &#8216;Thought provoking and potentially life-changing.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-why-more-or-less-everything-is-absolutely-fine-derren-brown-abridged/">Happy : Why More or Less Everything is Absolutely Fine &#8211; Derren Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Perfect for lovers of Quiet and The Power of Now, Emotional Agility shares a new way of relating to yourself and the world around you Every day we speak around 16,000 words &#8211; but inside minds we create tens of thousands more. Thoughts such as &#8216;I&#8217;m not spending enough time with my children&#8217; or &#8216;I&#8217;m [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/">Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Perfect for lovers of Quiet and The Power of Now, Emotional Agility shares a new way of relating to yourself and the world around you    </p>
<p>                     Every day we speak around 16,000 words &#8211; but inside minds we create tens of thousands more.     </p>
<p>                    Thoughts such as &#8216;I&#8217;m not spending enough time with my children&#8217; or &#8216;I&#8217;m not good enough to present my work&#8217; can seem to be unshakeable facts. In reality, they&#8217;re the judgemental opinions of our inner voice.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on more than twenty years of academic research and her own experiences, Susan David PhD, a psychologist and faculty member at Harvard Medical School, has pioneered a new way to make peace with our inner self, achieve our most valued goals and live life to the fullest.    </p>
<p>                     Become aware of your true nature, learn to face your emotions with acceptance and generosity, act according to your deepest values, and flourish.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Essential reading&#8217; Susan Cain, author of Quiet    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A practical, science-backed guide to looking inward and living intentionally&#8217; Arianna Huffington, author of The Sleep Revolution    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An accessible, reader-friendly voyage. Emotional Agility can be helpful to anyone.&#8217; Daniel Goleman, author of Emotional Intelligence</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/">Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Habits of a Happy Brain : Retrain Your Brain to Boost Your Serotonin, Dopamine, Oxytocin, &#038; Endorphin Levels &#8211; Loretta Graziano Breuning (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/habits-of-a-happy-brain-retrain-your-brain-to-boost-your-serotonin-dopamine-oxytocin-endorphin-levels-loretta-graziano-breuning-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/habits-of-a-happy-brain-retrain-your-brain-to-boost-your-serotonin-dopamine-oxytocin-endorphin-levels-loretta-graziano-breuning-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revolutionary approach to enhancing your happiness level! Get ready to boost your happiness in just 45 days! Habits of a Happy Brain shows you how to retrain your brain to turn on the chemicals that make you happy. Each page offers simple activities that help you understand the roles of your &#8220;happy chemicals&#8221;-serotonin, dopamine, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/habits-of-a-happy-brain-retrain-your-brain-to-boost-your-serotonin-dopamine-oxytocin-endorphin-levels-loretta-graziano-breuning-abridged/">Habits of a Happy Brain : Retrain Your Brain to Boost Your Serotonin, Dopamine, Oxytocin, &#038; Endorphin Levels &#8211; Loretta Graziano Breuning (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revolutionary approach to enhancing your happiness level!    </p>
<p>                    Get ready to boost your happiness in just 45 days! Habits of a Happy Brain shows you how to retrain your brain to turn on the chemicals that make you happy. Each page offers simple activities that help you understand the roles of your &#8220;happy chemicals&#8221;-serotonin, dopamine, oxytocin, and endorphin. You&#8217;ll also learn how to build new habits by rerouting the electricity in your brain to flow down a new pathway, making it even easier to trigger these happy chemicals and increase feelings of satisfaction when you need them most. Filled with dozens of exercises that will help you reprogram your brain, Habits of a Happy Brain shows you how to live a happier, healthier life!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/habits-of-a-happy-brain-retrain-your-brain-to-boost-your-serotonin-dopamine-oxytocin-endorphin-levels-loretta-graziano-breuning-abridged/">Habits of a Happy Brain : Retrain Your Brain to Boost Your Serotonin, Dopamine, Oxytocin, &#038; Endorphin Levels &#8211; Loretta Graziano Breuning (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happiness by Design : Finding Pleasure and Purpose in Everyday Life &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happiness-by-design-finding-pleasure-and-purpose-in-everyday-life-paul-dolan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happiness-by-design-finding-pleasure-and-purpose-in-everyday-life-paul-dolan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER How can we make it easier to be happy? Using the latest cutting-edge research, Professor Paul Dolan reveals that wellbeing isn&#8217;t about how we think &#8211; it&#8217;s about what we do. By making deliberate choices that bring us both pleasure and meaning, we can redesign our lives for maximum happiness &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-by-design-finding-pleasure-and-purpose-in-everyday-life-paul-dolan-abridged/">Happiness by Design : Finding Pleasure and Purpose in Everyday Life &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    How can we make it easier to be happy? Using the latest cutting-edge research, Professor Paul Dolan reveals that wellbeing isn&#8217;t about how we think &#8211; it&#8217;s about what we do. By making deliberate choices that bring us both pleasure and meaning, we can redesign our lives for maximum happiness &#8211; without thinking too hard about it.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Outstanding, cutting-edge, and profound. If you&#8217;re going to read one book on happiness, this is the one&#8217; Nassim Nicholas Taleb    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Bold and original &#8230; what I wish for my grandchildren: a life that is rich in activities both pleasurable and meaningful&#8217; Daniel Kahneman, author of Thinking Fast and Slow</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-by-design-finding-pleasure-and-purpose-in-everyday-life-paul-dolan-abridged/">Happiness by Design : Finding Pleasure and Purpose in Everyday Life &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selfie : How the West Became Self-Obsessed &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Electrifying&#8217; Financial Times &#8216;So interesting I literally couldn&#8217;t put it down&#8217; Sunday Times We are living in an age of heightened individualism. Success is a personal responsibility. Our culture tells us that to succeed is to be slim, rich, happy, extroverted, popular &#8211; flawless. The pressure to conform to this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/">Selfie : How the West Became Self-Obsessed &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Evening Standard<br />
                    &#8216;Electrifying&#8217; Financial Times<br />
                    &#8216;So interesting I literally couldn&#8217;t put it down&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    We are living in an age of heightened individualism. Success is a personal responsibility. Our culture tells us that to succeed is to be slim, rich, happy, extroverted, popular &#8211; flawless.    </p>
<p>                    The pressure to conform to this ideal has changed who we are. We have become self-obsessed. And our expectation of perfection comes at a cost. Millions are suffering under the torture of this impossible fantasy.    </p>
<p>                    It was not always like this. To explain how we got here, Will Storr takes us on a journey across continents and centuries. Full of thrilling and unexpected connections between history, psychology, economics, neuroscience and more, Selfie is an unforgettable book that makes sense of who we have become.    </p>
<p>                    As featured on Russell Brand&#8217;s Under The Skin podcast.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/">Selfie : How the West Became Self-Obsessed &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem. We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem.      </p>
<p>                    We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider world. As the latest research in psychology and neuroscience shows, we feel empathy most for those we find attractive and who seem similar to us and not at all for those who are different, distant or anonymous. Empathy therefore biases us in favour of individuals we know while numbing us to the plight of thousands. Guiding us expertly through the experiments, case studies and arguments on all sides, Paul Bloom ultimately shows that some of our worst decisions &#8211; in charity, child-raising, criminal justice, climate change and war &#8211; are motivated by this wolf in sheep&#8217;s clothing.     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly argued, urgent and humane, Against Empathy overturns widely held assumptions to reveal one of the most profound yet overlooked sources of human conflict.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happiness : A Guide to Developing Life&#8217;s Most Important Skill &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Although we are materially better off than ever before, surveys show that we are depressed and listless. In his revolutionary book, Buddhist monk Matthieu Ricard shows that happiness is not just an emotion, but a skill that can be developed. Free of jargon, Happiness contains simple exercises that will train the mind to recognize and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Happiness : A Guide to Developing Life&#8217;s Most Important Skill &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although we are materially better off than ever before, surveys show that we are depressed and listless. In his revolutionary book, Buddhist monk Matthieu Ricard shows that happiness is not just an emotion, but a skill that can be developed. Free of jargon, Happiness contains simple exercises that will train the mind to recognize and pursue happiness by concentrating on the fundamental things in life, and in doing so change the way we view the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Happiness : A Guide to Developing Life&#8217;s Most Important Skill &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Surprise : Embrace the Unpredictable and Engineer the Unexpected &#8211; Tania Luna, LeeAnn Renninger, PhD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/surprise-embrace-the-unpredictable-and-engineer-the-unexpected-tania-luna-leeann-renninger-phd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/surprise-embrace-the-unpredictable-and-engineer-the-unexpected-tania-luna-leeann-renninger-phd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Surprise: Embrace the Unpredictable and Engineer the Unexpected is a fascinating look at how we can handle and harness surprise in our work, relationships, and everyday lives. Pop Quiz! Do you prefer when: A) Things go according to plan? B) When the unexpected happens? Most of us pick control and predictability. Yet research reveals a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/surprise-embrace-the-unpredictable-and-engineer-the-unexpected-tania-luna-leeann-renninger-phd-abridged/">Surprise : Embrace the Unpredictable and Engineer the Unexpected &#8211; Tania Luna, LeeAnn Renninger, PhD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Surprise: Embrace the Unpredictable and Engineer the Unexpected is a fascinating look at how we can handle and harness surprise in our work, relationships, and everyday lives.      </p>
<p>                    Pop Quiz!     </p>
<p>                    Do you prefer when:<br />
                    A) Things go according to plan?<br />
                    B) When the unexpected happens?     </p>
<p>                    Most of us pick control and predictability. Yet research reveals a counterintuitive truth: surprise is the key that unlocks growth, innovation, and connection. It is also the secret ingredient in our best memories.     </p>
<p>                    Through colorful narratives and compelling scientific findings, authors Tania Luna and Dr. LeeAnn Renninger shine a light on the world&#8217;s least understood and most intriguing emotion. They reveal how shifting our perception of surprise lets us thrive in the face of uncertainty. And they show us how surprise acts as a shortcut that turns a typical product into a meaningful experience, a good idea into a viral one, awkward small talk into engaging conversation, and daily life into an adventure.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/surprise-embrace-the-unpredictable-and-engineer-the-unexpected-tania-luna-leeann-renninger-phd-abridged/">Surprise : Embrace the Unpredictable and Engineer the Unexpected &#8211; Tania Luna, LeeAnn Renninger, PhD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happy Ever After : A Radical New Approach to Living Well &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happy-ever-after-a-radical-new-approach-to-living-well-paul-dolan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happy-ever-after-a-radical-new-approach-to-living-well-paul-dolan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Smart, engaging and funny. It will make you question everything you think you know about what you want&#8217; Caroline Criado Perez, author of Invisible Women Be ambitious; find everlasting love; look after your health &#8230; There are countless stories about how we ought to live our lives. These narratives can make our lives easier, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-ever-after-a-radical-new-approach-to-living-well-paul-dolan-abridged/">Happy Ever After : A Radical New Approach to Living Well &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Smart, engaging and funny. It will make you question everything you think you know about what you want&#8217; Caroline Criado Perez, author of Invisible Women    </p>
<p>                    Be ambitious; find everlasting love; look after your health &#8230; There are countless stories about how we ought to live our lives. These narratives can make our lives easier, and they might sometimes make us happier too. But they can also trap us and those around us.    </p>
<p>                    In Happy Ever After, bestselling happiness expert Professor Paul Dolan draws on a variety of studies ranging over wellbeing, inequality and discrimination to bust the common myths about our sources of happiness. He shows that there can be many unexpected paths to lasting fulfilment. Some of these might involve not going into higher education, choosing not to marry, rewarding acts rooted in self-interest and caring a little less about living forever.    </p>
<p>                    By freeing ourselves from the myth of the perfect life, we might each find a life worth living.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-ever-after-a-radical-new-approach-to-living-well-paul-dolan-abridged/">Happy Ever After : A Radical New Approach to Living Well &#8211; Paul Dolan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hardcore Self Help: F**k Anxiety v. 1 &#8211; Robert Duff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hardcore-self-help-fk-anxiety-v-1-robert-duff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hardcore-self-help-fk-anxiety-v-1-robert-duff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hardcore Self Help: F**k Anxiety is for those of us that find the prospect of reading a traditional self help book to be way too boring. How are you supposed to make positive change in your life if the book itself feels like a chore? This book is definitely not a chore. In Hardcore Self [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hardcore-self-help-fk-anxiety-v-1-robert-duff-abridged/">Hardcore Self Help: F**k Anxiety v. 1 &#8211; Robert Duff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hardcore Self Help: F**k Anxiety is for those of us that find the prospect of reading a traditional self help book to be way too boring. How are you supposed to make positive change in your life if the book itself feels like a chore? This book is definitely not a chore. In Hardcore Self Help: F**k Anxiety, I talk to you like a friend. There is lots of swearing and humor and also loads of helpful and actionable information. You learn about anxiety and how to find the weapons within yourself to slay it for good.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hardcore-self-help-fk-anxiety-v-1-robert-duff-abridged/">Hardcore Self Help: F**k Anxiety v. 1 &#8211; Robert Duff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Social Intelligence : The New Science of Human Relationships &#8211; Daniel Goleman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/social-intelligence-the-new-science-of-human-relationships-daniel-goleman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/social-intelligence-the-new-science-of-human-relationships-daniel-goleman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Emotional Intelligence was an international phenomenon, appearing on the New York Times bestseller list for over a year and selling more than 5 million copies worldwide. Now, once again, Daniel Goleman has written a groundbreaking synthesis of the latest findings in biology and brain science, revealing that we are &#8216;wired to connect&#8217; and the surprisingly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-intelligence-the-new-science-of-human-relationships-daniel-goleman-abridged/">Social Intelligence : The New Science of Human Relationships &#8211; Daniel Goleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Emotional Intelligence was an international phenomenon, appearing on the New York Times bestseller list for over a year and selling more than 5 million copies worldwide. Now, once again, Daniel Goleman has written a groundbreaking synthesis of the latest findings in biology and brain science, revealing that we are &#8216;wired to connect&#8217; and the surprisingly deep impact of our relationships on every aspect our lives.    </p>
<p>                    Far more than we are consciously aware, our daily encounters with parents, spouses, bosses, and even strangers, shape our brains and affect cells throughout our bodies, down to the level of our genes &#8211; for good or ill. In Social Intelligence, Daniel Goleman explores an emerging new science with startling implications for our interpersonal world. Its most fundamental discovery: we are designed for sociability, constantly engaged in a &#8216;neural ballet&#8217; that connects us brain-to-brain with those around us.    </p>
<p>                    Goleman explains the surprising accuracy of first impressions, the basis of charisma and emotional power, the complexity of sexual attraction, and how we detect lies. He describes the &#8216;dark side&#8217; of social intelligence, from narcissism to Machiavellianism and psychopathy. He also reveals our astonishing capacity for &#8216;mindsight&#8217;, as well as the tragedy of those, like autistic children, whose mindsight is impaired.    </p>
<p>                    In this book Daniel Goleman delivers his most heartening news with powerful conviction: we humans have a built-in bias toward empathy, cooperation and altruism &#8211; provided we develop the social intelligence to nurture these capacities in ourselves and others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-intelligence-the-new-science-of-human-relationships-daniel-goleman-abridged/">Social Intelligence : The New Science of Human Relationships &#8211; Daniel Goleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Emotion Code : How to Release Your Trapped Emotions for Abundant Health, Love and Happiness &#8211; Dr Bradley Nelson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-emotion-code-how-to-release-your-trapped-emotions-for-abundant-health-love-and-happiness-dr-bradley-nelson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-emotion-code-how-to-release-your-trapped-emotions-for-abundant-health-love-and-happiness-dr-bradley-nelson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I believe that the discoveries in this book can change our understanding of how we store emotional experiences and in so doing, change our lives. The Emotion Code has already changed many lives around the world, and it is my hope that millions more will be led to use this simple tool to heal themselves [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-emotion-code-how-to-release-your-trapped-emotions-for-abundant-health-love-and-happiness-dr-bradley-nelson-abridged/">The Emotion Code : How to Release Your Trapped Emotions for Abundant Health, Love and Happiness &#8211; Dr Bradley Nelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I believe that the discoveries in this book can change our understanding of how we store emotional experiences and in so doing, change our lives. The Emotion Code has already changed many lives around the world, and it is my hope that millions more will be led to use this simple tool to heal themselves and their loved ones.&#8217; &#8211; Tony Robbins    </p>
<p>                    In this newly revised and expanded edition of The Emotion Code, renowned holistic physician and lecturer Dr. Bradley Nelson skilfully lays bare the inner workings of the subconscious mind. He reveals how emotionally-charged events from your past can still be haunting you in the form of &#8216;trapped emotions&#8217; &#8211; emotional energies that literally inhabit your body. These trapped emotions can fester in your life and body, creating pain, malfunction and eventual disease. They can also extract a heavy mental and emotional toll on you, impacting how you think, the choices that you make, and the level of success and abundance you are able to achieve. Perhaps most damaging of all, trapped emotional energies can gather around your heart, cutting off your ability to give and receive love.    </p>
<p>                    The Emotion Code is a powerful and simple way to rid yourself of this unseen baggage. Dr. Nelson&#8217;s method gives you the tools to identify and release the trapped emotions in your life, eliminating your &#8217;emotional baggage&#8217;, and opening your heart and body to the positive energies of the world. Filled with real-world examples from many years of clinical practice, The Emotion Code is a distinct and authoritative work that has become a classic on self-healing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-emotion-code-how-to-release-your-trapped-emotions-for-abundant-health-love-and-happiness-dr-bradley-nelson-abridged/">The Emotion Code : How to Release Your Trapped Emotions for Abundant Health, Love and Happiness &#8211; Dr Bradley Nelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Compass of Pleasure : How Our Brains Make Fatty Foods, Orgasm, Exercise, Marijuana, Generosity, Vodka, Learning, and Gambling Feel So Good &#8211; David J. Linden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author comes a &#8220;hugely entertaining&#8221; (NPR.org) look at vice and virtue through cutting-edge scienceAs he did in his award-winning book The Accidental Mind, David J. Linden-highly regarded neuroscientist, professor, and writer-weaves empirical science with entertaining anecdotes to explain how the gamut of behaviors that give us a buzz actually [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/">The Compass of Pleasure : How Our Brains Make Fatty Foods, Orgasm, Exercise, Marijuana, Generosity, Vodka, Learning, and Gambling Feel So Good &#8211; David J. Linden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author comes a &#8220;hugely entertaining&#8221; (NPR.org) look at vice and virtue through cutting-edge scienceAs he did in his award-winning book The Accidental Mind, David J. Linden-highly regarded neuroscientist, professor, and writer-weaves empirical science with entertaining anecdotes to explain how the gamut of behaviors that give us a buzz actually operates. The Compass of Pleasure makes clear why drugs like nicotine and heroin are addictive while LSD is not, how fast food restaurants ensure that diners will eat more, why some people cannot resist the appeal of a new sexual encounter, and much more. Provocative and illuminating, this is a radically new and thorough look at the desires that define us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/">The Compass of Pleasure : How Our Brains Make Fatty Foods, Orgasm, Exercise, Marijuana, Generosity, Vodka, Learning, and Gambling Feel So Good &#8211; David J. Linden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Make a new start in 2022 with positive daily habits for a healthy mind, from the incredible No. 1 New York Times bestseller THE INCREDIBLE NO. 1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;SUPERB, SMART, AND SUCCINCT&#8217; FORBES ______ Struggling to find structure? Finding yourself lacking motivation? Start by making your bed. Maintaining routine and structure is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Make a new start in 2022 with positive daily habits for a healthy mind, from the incredible No. 1 New York Times bestseller    </p>
<p>                    THE INCREDIBLE NO. 1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;SUPERB, SMART, AND SUCCINCT&#8217; FORBES<br />
                    ______    </p>
<p>                    Struggling to find structure? Finding yourself lacking motivation?    </p>
<p>                    Start by making your bed.    </p>
<p>                    Maintaining routine and structure is more important than ever in the age of home working, flexi-time and the general chaos of life.    </p>
<p>                    In Make Your Bed, Admiral William H. McRaven shares 10 life lessons he learned during his Navy Seal training that helped him overcome challenges not only in his long Naval career, but also throughout his life.    </p>
<p>                    He will teach you how to . . .<br />
                    * Master the essential daily habits for staying grounded<br />
                    * Learn how to keep your mind calm and ready for the day ahead<br />
                    * Find solace and companionship in the people around you<br />
                    * Cope with setbacks and keep moving forward<br />
                    * Stray beyond your comfort zone and take risks    </p>
<p>                    Written with great humility and optimism, this timeless book provides simple and universal wisdom, practical advice, and words of encouragement that will inspire every reader.<br />
                    ______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book to inspire your children and grandchildren to become everything that they can&#8217; The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiness Fantasy &#8211; Carl Cederstroem (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiness-fantasy-carl-cederstroem-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiness-fantasy-carl-cederstroem-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Happiness has meant different things in different times: according to Aristotle, only the gods could be truly happy, but if you lived ethically, you might come close; for medieval Christians, the best way to be happy was to suffer pain and for Romantic philosophers like Rousseau, society made happiness impossible. But what does it mean [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-fantasy-carl-cederstroem-abridged/">The Happiness Fantasy &#8211; Carl Cederstroem (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happiness has meant different things in different times: according to Aristotle, only the gods could be truly happy, but if you lived ethically, you might come close; for medieval Christians, the best way to be happy was to suffer pain and for Romantic philosophers like Rousseau, society made happiness impossible. But what does it mean to be happy today? In this devastatingly witty new book, Carl Cederstrom traces our present-day fantasy of happiness from its roots in the 60&#8217;s counter-culture. He argues that happiness is now defined by a desire to be &#8216;authentic&#8217;, to experience physical pleasure, and to cultivate one&#8217;s &#8216;brand&#8217; as an employee. Along the way we encounter the renegade Austrian psychoanalysts, Big Pharma, Californian bohemians, self-help gurus and Silicon Valley CEOs who have all contributed to our current fantasy. Whilst these ideals may have depicted the good life in the 70s, a time of affluence and abundance, they are no longer sustainable in our current age of austerity. It is high time, Cederstrom argues, that we construct new fantasies of happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-fantasy-carl-cederstroem-abridged/">The Happiness Fantasy &#8211; Carl Cederstroem (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unrequited : The Thinking Woman&#8217;s Guide to Romantic Obsession &#8211; Lisa A Phillips (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unrequited-the-thinking-womans-guide-to-romantic-obsession-lisa-a-phillips-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unrequited-the-thinking-womans-guide-to-romantic-obsession-lisa-a-phillips-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blending memoir, literary exposition, and revealing case studies, Unrequited is a powerful, surprising, and empathetic cultural and psychological exploration of one-sided romantic obsession. The summer Lisa A. Phillips turned thirty, she fell in love with someone who didn&#8217;t return her feelings. She soon became obsessed. She followed him around, called him compulsively, and talked about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unrequited-the-thinking-womans-guide-to-romantic-obsession-lisa-a-phillips-abridged/">Unrequited : The Thinking Woman&#8217;s Guide to Romantic Obsession &#8211; Lisa A Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blending memoir, literary exposition, and revealing case studies, Unrequited is a powerful, surprising, and empathetic cultural and psychological exploration of one-sided romantic obsession.    </p>
<p>                    The summer Lisa A. Phillips turned thirty, she fell in love with someone who didn&#8217;t return her feelings. She soon became obsessed. She followed him around, called him compulsively, and talked about him endlessly. One desperate morning, after she snuck into his apartment building, he picked up a baseball bat to protect himself and began to dial 911. Her unrequited love had changed her from a sane, conscientious college teacher and radio reporter into someone she barely recognized&#8211;someone who was taking her yearning much too far.    </p>
<p>                    In Unrequited, Phillips explores the tremendous force of obsessive love in women&#8217;s lives. She argues that it needs to be understood, respected, and channeled for personal growth&#8211;yet it also has the potential to go terribly awry. Interweaving her own story with frank interviews and in-depth research in science, psychology, cultural history, and literature, Phillips describes how romantic obsession takes root, grows, and strongly influences our thoughts and behaviors.    </p>
<p>                    Going beyond images of creepy, fatally attracted psychos, male fantasies of unbridled female desire, and the platitudes of self-help books, Phillips reveals a powerful, troubling, and surprisingly common phenomenon. As she illuminates this mysterious psychological experience, placing it in a rich and nuanced context, she offers compelling insights to help any woman who has experienced unrequited obsessive love and been mystified and troubled by its grip.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unrequited-the-thinking-womans-guide-to-romantic-obsession-lisa-a-phillips-abridged/">Unrequited : The Thinking Woman&#8217;s Guide to Romantic Obsession &#8211; Lisa A Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Will You Measure Your Life? &#8211; Clayton Christensen, James Allworth, Karen Dillon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-will-you-measure-your-life-clayton-christensen-james-allworth-karen-dillon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-will-you-measure-your-life-clayton-christensen-james-allworth-karen-dillon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How do you lead a fulfilling life? That profound question animates this book of inspiration and insight from world-class business strategist and bestselling author of The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma, Clayton Christensen. After beating a heart attack, advanced-stage cancer and a stroke in three successive years, the world-renowned innovation expert and author of one of the best [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-will-you-measure-your-life-clayton-christensen-james-allworth-karen-dillon-abridged/">How Will You Measure Your Life? &#8211; Clayton Christensen, James Allworth, Karen Dillon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do you lead a fulfilling life? That profound question animates this book of inspiration and insight from world-class business strategist and bestselling author of The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma, Clayton Christensen.    </p>
<p>                              After beating a heart attack, advanced-stage cancer and a stroke in three successive years, the world-renowned innovation expert and author of one of the best selling and most influential business books of all time &#8211; The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma &#8211; Clayton M. Christensen delivered a short but powerful speech to the Harvard Business School graduating class. He presented a set of personal guidelines that have helped him find meaning and happiness in his life &#8211; a challenge even the brightest and most motivated of students find daunting.    </p>
<p>                              Akin to The Last Lecture in its revelatory perspective following life-altering events, that speech subsequently became a hugely popular article in the Harvard Business Review and is now a groundbreaking book, putting forth a series of questions and models for success that have long been applied in the world of business, but also can be used to find cogent answers to pressing life questions: How can I be sure that I&#8217;ll find satisfaction in my career? How can I be sure that my relationships with my spouse, my family and my close friends become enduring sources of happiness? How can I avoid compromising my integrity (and stay out of jail)?    </p>
<p>                              How Will You Measure Your Life? is a highly original, surprising book from a singular business figure. It&#8217;s a book sure to inspire and educate readers &#8211; companies and individuals, students of business, mid-career professionals, and even parents &#8211; the world over.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-will-you-measure-your-life-clayton-christensen-james-allworth-karen-dillon-abridged/">How Will You Measure Your Life? &#8211; Clayton Christensen, James Allworth, Karen Dillon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Obedience to Authority : An Experimental View &#8211; Stanley Milgram (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/obedience-to-authority-an-experimental-view-stanley-milgram-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Experimental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/obedience-to-authority-an-experimental-view-stanley-milgram-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the 1960s, Stanley Milgram carried out a series of experiments in which human subjects were given progressively more painful electro-shocks in a careful calibrated series to determine to what extent people will obey orders even when they knew them to be painful and immoral &#8211; to determine how people will obey authority regardless of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/obedience-to-authority-an-experimental-view-stanley-milgram-abridged/">Obedience to Authority : An Experimental View &#8211; Stanley Milgram (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the 1960s, Stanley Milgram carried out a series of experiments in which human subjects were given progressively more painful electro-shocks in a careful calibrated series to determine to what extent people will obey orders even when they knew them to be painful and immoral &#8211; to determine how people will obey authority regardless of consequences. These experiments came under heavy criticism at the time but have ultimately been vindicated by the scientific community. This book is Milgram&#8217;s vivid and persuasive explanation of his methods.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/obedience-to-authority-an-experimental-view-stanley-milgram-abridged/">Obedience to Authority : An Experimental View &#8211; Stanley Milgram (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Enhance your copywriting skills with psychology-driven techniques to create stand out copy that taps into consumer decision making and sells, using this second edition of the ultimate copywriting survival guide for the 21st century &#8211; essential to every marketing or creative professional&#8217;s bookshelf. With many professionals now developing their skills on the job, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/">Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enhance your copywriting skills with psychology-driven techniques to create stand out copy that taps into consumer decision making and sells, using this second edition of the ultimate copywriting survival guide for the 21st century &#8211; essential to every marketing or creative professional&#8217;s bookshelf.    </p>
<p>                    With many professionals now developing their skills on the job, it is notoriously difficult to benchmark successful copy. This book provides a step up for those who already know the basics of writing copy, and are seeking more advanced, psychology-driven techniques to gain the competitive edge. With practical insight into human decision making and consumer engagement, it will inspire the clear-cut confidence needed to create, quantify, and sell stand out copy in a cluttered marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    Complementing the &#8216;how to&#8217; perspective of copywriting, with impressive interviews from leading ad agencies and copywriters across the globe, this second edition addresses the everyday issues faced in a multitude of roles, including:    </p>
<p>                    -Practical advice to measure and benchmark effective copy<br />
                    -Guidance on creating and critiquing briefs<br />
                    -New chapters on how to weave copywriting skills into the wider industry<br />
                    -Storytelling and content marketing<br />
                    -The impact of evolving channels like mobile and social media    </p>
<p>                    Practical, inspiring and extremely digestible, Persuasive Copywriting is the only vibrant, all-encompassing guide to copywriting that you need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/">Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joy on Demand : The Art of Discovering the Happiness Within &#8211; Chade-Meng Tan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/joy-on-demand-the-art-of-discovering-the-happiness-within-chade-meng-tan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/joy-on-demand-the-art-of-discovering-the-happiness-within-chade-meng-tan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A long-awaited follow-up to the New York Times bestselling Search Inside Yourself shows us how to cultivate joy within the context of our fast-paced lives and explains why it is critical to creativity, innovation, confidence, and ultimately success in every arena. In Joy on Demand, Chade-Meng Tan shows that you don&#8217;t need to meditate for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-on-demand-the-art-of-discovering-the-happiness-within-chade-meng-tan-abridged/">Joy on Demand : The Art of Discovering the Happiness Within &#8211; Chade-Meng Tan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A long-awaited follow-up to the New York Times bestselling Search Inside Yourself shows us how to cultivate joy within the context of our fast-paced lives and explains why it is critical to creativity, innovation, confidence, and ultimately success in every arena.  In Joy on Demand, Chade-Meng Tan shows that you don&#8217;t need to meditate for hours, days, months or years to achieve lasting joy-you can actually get consistent access to it in as little as fifteen seconds. Explaining joy and meditation as complementary things that naturally reinforce each other, Meng explains how these two skills form a virtuous cycle, and once put into motion, become a solid practice that can be sustained in daily life.  For many years, meditation has been taught and practiced in cultures where almost all meditators practice full-time for years, resulting in training programs optimized for practitioners with lots of free time and not much else to do but develop profound mastery over the mind.<br />
                    Seeing a disconnect between the traditional practice and the modern world, the bestselling author and Google&#8217;s &#8220;Jolly Good Fellow&#8221; has developed a program, through &#8220;wise laziness,&#8221; to help readers meditate more efficiently and effectively. Meng shares the three pillars of joy (inner peace, insight, and happiness), why joy is the secret is to success, and demonstrates the practical tools anyone can use to cultivate it on demand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-on-demand-the-art-of-discovering-the-happiness-within-chade-meng-tan-abridged/">Joy on Demand : The Art of Discovering the Happiness Within &#8211; Chade-Meng Tan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
