<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Islamic Worship Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/islamic-worship/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/islamic-worship/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Islamic Worship Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/islamic-worship/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</title>
		<link>/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Worship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Koran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Slavery & Abolition Of Slavery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when authorities you venerate condone something you know is wrong? Every major religion and philosophy once condoned or approved of slavery, but in modern times nothing is seen as more evil. Americans confront this crisis of authority when they erect statues of Founding Fathers who slept with their slaves. And Muslims faced it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/">Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when authorities you venerate condone something you know is wrong?</p>
<p>                    Every major religion and philosophy once condoned or approved of slavery, but in modern times nothing is seen as more evil. Americans confront this crisis of authority when they erect statues of Founding Fathers who slept with their slaves. And Muslims faced it when ISIS revived sex slavery, justifying it with verses from the Quran and the practice of Muhammad.</p>
<p>                    Exploring the moral and ultimately theological problem of slavery, Jonathan A.C. Brown traces how the Christian, Jewish and Islamic traditions have tried to reconcile modern moral certainties with the infallibility of God&#8217;s message. He lays out how Islam viewed slavery in theory, and the reality of how it was practiced across Islamic civilization. Finally, Brown carefully examines arguments put forward by Muslims for the abolition of slavery.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/">Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secrets of Divine Love : A Spiritual Journey into the Heart of Islam &#8211; A Helwa</title>
		<link>/secrets-of-divine-love-a-spiritual-journey-into-the-heart-of-islam-a-helwa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Theology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Worship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Koran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/secrets-of-divine-love-a-spiritual-journey-into-the-heart-of-islam-a-helwa/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you longing to experience a more intimate and loving relationship with the Divine? Secrets of Divine Love draws upon spiritual secrets of the Qur&#8217;an, ancient mystical poetry, and stories from the world&#8217;s greatest prophets and spiritual masters to help you reignite your faith, overcome your doubts, and deepen your connection with God. Through the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-divine-love-a-spiritual-journey-into-the-heart-of-islam-a-helwa/">Secrets of Divine Love : A Spiritual Journey into the Heart of Islam &#8211; A Helwa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you longing to experience a more intimate and loving relationship with the Divine?     </p>
<p>                    Secrets of Divine Love draws upon spiritual secrets of the Qur&#8217;an, ancient mystical poetry, and stories from the world&#8217;s greatest prophets and spiritual masters to help you reignite your faith, overcome your doubts, and deepen your connection with God.    </p>
<p>                    Through the use of scientific evidence, practical exercises, and guided meditations, you will develop the tools and awareness needed to discern and overcome your negative inner critic that prevents you from experiencing God&#8217;s all-encompassing love.    </p>
<p>                    The passages in this book serve as a compass and guiding light that returns you to the source of divine peace and surrender. Through the principles and practices of Islam, you will learn how to unlock your spiritual potential and unveil your divine purpose. Secrets of Divine Love uses a rational, yet heart-based approach towards the Qur&#8217;an that not only enlightens the mind, but inspires the soul towards deeper intimacy with God.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-divine-love-a-spiritual-journey-into-the-heart-of-islam-a-helwa/">Secrets of Divine Love : A Spiritual Journey into the Heart of Islam &#8211; A Helwa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
