<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Historical Romance Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/historical-romance/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/historical-romance/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Historical Romance Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/historical-romance/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Regency Gold &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/regency-gold-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/regency-gold-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From beloved historical romance author Marion Chesney comes the second installment in the Regency Intrigue series. With little to live on but her romantic daydreams&#8211;which frequently starred the dashing Marquess of Fleetwater&#8211;Jean Lindsay lived a rather dismal life with her nasty, drunken uncle. Jean was always the object of ridicule, that is, until news of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/regency-gold-m-c-beaton/">Regency Gold &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From beloved historical romance author Marion Chesney comes the second installment in the Regency Intrigue series.    </p>
<p>                    With little to live on but her romantic daydreams&#8211;which frequently starred the dashing Marquess of Fleetwater&#8211;Jean Lindsay lived a rather dismal life with her nasty, drunken uncle.    </p>
<p>                    Jean was always the object of ridicule, that is, until news of her unexpected inheritance spread. Suddenly her worn dresses became quaint and her forthright manner turned magically to charming, but to Jean&#8217;s horror, someone wanted her dead!    </p>
<p>                    With the marquess nearby to save her pretty neck, Jean felt quite safe &#8230; and quite smitten. As for her hero &#8230; how had an unsophisticated child from a Scottish manse turned his head and his heart askew?    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/regency-gold-m-c-beaton/">Regency Gold &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</title>
		<link>/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD *************************** Memphis, Tennessee, 1939 Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story </p>
<p>                    OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD</p>
<p>                    THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD</p>
<p>                    ***************************</p>
<p>                    Memphis, Tennessee, 1939</p>
<p>                    Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. But when their father must rush their mother to the hospital one stormy night, Rill is left in charge, until strangers arrive in force. Wrenched from all that is familiar and thrown into a Tennessee Children&#8217;s Home Society orphanage, the Foss children are assured that they will soon be returned to their parents &#8211; but they quickly realize the dark truth&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Aiken, South Carolina, present day</p>
<p>                    Born into wealth and privilege, Avery Stafford seems to have it all: a successful career, a handsome fiance, and a lavish wedding on the horizon. But when Avery returns home to help her father weather a health crisis, a chance encounter leaves her with uncomfortable questions and compels her to take a journey through her family&#8217;s long-hidden history, on a path that will ultimately lead either to devastation or to redemption.</p>
<p>                    *********************</p>
<p>                    Based on one of America&#8217;s most notorious real-life scandals, in which Georgia Tann, director of a Memphis-based adoption organization, kidnapped and sold poor children to wealthy families all over the country, Before We Were Yours is a riveting, wrenching and ultimately uplifting global bestseller. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A tale of enduring power&#8217; Paula McLain</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is impossible not to get swept up in this near-perfect novel&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Girl With a Pearl Earring &#8211; Tracy Chevalier</title>
		<link>/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OVER FIVE MILLION COPIES SOLD WORLDWIDE &#8216;A phenomenon&#8217; Jessie Burton &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Truly magical&#8217; Guardian Those eyes are fixed on someone. But who? What is she thinking as she stares out from one of the world&#8217;s best-loved paintings? Johannes Vermeer can spot exceptional beauty. When servant girl Griet catches his eye, she soon becomes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/">Girl With a Pearl Earring &#8211; Tracy Chevalier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OVER FIVE MILLION COPIES SOLD WORLDWIDE</p>
<p>                                &#8216;A phenomenon&#8217; Jessie Burton</p>
<p>                                &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                                &#8216;Truly magical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                              Those eyes are fixed on someone. But who? What is she thinking as she stares out from one of the world&#8217;s best-loved paintings?</p>
<p>                              Johannes Vermeer can spot exceptional beauty. When servant girl Griet catches his eye, she soon becomes both student and muse. But then he gives her his wife&#8217;s pearl earrings to wear for a portrait, and a scandal erupts that could threaten Griet&#8217;s future&#8230;</p>
<p>                                Vivid and captivating, this timeless modern classic has become a successful film and an international bestseller, with over 5 million copies sold around the world; now with a new introduction by the author.</p>
<p>                              &#8216;A veritable work of art&#8230; one of those rare novels where all the decisions made by the author appear inevitable and right&#8217; Rose Tremain</p>
<p>                              &#8216;Timeless, delicate and as exquisitely measured as one of Vermeer&#8217;s paintings. Tense yet perfectly-paced and filled with the beauty of life&#8217;s colours, Girl with the Pearl Earring is a masterpiece in its own right. Just a phenomenon. I will hold this novel close for the rest of my life&#8217; Jessie Burton, author of The Minaturist</p>
<p>                              &#8216;If ever a novel rightly deserves its &#8220;five millions copies sold&#8221; achievement, it is this dazzling little masterpiece &#8230; Absolute magic&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                              &#8216;A portrait of radiance&#8230;Tracy Chevalier brings the real artist Vermeer and a fictional muse to life in a jewel of a novel&#8217; Time</p>
<p>                              &#8216;Chevalier doesn&#8217;t put a foot wrong in this triumphant work &#8230; It is a beautifully written tale that mirrors the elegance of the painting that inspired it&#8217; Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>                              &#8216;A wonderful novel, mysterious, steeped in atmosphere, deeply revealing about the process of painting&#8230;truly magical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                              &#8216;It is no wonder that this beautifully-written story has sold more than five million copies and been made into a successful film. An absolute triumph&#8217; Woman&#8217;s Weekly</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/">Girl With a Pearl Earring &#8211; Tracy Chevalier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Enchantress &#8211; May McGoldrick</title>
		<link>/the-enchantress-may-mcgoldrick/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-enchantress-may-mcgoldrick/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Beginning with The Dreamer, May McGoldrick&#8217;s Highland Treasure Trilogy captures the lives and loves of three Scottish sisters. Now, meet Laura&#8230;The Enchantress&#8230;Fleeing persecution from the English king, the three Percy sisters scattered to different corners of Scotland. But when the level-headed Laura found herself abducted by the fearsome Laird of Blackfearn, all her well-made plans [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-enchantress-may-mcgoldrick/">The Enchantress &#8211; May McGoldrick</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Beginning with The Dreamer, May McGoldrick&#8217;s Highland Treasure Trilogy captures the lives and loves of three Scottish sisters. Now, meet Laura&#8230;The Enchantress&#8230;Fleeing persecution from the English king, the three Percy sisters scattered to different corners of Scotland. But when the level-headed Laura found herself abducted by the fearsome Laird of Blackfearn, all her well-made plans were torn asunder. His reckless and wild ways left Laura burning in his wake-and awakened in her a passion as untamed as his own&#8230;.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-enchantress-may-mcgoldrick/">The Enchantress &#8211; May McGoldrick</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Folly &#8211; M. C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/folly-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/folly-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The haughty Beverley family is obsessed with regaining Mannerling, the exquisite seventeenth-century mansion gambled away by their now-deceased father, Sir Beverley. Three of the six Beverley daughters have failed to win back their ancestral estate &#8211; settling for love matches over mere bricks and mortar. Now it is Rachel&#8217;s turn to woo the latest eligible [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/folly-m-c-beaton/">Folly &#8211; M. C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The haughty Beverley family is obsessed with regaining Mannerling, the exquisite seventeenth-century mansion gambled away by their now-deceased father, Sir Beverley. Three of the six Beverley daughters have failed to win back their ancestral estate &#8211; settling for love matches over mere bricks and mortar. Now it is Rachel&#8217;s turn to woo the latest eligible bachelor-in-residence, handsome widower Charles Blackwood.     </p>
<p>                    Yet her plan to win the autocratic Charles almost comes to naught: At their first meeting, Rachel forgets herself and admonishes Charles for neglecting his two small children. The antics of young Beth and Mark Blackwood successfully throw Charles and Rachel together, but does Rachel love Charles for himself or for Mannerling?    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/folly-m-c-beaton/">Folly &#8211; M. C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Plain Jane &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/plain-jane-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/plain-jane-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The second book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming A House for the Season series. It&#8217;s up to the servants of No. 67 Clarges Street to hatch a scheme&#8230; and arrange a match! &#8216;Oh, to be as beautiful as Euphemia!&#8217; sighs plain Jane Hart when she joins her sister at No.67 for the Season, as then Lord [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/plain-jane-m-c-beaton/">Plain Jane &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The second book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming A House for the Season series. </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s up to the servants of No. 67 Clarges Street to hatch a scheme&#8230; and arrange a match!</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Oh, to be as beautiful as Euphemia!&#8217; sighs plain Jane Hart when she joins her sister at No.67 for the Season, as then Lord Tregarthan might notice her&#8230; as she has noticed him and forever lost her heart.  </p>
<p>                    And while it is Euphemia&#8217;s fate to flit her way through balls and into the arms of a marquis, Jane&#8217;s is to stay at home&#8230; until the Downstairs staff transform the plain Miss into the Season&#8217;s sensation and send her waltzing into a daring liaison with the man of her dreams</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/plain-jane-m-c-beaton/">Plain Jane &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lady Fortescue Steps Out &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/lady-fortescue-steps-out-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lady-fortescue-steps-out-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Poor Relation series. What do you do if you are of noble stock, but impoverished, and living in London with a certain style to maintain? One has to work&#8230; but One&#8217;s relatives will be appalled when One turns One&#8217;s hand to trade &#8211; and opens a hotel, The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lady-fortescue-steps-out-m-c-beaton/">Lady Fortescue Steps Out &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Poor Relation series. </p>
<p>                    What do you do if you are of noble stock, but impoverished, and living in London with a certain style to maintain?  </p>
<p>                    One has to work&#8230;  but One&#8217;s relatives will be appalled when One turns One&#8217;s hand to trade &#8211; and opens a hotel, The Poor Relation, offering employment to others of the same social standing and in the same awkward situation.   This is precisely what Mrs Fortescue decides upon and, together with friend Colonel Sandhurst, transforms her decrepit Bond Street home into a posh hotel, offering guests the pleasure of being waited upon by the nobility.  </p>
<p>                    So with the help of other down-and-out aristocrats  they do just that &#8211; and London&#8217;s newest, and most fashionable! &#8211; hotel is born&#8230; much to the dismay of the Duke of Rowcester, Lady Fortescue&#8217;s nephew, who is convinced his aunt&#8217;s foray into trade will denigrate the illustrious family name!</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lady-fortescue-steps-out-m-c-beaton/">Lady Fortescue Steps Out &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Original Miss Honeyford &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-original-miss-honeyford-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-original-miss-honeyford-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Miss Honeyford was sour on romance, but she had been duly dispatched to London to save the family fortune by hunting forand securinga wealthy husband and thereby proving her role as a loving, if not entirely dutiful, daughter. Honoraria obeyed. But if she was reluctantly willing to surrender her hand, this beautiful young lady who [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-original-miss-honeyford-m-c-beaton/">The Original Miss Honeyford &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miss Honeyford was sour on romance, but she had been duly dispatched to London to save the family fortune by hunting forand securinga wealthy husband and thereby proving her role as a loving, if not entirely dutiful, daughter. Honoraria obeyed. But if she was reluctantly willing to surrender her hand, this beautiful young lady who could ride, shoot, and argue with any man was not about to lose her head or her heart to any of the dismal cads and lads of the marriage mart.     </p>
<p>                    First she met the arrogantly attractive Lord Alistair Stewart, who treated her infuriatingly like a little girl. And then she met the skillfully seductive Lord Channington, who treated her intoxicatingly like the desirable full-grown woman that she was. But now that she had a choice, which role would she choose and just how much risk was she willing to run?    </p>
<p>                    The Regency series brings us heroines of style, grace, and determinationwomen who are not afraid to use their smarts to seek the stature or standing they feel they need. They may come from humble beginnings or not, but what these heroines share is an unmatched determination that leaves us turning page after page as we follow them in their dance.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-original-miss-honeyford-m-c-beaton/">The Original Miss Honeyford &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deborah Goes to Dover &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/deborah-goes-to-dover-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deborah-goes-to-dover-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fifth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. The engaging Miss Hannah Pym delights all as she resumes her matchmaking adventures aboard the English stage &#8211; when lonely hearts chance across her intrepid path they&#8217;re sure to find themselves en route for romance! Destined for Dover, Miss Pym has her matchmaking work cut [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deborah-goes-to-dover-m-c-beaton/">Deborah Goes to Dover &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fifth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. </p>
<p>                    The engaging Miss Hannah Pym delights all as she resumes her matchmaking adventures aboard the English stage &#8211; when lonely hearts chance across her intrepid path they&#8217;re sure to find themselves en route for romance!</p>
<p>                    Destined for Dover, Miss Pym has her matchmaking work cut out for her when she encounters the pretty but hoydenish Lady Deborah Western! Encouraged by an unruly twin brother, the spirited, golden-haired Deborah seems set on dressing and acting the tomboy, much to the dismay of her handsome neighbor, the Earl of Ashton&#8230;</p>
<p>                    To Deb, the earl is a dull stick, always lecturing on the behavior of a proper lady. But her desire to fish, hunt, and ride astride is quickly replaced with more romantic notions when the tall, green-eyed earl challenges her to a horse race and wins himself an unforgettable kiss. </p>
<p>                    Miss Pym can&#8217;t resist the opportunity to match-make, and with the help of her clever maneuverings, Lady Deborah will soon be well and truly matched &#8211; perhaps even to the earl himself!</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deborah-goes-to-dover-m-c-beaton/">Deborah Goes to Dover &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Romance &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/romance-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/romance-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As one of the two remaining unmarried Beverley sisters, Belinda considers herself the last hope for Mannerling, the beloved estate gambled away by their father. Each of her four elder sisters had hoped&#8211;even schemed&#8211;to marry one of Mannerling&#8217;s successive owners. But all had chosen true love over their ancestral home. Practical and duty-bound, Belinda will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/romance-m-c-beaton/">Romance &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As one of the two remaining unmarried Beverley sisters, Belinda considers herself the last hope for Mannerling, the beloved estate gambled away by their father. Each of her four elder sisters had hoped&#8211;even schemed&#8211;to marry one of Mannerling&#8217;s successive owners. But all had chosen true love over their ancestral home.    </p>
<p>                    Practical and duty-bound, Belinda will woo and wed Lord St. Clair, current holder of the estate. True, he is a silly fop, hardly what she desires in a husband, but she vows to make the man love her&#8211;even at the expense of her own happiness.    </p>
<p>                    However, dashing Lord Gyre can hardly ignore the ridiculous drama &#8212; Belinda is far too good for that dandy St. Clair. Therefore, his lordship decides it is his duty to win the lovely Belinda&#8217;s heart!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/romance-m-c-beaton/">Romance &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Flirt &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-flirt-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-flirt-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If I could have foreseen the future, I would have married the first man who asked me! Tongues were set wagging when Elizabeth Markham&#8217;s glamorous young parents were killed, sinking their only child to the unspeakable class of poor relation. Forced to live with her cruel, miserly uncle Julius, Elizabeth is forbidden to partake in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-flirt-m-c-beaton/">The Flirt &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If I could have foreseen the future, I would have married the first man who asked me!    </p>
<p>                    Tongues were set wagging when Elizabeth Markham&#8217;s glamorous young parents were killed, sinking their only child to the unspeakable class of poor relation. Forced to live with her cruel, miserly uncle Julius, Elizabeth is forbidden to partake in the season&#8217;s festivities. Marriage is her only escape, and she enacts a daring plan to trick her way into the Duke of Dunster&#8217;s exclusive house party, to snare one of the eligible dandies sure to dance attendance on her.    </p>
<p>                    Her plan proceeds swimmingly, as Elizabeth flirts with all but the arrogant Lord Charles Lufford, considered to be quite a catch. She ignores him thoroughly until her uncle discovers her deception and Charles saves her&#8211;by announcing their engagement!    </p>
<p>                    But Elizabeth&#8217;s troubles are far from over, for in her absence she had come into an inheritance. And her uncle, along with one other sinister party would rather see her perish than receive it.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-flirt-m-c-beaton/">The Flirt &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wicked Godmother &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-wicked-godmother-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wicked-godmother-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The third book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming A House for the Season series. It&#8217;s double trouble for poor, put-upon Harriet! Lovely but penniless Harriet Metcalf is horrified when she is named in a nobleman&#8217;s will as guardian of his two ghastly and snobbish twin daughters. The innocent Harriet doesn&#8217;t feel wily enough to cope with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wicked-godmother-m-c-beaton/">The Wicked Godmother &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The third book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming A House for the Season series. </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s double trouble for poor, put-upon Harriet!</p>
<p>                    Lovely but penniless Harriet Metcalf is horrified when she is named in a nobleman&#8217;s will as guardian of his two ghastly and snobbish twin daughters.  The innocent Harriet doesn&#8217;t feel wily enough to cope with the intricacies of the London Season &#8211; not to mention two of its most eligible bachelors, the Marquis of Huntington and Lord Vere.</p>
<p>                    Harriet views them only as suitors for the twins, while the gentlemen see only Harriet&#8217;s charms.  And soon she finds herself falling for one of them&#8230; but a cruel betrayal will be her ruin unless the Clarges Street servants can save her honour, while she loses her heart!</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wicked-godmother-m-c-beaton/">The Wicked Godmother &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sweet Masquerade &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/sweet-masquerade-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sweet-masquerade-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The tenth Earl of Berham does not know what to do. An attractive thirty-two-year-old bachelor, he has been appointed guardian of the young Freddie Armstrong, the eighteen-year-old grandson of his late father&#8217;s dear friend. That&#8217;s bad enough. Then he discovers that the boy is really a girl! It is against all convention and against his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sweet-masquerade-m-c-beaton/">Sweet Masquerade &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The tenth Earl of Berham does not know what to do. An attractive thirty-two-year-old bachelor, he has been appointed guardian of the young Freddie Armstrong, the eighteen-year-old grandson of his late father&#8217;s dear friend. That&#8217;s bad enough. Then he discovers that the boy is really a girl! It is against all convention and against his personal code to keep a young lady concealed in his own home. He must find a solution.    </p>
<p>                    The earl&#8217;s frequent visitor, Lady Clarissa Rennenord, heartily agrees&#8211;but for less noble reasons. Lady Clarissa hopes to snare the earl in marriage and does not want any competition. She recommends that Freddie be sent to a seminary. No one but Lady Rennenord knows what a horrid place it is&#8211;and no one, including Lady Rennenord, expects Freddie to escape. Now Freddie is back, and the earl finds her presence unsettling in more ways than one.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sweet-masquerade-m-c-beaton/">Sweet Masquerade &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Education of Miss Patterson Lib/E &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-education-of-miss-patterson-lib-e-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-education-of-miss-patterson-lib-e-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For lovely young Miss Patricia Patterson, life seemed a delightful dream until the specter of her guardian, Lord Charles Gaunt, cast a shadow over her carefree days of idleness and enchanting evenings of dazzling balls and delicious flirtations. Lord Charles demanded she act the part of a proper and perfectly boring young miss. Even worse, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-miss-patterson-lib-e-m-c-beaton/">The Education of Miss Patterson Lib/E &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For lovely young Miss Patricia Patterson, life seemed a delightful dream until the specter of her guardian, Lord Charles Gaunt, cast a shadow over her carefree days of idleness and enchanting evenings of dazzling balls and delicious flirtations. Lord Charles demanded she act the part of a proper and perfectly boring young miss. Even worse, he insisted she devote her waking hours to cultivating her mind rather than captivating her swarm of admirers. Thus, the battle was joined between the handsome, arrogant aristocrat who had Patricia in his lawful power, and Patricia, who vowed to turn this hateful tyrant into her lovelorn slave.&#8221;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-miss-patterson-lib-e-m-c-beaton/">The Education of Miss Patterson Lib/E &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Back in Society &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/back-in-society-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/back-in-society-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Life is finally looking up for the poor relations. The Prince of Wales&#8217; coat of arms gleams over the hotel entrance. All but one of the rooms are filled by the open-handed Prince Hugo and his entourage. The owners have taken on a new partner, Mr. Jason Davy, a popular actor. Even curmudgeonly Sir Philip [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-in-society-m-c-beaton/">Back in Society &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Life is finally looking up for the poor relations. The Prince of Wales&#8217; coat of arms gleams over the hotel entrance. All but one of the rooms are filled by the open-handed Prince Hugo and his entourage. The owners have taken on a new partner, Mr. Jason Davy, a popular actor. Even curmudgeonly Sir Philip hasn&#8217;t uttered anything loathsome for days. They have finally reached a position comfortable enough to allow them to consider offers to buy the hotel.    </p>
<p>                    The poor relations&#8217; hard-earned success, however, is in stark contrast to the plight of their latest guest, Lady Jane Fremney. The slight, beautiful youngest daughter of the Earl of Durby has been cast out of her family for refusing to marry the man her father has chosen. Lonely and bankrupt, Lady Jane has decided to commit suicide. But when Miss Tonks uncovers her plans, the poor relations go into action again to rescue Lady Jane from suicide, her father, and her intended husband.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-in-society-m-c-beaton/">Back in Society &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beatrice Goes to Brighton &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/beatrice-goes-to-brighton-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beatrice-goes-to-brighton-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fourth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. The unsinkable Miss Pym returns to the English stagecoach in search of adventure and troubled hearts, and with her delightful schemes and discerning eye, she never fails to strike a match by journey&#8217;s end. Lady Beatrice Marsham is in quite a coil. No sooner is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beatrice-goes-to-brighton-m-c-beaton/">Beatrice Goes to Brighton &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fourth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. The unsinkable Miss Pym returns to the English stagecoach in search of adventure and troubled hearts, and with her delightful schemes and discerning eye, she never fails to strike a match by journey&#8217;s end.  Lady Beatrice Marsham is in quite a coil. No sooner is she widowed from a brutish gambling husband, than her heartless family is forcing her into another horrid marriage. Fleeing by stagecoach to the Brighton seaside, the proud beauty meets Miss Hannah Pym, who is determined to find her a proper match.  The handsome and kind Lord Alistair Munro would be perfect. Unfortunately, he is convinced of the ton gossip that proclaims Lady Beatrice a cruel flirt. Miss Pym, however, is not worried. The lady&#8217;s hard heart has softened much since coming to Brighton. and though Lord Alistair disapproves of the old Lady Beatrice, by Miss Pym&#8217;s clever design, he is sure to fall in love with the new and improved model&#8230;&#8217;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist  &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beatrice-goes-to-brighton-m-c-beaton/">Beatrice Goes to Brighton &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Banishment &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/banishment-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/banishment-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Isabella Beverley is blessed with unparalleled beauty but, unfortunately, has been raised in the most snobbish and haughty of families. And when her father gambles away their fortune &#8211; including Mannerling, the exquisite family mansion, Isabella discovers that there is very little sympathy for her plight. As the eldest, Isabella is chosen to court Mr. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/banishment-m-c-beaton/">Banishment &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Isabella Beverley is blessed with unparalleled beauty but, unfortunately, has been raised in the most snobbish and haughty of families. And when her father gambles away their fortune &#8211; including Mannerling, the exquisite family mansion, Isabella discovers that there is very little sympathy for her plight.<br />
                    As the eldest, Isabella is chosen to court Mr. Judd, the roguish bachelor who won Mannerling. Surely no sacrifice is too great to regain Mannerling? But tempting her away from Mr. Judd is Lord Fitzpatrick, an Irish rake who fears Isabella can never love a man as she does her home &#8211; but is nonetheless determined to convince her to choose man over manse!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/banishment-m-c-beaton/">Banishment &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deirdre and Desire &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/deirdre-and-desire-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deirdre-and-desire-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Red-haired, jade-eyed Deirdre is determined to marry for Love &#8211; nothing else will do. So the fact her father&#8217;s candidate for her hand, Lord Harry Desire, is well bred and good looking, interests her not a jot! But the feelings he arouses in her are truly distracting. Deirdre&#8217;s discovery of what desire can mean and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deirdre-and-desire-m-c-beaton/">Deirdre and Desire &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Red-haired, jade-eyed Deirdre is determined to marry for Love &#8211; nothing else will do.  So the fact her father&#8217;s candidate for her hand, Lord Harry Desire, is well bred and good looking, interests her not a jot! But the feelings he arouses in her are truly distracting.    </p>
<p>                    Deirdre&#8217;s discovery of what desire can mean and where her heart really lies brings about a delicious climax to this adventure of intrigue, misunderstanding &#8211; and love!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deirdre-and-desire-m-c-beaton/">Deirdre and Desire &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Silken Bonds &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/silken-bonds-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/silken-bonds-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Modern notions were all well and good &#8211; but where did one find a man to share them? Though Frederica chafes at the restricted life she lives as the adopted daughter of an infamous bluestocking, she does agree with the philosophy: until men learn to appreciate women as intellectual equals, Frederica is better off without [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/silken-bonds-m-c-beaton/">Silken Bonds &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Modern notions were all well and good &#8211; but where did one find a man to share them?    </p>
<p>                    Though Frederica chafes at the restricted life she lives as the adopted daughter of an infamous bluestocking, she does agree with the philosophy: until men learn to appreciate women as intellectual equals, Frederica is better off without them!    </p>
<p>                    But her sister&#8217;s recent elopement sparks fires of romance in Frederica&#8217;s well-educated head. She is ripe to accept the considerable charms of Lord Harry Danger who saves her from a pack of drunken thugs &#8211; but if only he would treat her as an equal and stop all that silly flirting!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/silken-bonds-m-c-beaton/">Silken Bonds &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miss Tonks Turns to Crime &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/miss-tonks-turns-to-crime-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/miss-tonks-turns-to-crime-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One cannot live of dignity alone! The poor relations banded together some time ago to run The Poor Relation Hotel in the hope their embarrassed relatives would buy them out, but as the hotel prospered, so they began to enjoy the fruit of their labour. But once again they need money to go on and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/miss-tonks-turns-to-crime-m-c-beaton/">Miss Tonks Turns to Crime &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One cannot live of dignity alone!    </p>
<p>                    The poor relations banded together some time ago to run The Poor Relation Hotel in the hope their embarrassed relatives would buy them out, but as the hotel prospered, so they began to enjoy the fruit of their labour.    </p>
<p>                    But once again they need money to go on and so poor, faded Miss Tonks is dispatched to her rich sister to steal something valuable from her in order to keep the hotel on its feet.  All the other poor relations have their doubts about Miss Tonks&#8217; chances for success, but the shy spinster as more than a few surprises up her sleeve!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/miss-tonks-turns-to-crime-m-c-beaton/">Miss Tonks Turns to Crime &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Love Match &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-love-match-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-love-match-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>By day she champions women&#8217;s rights but by night she plots romance! No young lady can be more devoted to the teachings of the infamous blue stocking Mrs Waverley than Felicity, her adopted author. Yet Felicity leads a secret life: that of an author of a scandalous new novel &#8211; the tale of a lady [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-love-match-m-c-beaton/">The Love Match &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By day she champions women&#8217;s rights but by night she plots romance!     </p>
<p>                    No young lady can be more devoted to the teachings of the infamous blue stocking Mrs Waverley than Felicity, her adopted author.  Yet Felicity leads a secret life: that of an author of a scandalous new novel &#8211; the tale of a lady &#8220;rake&#8221; and her passionate exploits.     </p>
<p>                    Yet there is one titled gentleman who is intrigued with this mysterious, headstrong young woman who is taking Society by storm &#8212;  and Felicity  soon learns that real life is infinitely more interesting than fiction!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-love-match-m-c-beaton/">The Love Match &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Adventuress &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-adventuress-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-adventuress-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fifth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming A House for the Season series. Appearances can be very deceptive&#8230; At first, Emily Goodenough and her uncle are exactly what the servants at No. 67 Clarges Street are hoping for: respectable tenants to usher in an uneventful Season. But all is not what it seems and it&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-adventuress-m-c-beaton/">The Adventuress &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fifth book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming A House for the Season series. </p>
<p>                    Appearances can be very deceptive&#8230;</p>
<p>                    At first, Emily Goodenough and her uncle are exactly what the servants at No. 67 Clarges Street are hoping for: respectable tenants to usher in an uneventful Season.  But all is not what it seems and it&#8217;s not long before Rainbird the butler uncovers their secret: Mr Goodenough is an ex-butler and his &#8216;daughter&#8217; a runaway chambermaid!</p>
<p>                    Rainbird&#8217;s resolve is tested, however, when he learns of villainous Mr Percival Pardon&#8217;s plot to unmask the pair and force his attentions on Emily. So the staff join forces with their former fellow servants in a scheme to make the Goodenoughs Society&#8217;s darlings, foil Mr Pardon&#8217;s plot, and snare the man of her dreams for Emily in the bargain!</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-adventuress-m-c-beaton/">The Adventuress &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Intrigue &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/intrigue-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/intrigue-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As scandal and intrigue swirl around her, Jessica must discover where the heart finds true happiness. . . . Mannerling, the splendid family estate gambled away by Sir Beverley, remains the passion of his daughters. Beverley himself has died; the eldest daughter, Isabella -having failed in her bid to reclaim the family home&#8211;is blissfully wed. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intrigue-m-c-beaton/">Intrigue &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As scandal and intrigue swirl around her, Jessica must discover where the heart finds true happiness. . . .    </p>
<p>                    Mannerling, the splendid family estate gambled away by Sir Beverley, remains the passion of his daughters. Beverley himself has died; the eldest daughter, Isabella -having failed in her bid to reclaim the family home&#8211;is blissfully wed. The mantle of saviour now falls to the next eldest daughter, Jessica.    </p>
<p>                    How fortunate then that the new owner of Mannerling had a marriageable son. In truth, Harry is a brutal letch, a drunkard, and a wastrel, but Jessica, blinded by determination, vows to secure a betrothal. She is barely aware of the attentions of handsome, charming Professor Robert Sommerville, whose affection for Jessica is equalled only by the fear that her obsession to secure Mannerling will lead to disaster for all concerned.<br />
                    As scandal and intrigue swirl around her, Jessica must discover where the heart finds true happiness. . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intrigue-m-c-beaton/">Intrigue &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Scandalous Lady Wright &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-scandalous-lady-wright-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-scandalous-lady-wright-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fashionable society regards Sir Benjamin Wright with the utmost honour and respect. Yet Lady Emma knows that her husband is, in fact, a drunken jealous brute who delights in humiliating her both in and out of the bedroom. So, his unexpected murder is a blessing, she thinks &#8211; that is, until the constable&#8217;s accusing finger [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-scandalous-lady-wright-m-c-beaton/">The Scandalous Lady Wright &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fashionable society regards Sir Benjamin Wright with the utmost honour and respect. Yet Lady Emma knows that her husband is, in fact, a drunken jealous brute who delights in humiliating her both in and out of the bedroom.    </p>
<p>                    So, his unexpected murder is a blessing, she thinks &#8211; that is, until the constable&#8217;s accusing finger points to her as the murderer. But it soon becomes apparent that her late husband hid many secrets and enemies.    </p>
<p>                    When the practical Comte Saint-Juste arrives on the scene offering his services, Lady Emma is about to discover what the French dedication to l&#8217;amour really means&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-scandalous-lady-wright-m-c-beaton/">The Scandalous Lady Wright &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Perfect Gentleman &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-perfect-gentleman-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-perfect-gentleman-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the prolific M. C. Beaton, a Regency romance where love flourishes in the most unexpected places From the top of his flawlessly groomed head to the waxed tips of his fashionable shoes, Lord Andrew Childe was every inch the perfect gentleman. But Andrew&#8217;s arrogant composure was almost always shattered by the impertinent Penelope Mortimer, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-perfect-gentleman-m-c-beaton/">The Perfect Gentleman &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the prolific M. C. Beaton, a Regency romance where love flourishes in the most unexpected places    </p>
<p>                    From the top of his flawlessly groomed head to the waxed tips of his fashionable shoes, Lord Andrew Childe was every inch the perfect gentleman. But Andrew&#8217;s arrogant composure was almost always shattered by the impertinent Penelope Mortimer, an achingly lovely country beauty who had a clear knack for ruffling his lordship&#8217;s feathers.    </p>
<p>                    Her nose for trouble seemed to land Lord Andrew in the most awkward situations&#8211;and love itself quickly became the most delicate of them all!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-perfect-gentleman-m-c-beaton/">The Perfect Gentleman &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The First Rebellion &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-first-rebellion-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-first-rebellion-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>His kiss has left her flushed and disconcerted &#8211; perhaps men are best avoided after all! The Earl of Tredair has had his fill of balls, routs, and silly misses, and he despairs of finding anyone out of the ordinary &#8211; that is, until he meets Miss Fanny Waverley. Most unique and intriguing, she and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-rebellion-m-c-beaton/">The First Rebellion &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>His kiss has left her flushed and disconcerted &#8211; perhaps men are best avoided after all!    </p>
<p>                    The Earl of Tredair has had his fill of balls, routs, and silly misses, and he despairs of finding anyone out of the ordinary &#8211; that is, until he meets Miss Fanny Waverley.    </p>
<p>                    Most unique and intriguing, she and her two sisters are the adopted daughters of the reclusive bluestocking Madame Waverley. They have been raised as her disciples to spread the word of women&#8217;s rights and to encourage poor oppressed females to stand up against the iniquities of the male sex.    </p>
<p>                    The beautiful Miss Fanny, however, finds it quite hard to think of all men as cruel and lustful beasts &#8211; how can she, when now she finds herself longing to kiss one of the most hated of the species!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-rebellion-m-c-beaton/">The First Rebellion &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Penelope Goes to Portsmouth &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/penelope-goes-to-portsmouth-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/penelope-goes-to-portsmouth-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The third book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. Kind-hearted Miss Hannah Pym is off to Portsmouth in the company of the beautiful but practical Miss Penelope Wilkins. Miss Pym quickly realises that Penelope needs someone to enliven her sheltered life, someone perhaps like their handsome travelling companion, Lord Augustus Railton. Penelope, however, thinks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/penelope-goes-to-portsmouth-m-c-beaton/">Penelope Goes to Portsmouth &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The third book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming Travelling Matchmaker series. Kind-hearted Miss Hannah Pym is off to Portsmouth in the company of the beautiful but practical Miss Penelope Wilkins. Miss Pym quickly realises that Penelope needs someone to enliven her sheltered life, someone perhaps like their handsome travelling companion, Lord Augustus Railton. Penelope, however, thinks Lord Augustus is a ne&#8217;er-do-well&#8230;Hannah&#8217;s hopes for adventure, on the other hand, are fulfilled when the coach happens upon a footman who faces hanging for a crime he didn&#8217;t commit.  &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist  &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/penelope-goes-to-portsmouth-m-c-beaton/">Penelope Goes to Portsmouth &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Dear Duchess &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/my-dear-duchess-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-dear-duchess-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Handsome, dashing Henry Wright, the Duke of Westerland, needed a wife in a desperately short period of time. If he could not find a wife, he would lose the legacy he so desperately desired. Young, lovely, but sheltered Miss Frederica Sayers needed a husband just as much as Henry Wright needed a wife, only she [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-dear-duchess-m-c-beaton/">My Dear Duchess &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Handsome, dashing Henry Wright, the Duke of Westerland, needed a wife in a desperately short period of time. If he could not find a wife, he would lose the legacy he so desperately desired.    </p>
<p>                    Young, lovely, but sheltered Miss Frederica Sayers needed a husband just as much as Henry Wright needed a wife, only she needed a husband to save her from the life of shame that almost certainly awaited her when she fled the callous cruelty of her family.    </p>
<p>                    Marriage between the dashing lord and this reckless runaway was clearly the answer for both of them&#8211;until the duke discovered he had a duchess he could not tame and the duchess found that she would rather lose her spotless reputation than lose the duke to another beautiful woman who was everything she was not.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-dear-duchess-m-c-beaton/">My Dear Duchess &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Miser of Mayfair &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-miser-of-mayfair-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-miser-of-mayfair-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming A House for the Season series. Is Number 67 Clarges Steet the unluckiest house in Mayfair? Every Season the beaux mondes of the Regency would hire a house in the heart of London&#8217;s fashionable West End at a disproportionately high rent for often inferior accommodation and yet No.67 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miser-of-mayfair-m-c-beaton/">The Miser of Mayfair &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first book in M.C. Beaton&#8217;s charming A House for the Season series.</p>
<p>                    Is Number 67 Clarges Steet the unluckiest house in Mayfair?</p>
<p>                    Every Season the beaux mondes of the Regency would hire a house in the heart of London&#8217;s fashionable West End at a disproportionately high rent for often inferior accommodation and yet No.67 Clarges Street, a town house complete with staff, remains vacant from year to year.  Could it be that it is associated with ill luck and even death?  Something must be done so that the servants of the house don&#8217;t lose their livelihood&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Salvation seems to come in the form of Roderick Sinclair who confirms he wishes to rent the house for the current Season.  The staff are overjoyed &#8211; until they find that Mr Sinclair is a terrible miser who is planning no parties.  Furthermore, his ward, Fiona, though a dazzling Highland beauty, does not seem to possess one bright idea in her head.  But it is Rainbird, No.67&#8217;s clever and elegant butler, who sees through her facade and resolves to help his mysterious mistress in whatever way he can&#8230;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Romance fans are in for a treat&#8217; &#8211; Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;[M. C. Beaton] is the best of the Regency writers&#8217; &#8211; Kirkus Reviews</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miser-of-mayfair-m-c-beaton/">The Miser of Mayfair &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sins Of Lady Dacey &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-sins-of-lady-dacey-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sins-of-lady-dacey-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The local society could only speculate how a pair of turtledoves would cope as the guests of the scandalous Lady Dacey. Surely she would attempt to corrupt them &#8211; an act that both Pamela Perryworth and Honoraria Goodham would see as welcome entertainment in their rigid, joyless lives. Though Mrs. Perryworth is married &#8211; most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sins-of-lady-dacey-m-c-beaton/">The Sins Of Lady Dacey &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The local society could only speculate how a pair of turtledoves would cope as the guests of the scandalous Lady Dacey. Surely she would attempt to corrupt them &#8211; an act that both Pamela Perryworth and Honoraria Goodham would see as welcome entertainment in their rigid, joyless lives.</p>
<p>Though Mrs. Perryworth is married &#8211; most unhappily &#8211; and the young Honoraria has a cloying tendency to read too much scripture, the purity and loveliness of both ladies nonetheless inflames the senses of two notorious lords. Mr. Sean Delaney loses his heart at first sight of the fair Mrs. Perryworth while the disreputable Duke of Ware is quite disturbed by the innocent Honoraria, who unknowingly dares to tempt his jaded heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sins-of-lady-dacey-m-c-beaton/">The Sins Of Lady Dacey &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Colonel Sandhurst to the Rescue &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/colonel-sandhurst-to-the-rescue-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/colonel-sandhurst-to-the-rescue-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A case of mistaken identity is transformed into a case of true love! As usual, the poor relations are in need of money to finance the hotel and this time it is up to Colonel Sandhurst to come to the rescue. After coming across Sir Randolph&#8217;s daughter Frederica, who is running away to escape an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/colonel-sandhurst-to-the-rescue-m-c-beaton/">Colonel Sandhurst to the Rescue &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A case of mistaken identity is transformed into a case of true love!    </p>
<p>                    As usual, the poor relations are in need of money to finance the hotel and this time it is up to Colonel Sandhurst to come to the rescue.  After coming across Sir Randolph&#8217;s daughter  Frederica, who is running away to escape an awful marriage to Lord Bewley, the Colonel devises a plan to force Sir Randolph to settle his six month outstanding hotel bill and save Frederica from her terrible fate.    </p>
<p>                    The clever plan is thwarted when Lord Bewley shows up at the drop point instead of Sir Randolph, and the poor relations must make a deal with Lord Bewley in order to get their money&#8230; and keep Colonel Sandhurst out of gaol!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/colonel-sandhurst-to-the-rescue-m-c-beaton/">Colonel Sandhurst to the Rescue &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Quadrille &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/quadrille-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/quadrille-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Love and jealousy abound in this playful romance, set during the British Regency. Everyone in the ton knew that Lord Hubert Challenge had married country mouse Mary Tyre for her dowry, but no one had yet guessed that Mary had actually fallen in love with her husband! And she was willing to try anything&#8211;sumptuous clothes, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/quadrille-m-c-beaton/">Quadrille &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Love and jealousy abound in this playful romance, set during the British Regency.     </p>
<p>                    Everyone in the ton knew that Lord Hubert Challenge had married country mouse Mary Tyre for her dowry, but no one had yet guessed that Mary had actually fallen in love with her husband! And she was willing to try anything&#8211;sumptuous clothes, a saucy manner, even flirting with another man&#8211;to get her handsome husband&#8217;s attention &#8230; until she learned that two could play at that particular game.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/quadrille-m-c-beaton/">Quadrille &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ghost And Lady Alice &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-ghost-and-lady-alice-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ghost-and-lady-alice-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ghost-and-lady-alice-m-c-beaton/">The Ghost And Lady Alice &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ghost-and-lady-alice-m-c-beaton/">The Ghost And Lady Alice &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>At the Sign of the Golden Pineapple &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/at-the-sign-of-the-golden-pineapple-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/at-the-sign-of-the-golden-pineapple-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I do not think I want to be married at all. I want to be rich. Very rich&#8230; When Henrietta Bascombe opens a confectionary shop in order to turn her pittance of an inheritance into a fortune, her friends are shocked to hear of such a well-bred lady going into trade. The Earl of Carrisdown [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/at-the-sign-of-the-golden-pineapple-m-c-beaton/">At the Sign of the Golden Pineapple &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I do not think I want to be married at all. I want to be rich. Very rich&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    When Henrietta Bascombe opens a confectionary shop in order to turn her pittance of an inheritance into a fortune, her friends are shocked to hear of such a well-bred lady going into trade. The Earl of Carrisdown is both drawn to and repelled by her shopgirl status. Undaunted, Henrietta proceeds to hang out the traditional confectioners&#8217; sign of a golden pineapple and soon finds a set of beautiful women in her employ, drawing the attention of the Earl of Carrisdown&#8217;s younger brother and best friend. Distressed by the situation, the earl makes it his mission to put Henrietta out of business. But he looks forward to tangling with the fiery sweetshop owner more than he&#8217;s willing to admit.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/at-the-sign-of-the-golden-pineapple-m-c-beaton/">At the Sign of the Golden Pineapple &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deception &#8211; M. C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/deception-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deception-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When one of her sisters is attacked by Harry Devers, the lecherous son of Mannerling&#8217;s present owner, Abigail Beverley puts her obsession with reclaiming the mansion on hold. Then Abigail meets the dashing and extremely eligible Lord Burfield, fresh back from the army and in full-time pursuit of a bride. Yet unexpected circumstances force the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deception-m-c-beaton/">Deception &#8211; M. C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When one of her sisters is attacked by Harry Devers, the lecherous son of Mannerling&#8217;s present owner, Abigail Beverley puts her obsession with reclaiming the mansion on hold. Then Abigail meets the dashing and extremely eligible Lord Burfield, fresh back from the army and in full-time pursuit of a bride.    </p>
<p>                    Yet unexpected circumstances force the insufferable Harry Devers to recuperate from a riding accident in the Beverley home, where Abigail&#8217;s twin sister Rachel nurses him back to health &#8211; and into betrothal. Stirred from its brief slumber, Abigail&#8217;s fury returns, alive and kicking. So when Rachel begins to have doubts about marrying Harry, Abigail devises a daring plan to win back Mannerling once and for all.    </p>
<p>                    But perhaps Abigail would be better off concentrating on Lord Burfield, lest he be snapped up by Prudence Makepeace!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deception-m-c-beaton/">Deception &#8211; M. C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Homecoming &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/homecoming-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/homecoming-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lizzie is the sixth and youngest daughter of the late Sir Beverley, the patriarch who gambled away their beloved estate, Mannerling. Each of Lizzie&#8217;s sisters had been entrusted by their ambitious mother to cast lures for the various owners of their former home. Instead, each one happily married for love. Now it&#8217;s Lizzie&#8217;s turn to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/homecoming-m-c-beaton/">Homecoming &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lizzie is the sixth and youngest daughter of the late Sir Beverley, the patriarch who gambled away their beloved estate, Mannerling. Each of Lizzie&#8217;s sisters had been entrusted by their ambitious mother to cast lures for the various owners of their former home. Instead, each one happily married for love. Now it&#8217;s Lizzie&#8217;s turn to save Mannerling.    </p>
<p>                    Yet the new owner, the Duke of Severnshire, is far too arrogant for Lizzie&#8217;s heart. And while the duke has no intentions toward the saucy chit, her curt dismissal of him is perplexing&#8211;for no woman has ever refused him! Now, as his lavish house party to select a bride becomes a whirlwind of mismatches and scandal, lovely Lizzie is turning the duke&#8217;s own thoughts away from a suitable marriage&#8211;to the wonders of falling in love!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/homecoming-m-c-beaton/">Homecoming &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mrs Budley Falls from Grace &#8211; M.C. Beaton</title>
		<link>/mrs-budley-falls-from-grace-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mrs-budley-falls-from-grace-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Another Poor Relation has to resort to genteel thievery to make end meet &#8211; but she gets much more than she bargains for! Cut off by her own relations, pretty, dainty widow Eliza Budley must visit some other family manor to purloin expensive baubles. Happily, the rich Marquess of Peterhouse is in his dotage and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mrs-budley-falls-from-grace-m-c-beaton/">Mrs Budley Falls from Grace &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Another Poor Relation has to resort to genteel thievery to make end meet &#8211; but she gets much more than she bargains for!    </p>
<p>                    Cut off by her own relations, pretty, dainty widow Eliza Budley must visit some other family manor to purloin expensive baubles.  Happily, the rich Marquess of Peterhouse is in his dotage and wouldn&#8217;t know a relative from a bedpost, so Eliza is sent to play the imposter.    </p>
<p>                    But things do not go as planned and Eliza is met by the new Marquess &#8211; wickedly handsome, and with all his wits about him.  And somehow Eliza finds herself confessing her bluff to him and he in turn is much taken with her daring and charm  &#8211; but can he fall in love with such a scheming  widow from the world of trade? Time for the other Poor Relations to get involved and help these confused lovers!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mrs-budley-falls-from-grace-m-c-beaton/">Mrs Budley Falls from Grace &#8211; M.C. Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alec Mackenzie&#8217;s Art of Seduction : Mackenzies &#8211; Jennifer Ashley</title>
		<link>/alec-mackenzies-art-of-seduction-mackenzies-jennifer-ashley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alec-mackenzies-art-of-seduction-mackenzies-jennifer-ashley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fugitive Highlander. A proper English lady. A dangerous liaison. Alec Mackenzie knows Lady Celia is key to finding his missing brother. The trouble is, Alec is supposed to be dead, and he needs the world to keep believing that. Alec will do anything to find his brother, Will, including pretend to be a penniless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alec-mackenzies-art-of-seduction-mackenzies-jennifer-ashley/">Alec Mackenzie&#8217;s Art of Seduction : Mackenzies &#8211; Jennifer Ashley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fugitive Highlander.    </p>
<p>                    A proper English lady.    </p>
<p>                    A dangerous liaison.    </p>
<p>                    Alec Mackenzie knows Lady Celia is key to finding his missing brother. The trouble is, Alec is supposed to be dead, and he needs the world to keep believing that.    </p>
<p>                    Alec will do anything to find his brother, Will, including pretend to be a penniless drawing master to London aristocrats. The one man who might know where his brother is being held is a powerful duke, and that duke has daughter who needs art lessons &#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Lady Celia is intrigued by the Scotsman, so obviously a warrior, who pretends he is not. She&#8217;s also intrigued by his instruction on painting the human form, something no young lady should take an interest in. But Celia, ruined by The Disaster and already beyond hope, dares to let the Highlander teach her all he knows &#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alec-mackenzies-art-of-seduction-mackenzies-jennifer-ashley/">Alec Mackenzie&#8217;s Art of Seduction : Mackenzies &#8211; Jennifer Ashley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wicked and the Wallflower : The Bareknuckle Bastards Book I &#8211; Sarah MacLean, Read by Justine Eyre</title>
		<link>/wicked-and-the-wallflower-the-bareknuckle-bastards-book-i-sarah-maclean-read-by-justine-eyre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wicked-and-the-wallflower-the-bareknuckle-bastards-book-i-sarah-maclean-read-by-justine-eyre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Wicked Comes Calling . . . When a mysterious stranger finds his way into her bedchamber and offers his help in landing a duke, Lady Felicity Faircloth agrees&#8211;on one condition. She&#8217;s seen enough of the world to believe in passion, and won&#8217;t accept a marriage without it. The Wallflower Makes a Dangerous Bargain . [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wicked-and-the-wallflower-the-bareknuckle-bastards-book-i-sarah-maclean-read-by-justine-eyre/">Wicked and the Wallflower : The Bareknuckle Bastards Book I &#8211; Sarah MacLean, Read by Justine Eyre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Wicked Comes Calling . . .    </p>
<p>                    When a mysterious stranger finds his way into her bedchamber and offers his help in landing a duke, Lady Felicity Faircloth agrees&#8211;on one condition. She&#8217;s seen enough of the world to believe in passion, and won&#8217;t accept a marriage without it.    </p>
<p>                    The Wallflower Makes a Dangerous Bargain . . .    </p>
<p>                    Bastard son of a duke and king of London&#8217;s dark streets, Devil has spent a lifetime wielding power and seizing opportunity, and the spinster wallflower is everything he needs to exact a revenge years in the making. All he must do is turn the plain little mouse into an irresistible temptress, set his trap, and destroy his enemy.    </p>
<p>                    For the Promise of Passion . . .    </p>
<p>                    But there&#8217;s nothing plain about Felicity Faircloth, who quickly decides she&#8217;d rather have Devil than another. Soon, Devil&#8217;s carefully laid plans are in chaos and he must choose between everything he&#8217;s ever wanted . . . and the only thing he&#8217;s ever desired.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wicked-and-the-wallflower-the-bareknuckle-bastards-book-i-sarah-maclean-read-by-justine-eyre/">Wicked and the Wallflower : The Bareknuckle Bastards Book I &#8211; Sarah MacLean, Read by Justine Eyre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Duchess Deal : Girl Meets Duke &#8211; Tessa Dare</title>
		<link>/the-duchess-deal-girl-meets-duke-tessa-dare/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-duchess-deal-girl-meets-duke-tessa-dare/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When girl meets Duke, their marriage breaks all the rules&#8230;Since his return from war, the Duke of Ashbury&#8217;s to-do list has been short and anything but sweet: brooding, glowering, menacing London ne&#8217;er-do-wells by night. Now there&#8217;s a new item on the list. He needs an heir-which means he needs a wife. When Emma Gladstone, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-duchess-deal-girl-meets-duke-tessa-dare/">The Duchess Deal : Girl Meets Duke &#8211; Tessa Dare</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When girl meets Duke, their marriage breaks all the rules&#8230;Since his return from war, the Duke of Ashbury&#8217;s to-do list has been short and anything but sweet: brooding, glowering, menacing London ne&#8217;er-do-wells by night. Now there&#8217;s a new item on the list. He needs an heir-which means he needs a wife. When Emma Gladstone, a vicar&#8217;s daughter turned seamstress, appears in his library wearing a wedding gown, he decides on the spot that she&#8217;ll do.  His terms are simple:  &#8211; They will be husband and wife by night only.  &#8211; No lights, no kissing. &#8211; No questions about his battle scars. &#8211; Last, and most importantly&#8230;Once she&#8217;s pregnant with his heir, they need never share a bed again.  But Emma is no pushover. She has a few rules of her own:  &#8211; They will have dinner together every evening. &#8211; With conversation.  &#8211; And unlimited teasing.  &#8211; Last, and most importantly&#8230;Once she&#8217;s seen the man beneath the scars, he can&#8217;t stop her from falling in love&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-duchess-deal-girl-meets-duke-tessa-dare/">The Duchess Deal : Girl Meets Duke &#8211; Tessa Dare</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polly &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/polly-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/polly-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>She was a bewitching young girl, that pretty Polly Marsh, and she knew it. She also knew that beauty could be her passport into the castles where she had always known she belonged. So she set her sights on a duke and joined the firm of Westerman&#8217;s as a stenographer. Surely one of that noble [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/polly-m-c-beaton/">Polly &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>She was a bewitching young girl, that pretty Polly Marsh, and she knew it. She also knew that beauty could be her passport into the castles where she had always known she belonged. So she set her sights on a duke and joined the firm of Westerman&#8217;s as a stenographer. Surely one of that noble family would notice her, and then all her dreams would come true! The trouble with pretty Polly Marsh was that she just didn&#8217;t know her place. But others did&#8211;and were only too happy to remind her that dashing Lord Peter was merely playing at love when he appeared to be paying her court. The duchess was beside herself. Peter&#8217;s brother, the starchy Marquis of Wollerton, was desperate to pry Peter from Polly&#8217;s side. But Polly was determined to have Peter&#8211;and her dream. Peter wouldn&#8217;t betray her, would he?    </p>
<p>                    In this whirlwind series, Marion Chesney brings us spirited, independent women who are at once bewitching, beguiling, and determined to have their say and make their mark on both their world and the world at large, be it within their social circle or extending beyond. With their arms wide open, these women are absolutely original and unforgettable, as are the tales in which they are featured. Here is life, in all of its folly and foibles, in a dizzying place where dreams are both shattered and made.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/polly-m-c-beaton/">Polly &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Una visita inesperada &#8211; Irenea Morales</title>
		<link>/una-visita-inesperada-irenea-morales/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/una-visita-inesperada-irenea-morales/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Londres, 1913 Los planes de la joven viuda Florence Morland de presentar a su hermana pequeña, Daisy, en sociedad y disfrutar de la temporada londinense se ven truncados cuando recibe una tentadora invitación: la nueva propietaria de Des Bienheureux, la idílica finca del norte de Francia que antaño perteneció a la familia, desea que ambas [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/una-visita-inesperada-irenea-morales/">Una visita inesperada &#8211; Irenea Morales</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Londres, 1913<br />
                    Los planes de la joven viuda Florence Morland de presentar a su hermana pequeña, Daisy, en sociedad y disfrutar de la temporada londinense se ven truncados cuando recibe una tentadora invitación: la nueva propietaria de Des Bienheureux, la idílica finca del norte de Francia que antaño perteneció a la familia, desea que ambas se unan al resto de sus invitados para pasar el verano entre sus bucólicos jardines.<br />
                    El recuerdo de antiguos amores, así como el anhelo de los nuevos, florecerá nada más traspasar su mágico umbral, y las dos hermanas descubrirán, entre sesiones de espiritismo y escapadas a la luz de la luna, que no todo es joie de vivre y que los secretos que se esconden la una a la otra no son nada comparados con los que atesora la antigua mansión familiar.<br />
                    Un mal ancestral acecha aletargado entre raíces y sombras, esperando la oportunidad de ser liberado.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/una-visita-inesperada-irenea-morales/">Una visita inesperada &#8211; Irenea Morales</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scandalous Duke &#8211; Scarlett Scott, Read by Rosalyn Landor</title>
		<link>/scandalous-duke-scarlett-scott-read-by-rosalyn-landor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/scandalous-duke-scarlett-scott-read-by-rosalyn-landor/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Felix Markham, Duke of Winchelsea, has devoted his life to being the perfect statesman and raising his daughter after his beloved wife&#8217;s death. But when devastating bombings on the railway leave London in an uproar, he is determined to bring the mastermind of the attacks to justice. He will lure the fox from his den [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scandalous-duke-scarlett-scott-read-by-rosalyn-landor/">Scandalous Duke &#8211; Scarlett Scott, Read by Rosalyn Landor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Felix Markham, Duke of Winchelsea, has devoted his life to being the perfect statesman and raising his daughter after his beloved wife&#8217;s death. But when devastating bombings on the railway leave London in an uproar, he is determined to bring the mastermind of the attacks to justice. He will lure the fox from his den by any means. In her youth, Johanna McKenna donned a French accent and stage name to escape the clutches of her violent father and became the darling of the New York City stage as Rose Beaumont. Her past comes calling when her brother&#8217;s reappearance in her life leads her into a dangerous web of deceit. She finds herself hopelessly trapped until she receives an offer she cannot refuse from London&#8217;s most famous theater. Felix&#8217;s plan is clear: bring the famed Rose of New York to London, secure her as his mistress, and drive his quarry to English shores. But the more time he spends in Johanna&#8217;s company, the more he realizes nothing is as it seems, least of all the woman who feels as if she were made to be in his arms. When he finally learns the truth, it may be too late to save both his city and the enigmatic lady who has stolen his heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scandalous-duke-scarlett-scott-read-by-rosalyn-landor/">Scandalous Duke &#8211; Scarlett Scott, Read by Rosalyn Landor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Poppy Wife : A Novel of the Great War &#8211; Caroline Scott</title>
		<link>/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 1 Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A beautifully evocative reminder of what it means to come back from war and to face the age-old question of whether it is better to have survived or to have died. Highly recommended.&#8221;&#8211;Library Journal, starred review In the tradition of Jennifer Robson and Hazel Gaynor, this unforgettable debut novel is a sweeping tale of forbidden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/">The Poppy Wife : A Novel of the Great War &#8211; Caroline Scott</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A beautifully evocative reminder of what it means to come back from war and to face the age-old question of whether it is better to have survived or to have died. Highly recommended.&#8221;&#8211;Library Journal, starred review</p>
<p>                    In the tradition of Jennifer Robson and Hazel Gaynor, this unforgettable debut novel is a sweeping tale of forbidden love, profound loss, and the startling truth of the broken families left behind in the wake of World War I.</p>
<p>                    1921. Survivors of the Great War are desperately trying to piece together the fragments of their broken lives. While many have been reunited with their loved ones, Edie&#8217;s husband Francis has not come home. Francis is presumed to have been killed in action, but Edie believes he might still be alive.</p>
<p>                    Harry, Francis&#8217;s brother, was there the day Francis was wounded. He was certain it was a fatal wound&#8211;that he saw his brother die&#8211;but as time passes, Harry begins questioning his memory of what happened. Could Francis, like many soldiers, merely be lost and confused somewhere? Hired by grieving families, Harry returns to the Western Front to photograph gravesites. As he travels through battle-scarred France and Belgium gathering news for British wives and mothers, he searches for evidence of Francis.</p>
<p>                    When Edie receives a mysterious photograph of Francis, she is more convinced than ever he might still be alive. And so, she embarks on a journey in the hope of finding some trace of her husband. Is he truly gone? And if he isn&#8217;t, then why hasn&#8217;t he come home? </p>
<p>                    As Harry and Edie&#8217;s paths converge, they get closer to the truth about Francis and, as they do, are faced with the life-changing impact of the answers they discover. </p>
<p>                    Artful and incredibly moving, The Poppy Wife tells the unforgettable story of the soldiers lost amid the chaos and ruins, and those who were desperate to find them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/">The Poppy Wife : A Novel of the Great War &#8211; Caroline Scott</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shaman : Number 2 in series &#8211; Noah Gordon</title>
		<link>/shaman-number-2-in-series-noah-gordon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shaman-number-2-in-series-noah-gordon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Jeremy Cole, the legendary doctor and hero of THE PHYSICIAN, left an enduring legacy. From the eleventh century on, the eldest son in each generation of the Cole family has borne the same first name and middle initial and many of these men have followed the medical profession. A few have been blessed with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shaman-number-2-in-series-noah-gordon/">Shaman : Number 2 in series &#8211; Noah Gordon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robert Jeremy Cole, the legendary doctor and hero of THE PHYSICIAN, left an enduring legacy. From the eleventh century on, the eldest son in each generation of the Cole family has borne the same first name and middle initial and many of these men have followed the medical profession. A few have been blessed with their ancestor&#8217;s diagnostic skill and the &#8216;sixth sense&#8217; they call The Gift, the ability to know instinctively when death is impending.<br />
                             The tragedy of Rob J.&#8217;s life is the deafness of his son, Robert Jefferson Cole, who is called Shaman by everyone who knows him. Shaman&#8217;s life is difficult. First, he must learn to speak so that he can take his place in the hearing world, and then he must fight against the prejudices of a society where physical differences matter. As Shaman struggles to achieve his identity, the Coles, along with the rest of America, are drawn into the conflict between the North and the South.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shaman-number-2-in-series-noah-gordon/">Shaman : Number 2 in series &#8211; Noah Gordon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</title>
		<link>/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER A RICHARD AND JUDY BOOKCLUB PICK &#8216;Utterly engrossing&#8217; Guardian It is wash-day for the housemaids at Longbourn House, and Sarah&#8217;s hands are chapped and raw. Domestic life below stairs, ruled with a tender heart and an iron will by Mrs Hill the housekeeper, is about to be disturbed by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/">Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER<br />
                    A RICHARD AND JUDY BOOKCLUB PICK<br />
                    &#8216;Utterly engrossing&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    It is wash-day for the housemaids at Longbourn House, and Sarah&#8217;s hands are chapped and raw. Domestic life below stairs, ruled with a tender heart and an iron will by Mrs Hill the housekeeper, is about to be disturbed by the arrival of a new footman, bearing secrets and the scent of the sea.    </p>
<p>                    What readers are saying:    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A novel to be savoured&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;Highly recommended&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;Very enjoyable exploration of the background to Pride and Prejudice&#8217;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/">Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
