<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Social Forecasting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/social-forecasting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/social-forecasting/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Social Forecasting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/social-forecasting/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</title>
		<link>/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Internet and smartphone are just the latest in a 250 year long cycle of disruption that has continuously changed the way we live, the way we work and the way we interact. The coming Augmented Age, however, promises a level of disruption, behavioral shifts and changes that are unparalleled. While consumers today are camping [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/">Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Internet and smartphone are just the latest in a 250 year long cycle of disruption that has continuously changed the way we live, the way we work and the way we interact. The coming Augmented Age, however, promises a level of disruption, behavioral shifts and changes that are unparalleled. While consumers today are camping outside of an Apple store waiting to be one of the first to score a new Apple Watch or iPhone, the next generation of wearables will be able to predict if we&#8217;re likely to have a heart attack and recommend a course of action. We watch news of Google&#8217;s self-driving cars, but don&#8217;t likely realize this means progressive cities will have to ban human drives in the next decade because us humans are too risky.  Following on from the Industrial or Machine Age, the Space Age and the Digital Age, the Augmented Age will be based on four key disruptive themes &#8211; Artificial Intelligence, Experience Design, Smart Infrastructure, and Health Tech. Historically the previous &#8216;ages&#8217; brought significant disruption and changes, but on a net basis jobs were created, wealth was enhanced, and the health and security of society improved. What will the Augmented Age bring?<br />
                    Will robots take our jobs, and AI&#8217;s subsume us as inferior intelligences, or will this usher in a new age of abundance?  Augmented is a book on future history, but more than that, it is a story about how you will live your life in a world that will change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 250 years. Are you ready to adapt? Because if history proves anything, you don&#8217;t have much of a choice.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/">Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
