<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Graphical &amp; Digital Media Applications Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/graphical-digital-media-applications/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/graphical-digital-media-applications/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Graphical &amp; Digital Media Applications Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/graphical-digital-media-applications/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want. Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want.    </p>
<p>                    Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, product managers, entrepreneurs, and aspiring strategists simple to advanced methods that can be applied right away. You&#8217;ll gain valuable perspective through business cases and historical context. This second edition includes new real-world examples, updated techniques, and a chapter on conducting qualitative online user research.    </p>
<p>                    Define value propositions and validate target users through provisional personas and customer discovery techniques<br />
                    Explore marketplace opportunities by conducting competitive research and analysis<br />
                    Design experiments using rapid prototypes that are focused on the business model<br />
                    Conduct online user research to gain valuable insights quickly on any budget<br />
                    Test business ideas and validate marketing channels by running online advertising and landing page campaigns</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With roughly 95,000 blogs launched worldwide every 24 hours (BlogPulse), making a fledgling site stand out isn&#8217;t easy. This authoritative handbook gives creative hopefuls a leg up. Joy Cho, of the award-winning Oh Joy!, offers expert advice on starting and growing a blog, from design and finance to overcoming blogger&#8217;s block, attracting readers, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/">Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With roughly 95,000 blogs launched worldwide every 24 hours (BlogPulse), making a fledgling site stand out isn&#8217;t easy. This authoritative handbook gives creative hopefuls a leg up. Joy Cho, of the award-winning Oh Joy!, offers expert advice on starting and growing a blog, from design and finance to overcoming blogger&#8217;s block, attracting readers, and more. With a foreword from Grace Bonney of Design*Sponge plus expert interviews, this book will fine-tune what the next generation of bloggers shares with the world. Learn how to design your site, choose the right platform, attract a fan base, finance your blog, maintain work/life balance, manage comments, find content inspiration, overcome blogger&#8217;s block, choose the right ads, develop a voice, protect your work, create a media kit, leverage your social network, take better photographs, set up an affiliate program, partner with sponsors, build community, go full-time with your blog, and more!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/">Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brand Gap, The : Revised Edition &#8211; Marty Neumeier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE BRAND GAP is the first book to present a unified theory of brand-building. Whereas most books on branding are weighted toward either a strategic or creative approach, this book shows how both ways of thinking can unite to produce a &#8220;charismatic brand&#8221;-a brand that customers feel is essential to their lives. In an entertaining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/">Brand Gap, The : Revised Edition &#8211; Marty Neumeier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE BRAND GAP is the first book to present a unified theory of brand-building.  Whereas most books on branding are weighted toward either a strategic or creative approach, this book shows how both ways of thinking can unite to produce a &#8220;charismatic brand&#8221;-a brand that customers feel is essential to their lives. In an entertaining two-hour read you&#8217;ll learn:     </p>
<p>                    * the new definition of brand<br />
                    * the five essential disciplines of brand-building<br />
                    * how branding is changing the dynamics of competition<br />
                    * the three most powerful questions to ask about any brand<br />
                    * why collaboration is the key to brand-building<br />
                    * how design determines a customer&#8217;s experience<br />
                    * how to test brand concepts quickly and cheaply<br />
                    * the importance of managing brands from the inside<br />
                    * 220-word brand glossary     </p>
<p>                    From the back cover:<br />
                    Not since McLuhan&#8217;s THE MEDIUM IS THE MESSAGE has a book compressed so many ideas into so few pages. Using the visual language of the boardroom, Neumeier presents the first unified theory of branding-a set of five disciplines to help companies bridge the gap between brand strategy and customer experience. Those with a grasp of branding will be inspired by the new perspectives they find here, and those who would like to understand it better will suddenly &#8220;get it.&#8221; This deceptively simple book offers everyone in the company access to &#8220;the most powerful business tool since the spreadsheet.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/">Brand Gap, The : Revised Edition &#8211; Marty Neumeier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The One Hour Content Plan : The Solopreneur&#8217;s Guide to a Year&#8217;s Worth of Blog Post Ideas in 60 Minutes and Creating Content That Hooks and Sells &#8211; Meera Kothand (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-one-hour-content-plan-the-solopreneurs-guide-to-a-years-worth-of-blog-post-ideas-in-60-minutes-and-creating-content-that-hooks-and-sells-meera-kothand-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-one-hour-content-plan-the-solopreneurs-guide-to-a-years-worth-of-blog-post-ideas-in-60-minutes-and-creating-content-that-hooks-and-sells-meera-kothand-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does any of this sound like you? 1. You never know what to write On most days you struggle to come up with blog post ideas and haven&#8217;t planned in advance what your content is going to be about. You&#8217;re always looking to fill a publishing queue. 2. You chase after content trends You go [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-one-hour-content-plan-the-solopreneurs-guide-to-a-years-worth-of-blog-post-ideas-in-60-minutes-and-creating-content-that-hooks-and-sells-meera-kothand-abridged/">The One Hour Content Plan : The Solopreneur&#8217;s Guide to a Year&#8217;s Worth of Blog Post Ideas in 60 Minutes and Creating Content That Hooks and Sells &#8211; Meera Kothand (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does any of this sound like you?    </p>
<p>                    1. You never know what to write    </p>
<p>                    On most days you struggle to come up with blog post ideas and haven&#8217;t planned in advance what your content is going to be about.     </p>
<p>                    You&#8217;re always looking to fill a publishing queue.     </p>
<p>                    2. You chase after content trends    </p>
<p>                    You go after what you think will make your post go viral or get more shares. There isn&#8217;t necessarily a thread in any of your content pieces.    </p>
<p>                    3. Your content doesn&#8217;t have a strong link to the products or services you offer    </p>
<p>                    You&#8217;re not sure how to create content to promote your products or services.     </p>
<p>                    If you&#8217;re nodding yes to any of the above,  The 1- Hour Content Plan will help you generate countless ideas. To be exact, a full year&#8217;s worth of traffic building and sales boosting content ideas in 60 minutes or less.     </p>
<p>                    Here&#8217;s what&#8217;s packed in this how-to guide:     </p>
<p>                    Three core ways to INSTANTLY generate content ideas with ease. Ditch the content overwhelm and never ever struggle with what to write again. 5 types of content that will inch your subscriber towards becoming a buyer and sell your products and services with ease. (And why you need ALL five!)<br />
                    The fastest way to determine your BRAND VOICE so that you create content that fits you like a glove. No &#8220;whishy-washy&#8221; ideas. No guessing. 8 MUST-NOT neglect elements that either make or break your blog posts and how to optimize each of them. The trap that bloggers and solopreneurs fall into with producing content and how ways to HOOK more eyeballs on your content.     </p>
<p>                    Imagine for a minute how your blog and business would change if you NEVER run out of blog post ideas&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    You know exactly what to create,  when and what results it&#8217;ll drive.    </p>
<p>                    Your offers (paid and free) become seductive magnets of YES! that readers cannot resist.    </p>
<p>                    Every single piece of content has a purpose in growing your blog and business,  sells your products and services for you and builds your online presence&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s the power of a content strategy and the promise behind the &#8216;One Hour Content Plan.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Intrigued yet?    </p>
<p>                    Then scroll to the top and click or tap &#8220;Buy Now.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Get your content to work harder for you with the One Hour Content Plan!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-one-hour-content-plan-the-solopreneurs-guide-to-a-years-worth-of-blog-post-ideas-in-60-minutes-and-creating-content-that-hooks-and-sells-meera-kothand-abridged/">The One Hour Content Plan : The Solopreneur&#8217;s Guide to a Year&#8217;s Worth of Blog Post Ideas in 60 Minutes and Creating Content That Hooks and Sells &#8211; Meera Kothand (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
