<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Business Studies: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/business-studies-general/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/business-studies-general/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Business Studies: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/business-studies-general/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>THE ENTREPRENEURIAL BIBLE TO VENTURE CAPITAL: Inside Secrets from the Leaders in the Startup Game &#8211; Andrew Romans (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>40 leading venture capitalists come together to teach entrepreneurs how to succeed with their startupThe Entrepreneurial Bible to Venture Capital is packed with invaluable advice about how to raise angel and venture capital funding, how to build value in a startup, and how to exit a company with maximum value for both founders and investors. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/">THE ENTREPRENEURIAL BIBLE TO VENTURE CAPITAL: Inside Secrets from the Leaders in the Startup Game &#8211; Andrew Romans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>40 leading venture capitalists come together to teach entrepreneurs how to succeed with their startupThe Entrepreneurial Bible to Venture Capital is packed with invaluable advice about how to raise angel and venture capital funding, how to build value in a startup, and how to exit a company with maximum value for both founders and investors. It guides entrepreneurs through every step in an entrepreneurial venture from the legalities of raising initial capital to knowing when to change tactics.    </p>
<p>                    Andrew Romans is the co-founder and general partner of Rubicon Venture Capital, a venture capital fund that invests in privately held technology companies and enables its investors to co-invest along side the fund on a deal-by-deal basis via innovative sidecar funds right up to IPO or M&#038;A exit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/">THE ENTREPRENEURIAL BIBLE TO VENTURE CAPITAL: Inside Secrets from the Leaders in the Startup Game &#8211; Andrew Romans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee and Po Bronson and Ashley Merryman&#8217;s Nurture Shock, New York Times &#8220;Your Money&#8221; columnist Ron Lieber delivers a taboo-shattering manifesto that explains how talking openly to children about money can help parents raise modest, patient, grounded young adults who are financially wise beyond [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/">The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee and Po Bronson and Ashley Merryman&#8217;s Nurture Shock, New York Times &#8220;Your Money&#8221; columnist Ron Lieber delivers a taboo-shattering manifesto that explains how talking openly to children about money can help parents raise modest, patient, grounded young adults who are financially wise beyond their years.  For Ron Lieber, a personal finance columnist and father, good parenting means talking about money with our kids. Children are hyper-aware of money, and they have scores of questions about its nuances. But when parents shy away from the topic, they lose a tremendous opportunity-not just to model the basic financial behaviors that are increasingly important for young adults but also to imprint lessons about what the family truly values.  Written in a warm, accessible voice, grounded in real-world experience and stories from families with a range of incomes, The Opposite of Spoiled is both a practical guidebook and a values-based philosophy.<br />
                    The foundation of the book is a detailed blueprint for the best ways to handle the basics: the tooth fairy, allowance, chores, charity, saving, birthdays, holidays, cell phones, checking accounts, clothing, cars, part-time jobs, and college tuition. It identifies a set of traits and virtues that embody the opposite of spoiled, and shares how to embrace the topic of money to help parents raise kids who are more generous and less materialistic.  But The Opposite of Spoiled is also a promise to our kids that we will make them better with money than we are. It is for all of the parents who know that honest conversations about money with their curious children can help them become more patient and prudent, but who don&#8217;t know how and when to start.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/">The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Execution Factor: The One Skill that Drives Success &#8211; Kim Perell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-execution-factor-the-one-skill-that-drives-success-kim-perell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-execution-factor-the-one-skill-that-drives-success-kim-perell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn the best-kept secret of the world&#8217;s most successful entrepreneurs: EXECUTION! Kim Perell made headlines for her amazing transformative story of a startup entrepreneur to an internationally renowned CEO and prominent angel investor. From her modest beginnings at her kitchen table, she went from broke to multi-millionaire in just a few short years. Today, she [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-execution-factor-the-one-skill-that-drives-success-kim-perell-abridged/">The Execution Factor: The One Skill that Drives Success &#8211; Kim Perell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn the best-kept secret of the world&#8217;s most successful entrepreneurs: EXECUTION!<br />
                    Kim Perell made headlines for her amazing transformative story of a startup entrepreneur to an internationally renowned CEO and prominent angel investor.  From her modest beginnings at her kitchen table, she went from broke to multi-millionaire in just a few short years.  Today, she has investments in over 70 startups many of which have been sold to some of the largest Fortune 500 companies.  Now, in The Execution Factor, she offers indispensable wisdom as she shares her personal journey and proven program for achieving success.<br />
                    The Execution Factor offers a straightforward approach to success &#8211; deliberately designed in a way that anyone can master. Perell flips the notion on its head that success is all about having a great idea, an advanced degree or a high IQ.  Because people around the world have achieved their dreams without any of those things.  Perell believes the ability to execute is the difference between success and failure.<br />
                    **Perell is so confident that committing to mastering these 5 traits of execution will lead to your success, that she is putting all of her book royalties into an Execution Fund to help others turn their dreams into reality.  The Execution Fund is a seed stage fund that will invest a minimum of $1 million into execution-led companies, providing early financing to entrepreneurs and connecting them with an extensive network of industry experts.**<br />
                    The Execution Factor is for anyone looking to transform themselves from a &#8220;dreamer&#8221; to a &#8220;doer&#8221; and will make you feel like you have a success coach by your side. Perell teaches her unique 5 traits of execution: vision, passion, action, resilience, and relationships.  By the time you&#8217;ve completed the book you will have a have a blueprint to achieve your dreams in business and in life. Don&#8217;t settle for ordinary when you can have extraordinary.   Master execution and change your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-execution-factor-the-one-skill-that-drives-success-kim-perell-abridged/">The Execution Factor: The One Skill that Drives Success &#8211; Kim Perell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Widgets: The 12 New Rules for Managing Your Employees as if They&#8217;re Real People &#8211; Rodd Wagner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author Rodd Wagner tackles one of the most destructive problems facing organizations today-the breakdown of the relationship between employees and the organizations they work for &#8220;Your people are not your greatest asset. They&#8217;re not yours, and they&#8217;re not assets.&#8221; With this declaration, one of the leading authorities on employee performance rolls [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/">Widgets: The 12 New Rules for Managing Your Employees as if They&#8217;re Real People &#8211; Rodd Wagner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author Rodd Wagner tackles one of the most destructive problems facing organizations today-the breakdown of the relationship between employees and the organizations they work for    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Your people are not your greatest asset. They&#8217;re not yours, and they&#8217;re not assets.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    With this declaration, one of the leading authorities on employee performance rolls up his sleeves against the weasel words, contradictions, bad habits, and intrusions that reduce people to &#8220;human resources.&#8221; To &#8220;FTEs.&#8221; To &#8220;human capital.&#8221; To flesh-and-blood widgets.    </p>
<p>                    Armed with empirical evidence from the provocative studies he leads around the globe, Wagner guides you through the new realities of what it takes to get the highest levels of intensity from people in a more mercenary, skeptical, and wired work world. He explains how elements such as individualization, fearlessness, transparency, recognition, and coolness are reciprocated with loyalty, productivity, innovation, and&#8211;inescapably&#8211;corporate reputation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/">Widgets: The 12 New Rules for Managing Your Employees as if They&#8217;re Real People &#8211; Rodd Wagner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge    </p>
<p>                    With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. This clear, concise, and accessible guide from two industry insiders shows you how to navigate this brave new blockchain world-and how to invest in these emerging assets to secure your financial future.    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets gives you all the tools you need:    </p>
<p>                    * An actionable framework for investigating and valuing cryptoassets     </p>
<p>                    * Portfolio management techniques to maximize returns while managing risk    </p>
<p>                    * Historical context and tips to navigate inevitable bubbles and manias    </p>
<p>                    * Practical guides to exchanges, wallets, capital market vehicles, and ICOs    </p>
<p>                    * Predictions on how blockchain technology may disrupt current portfolios    </p>
<p>                    In addition to offering smart investment strategies, this authoritative resource will help you understand how these assets were created, how they work, and how they are evolving amid the blockchain revolution. The authors define a clear and original cryptoasset taxonomy, composed of cryptocurrencies, cryptocommodities, and cryptotokens, with insights into how each subset is blending technology and markets. You&#8217;ll find a variety of methods to invest in these assets, whether through global exchanges that trade 24/7 or initial cryptoasset offerings (ICOs). By sequentially building on the concepts of each prior chapter, the book will provide you with a full understanding of the cryptoasset economy and the opportunities that await the innovative investor .    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets represent the future of money and markets. This book is your guide to that future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Speaker, Leader, Champion: Succeed at Work Through the Power of Public Speaking, featuring the prize-winning speeches of Toastmasters World Champions &#8211; Jeremey Donovan, Ryan Avery (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/speaker-leader-champion-succeed-at-work-through-the-power-of-public-speaking-featuring-the-prize-winning-speeches-of-toastmasters-world-champions-jeremey-donovan-ryan-avery-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/speaker-leader-champion-succeed-at-work-through-the-power-of-public-speaking-featuring-the-prize-winning-speeches-of-toastmasters-world-champions-jeremey-donovan-ryan-avery-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The secrets of superb public speaking-based on the best of the best of Toastmasters Toastmasters, a name synonymous with public speaking, is dedicated to developing its members&#8217; communication and leadership skills. Now Distinguished Toastmaster Jeremey Donovan and Public Speaking World Champion Ryan Avery break down the winning speeches from Toastmasters&#8217; prestigious annual competition-providing you with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/speaker-leader-champion-succeed-at-work-through-the-power-of-public-speaking-featuring-the-prize-winning-speeches-of-toastmasters-world-champions-jeremey-donovan-ryan-avery-abridged/">Speaker, Leader, Champion: Succeed at Work Through the Power of Public Speaking, featuring the prize-winning speeches of Toastmasters World Champions &#8211; Jeremey Donovan, Ryan Avery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The secrets of superb public speaking-based on the best of the best of Toastmasters    </p>
<p>                    Toastmasters, a name synonymous with public speaking, is dedicated to developing its members&#8217; communication and leadership skills.    </p>
<p>                     Now Distinguished Toastmaster Jeremey Donovan and Public Speaking World Champion Ryan Avery break down the winning speeches from Toastmasters&#8217; prestigious annual competition-providing you with tips and techniques guaranteed to improve your speaking, presentation, and communication skills. They also include a special section of insights and advice for readers who aspire to become serious public speaking competitors.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Speaker, Leader, Champion demystifies what makes a presentation extraordinary.This engaging, actionable book will teach you how to go from appreciating a powerful speech to delivering one yourself.&#8221;<br />
                    -Adam Grant, professor at the Wharton School at the University of Pennsylvania and New York Times bestselling author of Give and Take    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Whether you present in the boardroom, classroom, or lunchroom, the guidance will help you become a more confident, authentic, and engaging speaker.&#8221;<br />
                    -Matt Abrahams, strategic communication lecturer at the Stanford University Graduate School of Business and author of Speaking Up Without Freaking Out    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;To change the world, you need to lead. To lead, you need to communicate. To communicate, you need this book.&#8221;<br />
                    -Presiyan Vasilev, 2013 World Champion of Public Speaking    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book translates the secret sauce of public speaking into easy-to-use tips.&#8221;<br />
                    -Zoe Chance, assistant professor of marketing at the Yale University School of Management</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/speaker-leader-champion-succeed-at-work-through-the-power-of-public-speaking-featuring-the-prize-winning-speeches-of-toastmasters-world-champions-jeremey-donovan-ryan-avery-abridged/">Speaker, Leader, Champion: Succeed at Work Through the Power of Public Speaking, featuring the prize-winning speeches of Toastmasters World Champions &#8211; Jeremey Donovan, Ryan Avery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moms Mean Business : A Guide to Creating a Successful Company and Happy Life as a Mom Entrepreneur &#8211; Lara Galloway, Erin Baebler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/moms-mean-business-a-guide-to-creating-a-successful-company-and-happy-life-as-a-mom-entrepreneur-lara-galloway-erin-baebler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/moms-mean-business-a-guide-to-creating-a-successful-company-and-happy-life-as-a-mom-entrepreneur-lara-galloway-erin-baebler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are 9 million women-owned businesses in the United States; they account for $1.3 trillion in revenue. American women are starting businesses at a rate twice that of men. Most of these women are also moms. What does it take to be successful as both a mom and as an entrepreneur? Moms Mean Business gives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moms-mean-business-a-guide-to-creating-a-successful-company-and-happy-life-as-a-mom-entrepreneur-lara-galloway-erin-baebler-abridged/">Moms Mean Business : A Guide to Creating a Successful Company and Happy Life as a Mom Entrepreneur &#8211; Lara Galloway, Erin Baebler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are 9 million women-owned businesses in the United States; they account for $1.3 trillion in revenue. American women are starting businesses at a rate twice that of men. Most of these women are also moms.     </p>
<p>                    What does it take to be successful as both a mom and as an entrepreneur? Moms Mean Business gives existing and potential mom business owners the encouragement, advice, and healthy dose of how-to they need.     </p>
<p>                    In this helpful guide, you will create a customized strategy that includes:<br />
                    A personal definition of success in both life and business&#8211;and the way to achieve it<br />
                    The tools needed to manage time and productivity when your priorities as a mom and business owner conflict<br />
                    A mom-friendly business plan to get you focused<br />
                    An approach to self-care that allows you to handle all that&#8217;s thrown your way<br />
                    Tips, checklists, and guidance to quickly solve the problems mom entrepreneurs encounter     </p>
<p>                    Behind-the-scenes stories and advice from well-known mom entrepreneurs make Moms Mean Business fun to read and full of that all-important me, too! factor. It is inspiring, motivating, and, above all, practical.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moms-mean-business-a-guide-to-creating-a-successful-company-and-happy-life-as-a-mom-entrepreneur-lara-galloway-erin-baebler-abridged/">Moms Mean Business : A Guide to Creating a Successful Company and Happy Life as a Mom Entrepreneur &#8211; Lara Galloway, Erin Baebler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Be a Capitalist Without Any Capital : The Four Rules You Must Break to Get Rich &#8211; Nathan Latka (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-a-capitalist-without-any-capital-the-four-rules-you-must-break-to-get-rich-nathan-latka-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-a-capitalist-without-any-capital-the-four-rules-you-must-break-to-get-rich-nathan-latka-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You don&#8217;t need to be university educated, have money, be creative, or even have an idea to get rich. You just need to be willing to break the rules. How to be a Capitalist Without Any Capital will teach you how to be a modern opportunist &#8211; investor, entrepreneur, or side hustler &#8211; by breaking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-capitalist-without-any-capital-the-four-rules-you-must-break-to-get-rich-nathan-latka-abridged/">How to Be a Capitalist Without Any Capital : The Four Rules You Must Break to Get Rich &#8211; Nathan Latka (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You don&#8217;t need to be university educated, have money, be creative, or even have an idea to get rich. You just need to be willing to break the rules.    </p>
<p>                    How to be a Capitalist Without Any Capital will teach you how to be a modern opportunist &#8211; investor, entrepreneur, or side hustler &#8211; by breaking these four golden rules of the old guard:     </p>
<p>                    1. Focus on one skill: Wrong. Don&#8217;t cultivate one great skill to get ahead. In today&#8217;s business world, success goes to the multitaskers.    </p>
<p>                    2. Be unique: Wrong. The way to get rich is not by launching a new idea but by aggressively copying others and then adding your own twist.     </p>
<p>                    3. Focus on one goal: Wrong. Focus instead on creating a system to produce the outcome you want, not just once, but over and over again.     </p>
<p>                    4. Appeal to the masses: Wrong. The masses are broke ($4k average net worth in America?). Let others cut a trail through the jungle so you can peacefully walk in and capitalize on their hard work.    </p>
<p>                    By rejecting these defunct rules and following Nathan Latka&#8217;s unconventional path, you can copy other people&#8217;s ideas shamelessly, bootstrap a start-up with almost no funding, invest in small local businesses for huge payoffs, and reap all the benefits.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-capitalist-without-any-capital-the-four-rules-you-must-break-to-get-rich-nathan-latka-abridged/">How to Be a Capitalist Without Any Capital : The Four Rules You Must Break to Get Rich &#8211; Nathan Latka (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Losing the Signal : The Untold Story Behind the Extraordinary Rise and Spectacular Fall of BlackBerry &#8211; Jacquie McNish, Sean Silcoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/losing-the-signal-the-untold-story-behind-the-extraordinary-rise-and-spectacular-fall-of-blackberry-jacquie-mcnish-sean-silcoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/losing-the-signal-the-untold-story-behind-the-extraordinary-rise-and-spectacular-fall-of-blackberry-jacquie-mcnish-sean-silcoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Canadian National Business Book Award 2016 Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015 In 2009, BlackBerry controlled half of the US smartphone market. Today that number is less than one per cent. What went so wrong? Losing the Signal is the riveting story of a company that toppled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/losing-the-signal-the-untold-story-behind-the-extraordinary-rise-and-spectacular-fall-of-blackberry-jacquie-mcnish-sean-silcoff-abridged/">Losing the Signal : The Untold Story Behind the Extraordinary Rise and Spectacular Fall of BlackBerry &#8211; Jacquie McNish, Sean Silcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Canadian National Business Book Award 2016<br />
                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015    </p>
<p>                    In 2009, BlackBerry controlled half of the US smartphone market. Today that number is less than one per cent. What went so wrong?    </p>
<p>                    Losing the Signal is the riveting story of a company that toppled global giants before succumbing to the ruthlessly competitive forces of Silicon Valley. This is not a conventional tale of modern business failure by fraud and greed; instead, the rise and fall of BlackBerry reveals the dangerous speed at which innovators race along the information superhighway.    </p>
<p>                    With unprecedented access to key players, senior executives, directors, and competitors, Losing the Signal unveils the remarkable rise of a company that started above a bagel store in a small Canadian city and went on to control half of the US smartphone market. However, at the very moment BlackBerry was ranked the world&#8217;s fastest-growing company, internal feuds and chaotic growth crippled the company as it faced its gravest test: the entry of Apple and Google into the mobile phone market.    </p>
<p>                    Expertly told by acclaimed journalists Jacquie McNish and Sean Silcoff, this is an entertaining, whirlwind narrative that goes behind the scenes to reveal one of the most compelling business stories of the new century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/losing-the-signal-the-untold-story-behind-the-extraordinary-rise-and-spectacular-fall-of-blackberry-jacquie-mcnish-sean-silcoff-abridged/">Losing the Signal : The Untold Story Behind the Extraordinary Rise and Spectacular Fall of BlackBerry &#8211; Jacquie McNish, Sean Silcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out of Our Minds : The Power of Being Creative &#8211; Ken Robinson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-our-minds-the-power-of-being-creative-ken-robinson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-our-minds-the-power-of-being-creative-ken-robinson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ken Robinson argues that organisations everywhere are trying to fix a problem that originates in schools and universities: &#8220;It is often said that education and training are the keys to the future. They are, but a key can be turned in two directions. Turn it one way and you lock resources away, even from those [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-our-minds-the-power-of-being-creative-ken-robinson-abridged/">Out of Our Minds : The Power of Being Creative &#8211; Ken Robinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ken Robinson argues that organisations everywhere are trying to fix a problem that originates in schools and universities: &#8220;It is often said that education and training are the keys to the future. They are, but a key can be turned in two directions. Turn it one way and you lock resources away, even from those they belong to. Turn it the other way and you release resources and give people back to themselves. To realize our true creative potential-in our organizations, in our schools and in our communities we need to think differently about ourselves and to act differently towards each other. We must learn to be creative.&#8221; Ken Robinson The updated 3rd edition features a new introduction, modernized case studies, updated demographics and revised sections around technological developments and recent changes to the education system.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-our-minds-the-power-of-being-creative-ken-robinson-abridged/">Out of Our Minds : The Power of Being Creative &#8211; Ken Robinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of FORTUNE Magazine&#8217;s Top 5 Business Book Must-Reads How do you cut through the noise, commotion, and bad information that is right now cluttering up your customers&#8217; digital space? EPIC CONTENT MARKETINGOne of the world&#8217;s leading experts on content marketing, Joe Pulizzi explains how to attract prospects and customers by creating information and content [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of FORTUNE Magazine&#8217;s Top 5 Business Book Must-Reads How do you cut through the noise, commotion, and bad information that is right now cluttering up your customers&#8217; digital space?    </p>
<p>                    EPIC CONTENT MARKETINGOne of the world&#8217;s leading experts on content marketing, Joe Pulizzi explains how to attract prospects and customers by creating information and content they actually want to engage with. No longer can we interrupt our customers with mediocre content and sales messages they don&#8217;t care about.    </p>
<p>                    Epic Content Marketing takes you step-by-stepthrough the process of developing stories that inform and entertain and compel customers to act&#8211;without actually telling them to. Epic content, distributed to the right person at the right time, is the way to truly capture the hearts and minds of customers. It&#8217;s how to position your business as a trusted expert in its industry. It&#8217;s what customers share and talk about.    </p>
<p>                    Once we hook customers with epic content, they reward us by sending our sales through the roof.    </p>
<p>                    Epic Content Marketing provides everything youneed to:    </p>
<p>                    Determine what your content niche should be to attract and retain customersDiscover and develop your content marketing mission statementSet up a process for creating and curating epic contentLearn how to leverage social and e-mail channels to create&#8211;and grow&#8211;your audienceMeasure the performance of your content&#8211;and increase your content marketing budget    </p>
<p>                    With in-depth case studies of how John Deere, LEGO, Coca-Cola, and other leading corporations are using content to drive epic sales, this groundbreaking guide gives you all the tools to start creating and disseminating content that leads directly to greater profits and growth.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re the CMO of a Fortune 500, a digital marketer, or an entrepreneur, Epic Content Marketing gives you the tools you need to vanquish the competition. Start your epic journey now!    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR EPIC CONTENT MARKETING&#8221;From the man who invented content marketing. Listen to this guy. He really understands the new world of marketing. The concepts in Epic Content Marketing are usable all over the world&#8211;instantly usable and useful for any business.&#8221; &#8212; Don Schultz, the &#8220;father of integrated marketing,&#8221; Professor Emeritus at Northwestern University&#8217;s Medill School of Journalism, and author of 13 books    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi&#8217;s ideas are so consistently . . . well, epic (!) that they really don&#8217;t need any endorsement by anyone. But here&#8217;s mine anyway: You don&#8217;t need MORE content. You need the right kind of content,strategically applied. For those organizations struggling to create a content marketing program that drives results, Joe delivers. Again.&#8221; &#8212; Ann Handley, coauthor of Content Rules and Chief Content Officer, MarketingProfs    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;As Joe shows us in his wonderful Epic Content Marketing, you must unlearn interrupting people with your nonsense. Instead, publish the valuable content they want to consume and are eager to share.&#8221; &#8212; David Meerman Scott, marketing strategist and bestselling author ofThe New Rules of Marketing and PR    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is a brilliant canter through the rapid and ever-changing world of content marketing. Joe has managed to capture the right blend of art and science as he plots the major trends impacting all marketers right now.&#8221; &#8212; Jonathan Mildenhall, VP, Global Advertising Strategy and Creative Excellence, Coca-Cola Company    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You could say that Joe Pulizzi wrote the book on content marketing, but now it&#8217;s more than just a saying.It&#8217;s what you&#8217;re holding in your hands. If you truly want to be successful at content marketing, Pulizzi is one of the few who can show you the way.&#8221; &#8212; Mitch Joel, President, Twist Image, and author of Six Pixels of Separation and CTRL ALT Delete    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi may know more about content marketing than any person alive. He proves it in these pages.&#8221; &#8212; Jay Baer, New York Times bestselling author of Youtility: Why Smart Marketing is About Help Not Hype    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The future of successful brand building, and especially the art of solidifying the emotional connection between people and brands, will require expertise in Content Marketing. Epic Content Marketing gives all the details practitioners need without overcomplicating.&#8221; &#8212; Professor JoAnn Sciarrino, Knight Chair, Digital Advertising and Marketing, UNC Chapel Hill    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi is the godfather of our burgeoning profession of Content Marketing. He lays out the objectives, principles, and core strategies of our field in a way that&#8217;s easy-to-understand, inspiring, and entertaining. If your company doesn&#8217;t yet realize that it&#8217;s a media company, with all the challenges and advantages that implies, you&#8217;re missing the most powerful way to connect with your customers.&#8221; &#8212; Julie Fleischer, Director, Media &#038; Consumer Engagement, Kraft Foods</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever. From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business     </p>
<p>                    Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever.    </p>
<p>                    From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the go-to guide to building a solid small-business by establishing a loyal audience before you sell any products or services. In these pages, Joe Pulizzi provides a lower-risk, better way to build a successful business by re-engineering the process that so often leads to failure: You&#8217;ll learn how to develop valuable content, build an audience around that content-and then create a product for that audience. Content Inc. walks you through the entire process, showing how to    </p>
<p>                    Identify the intersection of your expertise and your future customer&#8217;s needs<br />
                    Determine how to &#8220;tilt&#8221; your sweet spot to find a place where little or no competition exists<br />
                    Establish your number-one channel for disseminating content (blog, podcast, YouTube, etc.)<br />
                    Use social-media and SEO to convert one-time visitors into long-term subscribers<br />
                    Grow your business by expanding into multiple delivery channels<br />
                    Monetize your product or service for ultimate business success<br />
                    Understand how to sell your content asset for millions or build the business into a large enterprise    </p>
<p>                    This fully updated edition includes new and enhanced coverage of platforms like TikTok, SnapChat, and Instagram, a new section about the exit strategy for the model, more practical how-tos, and current examples of companies that have successfully implemented these strategies.      </p>
<p>                    Apply the methods laid out for you in Content Inc., and before you know it, you&#8217;ll be running your own profitable, scalable business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Content Marketing: How to Create Great Content, Reach More Customers, and Build a Worldwide Marketing Strategy that Works &#8211; Pam Didner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Engage Customers Around the World with Cross-Regional Content MarketingTechnology has virtually erased national borders, forever transforming the way we reach and engage customers, as well as the way we search for and consumecontent. Global Content Marketing takes you step-by-step through the process of creating and refining your strategies to meet this new reality. LEARN HOW [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/">Global Content Marketing: How to Create Great Content, Reach More Customers, and Build a Worldwide Marketing Strategy that Works &#8211; Pam Didner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Engage Customers Around the World with Cross-Regional Content MarketingTechnology has virtually erased national borders, forever transforming the way we reach and engage customers, as well as the way we search for and consumecontent. Global Content Marketing takes you step-by-step through the process of creating and refining your strategies to meet this new reality.    </p>
<p>                    LEARN HOW TO:    </p>
<p>                    Create content that engages people&#8211;regardless of their country and cultureIdentify key actions and strategies to apply to your projectsConnect &#8220;dots&#8221; that others don&#8217;t see and connect them in ways you never thought of before    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Content marketing across geographies is a diff erent animal. In this smart, practical, and authoritative book, Pam Didner has tamed this animal for all of us.&#8221; &#8212; DOUG KESSLER, Creative Director, Velocity    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable guide to developing and distributing your global content effectively.&#8221; &#8212; NANCY BHAGAT, former VP, Global Marketing Strategy, Intel, and current Divisional CMO, TE Connectivity    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book is the blueprint for engineering a modern scalable content marketing operation.&#8221; &#8212; PAWAN DESHPANDE, CEO, Curata    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Finally the book that explores all critical aspects of global content marketing! Whether you are a small business or a Fortune 500 company, it is essential to understand the 4P&#8217;s developed by Pam Didner. Read it and take your content strategy to the whole new level.&#8221;  &#8212; EKATERINA WALTER, author of Think Like Zuck and coauthor of The Power of Visual Storytelling</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/">Global Content Marketing: How to Create Great Content, Reach More Customers, and Build a Worldwide Marketing Strategy that Works &#8211; Pam Didner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fifth Trimester : The Working Mom&#8217;s Guide to Style, Sanity, and Success After Baby &#8211; Lauren Smith Brody (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fifth-trimester-the-working-moms-guide-to-style-sanity-and-success-after-baby-lauren-smith-brody-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fifth-trimester-the-working-moms-guide-to-style-sanity-and-success-after-baby-lauren-smith-brody-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Packed with honest, funny, and comforting advice&#8211;&#8220;a book you MUST read if you are returning to work after the birth of a child&#8230;. I loved it and you will too.&#8221; &#8211;New York Times bestselling author Lois P. Frankel, Ph.D. The first three trimesters (and the fourth&#8211;those blurry newborn days) are for the baby, but the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fifth-trimester-the-working-moms-guide-to-style-sanity-and-success-after-baby-lauren-smith-brody-abridged/">The Fifth Trimester : The Working Mom&#8217;s Guide to Style, Sanity, and Success After Baby &#8211; Lauren Smith Brody (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Packed with honest, funny, and comforting advice&#8211;&#8220;a book you MUST read if you are returning to work after the birth of a child&#8230;. I loved it and you will too.&#8221; &#8211;New York Times bestselling author Lois P. Frankel, Ph.D.      </p>
<p>                    The first three trimesters (and the fourth&#8211;those blurry newborn days) are for the baby, but the Fifth Trimester is when the working mom is born. A funny, tells-it-like-it-is guide for new mothers coping with the demands of returning to the real world after giving birth, The Fifth Trimester contains advice from 800 moms, including:     </p>
<p>                     -The boss-approved way to ask for flextime (and more money!)<br />
                    -How to know if it&#8217;s more than &#8220;just the baby blues&#8221;<br />
                    -How to pump breastmilk on an airplane (or, if you must, in a bathroom)<br />
                    -What military science knows about working through sleep deprivation<br />
                    -Your new sixty-second get-out-of-the-house beauty routine<br />
                    -How to turn your commute into a mini-therapy session<br />
                    -Your daycare tour or nanny interview, totally decoded</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fifth-trimester-the-working-moms-guide-to-style-sanity-and-success-after-baby-lauren-smith-brody-abridged/">The Fifth Trimester : The Working Mom&#8217;s Guide to Style, Sanity, and Success After Baby &#8211; Lauren Smith Brody (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Success and Luck : Good Fortune and the Myth of Meritocracy &#8211; Robert H. Frank (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/success-and-luck-good-fortune-and-the-myth-of-meritocracy-robert-h-frank-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/success-and-luck-good-fortune-and-the-myth-of-meritocracy-robert-h-frank-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times bestselling author and economics columnist Robert Frank, a compelling book that explains why the rich underestimate the importance of luck in their success, why that hurts everyone, and what we can do about it How important is luck in economic success? No question more reliably divides conservatives from liberals. As conservatives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-and-luck-good-fortune-and-the-myth-of-meritocracy-robert-h-frank-abridged/">Success and Luck : Good Fortune and the Myth of Meritocracy &#8211; Robert H. Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times bestselling author and economics columnist Robert Frank, a compelling book that explains why the rich underestimate the importance of luck in their success, why that hurts everyone, and what we can do about it  How important is luck in economic success? No question more reliably divides conservatives from liberals. As conservatives correctly observe, people who amass great fortunes are almost always talented and hardworking. But liberals are also correct to note that countless others have those same qualities yet never earn much. In recent years, social scientists have discovered that chance plays a much larger role in important life outcomes than most people imagine. In Success and Luck, bestselling author and New York Times economics columnist Robert Frank explores the surprising implications of those findings to show why the rich underestimate the importance of luck in success&#8211;and why that hurts everyone, even the wealthy.<br />
                    Frank describes how, in a world increasingly dominated by winner-take-all markets, chance opportunities and trivial initial advantages often translate into much larger ones&#8211;and enormous income differences&#8211;over time; how false beliefs about luck persist, despite compelling evidence against them; and how myths about personal success and luck shape individual and political choices in harmful ways.  But, Frank argues, we could decrease the inequality driven by sheer luck by adopting simple, unintrusive policies that would free up trillions of dollars each year&#8211;more than enough to fix our crumbling infrastructure, expand healthcare coverage, fight global warming, and reduce poverty, all without requiring painful sacrifices from anyone. If this sounds implausible, you&#8217;ll be surprised to discover that the solution requires only a few, noncontroversial steps.  Compellingly readable, Success and Luck shows how a more accurate understanding of the role of chance in life could lead to better, richer, and fairer economies and societies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-and-luck-good-fortune-and-the-myth-of-meritocracy-robert-h-frank-abridged/">Success and Luck : Good Fortune and the Myth of Meritocracy &#8211; Robert H. Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s business world, it takes more than a website to stay competitive. The smartest, most successful companies are using radically new membership models, subscription-based formats, and freemium pricing structures to grow their customer base-and explode their market valuation-in the most disruptive shift in business since the Industrial Revolution. This is The Membership Economy. Written [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/">The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s business world, it takes more than a website to stay competitive. The smartest, most successful companies are using radically new membership models, subscription-based formats, and freemium pricing structures to grow their customer base-and explode their market valuation-in the most disruptive shift in business since the Industrial Revolution.    </p>
<p>                    This is The Membership Economy.    </p>
<p>                     Written by an expertconsultant, this groundbreaking book will show you how to turn ordinary customers into members for life. Learn how to:    </p>
<p>                     Turn digital subscriptions into forever sales Build an online community your customers will loveDevelop new loyalty programs that really pay offTransform freemium users into superusers Create a self-generating revenue stream Keep memberships and profits growing for years to come<br />
                    Whether you&#8217;re a small business with limited resources, an established company using a traditional business model, or a hungry start-up who wants a bigger bang for your buck, this comprehensive guide provides a wealth of membership-building options to suit every need.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll learn the best-kept secrets of top industry leaders, from global giants like Am Ex and Weight Watchers to smaller dot-com successes like SurveyMonkey and Pandora. You&#8217;ll find proven strategies for creating membership programs for everything from vacation timeshares and car rentals to video streaming and Software-as-a-Service.    </p>
<p>                     Most importantly, you&#8217;ll discover what works, and what doesn&#8217;t, from some of the key players in the new membership economy. It&#8217;s not about ownership; it&#8217;s about access, options, and freedom.    </p>
<p>                    When you join forces with your customers, membership has its rewards-for you, your company, and your continued success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/">The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flawless Consulting : A Guide to Getting Your Expertise Used &#8211; Peter Block (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This Third Edition to Peter Block&#8217;s Flawless Consulting addresses business changes and new challenges since the second edition was written ten years ago. It tackles the challenges next-generation consultants face, including more guidance on how to ask better questions, dealing with difficult clients, working in an increasingly virtual world, how to cope with complexities in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/">Flawless Consulting : A Guide to Getting Your Expertise Used &#8211; Peter Block (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This Third Edition to Peter Block&#8217;s Flawless Consulting addresses business changes and new challenges since the second edition was written ten years ago. It tackles the challenges next-generation consultants face, including more guidance on how to ask better questions, dealing with difficult clients, working in an increasingly virtual world, how to cope with complexities in international consulting, case studies, and guidelines on implementation. Also included are illustrative examples and exercises to help you cement the guides offered.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flawless-consulting-a-guide-to-getting-your-expertise-used-peter-block-abridged/">Flawless Consulting : A Guide to Getting Your Expertise Used &#8211; Peter Block (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain : The Next Everything &#8211; Stephen P Williams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blockchain-the-next-everything-stephen-p-williams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blockchain-the-next-everything-stephen-p-williams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The perfect book for everybody who&#8217;s either never heard of Blockchain or simply wants to know more about the technology which is about to transform the world we live in for the better. What is blockchain? Why does everyone from tech experts to business moguls to philanthropists believe it is a paradigm-shifting technology, bound to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blockchain-the-next-everything-stephen-p-williams-abridged/">Blockchain : The Next Everything &#8211; Stephen P Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The perfect book for everybody who&#8217;s either never heard of Blockchain or simply wants to know more about the technology which is about to transform the world we live in for the better.     </p>
<p>                     What is blockchain? Why does everyone from tech experts to business moguls to philanthropists believe it is a paradigm-shifting technology, bound to revolutionize society as significantly as the internet? Indeed, why is blockchain touted as The Next Everything?    </p>
<p>                     In this deft, fascinating, and easy-to-digest introduction to one of the most important innovations of recent times, Stephen P. Williams answers these questions, revealing how cryptocurrencies like bitcoin are just one example among dozens of transformative applications that this relatively new technology makes possible. He interprets the complexity into digestible anecdotes, metaphors, and straightforward descriptions for readers who don&#8217;t know tech, and explains all of blockchain&#8217;s most important aspects: why this so-called digital ledger is unhackable and unchangeable; how its distributed nature may transfer power from central entities like banks, government, and corporations to ordinary citizens around the world; and what its widespread use will mean for society as a whole.    </p>
<p>                     Taking us on a dazzlingly vivid tour through the systems predicted to soon underpin economics, politics, global trade, science, art, and numerous other aspects of our everyday lives, Blockchain: The Next Everything is a truly extraordinary journey into our future. Review&#8221;Finally: a book that engagingly and entertainingly tells you what blockchain is and how it works. It makes clear why it&#8217;s so important for our future, showing how this technology can help with everything from voting rights to economic inequality to corporate transparency to climate change. Stephen P. Williams&#8217; Blockchain: The Next Everything is a must-read for anyone who wants to understand where the world is headed.&#8221; (Hunter Lovins, author of Natural Capitalism and President and Founder of Natural Capitalism Solutions)    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Stephen P. Williams has created a small miracle &#8211; a book about blockchain that helps the rest of us understand what it is, how it works and what the implications are for the future of our world. From the first page to the last, just when you think you know what this book is, it surprises you. By turns poetic, philosophical, explanatory and provocative, Blockchain: The Next Everything is a must-read for anyone who has ever wondered what all the hype is about, and why they should care.&#8221; (Ty Montague, author of True Story and Founder of Co:Collective)    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Shakespeare famously advised readers to be on watch for tides in human history. Now we have blockchain. If you are curious about it, read this book. Stephen P. Williams has created a remarkable and remarkably accessible piece of work on one of the most important topics of our time.&#8221;  (Rye Barcott, author of It Happened on the Way to War and co-founder of Double Time Capital)    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;An astonishing, illuminating tour of a mind-bending new economic model&#8211;written with the verve and page-turning appeal of a novel.  A book for the nerd but especially for the rest of us scratching our tech-terrified heads.  And&#8211;how did he do this?&#8211;it&#8217;s inspiring and fun.&#8221; (Patricia Hampl, author of The Art of the Wasted Day)    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This short introduction to a cutting-edge technology is appealingly informative and hopeful.&#8221; (Publishers Weekly)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blockchain-the-next-everything-stephen-p-williams-abridged/">Blockchain : The Next Everything &#8211; Stephen P Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD. This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career. An MBA at a top business school is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold     </p>
<p>                    ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD.    </p>
<p>                    This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career.    </p>
<p>                    An MBA at a top business school is an enormous investment in time and cash. And if you don&#8217;t want to work for a consulting firm or an investment bank, the chances are it simply isn&#8217;t worth it.    </p>
<p>                    The Personal MBA gives you simple mental models for every subject that&#8217;s key to commercial success. From the basics of products and marketing to the nuances of teamwork and systems, this book distils everything you need to know to take on the MBA graduates and win.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;File this book under: NO EXCUSES&#8217; Seth Godin    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;No matter what they tell you, an MBA is not essential. If you combine reading this book with actually trying stuff, you&#8217;ll be far ahead in the business game&#8217; Kevin Kelly, founder of Wired</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company     </p>
<p>                    What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and delivering value consistently, day in and day out.    </p>
<p>                    In Top of Mind, the cofounder of a leading content marketing company shows you how to create business opportunities by occupying the space at the top of your audience&#8217;s minds-and keeping it there. This groundbreaking book explains how consumer needs and expectations have changed and what this shift means for readers interested in building a brand-whether you&#8217;re a leader in marketing engaging potential customers, a VP of sales bringing in new business, or a director of HR who&#8217;s recruiting the best talent in the industry. It provides effective ways to establish trust and foster connections; maintain transparency and consistency; identify and clearly communicate the &#8220;why&#8221; behind the message; and create processes to make that message part of a brand&#8217;s DNA.     </p>
<p>                    Maintaining a prominent spot in your audience&#8217;s minds will increase the likelihood that the moment they need to make a choice, you&#8217;ll be the first one they call.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Misfit Economy : Lessons in Creativity from Pirates, Hackers, Gangsters and Other Informal Entrepreneurs &#8211; Alexa Clay, Kyra Maya Phillips (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-misfit-economy-lessons-in-creativity-from-pirates-hackers-gangsters-and-other-informal-entrepreneurs-alexa-clay-kyra-maya-phillips-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-misfit-economy-lessons-in-creativity-from-pirates-hackers-gangsters-and-other-informal-entrepreneurs-alexa-clay-kyra-maya-phillips-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Misfit Economy is about people who are just as innovative, entrepreneurial, and visionary as the Jobses, Edisons, and Fords of the world, except they&#8217;re not operating out of Silicon Valley. They&#8217;re in the street markets of Sao Paulo and Guangzhou, the rubbish dumps of Lagos, the flooded coastal towns of Thailand. They are pirates, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-misfit-economy-lessons-in-creativity-from-pirates-hackers-gangsters-and-other-informal-entrepreneurs-alexa-clay-kyra-maya-phillips-abridged/">The Misfit Economy : Lessons in Creativity from Pirates, Hackers, Gangsters and Other Informal Entrepreneurs &#8211; Alexa Clay, Kyra Maya Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Misfit Economy is about people who are just as innovative, entrepreneurial, and visionary as the Jobses, Edisons, and Fords of the world, except they&#8217;re not operating out of Silicon Valley. They&#8217;re in the street markets of Sao Paulo and Guangzhou, the rubbish dumps of Lagos, the flooded coastal towns of Thailand. They are pirates, slum dwellers, computer hackers, dissidents, and inner city gang members.<br />
                         Across the globe, diverse innovators are working in the black, grey, and informal economies to develop solutions to myriad challenges. Far from being &#8220;deviant entrepreneurs&#8221; that pose threats to our social and economic stability, these innovators display remarkable ingenuity, pioneering original methods and best practices that we can learn from and apply to formal markets in urgent need of change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-misfit-economy-lessons-in-creativity-from-pirates-hackers-gangsters-and-other-informal-entrepreneurs-alexa-clay-kyra-maya-phillips-abridged/">The Misfit Economy : Lessons in Creativity from Pirates, Hackers, Gangsters and Other Informal Entrepreneurs &#8211; Alexa Clay, Kyra Maya Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rocket: Eight Lessons to Secure Infinite Growth &#8211; Michael Silverstein, Dylan Bolden, Rune Jacobsen, Rohan Sajdeh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rocket-eight-lessons-to-secure-infinite-growth-michael-silverstein-dylan-bolden-rune-jacobsen-rohan-sajdeh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rocket-eight-lessons-to-secure-infinite-growth-michael-silverstein-dylan-bolden-rune-jacobsen-rohan-sajdeh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Make profits soar by converting casual consumers into apostles Rocket showcases the stories of sixteen entrepreneurs. It draws out the lessons that you can apply Monday morning in your business. Authentic and specific Boston Consulting Group case studies about the rocketeers/inventors who created brand legacies. For everyone who wants a business to grow faster than [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rocket-eight-lessons-to-secure-infinite-growth-michael-silverstein-dylan-bolden-rune-jacobsen-rohan-sajdeh-abridged/">Rocket: Eight Lessons to Secure Infinite Growth &#8211; Michael Silverstein, Dylan Bolden, Rune Jacobsen, Rohan Sajdeh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Make profits soar by converting casual consumers into apostles    </p>
<p>                    Rocket showcases the stories of sixteen entrepreneurs. It draws out the lessons that you can apply Monday morning in your business. Authentic and specific Boston Consulting Group case studies about the rocketeers/inventors who created brand legacies.    </p>
<p>                    For everyone who wants a business to grow faster than a competitor-this motivating book gives you a step-by-step approach to growth, share gain, and higher profits.    </p>
<p>                    Michael Silverstein  is a senior partner and managing director of the consumer practice at BCG.    </p>
<p>                    Dylan Bolden  is a senior partner and managing director at BCG.    </p>
<p>                    Rune Jacobsen  is a senior partner and managing director at BCG    </p>
<p>                    Rohan Sajdeh  is a senior partner and managing director at BCG.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rocket-eight-lessons-to-secure-infinite-growth-michael-silverstein-dylan-bolden-rune-jacobsen-rohan-sajdeh-abridged/">Rocket: Eight Lessons to Secure Infinite Growth &#8211; Michael Silverstein, Dylan Bolden, Rune Jacobsen, Rohan Sajdeh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Imperfect Courage: Live a Life of Purpose by Leaving Comfort and Going Anyway &#8211; Jessica Honegger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/imperfect-courage-live-a-life-of-purpose-by-leaving-comfort-and-going-anyway-jessica-honegger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/imperfect-courage-live-a-life-of-purpose-by-leaving-comfort-and-going-anyway-jessica-honegger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Want to make a move but scared to leave your comfort zone? Go anyway. &#8220;Jessica&#8217;s perspective of global sisterhood and the power of lifting each other up in the midst of fear and scarcity is exactly what we need today. This book is both an invitation and a challenge to bravely show up for ourselves, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imperfect-courage-live-a-life-of-purpose-by-leaving-comfort-and-going-anyway-jessica-honegger-abridged/">Imperfect Courage: Live a Life of Purpose by Leaving Comfort and Going Anyway &#8211; Jessica Honegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Want to make a move but scared to leave your comfort zone? Go anyway.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Jessica&#8217;s perspective of global sisterhood and the power of lifting each other up in the midst of fear and scarcity is exactly what we need today. This book is both an invitation and a challenge to bravely show up for ourselves, for the people we love, and for the strangers that we will one day call family. I say, Amen!&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;Bren Brown, Ph.D., Author of the #1 New York Times bestseller Braving the Wilderness     </p>
<p>                     In Imperfect Courage, the founder of the popular fair trade jewelry brand Noonday Collection shares her story of starting the rapid-growing business that impacts over 4,500 artisans in vulnerable communities across the globe&#8211;and invites readers on a journey of transformation, challenging them to trade their comfort zones for a life of impact and adventure.    </p>
<p>                     In 2015, Inc. magazine recognized Noonday Collection as one of the fastest-growing companies in America. But years earlier, as Jessica Honegger stood at a pawn-shop counter in Austin, Texas, and handed over her grandmother&#8217;s gold jewelry, her goal was much more personal: to fund the adoption of her Rwandan son, Jack, by selling artisan-made jewelry.     </p>
<p>                     This first step launched an unexpected side-hustle that would grow into Noonday Collection. Jessica embarked on this new journey and teamed up with her first artisan partner, Jalia, a Ugandan jewelry maker. She saw the meaningful impact Noonday brought to Jalia&#8217;s community and knew it was the right move.     </p>
<p>                     Fear crept into Jessica&#8217;s heart as she realized her success, or failure, meant the same for Jalia. But refusing to let fear hinder her goals, Jessica found the necessary (if imperfect) courage she needed along the way&#8211;the courage to leave comfort and embrace a life of risk and impact.     </p>
<p>                     Discover Your Imperfect Courage<br />
                     In Imperfect Courage, Jessica takes you by the hand and invites you to trade your comfort zone for a life of impact and meaning.     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; First, she invites you to draw a circle of compassion around yourself and leads you through some soul-searching aimed at setting you free from shame.<br />
                     &#8211; Next, she challenges all of us to come together, dare to be vulnerable with one another, and commit to building a culture of collaboration.<br />
                     &#8211; Finally, Jessica calls on you to broaden your circle of compassion to embrace the entire globe&#8211;and to bring your beautifully imperfect courage to a world that needs you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imperfect-courage-live-a-life-of-purpose-by-leaving-comfort-and-going-anyway-jessica-honegger-abridged/">Imperfect Courage: Live a Life of Purpose by Leaving Comfort and Going Anyway &#8211; Jessica Honegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Create a personal &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence to spark professional and personal success&#8221;Other people have the answers, deals, money, access, power, and influence you need to get what you want in this world. To achieve any goal, you need other people to help you do it.&#8221; &#8212; JUDY ROBINETT As anyone in business knows, strategic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/">How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Create a personal &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence to spark professional and personal success&#8221;Other people have the answers, deals, money, access, power, and influence you need to get what you want in this world. To achieve any goal, you need other people to help you do it.&#8221; &#8212; JUDY ROBINETT    </p>
<p>                    As anyone in business knows, strategic planning iscritical to achieving long-term success. In How to Be a Power Connector, super-networker Judy Robinett argues that strategic relationship planning should be your top priority.    </p>
<p>                    When you combine your specific skills and talents with a clear, workable path for creating and managing your relationships, nothing will stop you from meeting your goals. With high-value connections, you&#8217;ll tap into a dynamic &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence guaranteed to accelerate your personal and professional success.    </p>
<p>                    Robinett uses her decades of experience connecting the world&#8217;s highest achievers with one another to help you build high-value relationships. She reveals all the secrets of her trade, including proven ways to:    </p>
<p>                    Find and enter the best network &#8220;ecosystem&#8221; to meet your goalsReach even the most unreachable people quickly and effectivelyGet anyone&#8217;s contact information within 30 secondsCreate a &#8220;3-D connection&#8221; that adds value to multiple people at the same timeAccess key infl uencers through industry and community eventsSubtly seed conversation with information about interests and needsUse social media to your best advantage    </p>
<p>                    Robinett has based her methods on solid researchproving that social groups begin to break up when they become larger than 150 people, and that 50 members is the optimal size for group communication. As such, she has developed what she calls the &#8220;5+50+100&#8243; method: contact your top 5 connections daily, your Key 50 weekly, and your Vital 100 monthly. this is your power grid, and it will work wonders for your career.    </p>
<p>                    Nothing will stop you when you learn How to Be aPower Connector.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR HOW TO BE A POWER CONNECTOR:&#8221;Unlike many books in this genre, this one is written by a woman who has lived it.. . . Judy Robinett offers guidance on how to form authentic relationships thatbring mutual benefits.&#8221; &#8212; ADAM GRANT, Wharton professor and New York Times bestselling author of Give and Take    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;How to Be a Power Connector is like an MBA in networking: an advanced course in finding and developing quality relationships with the people who can make the biggest difference in your professional success.&#8221; &#8212; IVAN MISNER, founder and chairman of BNI    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Talk about power! Follow Judy Robinett&#8217;s logical, straightforward, and helpfully detailed advice, and you can be a &#8216;Power Connector&#8217; yourself! Great ideas, wellpresented, with no &#8216;wasted space&#8217; in her argument!&#8221; &#8212; DON PEPPERS, coauthor of Extreme Trust: Honesty as a Competitive Advantage    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Absolutely brilliant. A step-by-step guide to building a network that will be both invaluable to you and just as valuable to those whose lives you will now have theopportunity to touch. I can&#8217;t imagine a more powerful book for one who truly desires to be a Power Connector.&#8221; &#8212; BOB BURG, coauthor of The Go-Giver and author of Adversaries into Allies    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In the C-Suite or in your personal life everything comes down to the quality of your relationships. Judy&#8217;s book helps you attract and maintain the relationships that will get you what you want most. Be a super connector now!&#8221; &#8212; JEFFREY HAYZLETT, TV host and bestselling author of Running the Gauntlet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/">How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes the simplest and most effective investment strategy for building wealth over the long term: buy and hold, at very low cost, a mutual fund that tracks the S&#038;P 500 Stock Index. Such an index portfolio is the only investment that guarantees your fair share of stock market returns. This strategy is favored by Warren Buffett, who has endorsed this best selling 10th Anniversary Edition. The book shows you how to make index investing work for you and help you achieve your financial goals, cut through the hype to see what&#8217;s really in your best interest, and analyze the metrics that truly matter. You&#8217;ll gain candid insight from some of the world&#8217;s best financial minds: not only Warren Buffett, but Benjamin Graham, Paul Samuelson, Burton Malkiel, and others.<br />
                    Updated with current data and laced with two new chapters on asset allocation and retirement investing, the new Little Book of Common Sense Investing gives you a solid strategy for building your financial future. * Build a broadly diversified, low-cost portfolio without the risks of individual stocks, manager selection, and sector rotation * Forget the fads and focus on what works in the real world * Emphasize business reality over market expectations * Understand how index investing is the only game that assures your fair share of stock market returns Too many investors trade franticly, turning a winners game into a losers game, while index investing allows you to sit back and let the market do the work for you. Learn how to harness the magic of compounding returns while avoiding the tyranny of compounding costs. Bogle describes his simple method for developing rational expectations for future market returns, and what he sees coming over the next decade.  The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the guidebook to your financial future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW* In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement. &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW*    </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New York Magazine    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compellingly motivational read&#8217; The Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book you need in your life&#8217; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                    *Winner of the 2014 Goodreads Choice Award for Best Business Book*    </p>
<p>                    In the space of ten years, Sophia Amoruso has gone from high-school dropout to founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal, one of the fastest-growing retailers in the world.     </p>
<p>                    Sophia&#8217;s never been a typical executive, or a typical anything, and she&#8217;s written #GIRLBOSS for other girls like her: outsiders (and insiders) seeking a unique path to success.    </p>
<p>                    Filled with brazen wake-up calls, cunning and frank observations, and behind-the-scenes stories from Nasty Gal&#8217;s meteoric rise, #GIRLBOSS covers a lot of ground. It proves that success doesn&#8217;t come from where you went to college or how popular you were in school. Success is about trusting your instincts and following your gut, knowing which rules to follow and which to break.    </p>
<p>                    Inspiring, motivating and empowering, #GIRLBOSS will give you the kick up the ass you need to reach your potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits and Other Writings &#8211; Philip A. Fisher, Introduction byKenneth L. Fisher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Widely respected and admired, Philip Fisher is among the most influential investors of all time. His investment philosophies, introduced almost forty years ago, are not only studied and applied by today&#8217;s financiers and investors, but are also regarded by many as gospel. This book is invaluable reading and has been since it was first published [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/">Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits and Other Writings &#8211; Philip A. Fisher, Introduction byKenneth L. Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Widely respected and admired, Philip Fisher is among the most influential investors of all time. His investment philosophies, introduced almost forty years ago, are not only studied and applied by today&#8217;s financiers and investors, but are also regarded by many as gospel. This book is invaluable reading and has been since it was first published in 1958. The updated paperback retains the investment wisdom of the original edition and includes the perspectives of the author&#8217;s son Ken Fisher, an investment guru in his own right in an expanded preface and introduction &#8220;I sought out Phil Fisher after reading his Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits&#8230;A thorough understanding of the business, obtained by using Phil&#8217;s techniques&#8230;enables one to make intelligent investment commitments.&#8221; Warren Buffet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/">Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits and Other Writings &#8211; Philip A. Fisher, Introduction byKenneth L. Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Job-Ready Guide : How to Set Yourself Up for Career Success &#8211; Anastasia de Waal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-job-ready-guide-how-to-set-yourself-up-for-career-success-anastasia-de-waal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-job-ready-guide-how-to-set-yourself-up-for-career-success-anastasia-de-waal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To get the career you want, you need to be job-ready. This is your all-in-one guide to understanding what employers want and how to prepare yourself with a personal career plan. From gaining work experience, to mastering essential skills and acing the application process, The Job-Ready Guide is a complete resource for standing out from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-job-ready-guide-how-to-set-yourself-up-for-career-success-anastasia-de-waal-abridged/">The Job-Ready Guide : How to Set Yourself Up for Career Success &#8211; Anastasia de Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To get the career you want, you need to be job-ready. This is your all-in-one guide to understanding what employers want and how to prepare yourself with a personal career plan. From gaining work experience, to mastering essential skills and acing the application process, The Job-Ready Guide is a complete resource for standing out from the crowd and getting a job offer. It shows you how to build a strong CV, write an impressive cover letter, excel at interviews, and cultivate the professionalism that employers want.    </p>
<p>                    Moving from education into the workplace can be a challenge: the world of work demands skills that you may never have had to truly use &#8211; or think about &#8211; before. The Job-Ready Guide will help you to boost your employability, covering everything you need to prepare for and start a successful career. You&#8217;ll be able to conduct a systematic job search, learn how to network and develop a personal brand online, as well as hone valuable skills including leadership, teamwork, creativity and problem-solving. A highly practical, hands-on guide, this book is packed with useful features, including interactive exercises to help you in your real life; insider advice from employers; and tips from professionals at different stages in their careers who reveal &#8216;what they wish they&#8217;d known&#8217;.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-job-ready-guide-how-to-set-yourself-up-for-career-success-anastasia-de-waal-abridged/">The Job-Ready Guide : How to Set Yourself Up for Career Success &#8211; Anastasia de Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With must-have updates, a new edition of the bestselling method that shows how anyone can turn their one simple idea into millions &#8211; without lifting a finger! Stephen Key is an award-winning inventor who has licensed more than 20 product ideas. In 2011, he shared the secrets to his success in the bestselling book One [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/">One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With must-have updates, a new edition of the bestselling method that shows how anyone can turn their one simple idea into millions &#8211; without lifting a finger!    </p>
<p>                     Stephen Key is an award-winning inventor who has licensed more than 20 product ideas. In 2011, he shared the secrets to his success in the bestselling book One Simple Idea. Since that time, many changes have occurred in the entrepreneurial world.    </p>
<p>                    One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition has been revised and updated to reflect current trends and practices in the industry. In addition to teaching readers how to turn their ideas into marketable products that companies will want to license, Key expands upon his cutting-edge product development, sales, and negotiation strategies, making note of the new opportunities and technologies available to creative people today. The book also features real-life success stories from people who have used the author&#8217;s strategies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/">One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brotopia &#8211; IntervieweeEmily Chang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brotopia-interviewee-emily-chang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brotopia-interviewee-emily-chang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Instant National Bestseller A PBS NewsHour-New York Times Book Club Pick! Excellent. &#8211;San Francisco Chronicle Brotopia is more than a business book. Silicon Valley holds extraordinary power over our present lives as well as whatever utopia (or nightmare) might come next. &#8211;New York Times Silicon Valley is a modern utopia where anyone can change the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brotopia-interviewee-emily-chang-abridged/">Brotopia &#8211; IntervieweeEmily Chang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Instant National Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    A PBS NewsHour-New York Times Book Club Pick!     </p>
<p>                    Excellent. &#8211;San Francisco Chronicle     </p>
<p>                    Brotopia is more than a business book. Silicon Valley holds extraordinary power over our present lives as well as whatever utopia (or nightmare) might come next. &#8211;New York Times     </p>
<p>                    Silicon Valley is a modern utopia where anyone can change the world. Unless you&#8217;re a woman.     </p>
<p>                    For women in tech, Silicon Valley is not a fantasyland of unicorns, virtual reality rainbows, and 3D-printed lollipops, where millions of dollars grow on trees. It&#8217;s a Brotopia, where men hold all the cards and make all the rules. Vastly outnumbered, women face toxic workplaces rife with discrimination and sexual harassment, where investors take meetings in hot tubs and network at sex parties.     </p>
<p>                    In this powerful expos, Bloomberg TV journalist Emily Chang reveals how Silicon Valley got so sexist despite its utopian ideals, why bro culture endures despite decades of companies claiming the moral high ground (Don&#8217;t Be Evil! Connect the World!)&#8211;and how women are finally starting to speak out and fight back.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on her deep network of Silicon Valley insiders, Chang opens the boardroom doors of male-dominated venture capital firms like Kleiner Perkins, the subject of Ellen Pao&#8217;s high-profile gender discrimination lawsuit, and Sequoia, where a partner once famously said they won&#8217;t lower their standards just to hire women. Interviews with Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg, YouTube CEO Susan Wojcicki, and former Yahoo! CEO Marissa Mayer&#8211;who got their start at Google, where just one in five engineers is a woman&#8211;reveal just how hard it is to crack the Silicon Ceiling. And Chang shows how women such as former Uber engineer Susan Fowler, entrepreneur Niniane Wang, and game developer Brianna Wu, have risked their careers and sometimes their lives to pave a way for other women.     </p>
<p>                    Silicon Valley&#8217;s aggressive, misogynistic, work-at-all costs culture has shut women out of the greatest wealth creation in the history of the world. It&#8217;s time to break up the boys&#8217; club. Emily Chang shows us how to fix this toxic culture&#8211;to bring down Brotopia, once and for all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brotopia-interviewee-emily-chang-abridged/">Brotopia &#8211; IntervieweeEmily Chang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Learning, Home Learning, Distance Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned education writer comes a fascinating examination of the rapidly shifting world of college that every parent, student and educator needs to understand. In 2011-2012, some of the world&#8217;s most famous universities and technology entrepreneurs began a revolution in higher education. College courses that had been kept from all but an elite few [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/">The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned education writer comes a fascinating examination of the rapidly shifting world of college that every parent, student and educator needs to understand.    </p>
<p>                    In 2011-2012, some of the world&#8217;s most famous universities and technology entrepreneurs began a revolution in higher education. College courses that had been kept from all but an elite few were released to students around the world &#8212; for free. And thanks to exploding tuition prices, a volatile global economy and some high-tech innovations, we&#8217;re now poised for a total rethinking of what college is and should be. In the NEW YORK TIMES-bestselling THE END OF COLLEGE, Kevin Carey draws on new research to paint an exciting portrait of the near future of education. He explains how the college experience is being radically altered now and how it will emancipate millions of people around the world. Insightful and readable, THE END OF COLLEGE is an innovative roadmap to understanding tomorrow&#8217;s higher education today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/">The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reach Out: The Simple Strategy You Need to Expand Your Network and Increase Your Influence &#8211; Molly Beck (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reach-out-the-simple-strategy-you-need-to-expand-your-network-and-increase-your-influence-molly-beck-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reach-out-the-simple-strategy-you-need-to-expand-your-network-and-increase-your-influence-molly-beck-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical guide to building valuable career connections-through tools you already have and people you already know Success in life is more than having goals and skills. You need connections. And to get connections, you need to Reach Out-fearlessly, strategically, and every day of the work week. For many, this is a daunting and confusing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reach-out-the-simple-strategy-you-need-to-expand-your-network-and-increase-your-influence-molly-beck-abridged/">Reach Out: The Simple Strategy You Need to Expand Your Network and Increase Your Influence &#8211; Molly Beck (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical guide to building valuable career connections-through tools you already have and people you already know     </p>
<p>                    Success in life is more than having goals and skills. You need connections. And to get connections, you need to Reach Out-fearlessly, strategically, and every day of the work week.     </p>
<p>                    For many, this is a daunting and confusing task.     </p>
<p>                    Reach Out shows readers how to use social media and simple digital tools to begin building and expanding the number of people they know. Author Molly Beck explains how to:    </p>
<p>                    *Establish and strengthen your digital presence     </p>
<p>                    *Develop career goals that Reaching Out can help you obtain     </p>
<p>                    *Think strategically about who you have already met, who you could strengthen a relationship with, and who your current connections know    </p>
<p>                    *Determine who to Reach Out to and push past common networking fears to do it    </p>
<p>                    * Apply step-by-step instructions on how to craft email and social media messages to those you want to connect with    </p>
<p>                    *Optimize your efforts by managing both your time and your inbox     </p>
<p>                    The book features personal stories on networking from some of today&#8217;s top thought leaders. Studies, statistics, and real world examples illustrate the key concepts of Reaching Out. Whether you&#8217;re just starting out, changing jobs, or well-established and just eager to know more people, Reaching Out will help you turn career dreams into professional success by helping you connect with others who can put you on the fast track.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reach-out-the-simple-strategy-you-need-to-expand-your-network-and-increase-your-influence-molly-beck-abridged/">Reach Out: The Simple Strategy You Need to Expand Your Network and Increase Your Influence &#8211; Molly Beck (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related to the way managers treat employees.    </p>
<p>                    Kelsey Young is an optimistic but disillusioned sales associate working her way through college. Her world opens up when one of her professors challenges her to create a culture of service at her workplace by putting the five components of Legendary Service into practice. AlthoughFerguson&#8217;s, the store where Kelsey works, certainly isn&#8217;t known for service excellence, Kelsey believes she can make a positive difference. She quickly learns that culture change isn&#8217;t easy&#8211;and that her role as a frontline employee is more significant than she ever could have imagined.    </p>
<p>                    In characteristic Blanchard style, Legendary Service: The Key Is to Care is a quick and entertainingread for people at all organizational levels in every industry. When applied, its lessons will have a profound impact on the service experience your customers will receive. Whether a CEO or a part-time employee, every person can make a difference&#8211;and customer service iseveryone&#8217;s job.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR LEGENDARY SERVICE:&#8221;Read this book and establish a service culture in your organization.&#8221; &#8212; Horst Schulze, Chairman/CEO, Capella Hotel Group    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Legendary Service has great learnings for people at all organizational levels: for executives and managers, the value of a service culture; and for frontlinestaff, the reality that they are the face of the company and can make a difference. Legendary service&#8211;it&#8217;s everyone, always.&#8221; &#8212; Mark King, CEO and President, TaylorMade Golf    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Everything I know about service I learned from my career at Hilton Hotels, Marriott International, The Walt Disney Company, and Ken Blanchard. The One Minute Manager dramatically changed my thinking 32 years ago. LegendaryService will teach the next generation how to deliver sensational service. Buy it, study it, implement it.&#8221; &#8212; Lee Cockerell, Executive Vice President, Walt Disney World (Retired &#038; Inspired), and author of Creating Magic and The Customer Rules    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Kathy Cuff and Vicki Halsey have created a fantastic customer service model called ICARE. When you add their voices to that of the master storyteller KenBlanchard, you have a masterpiece entitled Legendary Service. It is a must-read for everyone who, like me, has a passion for service.&#8221; &#8212; Colleen Barrett, President Emeritus, Southwest Airlines, and coauthor of Lead with LUV    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken Blanchard has done it again and delivered the right book at the right time. Legendary Service provides the essentials of hospitality and servant leadership in a way that everyone can adopt&#8211;right now&#8211;today!&#8221; &#8212; John Caparella, President and COO,The Venetian, The Palazzo, and Sands Expo    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken, Kathy, and Vicki show us how to change everyday service events into memorable experiences. Their book is a must-read for anyone unwilling to acceptmediocrity.&#8221; &#8212; Leonardo Inghilleri, coauthor ofExceptional Service, Exceptional Profit</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Build a thriving consultancy with the updated edition of this classic bestseller Having inspired generations of consultants and entrepreneurs around the world, the &#8220;Rock Star of Consulting&#8221; Alan Weiss returns with a revised and completely updated edition of his authoritative guide to consulting success. Weiss provides his time-tested model on creating a flourishing consulting business, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/">Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Build a thriving consultancy with the updated edition of this classic bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Having inspired generations of consultants and entrepreneurs around the world, the &#8220;Rock Star of Consulting&#8221; Alan Weiss returns with a revised and completely updated edition of his authoritative guide to consulting success.      </p>
<p>                    Weiss provides his time-tested model on creating a flourishing consulting business, while incorporating and focusing on the many dynamic changes in solo and boutique consulting, coaching, and entrepreneurship. In addition to guidance on raising capital, attracting clients, and creating a marketing plan, he also gives brand new step-by-step advice on:    </p>
<p>                    * Harnessing today&#8217;s global opportunities<br />
                    * Developing brands across markets<br />
                    * Creating and licensing intellectual property<br />
                    * Avoiding the pitfalls of social media<br />
                    * Landing unsolicited referrals through counterintuitive methods<br />
                    * Managing and organizing your time wisely<br />
                    * Succeeding in the face of continuing turbulence    </p>
<p>                    Find out why this book has been the classic go-to for consultants for nearly twenty-five years, and learn how to grow your business into a $1 million-per-year firm today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/">Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The basis for a major documentary, two leading experts sound an urgent call for the radical reimagining of American education so we can equip students for the realities of the twenty-first-century economy. We prize academic achievement, pressuring our children to get into the &#8220;right&#8221; colleges, have the highest GPAs, and pursue advanced degrees. But while [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/">Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The basis for a major documentary, two leading experts sound an urgent call for the radical reimagining of American education so we can equip students for the realities of the twenty-first-century economy.<br />
                         We prize academic achievement, pressuring our children to get into the &#8220;right&#8221; colleges, have the highest GPAs, and pursue advanced degrees. But while students may graduate with credentials, by and large they lack the competencies needed to be thoughtful, engaged citizens and to get good jobs in our rapidly evolving economy. Alarmingly, our methods of schooling crush the creativity and initiative young people really need to thrive in the twenty-first century.<br />
                         Now bestselling author and education expert Tony Wagner and venture capitalist Ted Dintersmith call for a complete overhaul of American schools, sharing insights and stories from the front lines. Their powerful, urgent message identifies the growing gap between credentials and competence-and offers a framework for change.<br />
                        Most Likely to Succeed presents a new vision of American education, one that puts wonder, creativity, and initiative at the very heart of the learning process and prepares students for today&#8217;s economy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/">Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
