<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Animals &amp; Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/animals-society/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/animals-society/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Animals &amp; Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/animals-society/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Alex &#038; Me &#8211; Irene Pepperberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alex-me-irene-pepperberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animals & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Birds (ornithology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Birds, Including Cage Birds, As Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Animals & Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alex-me-irene-pepperberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Alex &#038; Me is the remarkable true story of an extraordinary relationship between psychologist Irene M. Pepperberg and Alex, an African Grey parrot who proved scientists and accepted wisdom wrong by demonstrating an astonishing ability to communicate and understand complex ideas. A New York Times bestseller and selected as one of the paper&#8217;s Top Ten [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alex-me-irene-pepperberg-abridged/">Alex &#038; Me &#8211; Irene Pepperberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Alex &#038; Me is the remarkable true story of an extraordinary relationship between psychologist Irene M. Pepperberg and Alex, an African Grey parrot who proved scientists and accepted wisdom wrong by demonstrating an astonishing ability to communicate and understand complex ideas. A New York Times bestseller and selected as one of the paper&#8217;s Top Ten Books of the Year, Alex &#038; Me is much more that the story of an incredible scientific breakthrough. It&#8217;s a poignant love story and an affectionate remembrance of Pepperberg&#8217;s irascible, unforgettable, and always surprising best friend.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alex-me-irene-pepperberg-abridged/">Alex &#038; Me &#8211; Irene Pepperberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agronomy & Crop Production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Husbandry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animals & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made the most courageous decision of her life: a commitment to change things.    </p>
<p>                     Driven by impulsive will and searing passion, Sonia left behind everything she knew and loved to search the planet for solutions to benefit animals, human health, and the environment. Over the course of living with farmers, hitchhiking with strangers, and risking her life, she developed surprising insights and solutions-both about the food industry and herself.    </p>
<p>                     Lively and heartfelt, Sonia takes readers on an unforgettable adventure from top-secret egg warehouses in Canada to dairy feedlots in the United States, from farm offices in Mexico to lush pastures in Belize, from flocks of village chickens in Indonesia to factory farms in Malaysia.    </p>
<p>                     Revelatory in scope, Project Animal Farm illuminates a hidden world that plays a part in all of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Words : What Animals Think and Feel &#8211; Carl Safina (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-words-what-animals-think-and-feel-carl-safina-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animals & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-words-what-animals-think-and-feel-carl-safina-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I wanted to know what they were experiencing, and why to us they feel so compelling, and so-close. This time I allowed myself to ask them the question that for a scientist was forbidden fruit: Who are you? Weaving decades of field observations with exciting new discoveries about the brain, Carl Safina&#8217;s landmark book offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-words-what-animals-think-and-feel-carl-safina-abridged/">Beyond Words : What Animals Think and Feel &#8211; Carl Safina (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I wanted to know what they were experiencing, and why to us they feel so compelling, and so-close. This time I allowed myself to ask them the question that for a scientist was forbidden fruit: Who are you?     </p>
<p>                    Weaving decades of field observations with exciting new discoveries about the brain, Carl Safina&#8217;s landmark book offers an intimate view of animal behavior to challenge the fixed boundary between humans and nonhuman animals. In Beyond Words, readers travel to Amboseli National Park in the threatened landscape of Kenya and witness struggling elephant families work out how to survive poaching and drought, then to Yellowstone National Park to observe wolves sort out the aftermath of one pack&#8217;s personal tragedy, and finally plunge into the astonishingly peaceful society of killer whales living in the crystalline waters of the Pacific Northwest.     </p>
<p>                    Beyond Words brings forth powerful and illuminating insight into the unique personalities of animals through extraordinary stories of animal joy, grief, jealousy, anger, and love. The similarity between human and nonhuman consciousness, self-awareness, and empathy calls us to re-evaluate how we interact with animals. Wise, passionate, and eye-opening at every turn, Beyond Words is ultimately a graceful examination of humanity&#8217;s place in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-words-what-animals-think-and-feel-carl-safina-abridged/">Beyond Words : What Animals Think and Feel &#8211; Carl Safina (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
