<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Coping With Personal Problems Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/coping-with-personal-problems/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/coping-with-personal-problems/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Coping With Personal Problems Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/coping-with-personal-problems/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Macho Paradox : Why Some Men Hurt Women and and How All Men Can Help &#8211; Jackson Katz</title>
		<link>/the-macho-paradox-why-some-men-hurt-women-and-and-how-all-men-can-help-jackson-katz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Men]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-macho-paradox-why-some-men-hurt-women-and-and-how-all-men-can-help-jackson-katz/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praise for The Macho Paradox &#8220;An honest, intellectually rigorous and insightful work that challenges readers to truly engage in a political discourse that can change lives, communities and nations.&#8221; &#8211;Rosalind Wiseman, author of Queen Bees and Wannabes &#8220;Jackson Katz is an American hero! With integrity and courage, he has taken his message&#8211;that the epidemic of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-macho-paradox-why-some-men-hurt-women-and-and-how-all-men-can-help-jackson-katz/">The Macho Paradox : Why Some Men Hurt Women and and How All Men Can Help &#8211; Jackson Katz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praise for The Macho Paradox</p>
<p>                    &#8220;An honest, intellectually rigorous and insightful work that challenges readers to truly engage in a political discourse that can change lives, communities and nations.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Rosalind Wiseman, author of Queen Bees and Wannabes</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jackson Katz is an American hero! With integrity and courage, he has taken his message&#8211;that the epidemic of violence against women is a men&#8217;s issue&#8211;into athletic terms, the military and frat houses across the country. His book explains carefully and convincingly why&#8211;and how&#8211;men can become part of the solution, and work with women to build a world in which everyone is safer.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    &#8211;Michael Kimmel, author of Manhood in America, spokesperson, National Organization for Men Against Sexism (NOMAS)</p>
<p>                    &#8220;If only men would read Katz&#8217;s book, it could serve as a potent form of male consciousness-raising.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Publishers Weekly</p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book leaves no man behind when it comes to taking violence against women personally&#8230;.After reading this book you can see how important it is to be a stand-up guy and not a standy-by guy, no matter what race or culture you come from.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Alfred L. McMichael, 14th Sergeant Major of the Marine Corps and now serving as the Sergeant Major of NATO</p>
<p>                    &#8220;A candid look at the cultural factors that lend themselves to tolerance of abuse and violence against women.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8220;These pages will empower both men and women to end the scourge of male violence and abuse. Katz knows how to cut to the core of the issues, demonstrating undeniably that stopping the degradation of women should be every man&#8217;s priority.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Lundy Bancroft, author of Why Does He Do That?: Inside the Minds of Angry and Controlling Men</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-macho-paradox-why-some-men-hurt-women-and-and-how-all-men-can-help-jackson-katz/">The Macho Paradox : Why Some Men Hurt Women and and How All Men Can Help &#8211; Jackson Katz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</title>
		<link>/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8211; Over five million copies sold worldwide! From renowned psychiatrist Dr. David D. Burns, the revolutionary volume that popularized Dr. Aaron T. Beck&#8217;s cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) and has helped millions combat feelings of depression and develop greater self-esteem. Anxiety and depression are the most common mental illnesses in the world, affecting 18% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/">Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8211; Over five million copies sold worldwide!</p>
<p>                    From renowned psychiatrist Dr. David D. Burns, the revolutionary volume that popularized Dr. Aaron T. Beck&#8217;s cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) and has helped millions combat feelings of depression and develop greater self-esteem.</p>
<p>                    Anxiety and depression are the most common mental illnesses in the world, affecting 18% of the U.S. population every year. But for many, the path to recovery seems daunting, endless, or completely out of reach.</p>
<p>                    The good news is that anxiety, guilt, pessimism, procrastination, low self-esteem, and other black holes of depression can be alleviated. In Feeling Good, eminent psychiatrist, David D. Burns, M.D., outlines the remarkable, scientifically proven techniques that will immediately lift your spirits and help you develop a positive outlook on life, enabling you to: Nip negative feelings in the budRecognize what causes your mood swingsDeal with guiltHandle hostility and criticismOvercome addiction to love and approvalBuild self-esteemFeel good everyday</p>
<p>                    This groundbreaking, life-changing book has helped millions overcome negative thoughts and discover joy in their daily lives. You owe it to yourself to FEEL GOOD!</p>
<p>                    I would personally evaluate David Burns&#8217; Feeling Good as one of the most significant books to come out of the last third of the Twentieth Century. ?- Dr. David F. Maas, Professor of English, Ambassador University</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/">Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Family Next Door : The Heartbreaking Imprisonment of the Thirteen Turpin Siblings and Their Extraordinary Rescue &#8211; John Glatt</title>
		<link>/the-family-next-door-the-heartbreaking-imprisonment-of-the-thirteen-turpin-siblings-and-their-extraordinary-rescue-john-glatt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-family-next-door-the-heartbreaking-imprisonment-of-the-thirteen-turpin-siblings-and-their-extraordinary-rescue-john-glatt/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times bestselling true crime author John Glatt comes the devastating story of the Turpins: a seemingly normal family whose dark secrets would shock and captivate the world. On January 14, 2018, a seventeen-year-old girl climbed out of the window of her Perris, California home and dialed 911 on a borrowed cell phone. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-family-next-door-the-heartbreaking-imprisonment-of-the-thirteen-turpin-siblings-and-their-extraordinary-rescue-john-glatt/">The Family Next Door : The Heartbreaking Imprisonment of the Thirteen Turpin Siblings and Their Extraordinary Rescue &#8211; John Glatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times bestselling true crime author John Glatt comes the devastating story of the Turpins: a seemingly normal family whose dark secrets would shock and captivate the world.  </p>
<p>                    On January 14, 2018, a seventeen-year-old girl climbed out of the window of her Perris, California home and dialed 911 on a borrowed cell phone. Struggling to stay calm, she told the operator that she and her 12 siblings&#8211;ranging in age from 2 to 29&#8211;were being abused by their parents. When the dispatcher asked for her address, the girl hesitated. &#8220;I&#8217;ve never been out,&#8221; she stammered. </p>
<p>                    To their family, neighbors, and online friends, Louise and David Turpin presented a picture of domestic bliss: dressing their thirteen children in matching outfits and buying them expensive gifts. But what police discovered when they entered the Turpin family home would eclipse the most shocking child abuse cases in history. For years, David and Louise had kept their children in increasing isolation, trapping them in a sinister world of torture, fear, and near starvation. </p>
<p>                    In the first major account of the case, investigative journalist John Glatt delves into the disturbing details and recounts the bravery of the thirteen siblings in the face of unimaginable horror.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-family-next-door-the-heartbreaking-imprisonment-of-the-thirteen-turpin-siblings-and-their-extraordinary-rescue-john-glatt/">The Family Next Door : The Heartbreaking Imprisonment of the Thirteen Turpin Siblings and Their Extraordinary Rescue &#8211; John Glatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deliver Me From Evil : A Sadistic Foster Mother, A Childhood Torn Apart &#8211; Alloma Gilbert</title>
		<link>/deliver-me-from-evil-a-sadistic-foster-mother-a-childhood-torn-apart-alloma-gilbert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deliver-me-from-evil-a-sadistic-foster-mother-a-childhood-torn-apart-alloma-gilbert/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When I was a little girl I believed what I was told over and over again: that I was evil, that I deserved to be tortured because I was the Devil&#8217;s child . . .&#8217; In April 2007 foster-mother Eunice Spry was sentenced to fourteen years in prison for her sadistic abuse of the children [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deliver-me-from-evil-a-sadistic-foster-mother-a-childhood-torn-apart-alloma-gilbert/">Deliver Me From Evil : A Sadistic Foster Mother, A Childhood Torn Apart &#8211; Alloma Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When I was a little girl I believed what I was told over and over again: that I was evil, that I deserved to be tortured because I was the Devil&#8217;s child . . .&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     In April 2007 foster-mother Eunice Spry was sentenced to fourteen years in prison for her sadistic abuse of the children in her care. The details of her cruelty were so sickening they shocked the country. Alloma Gilbert was one of Spry&#8217;s young victims, sent to live with her at the age of six and left at her mercy for eleven brutal years.    </p>
<p>                     Eunice used her own twisted religious beliefs as an excuse for punishing her foster children. When she took them to live on an isolated farmhouse, the abuse escalated to terrifying levels &#8211; a stick was thrust down Alloma&#8217;s throat so often it was stained red with blood, she was starved for over a year and survived only by secretly eating pigswill, and the vicious beatings were relentless. At the age of seventeen she finally escaped but, alone in the outside world, she fell prey to abusive men. It was the birth of her baby daughter that saved her, that finally taught her what love really is. Written with powerful honesty,  Deliver Me From Evil is a moving and inspiring story of survival.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deliver-me-from-evil-a-sadistic-foster-mother-a-childhood-torn-apart-alloma-gilbert/">Deliver Me From Evil : A Sadistic Foster Mother, A Childhood Torn Apart &#8211; Alloma Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Period Power : Harness Your Hormones and Get Your Cycle Working For You &#8211; Maisie Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gynaecology & Obstetrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Reproduction, Growth & Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Midwifery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hill&#8217;s advice is straightforward and no-nonsense&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian &#8216;A life-transforming book&#8230; fascinating &#8211; Daily Mail &#8216;Maisie Hill has written a bloody brilliant book (pun intended). Everything you need to know about periods and how they affect you and your life is here. It&#8217;s revolutionary&#8217; &#8211; Miranda Sawyer &#8216;Thank GOODNESS for Maisie Hill! Flipping open [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/">Period Power : Harness Your Hormones and Get Your Cycle Working For You &#8211; Maisie Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hill&#8217;s advice is straightforward and no-nonsense&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A life-transforming book&#8230; fascinating &#8211; Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Maisie Hill has written a bloody brilliant book (pun intended). Everything you need to know about periods and how they affect you and your life is here. It&#8217;s revolutionary&#8217; &#8211; Miranda Sawyer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thank GOODNESS for Maisie Hill! Flipping open the lid on a vital conversation. It&#8217;s about time we claimed the power of our periods!&#8217; &#8211; Gemma Cairney, broadcaster &#038; co-founder of Boom Shakalaka Productions    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is such an important book. Maisie&#8217;s insights and cycle strategy have changed my life and my cycle. Period Power is written with such intelligence, humour and a deep understanding of women&#8217;s health. If you have a period you need to read this book.&#8217; &#8211; Anna Jones, author of The Modern Cook&#8217;s Year    </p>
<p>                    A profound and practical blueprint for aligning daily life with your menstrual cycle.    </p>
<p>                    Period Power is the handbook to periods and hormones that will leave you wondering why the hell nobody told you this sooner.    </p>
<p>                    The hormones of the menstrual cycle profoundly influence our energy, mood and behaviour, but all too often we&#8217;re taught that our hormones make us unreliable, moody bitches, or that it&#8217;s our lot in life to put up with &#8216;women&#8217;s problems&#8217;. Maisie Hill, a women&#8217;s health practitioner, knows the power of working with the menstrual cycle and refuses to accept this theory. Instead, Maisie believes that our hormones are there to serve us and, if utilized correctly, can be used to help you get what you want out of life. Yes, we are hormonal, and that&#8217;s a very good thing.    </p>
<p>                    This revolutionary book reveals everything you need to know about taking control of your menstrual cycle and outlines The Cycle Strategy to help us perform at our best, throughout our cycle. In Period Power you will discover how to:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; maximise your natural superpowers each month while making adjustments for the darker days, and use Maisie&#8217;s favourite tips to improve them<br />
                    &#8211; identify your personal patterns, powers and pitfalls for each phase of the menstrual cycle<br />
                    &#8211; plan your month to perform at your best in all aspects of your life<br />
                    &#8211; figure out if you have a hormonal imbalance and what to do about it.    </p>
<p>                    Period Power is a no-nonsense guide with all the tools you need to improve your menstrual health.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/">Period Power : Harness Your Hormones and Get Your Cycle Working For You &#8211; Maisie Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Separation & Divorce]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>_____________________________ Is having &#8216;somebody to love&#8217; the most important thing in your life? Do you constantly believe in Mr Right, and that being with him would guarantee you would no longer feel depressed or lonely? Are you bored with &#8216;nice guys&#8217; who are open, honest and dependable? If being in love means being in pain, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/">Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>_____________________________<br />
                    Is having &#8216;somebody to love&#8217; the most important thing in your life?<br />
                    Do you constantly believe in Mr Right, and that being with him would guarantee you would no longer feel depressed or lonely?<br />
                    Are you bored with &#8216;nice guys&#8217; who are open, honest and dependable?     </p>
<p>                    If being in love means being in pain, this book was written for you. Leading relationship and marriage therapist Robin Norwood describes loving too much as a pattern of thoughts and behaviour, which certain women develop as a response to problems from childhood.     </p>
<p>                    Many women find themselves repeatedly drawn into unhappy and destructive relationships with men. They then struggle to make these doomed relationships work. This bestselling relationship self-help book investigates and reveals how powerfully addictive these unhealthy relationships are &#8211; but also gives a very specific programme for recovery from the disease of loving too much, a problem that plagues women everywhere.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/">Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in their working lives.    </p>
<p>                    Overcoming Mobbing is an informative, comprehensive guidebook written for the victims of mobbing and their families who often can&#8217;t make sense of the experience or mobilize resources for recovery. In an engaging, reader-friendly style, the book distinguishes mobbing from bullying in that it takes place within organizational or institutional settings and involves organizational dynamics. Mobbing is not about the occasional negative experience at work; it is ongoing negative acts, both<br />
                    overt and covert, over time, that erode workers&#8217; confidence in themselves and in their workplaces and that no amount of sophistication or maturity can make sense of.  Duffy and Sperry, leading authorities on this special type of aggression, provide effective strategies for recovery from mobbing as well as for<br />
                    prevention, and they demystify the experience through the use of case vignettes. More than a simple self-help book, this volume brings the concept and terminology relating to mobbing into the public vocabulary by virtue of its strong foundation in psychological and organizational research. It offers a detailed presentation of the causes and consequences of mobbing, helps readers avoid falling into the trap of misplacing blame, and holds organizations at the center of responsibility for<br />
                    preventing the abuse. In addition to those who have experienced mobbing themselves, this book is an invaluable resource for workplace managers and human resources personnel who wish to prevent or reverse mobbing within their own professional settings.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Upward Spiral : Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time &#8211; Alex Korb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Depression doesn&#8217;t happen all at once. It starts gradually and builds momentum over time. If you go through a difficult experience, you may stop taking care of yourself. You may stop exercising and eating healthy, which will end up making you feel even worse as time goes on. You are caught in a downward spiral, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/">The Upward Spiral : Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time &#8211; Alex Korb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Depression doesn&#8217;t happen all at once. It starts gradually and builds momentum over time. If you go through a difficult experience, you may stop taking care of yourself. You may stop exercising and eating healthy, which will end up making you feel even worse as time goes on. You are caught in a downward spiral, but you may feel too tired, too overwhelmed, and too scared to try and pull yourself back up. The good news is that just one small step can be a step in the right direction.    </p>
<p>                    In The Upward Spiral, neuroscientist Alex Korb demystifies the neurological processes in the brain that cause depression and offers effective ways to get better-one little step at a time. In the book, you&#8217;ll discover that there isn&#8217;t &#8220;one big solution&#8221; that will solve your depression. Instead, there are dozens of small, practical things you can do to alleviate your symptoms and start healing. Some are as simple as relaxing certain muscles to reduce feelings of anxiety, while others involve making small efforts toward more positive social interactions. Small steps in the right direction can have profound effects-giving you the power to literally &#8220;reshape&#8221; your brain.    </p>
<p>                    Like most people, you probably didn&#8217;t wake up one day and find yourself completely depressed. Instead, it probably happened over time, as a series of reactions to difficult situations and negative thinking. But if you are ready to reverse the trajectory of your depression and find lasting happiness, this book will show you how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/">The Upward Spiral : Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time &#8211; Alex Korb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Waiting : On Fertility, Medicine, and Motherhood &#8211; Belle Boggs (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-waiting-on-fertility-medicine-and-motherhood-belle-boggs-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-waiting-on-fertility-medicine-and-motherhood-belle-boggs-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A brilliant exploration of the natural, medical, psychological, and political facets of fertility When Belle Boggs&#8217;s The Art of Waiting was published in Orion in 2012, it went viral, leading to republication in Harper&#8217;s Magazine, an interview on NPR&#8217;s The Diane Rehm Show, and a spot at the intersection of highbrow and brilliant in New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-waiting-on-fertility-medicine-and-motherhood-belle-boggs-abridged/">The Art of Waiting : On Fertility, Medicine, and Motherhood &#8211; Belle Boggs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A brilliant exploration of the natural, medical, psychological, and political facets of fertility     </p>
<p>                    When Belle Boggs&#8217;s The Art of Waiting was published in Orion in 2012, it went viral, leading to republication in Harper&#8217;s Magazine, an interview on NPR&#8217;s The Diane Rehm Show, and a spot at the intersection of highbrow and brilliant in New York magazine&#8217;s Approval Matrix.     </p>
<p>                    In that heartbreaking essay, Boggs eloquently recounts her realization that she might never be able to conceive. She searches the apparently fertile world around her&#8211;the emergence of thirteen-year cicadas, the birth of eaglets near her rural home, and an unusual gorilla pregnancy at a local zoo&#8211;for signs that she is not alone. Boggs also explores other aspects of fertility and infertility: the way longing for a child plays out in the classic Coen brothers film Raising Arizona; the depiction of childlessness in literature, from Macbeth to Who&#8217;s Afraid of Virginia Woolf?; the financial and legal complications that accompany alternative means of family making; the private and public expressions of iconic writers grappling with motherhood and fertility. She reports, with great empathy, complex stories of couples who adopted domestically and from overseas, LGBT couples considering assisted reproduction and surrogacy, and women and men reflecting on childless or child-free lives.     </p>
<p>                    In The Art of Waiting, Boggs deftly distills her time of waiting into an expansive contemplation of fertility, choice, and the many possible roads to making a life and making a family.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-waiting-on-fertility-medicine-and-motherhood-belle-boggs-abridged/">The Art of Waiting : On Fertility, Medicine, and Motherhood &#8211; Belle Boggs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dangerous Personalities : An FBI Profiler Shows You How to Identify and Protect Yourself from Harmful People &#8211; Joe Navarro, Toni Sciarra Poynter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dangerous-personalities-an-fbi-profiler-shows-you-how-to-identify-and-protect-yourself-from-harmful-people-joe-navarro-toni-sciarra-poynter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Safety In The Home]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dangerous-personalities-an-fbi-profiler-shows-you-how-to-identify-and-protect-yourself-from-harmful-people-joe-navarro-toni-sciarra-poynter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What makes a narcissist go from self-involved to terrifying? In this national bestseller, Joe Navarro, a leading FBI profiler, unlocks the secrets to the personality disorders that put us all at risk. &#8220;I should have known.&#8221; &#8220;How could we have missed the warning signs?&#8221; &#8220;I always thought there was something off about him.&#8221; When we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerous-personalities-an-fbi-profiler-shows-you-how-to-identify-and-protect-yourself-from-harmful-people-joe-navarro-toni-sciarra-poynter-abridged/">Dangerous Personalities : An FBI Profiler Shows You How to Identify and Protect Yourself from Harmful People &#8211; Joe Navarro, Toni Sciarra Poynter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What makes a narcissist go from self-involved to terrifying? In this national bestseller, Joe Navarro, a leading FBI profiler, unlocks the secrets to the personality disorders that put us all at risk.      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I should have known.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8220;How could we have missed the warning signs?&#8221;<br />
                    &#8220;I always thought there was something off about him.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    When we wake up to new tragedies in the news every day&#8211;shootings, rampages, acts of domestic terrorism&#8211;we often blame ourselves for missing the mania lurking inside unsuspecting individuals. But how could we have known that the charismatic leader had the characteristics of a tyrant? And how can ordinary people identify threats from those who are poised to devastate their lives on a daily basis&#8211;the crazy coworkers, out-of-control family members, or relentless neighbors?     </p>
<p>                    In Dangerous Personalities, former FBI profiler Joe Navarro has the answers. He shows us how to identify the four most common dangerous personalities&#8211;the Narcissist, the Predator, the Paranoid, and the Unstable Personality&#8211; and how to analyze the potential threat level. Along the way, he provides essential tips and tricks to protect ourselves both immediately and in the long-term, as well as how to heal the trauma of being exposed to the destructive egos in our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerous-personalities-an-fbi-profiler-shows-you-how-to-identify-and-protect-yourself-from-harmful-people-joe-navarro-toni-sciarra-poynter-abridged/">Dangerous Personalities : An FBI Profiler Shows You How to Identify and Protect Yourself from Harmful People &#8211; Joe Navarro, Toni Sciarra Poynter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tell Me More : Stories About the 12 Hardest Things I&#8217;m Learning to Say &#8211; Kelly Corrigan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Painting & Art Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prints]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A story-driven collection of essays on the twelve powerful phrases we use to sustain our relationships, from the bestselling author of Glitter and Glue and The Middle Place &#8220;Kelly Corrigan takes on all the big, difficult questions here, with great warmth and courage.&#8221;&#8211;Glennon Doyle NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/">Tell Me More : Stories About the 12 Hardest Things I&#8217;m Learning to Say &#8211; Kelly Corrigan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A story-driven collection of essays on the twelve powerful phrases we use to sustain our relationships, from the bestselling author of Glitter and Glue and The Middle Place  &#8220;Kelly Corrigan takes on all the big, difficult questions here, with great warmth and courage.&#8221;&#8211;Glennon Doyle NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY REAL SIMPLE AND BUSTLE It&#8217;s a crazy idea: trying to name the phrases that make love and connection possible. But that&#8217;s just what Kelly Corrigan has set out to do here. In her New York Times bestselling memoirs,  Corrigan distilled our core relationships to their essences, showcasing a warm, easy storytelling style. Now, in Tell Me More,  she&#8217;s back with a deeply personal, unfailingly honest, and often hilarious examination of the essential phrases that turn the wheel of life.  In &#8220;I Don&#8217;t Know,&#8221; Corrigan wrestles to make peace with uncertainty, whether it&#8217;s over invitations that never came or a friend&#8217;s agonizing infertility. In &#8220;No,&#8221; she admires her mother&#8217;s ability to set boundaries and her liberating willingness to be unpopular. In &#8220;Tell Me More,&#8221; a facialist named Tish teaches her something important about listening. And in &#8220;I Was Wrong,&#8221; she comes clean about her disastrous role in a family fight&#8211;and explains why saying sorry may not be enough. With refreshing candor, a deep well of empathy, and her signature desire to understand &#8220;the thing behind the thing,&#8221; Corrigan swings between meditations on life with a preoccupied husband and two mercurial teenage daughters to profound observations on love and loss.  With the streetwise, ever-relatable voice that defines Corrigan&#8217;s work, Tell Me More is a moving and meaningful take on the power of the right words at the right moment to change everything. Praise for Tell Me More  &#8220;It is such a comfort just knowing that Kelly Corrigan exists: she is somehow both wise and self-deprecating; funny but unafraid of pain; frank but gentle. She is the sister/mother/best friend we all wish we could have&#8211;and because of this big-hearted book, we all get to.&#8221;&#8211;Ariel Levy, author of The Rules Do Not Apply  &#8220;With full-bodied humor and radical sensitivity, Kelly Corrigan transforms the mundane pain of life into a necessary spiritual text of sorts, one that reminds us that we have the right to grieve but the obligation to be grateful. This book will remind you that you are human&#8211;and of the fragile loveliness of being so.&#8221;&#8211;Lena Dunham</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/">Tell Me More : Stories About the 12 Hardest Things I&#8217;m Learning to Say &#8211; Kelly Corrigan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Eating Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she). When a personal crisis causes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she).    </p>
<p>                    When a personal crisis causes her world to come crashing down, Lori Gottlieb &#8211; an experienced therapist with a thriving practice in Los Angeles &#8211; is suddenly adrift. Enter Wendell, himself a veteran therapist with an unconventional style, whose sessions with Gottlieb will prove transformative for her.    </p>
<p>                    As Gottlieb explores the inner chambers of her own patients&#8217; lives &#8211; a self-absorbed Hollywood producer, a young newlywed diagnosed with a terminal illness, a senior citizen who feels she has nothing to live for, and a self-destructive twenty-something who can&#8217;t stop hooking up with the wrong guys &#8211; she finds that the questions they are struggling with are the very questions she is bringing to Wendell.    </p>
<p>                    Taking place over one year, and beginning with the devastating event that lands her in Wendell&#8217;s office, Maybe You Should Talk to Someone offers a rare and candid insight into a profession that is conventionally bound with rules and secrecy. Told with charm and compassion, vulnerability and humour, it&#8217;s also the story of an incredible relationship between two therapists, and a disarmingly funny and illuminating account of our own mysterious inner lives, as well as our power to transform them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon    </p>
<p>                    For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With vivid stories of his closed-door sessions with warring political groups, disputing businesspeople, and families in crisis, Daniel Shapiro presents a universally applicable method to successfully navigate conflict.  A deep, provocative book to reflect on and wrestle with, this book can change your life.    </p>
<p>                     Be warned: This book is not a quick fix. Real change takes work. You will learn how to master five emotional dynamics that can sabotage conflict outside your awareness:    </p>
<p>                    1. Vertigo: How can you avoid      getting emotionally consumed in conflict?<br />
                    2. Repetition compulsion: How can you stop      repeating the same conflicts again and again?<br />
                    3. Taboos: How can you discuss      sensitive issues at the heart of the conflict?<br />
                    4. Assault on the sacred: What should you do if      your values feel threatened?<br />
                    5. Identity politics: What can you do if      others use politics against you?     </p>
<p>                    In our era of discontent, this is just the book we need to resolve conflict in our own lives and in the world around us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Untangled : Guiding Teenage Girls Through the Seven Transitions into Adulthood &#8211; Lisa Damour (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leading clinical psychologist Lisa Damour identifies the seven key phases marking the journey from girlhood to womanhood, and offers practical advice for those raising teenage girls. We expect an enormous amount from our teenage girls in a world where they are bombarded with messages about how they should look, behave, succeed. Yet we also speak [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/">Untangled : Guiding Teenage Girls Through the Seven Transitions into Adulthood &#8211; Lisa Damour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading clinical psychologist Lisa Damour identifies the seven key phases marking the journey from girlhood to womanhood, and offers practical advice for those raising teenage girls.    </p>
<p>                    We expect an enormous amount from our teenage girls in a world where they are bombarded with messages about how they should look, behave, succeed. Yet we also speak as though adolescence is a nightmare rollercoaster ride for both parent and child, to be endured rather than enjoyed.     </p>
<p>                    In Untangled, world authority and clinical psychologist Lisa Damour provides an accessible, detailed, comprehensive guide to parenting teenage girls. She believes there is a predictable blueprint for how girls grow; seven easily recognisable &#8216;strands&#8217; of transition from childhood through adolescence and on to adulthood. Girls naturally develop at different rates, typically on more than one front, and the transition will be unique to every girl.     </p>
<p>                    Each chapter describes a phase, such as &#8216;contending with adult authority&#8217; and &#8216;entering the romantic world&#8217;, with hints and tips for parents and daughters, and a &#8216;when to worry&#8217; section. Damour writes sympathetically and clearly, providing a practical and helpful guide for any parent, and for teenage girls too.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/">Untangled : Guiding Teenage Girls Through the Seven Transitions into Adulthood &#8211; Lisa Damour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do You Believe in Magic? : Vitamins, Supplements, and All Things Natural: A Look Behind the Curtain &#8211; Dr Paul A Offit (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Medical expert Paul A. Offit, M.D., offers a scathing expos of the alternative medicine industry, revealing how even though some popular therapies are remarkably helpful due to the placebo response, many of them are ineffective, expensive, and even deadly. Dr. Offit reveals how alternative medicine&#8211;an unregulated industry under no legal obligation to prove its claims [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/">Do You Believe in Magic? : Vitamins, Supplements, and All Things Natural: A Look Behind the Curtain &#8211; Dr Paul A Offit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Medical expert Paul A. Offit, M.D., offers a scathing expos of the alternative medicine industry, revealing how even though some popular therapies are remarkably helpful due to the placebo response, many of them are ineffective, expensive, and even deadly.    </p>
<p>                    Dr. Offit reveals how alternative medicine&#8211;an unregulated industry under no legal obligation to prove its claims or admit its risks&#8211;can actually be harmful to our health.    </p>
<p>                    Using dramatic real-life stories, Offit separates the sense from the nonsense, showing why any therapy&#8211;alternative or traditional&#8211;should be scrutinized. He also shows how some nontraditional methods can do a great deal of good, in some cases exceeding therapies offered by conventional practitioners.    </p>
<p>                    An outspoken advocate for science-based health advocacy who is not afraid to take on media celebrities who promote alternative practices, Dr. Offit advises, &#8220;There&#8217;s no such thing as alternative medicine. There&#8217;s only medicine that works and medicine that doesn&#8217;t.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/">Do You Believe in Magic? : Vitamins, Supplements, and All Things Natural: A Look Behind the Curtain &#8211; Dr Paul A Offit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep & Dreams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all. Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all.    </p>
<p>                    Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising solutions for insomnia and other sleep disturbances, empowering readers to stop taking sleeping pills and enjoy the best sleep of their lives.    </p>
<p>                    Written in a clear and entertaining way, The Sleep Solution contains tips, tricks, exercises, and illustrations throughout. Dr Winter is an international expert on sleep and has helped thousands of patients &#8211; including professional athletes &#8211; rest better at night. Now, he&#8217;s ready to help you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All About Love : New Visions &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/all-about-love-new-visions-bell-hooks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/all-about-love-new-visions-bell-hooks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The word &#8220;love&#8221; is most often defined as a noun, yet&#8230;we would all love better if we used it as a verb,&#8221; writes bell hooks as she comes out fighting and on fire in All About Love. Here, at her most provocative and intensely personal, the renowned scholar, cultural critic, and feminist skewers our view [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-about-love-new-visions-bell-hooks-abridged/">All About Love : New Visions &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The word &#8220;love&#8221; is most often defined as a noun, yet&#8230;we would all love better if we used it as a verb,&#8221; writes bell hooks as she comes out fighting and on fire in All About Love. Here, at her most provocative and intensely personal, the renowned scholar, cultural critic, and feminist skewers our view of love as romance. In its place she offers a proactive new ethic for a people and a society bereft with lovelessness.  As bell hooks uses her incisive mind and razor-sharp pen to explore the question &#8220;What is love?&#8221; her answers strike at both the mind and heart. In thirteen concise chapters, hooks examines her own search for emotional connection and society&#8217;s failure to provide a model for learning to love. Razing the cultural paradigm that the ideal love is infused with sex and desire, she provides a new path to love that is sacred, redemptive, and healing for the individuals and for a nation. The Utne Reader declared bell hooks one of the &#8220;100 Visionaries Who Can Change Your Life.&#8221; All About Love is a powerful affirmation of just how profoundly she can.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-about-love-new-visions-bell-hooks-abridged/">All About Love : New Visions &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-alcoholic Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217; &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217;  &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller      </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice O&#8217;Keeffe, Guardian     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Truthful, modern and real&#8217; &#8211; Stylist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Brave, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober came to me at a time when I much needed it&#8230; The book became my best friend, and got me through, and took me on a journey.&#8217; &#8211; Sadie Frost     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Particularly lovely, because it&#8217;s not a deep and dark dive into someone&#8217;s terrible addiction. It&#8217;s a celebration of everything that she has gained from not drinking&#8217; &#8211; Laura Donnelly     </p>
<p>                    Ever sworn off alcohol for a month and found yourself drinking by the 7th? Think there&#8217;s &#8216;no point&#8217; in just one drink? Welcome! There are millions of us. 64% of Brits want to drink less.    </p>
<p>                    Catherine Gray was stuck in a hellish whirligig of Drink, Make horrible decisions, Hangover, Repeat. She had her fair share of &#8216;drunk tank&#8217; jail cells and topless-in-a-hot-tub misadventures.    </p>
<p>                    But this book goes beyond the binges and blackouts to deep-dive into uncharted territory: What happens after you quit drinking? This gripping, heart-breaking and witty book takes us down the rabbit-hole of an alternative reality. A life with zero hangovers, through sober weddings, sex, Christmases and breakups.     </p>
<p>                    In The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober, Catherine Gray shines a light on society&#8217;s drink-pushing and talks to top neuroscientists and psychologists about why we drink, delving into the science behind what it does to our brains and bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Much more than a tale from the netherworld of addicted drinking, this book is about the escape, and why a sober life can be more intoxicating than you ever imagined. Whether you&#8217;re a hopelessly devoted drinker, merely sober-curious, or you&#8217;ve already ditched the drink, you will love this book.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Haunting, admirable and enlightening&#8217; &#8211; The Pool     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A riveting, raw, yet humorous memoir with actionable advice. A truly unique blend of storytelling and science that holds a universe of hope.&#8217; &#8211; Annie Grace, author of This Naked Mind     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Like listening to your best friend teach you to be sober. Lighthearted but serious, it&#8217;s packed with ideas, tools, tips and, most importantly, reasons for living a sober life. This book is excellent.&#8217;- Eric Zimmer, host of podcast The One You Feed     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s fizzy writing succeeds in making this potentially boring-as-hell subject both engaging and highly seductive&#8217; &#8211; The Bookseller     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray is an exceptional writer. Her exquisitely crafted thoughts on the joys of being sober are not only deeply honest and pragmatic, but she manages to infuse tons of humor. This is a delightful, informative, and compelling read for all those who are sober or seeking sobriety.&#8217; &#8211; Sasha Tozzi, Huffington Post columnist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine&#8217;s writing style and voice captivate me. She has a way of translating her story into an experience I don&#8217;t want to end. I want to drink every drop she produces.&#8217; &#8211; Holly Whitaker, founder of Hip Sobriety School and co-presenter of Home podcast     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book is great. A balanced, informative and entertaining melange of memoir, sociology and psychology. I identified very strongly with huge sections of it.&#8217; &#8211; Jon Stewart, guitarist of Sleeper and Leaving AA, Staying Sober blogger >    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Sober is too often equated with &#8220;sombre&#8221; in our culture. Gray&#8217;s book turns that idea on its head. Her experience of sobriety is joyful and life-affirming. A must-read for anyone who has a nagging suspicion that alcohol may be taking away more than it&#8217;s giving.&#8217; &#8211; Hilda Burke, psychotherapist and couples counsellor     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray really captures the FUN we can have in sobriety. This book challenges the status quo; sobriet sounds as liberating as taking a trip to the jungle. Fun and inspirational. What an important book for our time! A joy to read.&#8217; &#8211; Samantha Moyo, founder of Morning Gloryville     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;No other author writes about sober living with as much warmth or emotional range as Catherine Gray. Her deep insight into the subtle psychologies of drinking, and of life, means that everything she writes is both utterly relatable and stretches our minds. Hers is a rare wisdom.&#8217; &#8211; Dr Richard Piper, CEO, Alcohol Change UK</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Loving Your Spouse When you Feel Like Walking Away : Real Help for Desperate Hearts in Difficult Marriages &#8211; Gary D. Chapman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/loving-your-spouse-when-you-feel-like-walking-away-real-help-for-desperate-hearts-in-difficult-marriages-gary-d-chapman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/loving-your-spouse-when-you-feel-like-walking-away-real-help-for-desperate-hearts-in-difficult-marriages-gary-d-chapman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What to do when you feel like giving up When you said, &#8220;I do,&#8221; you entered marriage with high hopes, dreaming it would be supremely happy. You never intended it to be miserable. Millions of couples are struggling in desperate marriages. But the story doesn&#8217;t have to end there. Dr. Gary Chapman writes, &#8220;I believe [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/loving-your-spouse-when-you-feel-like-walking-away-real-help-for-desperate-hearts-in-difficult-marriages-gary-d-chapman-abridged/">Loving Your Spouse When you Feel Like Walking Away : Real Help for Desperate Hearts in Difficult Marriages &#8211; Gary D. Chapman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What to do when you feel like giving up    </p>
<p>                    When you said, &#8220;I do,&#8221; you entered marriage with high hopes, dreaming it would be supremely happy.     </p>
<p>                    You never intended it to be miserable.    </p>
<p>                    Millions of couples are struggling in desperate marriages. But the story doesn&#8217;t have to end there. Dr. Gary Chapman writes, &#8220;I believe that in every troubled marriage, one or both partners can take positive steps that have the potential for changing the emotional climate in their marriage.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Loving Your Spouse When You Feel Like Walking Away, the revised and updated edition of the award-winning Desparate Marriages, teaches you how to: Recognize and reject the myths that hold you captiveBetter understand your spouse&#8217;s behaviorTake responsibility for your own thoughts, feelings, and actionsMake choices that can have a lasting, positive impact on you and your spouse    </p>
<p>                    An experienced marriage and family counselor, Gary Chapman speaks to those whose spouse is any of the following: IrresponsibleA workaholicControllingUncommunicativeVerbally abusivePhysically abusiveSexually abusiveUnfaithfulAddicted to alcohol or drugsDepressed    </p>
<p>                    Marriage has the same potential to be miserable as it does to be blissful. Read Loving Your Spouse When You Feel Like Walking Away to learn how you can turn things around.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/loving-your-spouse-when-you-feel-like-walking-away-real-help-for-desperate-hearts-in-difficult-marriages-gary-d-chapman-abridged/">Loving Your Spouse When you Feel Like Walking Away : Real Help for Desperate Hearts in Difficult Marriages &#8211; Gary D. Chapman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emotional Blackmail : When the People in Your Life Use Fear, Obligation, and Guilt to Manipulate You &#8211; Susan Forward, Illustrated byDonna Frazier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/emotional-blackmail-when-the-people-in-your-life-use-fear-obligation-and-guilt-to-manipulate-you-susan-forward-illustrated-by-donna-frazier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/emotional-blackmail-when-the-people-in-your-life-use-fear-obligation-and-guilt-to-manipulate-you-susan-forward-illustrated-by-donna-frazier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical guide to better communication that will break the blackmail cycle for good, by one of the nation&#8217;s leading therapists, Susan Forward. &#8220;Breathe a sigh of relief! Susan Forward helps you identify and correct an intensely destructive and confusing pattern of relating with those you love. I highly recommend this important book!&#8211;Susan Jeffers, Ph.D., [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-blackmail-when-the-people-in-your-life-use-fear-obligation-and-guilt-to-manipulate-you-susan-forward-illustrated-by-donna-frazier-abridged/">Emotional Blackmail : When the People in Your Life Use Fear, Obligation, and Guilt to Manipulate You &#8211; Susan Forward, Illustrated byDonna Frazier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical guide to better communication that will break the blackmail cycle for good, by one of the nation&#8217;s leading therapists, Susan Forward.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Breathe a sigh of relief! Susan Forward helps you identify and correct an intensely destructive and confusing pattern of relating with those you love. I highly recommend this important book!&#8211;Susan Jeffers, Ph.D., author of Feel the Fear and Do It Anyway    </p>
<p>                    If you really loved me&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    After all I&#8217;ve done for you&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    How can you be so selfish&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Do any of the above sound familiar? They&#8217;re all examples of emotional blackmail, a powerful form of manipulation in which people close to us threaten to punish us for not doing what they want. Emotional blackmailers know how much we value our relationships with them. They know our vulnerabilities and our deepest secrets. They are our mothers, our partners, our bosses and coworkers, our friends and our lovers. And no matter how much they care about us, they use this intimate knowledge to give themselves the payoff they want: our compliance.    </p>
<p>                    Susan Forward knows what pushes our hot buttons. Just as John Gray illuminates the communications gap between the sexes in Men Are from Mars, Women Are from Venus,  and Harriet Lerner describes an intricate dynamic in The Dance of Anger,  so Susan Forward presents the anatomy of a relationship damaged by manipulation, and gives readers an arsenal of tools to fight back.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-blackmail-when-the-people-in-your-life-use-fear-obligation-and-guilt-to-manipulate-you-susan-forward-illustrated-by-donna-frazier-abridged/">Emotional Blackmail : When the People in Your Life Use Fear, Obligation, and Guilt to Manipulate You &#8211; Susan Forward, Illustrated byDonna Frazier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ask Me About My Uterus : A Quest to Make Doctors Believe in Women&#8217;s Pain &#8211; Abby Norman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ask-me-about-my-uterus-a-quest-to-make-doctors-believe-in-womens-pain-abby-norman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Study & Revision Guides & Reference Material]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ask-me-about-my-uterus-a-quest-to-make-doctors-believe-in-womens-pain-abby-norman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the fall of 2010, Abby Norman&#8217;s strong dancer&#8217;s body dropped forty pounds and gray hairs began to sprout from her temples. She was repeatedly hospitalized in excruciating pain, but the doctors insisted it was a urinary tract infection and sent her home with antibiotics. Unable to get out of bed, much less attend class, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-me-about-my-uterus-a-quest-to-make-doctors-believe-in-womens-pain-abby-norman-abridged/">Ask Me About My Uterus : A Quest to Make Doctors Believe in Women&#8217;s Pain &#8211; Abby Norman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the fall of 2010, Abby Norman&#8217;s strong dancer&#8217;s body dropped forty pounds and gray hairs began to sprout from her temples. She was repeatedly hospitalized in excruciating pain, but the doctors insisted it was a urinary tract infection and sent her home with antibiotics. Unable to get out of bed, much less attend class, Norman dropped out of college and embarked on what would become a years-long journey to discover what was wrong with her. It wasn&#8217;t until she took matters into her own hands&#8211;securing a job in a hospital and educating herself over lunchtime reading in the medical library&#8211;that she found an accurate diagnosis of endometriosis.    </p>
<p>                    In Ask Me About My Uterus, Norman describes what it was like to have her pain dismissed, to be told it was all in her head, only to be taken seriously when she was accompanied by a boyfriend who confirmed that her sexual performance was, indeed, compromised. Putting her own trials into a broader historical, sociocultural, and political context, Norman shows that women&#8217;s bodies have long been the battleground of a never-ending war for power, control, medical knowledge, and truth. It&#8217;s time to refute the belief that being a woman is a preexisting condition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-me-about-my-uterus-a-quest-to-make-doctors-believe-in-womens-pain-abby-norman-abridged/">Ask Me About My Uterus : A Quest to Make Doctors Believe in Women&#8217;s Pain &#8211; Abby Norman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Audiology & Otology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Speech & Language Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A skilled science translator, Denworth makes decibels, teslas and brain plasticity understandable to all.&#8221;-Washington Post Lydia Denworth&#8217;s third son, Alex, was nearly two when he was identified with significant hearing loss that was likely to get worse. Denworth knew the importance of enrichment to the developing brain but had never contemplated the opposite: deprivation. How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/">I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A skilled science translator, Denworth makes decibels, teslas and brain plasticity understandable to all.&#8221;-Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    Lydia Denworth&#8217;s third son, Alex, was nearly two when he was identified with significant hearing loss that was likely to get worse. Denworth knew the importance of enrichment to the developing brain but had never contemplated the opposite: deprivation. How would a child&#8217;s brain grow outside the world of sound? How would he communicate? Would he learn to read and write?    </p>
<p>                    An acclaimed science journalist as well as a mother, Denworth made it her mission to find out, interviewing experts on language development, inventors of groundbreaking technology, Deaf leaders, and neuroscientists at the frontiers of brain plasticity research. I Can Hear You Whisper chronicles Denworth&#8217;s search for answers-and her new understanding of Deaf culture and the exquisite relationship between sound, language, and learning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/">I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
