<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Coding Theory &amp; Cryptology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/coding-theory-cryptology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/coding-theory-cryptology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Coding Theory &amp; Cryptology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/coding-theory-cryptology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan. Kaplan probes the inner corridors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan.    </p>
<p>                     Kaplan probes the inner corridors of the National Security Agency, the beyond-top-secret cyber units in the Pentagon, the &#8220;information warfare&#8221; squads of the military services, and the national security debates in the White House, to tell this never-before-told story of the officers, policymakers, scientists, and spies who devised this new form of warfare and who have been planning and (more often than people know) fighting these wars for decades.    </p>
<p>                     From the 1991 Gulf War to conflicts in Haiti, Serbia, Syria, the former Soviet republics, Iraq, and Iran, where cyber warfare played a significant role, Dark Territory chronicles, in fascinating detail, a little-known past that shines an unsettling light on our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When a pseudonymous programmer introduced &#8220;a new electronic cash system that&#8217;s fully peer-to-peer, with no trusted third party&#8221; to a small online mailing list in 2008, very few paid attention. Ten years later, and against all odds, this upstart autonomous decentralized software offers an unstoppable and globally-accessible hard money alternative to modern central banks. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/">The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When a pseudonymous programmer introduced &#8220;a new electronic cash system that&#8217;s fully peer-to-peer, with no trusted third party&#8221; to a small online mailing list in 2008, very few paid attention. Ten years later, and against all odds, this upstart autonomous decentralized software offers an unstoppable and globally-accessible hard money alternative to modern central banks. The Bitcoin Standard analyzes the historical context to the rise of Bitcoin, the economic properties that have allowed it to grow quickly, and its likely economic, political, and social implications.    </p>
<p>                     While Bitcoin is a new invention of the digital age, the problem it purports to solve is as old as human society itself: transferring value across time and space. Ammous takes the reader on an engaging journey through the history of technologies performing the functions of money, from primitive systems of trading limestones and seashells, to metals, coins, the gold standard, and modern government debt. Exploring what gave these technologies their monetary role, and how most lost it, provides the reader with a good idea of what makes for sound money, and sets the stage for an economic discussion of its consequences for individual and societal future-orientation, capital accumulation, trade, peace, culture, and art. Compellingly, Ammous shows that it is no coincidence that the loftiest achievements of humanity have come in societies enjoying the benefits of sound monetary regimes, nor is it coincidental that monetary collapse has usually accompanied civilizational collapse.    </p>
<p>                     With this background in place, the book moves on to explain the operation of Bitcoin in a functional and intuitive way. Bitcoin is a decentralized, distributed piece of software that converts electricity and processing power into indisputably accurate records, thus allowing its users to utilize the Internet to perform the traditional functions of money without having to rely on, or trust, any authorities or infrastructure in the physical world. Bitcoin is thus best understood as the first successfully implemented form of digital cash and digital hard money. With an automated and perfectly predictable monetary policy, and the ability to perform final settlement of large sums across the world in a matter of minutes, Bitcoin&#8217;s real competitive edge might just be as a store of value and network for final settlement of large payments-a digital form of gold with a built-in settlement infrastructure.    </p>
<p>                     Ammous&#8217; firm grasp of the technological possibilities as well as the historical realities of monetary evolution provides for a fascinating exploration of the ramifications of voluntary free market money. As it challenges the most sacred of government monopolies, Bitcoin shifts the pendulum of sovereignty away from governments in favor of individuals, offering us the tantalizing possibility of a world where money is fully extricated from politics and unrestrained by borders.    </p>
<p>                     The final chapter of the book explores some of the most common questions surrounding Bitcoin: Is Bitcoin mining a waste of energy? Is Bitcoin for criminals? Who controls Bitcoin, and can they change it if they please? How can Bitcoin be killed? And what to make of all the thousands of Bitcoin knock-offs, and the many supposed applications of Bitcoin&#8217;s &#8216;blockchain technology&#8217;? The Bitcoin Standard is the essential resource for a clear understanding of the rise of the Internet&#8217;s decentralized, apolitical, free-market alternative to national central banks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/">The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Science of Secrecy from Ancient Egypt to Quantum Cryptography From the best-selling author of Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, The Code Book is a history of man&#8217;s urge to uncover the secrets of codes, from Egyptian puzzles to modern day computer encryptions. As in Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, Simon Singh brings life to an anstonishing story of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/">The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Science of Secrecy from Ancient Egypt to Quantum Cryptography    </p>
<p>                              From the best-selling author of Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, The Code Book is a history of man&#8217;s urge to uncover the secrets of codes, from Egyptian puzzles to modern day computer encryptions.    </p>
<p>                              As in Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, Simon Singh brings life to an anstonishing story of puzzles, codes, languages and riddles that reveals man&#8217;s continual pursuit to disguise and uncover, and to work out the secret languages of others.    </p>
<p>                              Codes have influenced events throughout history, both in the stories of those who make them and those who break them. The betrayal of Mary Queen of Scots and the cracking of the enigma code that helped the Allies in World War II are major episodes in a continuing history of cryptography. In addition to stories of intrigue and warfare, Simon Singh also investigates other codes, the unravelling of genes and the rediscovery of ancient languages and most tantalisingly, the Beale ciphers, an unbroken code that could hold the key to a $20 million treasure.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/">The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
