<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Working Patterns &amp; Practices Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/working-patterns-practices/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/working-patterns-practices/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Working Patterns &amp; Practices Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/working-patterns-practices/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most powerful and instructive change manual you&#8217;ll ever read. It will persuade and inspire you to change your business, your work, and maybe your life.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, bestselling author of A Whole New Mind In Practically Radical, William C. Taylor, the New York Times bestselling co-author of Mavericks at Work offers a refreshing, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/">Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most powerful and instructive change manual you&#8217;ll ever read. It will persuade and inspire you to change your business, your work, and maybe your life.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, bestselling author of A Whole New Mind     </p>
<p>                    In Practically Radical, William C. Taylor, the New York Times bestselling co-author of Mavericks at Work offers a refreshing, rigorous new look at pragmatic ways to shake things up and make positive change in difficult times.     </p>
<p>                    Exploring how twenty-five for-profit companies and nonprofit organizations&#8211;including IBM, Zappos, Swatch, the Girl Scouts, and Interpol&#8211;made remarkable strides in tough circumstances, Practically Radical raises (and answers) the make-or-break questions facing today&#8217;s leaders in every field: Do you see opportunities the competition doesn&#8217;t see? The most successful organizations embrace one-of-a-kind ideas in a world filled with me-too thinking.Do you have new ideas about where to look for new ideas? Routine practices in one field can be revolutionary when they migrate to another.Are you the most of anything? In business today, the middle of the road is the road to ruin.Are you getting the best contributions from the most people? Change is not a game best played by loners.    </p>
<p>                    Anything but your typical business book, Practically Radical is a must-own for small business owners and CEOs, for managers at all levels, and innovators and entrepreneurs of every stripe.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/">Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ReWork : Change the Way You Work Forever &#8211; David Heinemeier Hansson, Jason Fried (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rework-change-the-way-you-work-forever-david-heinemeier-hansson-jason-fried-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rework-change-the-way-you-work-forever-david-heinemeier-hansson-jason-fried-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the founders of the trailblazing software company 37signals, here is a different kind of business book &#8211; one that explores a new reality. Today, anyone can be in business. Tools that used to be out of reach are now easily accessible. Technology that cost thousands is now just a few pounds or even free. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rework-change-the-way-you-work-forever-david-heinemeier-hansson-jason-fried-abridged/">ReWork : Change the Way You Work Forever &#8211; David Heinemeier Hansson, Jason Fried (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the founders of the trailblazing software company 37signals, here is a different kind of business book &#8211; one that explores a new reality. Today, anyone can be in business. Tools that used to be out of reach are now easily accessible. Technology that cost thousands is now just a few pounds or even free. Stuff that was impossible just a few years ago is now simple.     </p>
<p>                    That means anyone can start a business. And you can do it without working miserable 80-hour weeks or depleting your life savings. You can start it on the side while your day job provides all the cash flow you need. Forget about business plans, meetings, office space &#8211; you don&#8217;t need them.    </p>
<p>                    With its straightforward language and easy-is-better approach, Rework is the perfect playbook for anyone who&#8217;s ever dreamed of doing it on their own. Hardcore entrepreneurs, small-business owners, people stuck in day jobs who want to get out, and artists who don&#8217;t want to starve anymore will all find valuable inspiration and guidance in these pages.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s time to rework work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rework-change-the-way-you-work-forever-david-heinemeier-hansson-jason-fried-abridged/">ReWork : Change the Way You Work Forever &#8211; David Heinemeier Hansson, Jason Fried (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge. When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality. In Leaders Eat Last, Simon [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge.    </p>
<p>                    When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality.    </p>
<p>                    In Leaders Eat Last, Simon Sinek, internationally bestselling author of Start With Why, investigates these great leaders from Marine Corps Officers, who don&#8217;t just sacrifice their place at the table but often their own comfort and even their lives for those in their care, to the heads of big business and government &#8211; each putting aside their own interests to protect their teams.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Simple and elegant, it shows us how leaders should lead&#8217; William Ury, co-author of Getting to Yes</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Build It : The Rebel Playbook for World-Class Employee Engagement &#8211; Debra Corey, Glenn Elliott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/build-it-the-rebel-playbook-for-world-class-employee-engagement-debra-corey-glenn-elliott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/build-it-the-rebel-playbook-for-world-class-employee-engagement-debra-corey-glenn-elliott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The current way of treating people at work has failed. Globally, only 30% of employees are engaged in their jobs, and in this fast-paced world that&#8217;s just not enough. The world&#8217;s best companies understand this, and have been quietly treating people differently for nearly two decades. Now you can learn their secrets and discover The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/build-it-the-rebel-playbook-for-world-class-employee-engagement-debra-corey-glenn-elliott-abridged/">Build It : The Rebel Playbook for World-Class Employee Engagement &#8211; Debra Corey, Glenn Elliott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The current way of treating people at work has failed. Globally, only 30% of employees are engaged in their jobs, and in this fast-paced world that&#8217;s just not enough. The world&#8217;s best companies understand this, and have been quietly treating people differently for nearly two decades.     </p>
<p>                    Now you can learn their secrets and discover The Engagement Bridge (TM) model, proven to build bottom line value for companies through sustainable employee engagement.     </p>
<p>                    Companies with the best cultures generate stock market returns of twice the general market and enjoy half the employee turnover of their peers. Their staff innovate more, deliver better customer service and, hands-down, beat the competition. These companies outperform and disrupt their markets. They break the rules of traditional HR, they rebel against the status quo.     </p>
<p>                    Build it has found these rebels and the rulebreakers. From small startups to global powerhouses, this book shows that courage, commitment, and a people-centric mindset, rather than money and resources, are what you need to turn an average business into a category leader.     </p>
<p>                    The book follows the clear and proven Engagement Bridge (TM) model, developed from working with thousands of leading companies worldwide on their own employee engagement journeys. The practical model highlights the areas that leaders need to examine in order to build a highly engaged company culture and provides a framework for success.     </p>
<p>                    Build it is packed with tips, tools and real-life examples from employers including NASDAQ, Unilever, IBM, KPMG, 3M, and McDonald&#8217;s to help you start doing this not tomorrow, but today. Readers will learn:     </p>
<p>                    How employee engagement helps companies perform<br />
                    The key factors that drive engagement, and how they work together<br />
                    What the world&#8217;s most rebellious companies have done to break the rules of traditional HR and improve engagement<br />
                    How to implement The Engagement BridgeTM model to boost productivity, innovation, and better decision-making    </p>
<p>                     Unique in this category, Build it is written from two sharply different perspectives. Glenn Elliott is a multi-award winning Entrepreneur of the Year, CEO and growth investor. He talks candidly about the mistakes and missteps he has made whilst building Reward Gateway into a $300m category leader in employee engagement technology.     </p>
<p>                    Debra Corey brings 30 years experience in senior level HR roles at global companies such as Gap, Quintiles, Honeywell and Merlin Entertainments. She shares the practical tools and case studies that can kickstart your employee engagement plan, bringing her own pragmatic and engaging style to each situation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/build-it-the-rebel-playbook-for-world-class-employee-engagement-debra-corey-glenn-elliott-abridged/">Build It : The Rebel Playbook for World-Class Employee Engagement &#8211; Debra Corey, Glenn Elliott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover the secrets of one of the world&#8217;s leading talent acquisition experts In the newly revised Fourth Edition of Hire With Your Head: Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Great Teams, influential recruiting and hiring expert Lou Adler delivers a practical guide to consistently identifying and hiring the best people and scaling that process throughout your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/">Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover the secrets of one of the world&#8217;s leading talent acquisition experts    </p>
<p>                     In the newly revised Fourth Edition of Hire With Your Head: Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Great Teams, influential recruiting and hiring expert Lou Adler delivers a practical guide to consistently identifying and hiring the best people and scaling that process throughout your company.    </p>
<p>                     This book will help you address your hiring and recruitment issues, not just by making you more efficient, but also by reforming your entire process to align with how top talent actually look for new jobs, compare offers, and select opportunities.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll discover:    </p>
<p>                    Discover what it takes to ensure more Win-Win Hiring outcomes by hiring for the anniversary date rather than the start date<br />
                    How to use a &#8220;High Tech, High Touch&#8221; approach to raise the talent bar<br />
                    Expand the talent pool to include more outstanding, high potential and diverse talent by defining work as a series of key performance objectives    </p>
<p>                     Perfect for hiring managers, recruiters, and HR and business leaders, Hire with Your Head is a must-read resource for anyone seeking to improve their ability to find, attract, and retain the top talent the world has to offer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/">Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chief Joy Officer &#8211; Richard Sheridan, Foreword by Tom Peters (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chief-joy-officer-richard-sheridan-foreword-by-tom-peters-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chief-joy-officer-richard-sheridan-foreword-by-tom-peters-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 2018 Nautilus Book Award Winner for Business and Leadership! The founder of Menlo Innovations and author of the business culture cult classic Joy, Inc offers an inspirational guide to leaders seeking joy in the challenge of leading others. Rich Sheridan&#8217;s Joy, Inc. told the story of how his tiny software company in Ann Arbor, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chief-joy-officer-richard-sheridan-foreword-by-tom-peters-abridged/">Chief Joy Officer &#8211; Richard Sheridan, Foreword by Tom Peters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A 2018 Nautilus Book Award Winner for Business and Leadership!     </p>
<p>                    The founder of Menlo Innovations and author of the business culture cult classic Joy, Inc offers an inspirational guide to leaders seeking joy in the challenge of leading others.     </p>
<p>                    Rich Sheridan&#8217;s Joy, Inc. told the story of how his tiny software company in Ann Arbor, Michigan achieved success and renown by embracing offbeat culture and human-centered values. In Chief Joy Officer,  he turns his attention from culture to leadership, and draws on his experience running Menlo and consulting elsewhere to offer a wise, provocative guide on how anyone can build leadership capacity for joy within their own organization.     </p>
<p>                    Chief Joy Officer offers sage, hard-won advice to any manager or leader who yearns to make more of an impact on the lives of others, including:     </p>
<p>                     * Self-understanding is the cornerstone for every virtue of leadership: authenticity, trust, humility, and optimism.     </p>
<p>                     * Good leaders make more leaders: Learn to judge your performance not on whether people are doing what they&#8217;re told, but whether they&#8217;re developing independent leadership capacity.     </p>
<p>                     * Influencing up is just as important is influencing down: how to encourage different thinking in those above you in your organizations.     </p>
<p>                    Filled with colorful anecdotes from Sheridan&#8217;s personal journey and wisdom from many leadership mentors, Chief Joy Officer offers an approachable, down-to-earth philosophy and practice that will help even the most disillusioned of middle managers bring a renewed sense of purpose to their work building others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chief-joy-officer-richard-sheridan-foreword-by-tom-peters-abridged/">Chief Joy Officer &#8211; Richard Sheridan, Foreword by Tom Peters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Place To Work : The Art and Science of Creating an Extraordinary Workplace &#8211; Ron Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Malcolm Gladwell, Daniel Pink, and Freakonomics, comes a captivating and surprising journey through the science of workplace excellence. Why do successful companies reward failure? What can casinos teach us about building a happy workplace? How do you design an office that enhances both attention to detail and creativity? In The Best Place [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/">The Best Place To Work : The Art and Science of Creating an Extraordinary Workplace &#8211; Ron Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Malcolm Gladwell, Daniel Pink, and Freakonomics, comes a captivating and surprising journey through the science of workplace excellence.    </p>
<p>                     Why do successful companies reward failure?<br />
                     What can casinos teach us about building a happy workplace?<br />
                     How do you design an office that enhances both attention to detail and creativity?     </p>
<p>                     In The Best Place to Work, award-winning psychologist Ron Friedman, Ph.D. uses the latest research from the fields of motivation, creativity, behavioral economics, neuroscience, and management to reveal what really makes us successful at work. Combining powerful stories with cutting edge findings, Friedman shows leaders at every level how they can use scientifically-proven techniques to promote smarter thinking, greater innovation, and stronger performance.     </p>
<p>                     Among the many surprising insights, Friedman explains how learning to think like a hostage negotiator can help you diffuse a workplace argument, why placing a fish bowl near your desk can elevate your thinking, and how incorporating strategic distractions into your schedule can help you reach smarter decisions. Along the way, the book introduces the inventor who created the cubicle, the president who brought down the world&#8217;s most dangerous criminal, and the teenager who single-handedly transformed professional tennis&#8211;vivid stories that offer unexpected revelations on achieving workplace excellence.     </p>
<p>                     Brimming with counterintuitive insights and actionable recommendations, The Best Place to Work offers employees and executives alike game-changing advice for working smarter and turning any organization&#8211;regardless of its size, budgets, or ambitions&#8211;into an extraordinary workplace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/">The Best Place To Work : The Art and Science of Creating an Extraordinary Workplace &#8211; Ron Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Employee Experience Advantage : How to Win the War for Talent by Giving Employees the Workspaces they Want, the Tools they Need, and a Culture They Can Celebrate &#8211; Jacob Morgan, Foreword by Marshall Goldsmith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-employee-experience-advantage-how-to-win-the-war-for-talent-by-giving-employees-the-workspaces-they-want-the-tools-they-need-and-a-culture-they-can-celebrate-jacob-morgan-foreword-by-m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-employee-experience-advantage-how-to-win-the-war-for-talent-by-giving-employees-the-workspaces-they-want-the-tools-they-need-and-a-culture-they-can-celebrate-jacob-morgan-foreword-by-m/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Research Shows Organizations That Focus on Employee Experience Far Outperform Those That Don&#8217;t Recently a new type of organization has emerged, one that focuses on employee experiences as a way to drive innovation, increase customer satisfaction, find and hire the best people, make work more engaging, and improve overall performance. The Employee Experience Advantage is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-employee-experience-advantage-how-to-win-the-war-for-talent-by-giving-employees-the-workspaces-they-want-the-tools-they-need-and-a-culture-they-can-celebrate-jacob-morgan-foreword-by-m/">The Employee Experience Advantage : How to Win the War for Talent by Giving Employees the Workspaces they Want, the Tools they Need, and a Culture They Can Celebrate &#8211; Jacob Morgan, Foreword by Marshall Goldsmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Research Shows Organizations That Focus on Employee Experience Far Outperform Those That Don&#8217;t Recently a new type of organization has emerged, one that focuses on employee experiences as a way to drive innovation, increase customer satisfaction, find and hire the best people, make work more engaging, and improve overall performance. The Employee Experience Advantage is the first book of its kind to tackle this emerging topic that is becoming the #1 priority for business leaders around the world. Although everyone talks about employee experience nobody has really been able to explain concretely what it is and how to go about designing for it&#8230;until now. How can organizations truly create a place where employees want to show up to work versus need to show up to work? For decades the business world has focused on measuring employee engagement meanwhile global engagement scores remain at an all time low despite all the surveys and institutes that been springing up tackle this problem. Clearly something is not working. Employee engagement has become the short-term adrenaline shot that organizations turn to when they need to increase their engagement scores.<br />
                    Instead, we have to focus on designing employee experiences which is the long term organizational design that leads to engaged employees. This is the only long-term solution. Organizations have been stuck focusing on the cause instead of the effect. The cause is employee experience; the effect is an engaged workforce. Backed by an extensive research project that looked at over 150 studies and articles, featured extensive interviews with over 150 executives, and analyzed over 250 global organizations, this book clearly breaks down the three environments that make up every single employee experience at every organization around the world and how to design for them. These are the cultural, technological, and physical environments. This book explores the attributes that organizations need to focus on in each one of these environments to create COOL spaces, ACE technology, and a CELEBRATED culture. Featuring exclusive case studies, unique frameworks, and never before seen research, The Employee Experience Advantage guides readers on a journey of creating a place where people actually want to show up to work.<br />
                    Readers will learn: * The trends shaping employee experience * How to evaluate their own employee experience using the Employee Experience Score * What the world&#8217;s leading organizations are doing around employee experience * How to design for technology, culture, and physical spaces * The role people analytics place in employee experience * Frameworks for how to actually create employee experiences * The role of the gig economy * The future of employee experience * Nine types of organizations that focus on employee experience * And much more! There is no question that engaged employees perform better, aspire higher, and achieve more, but you can&#8217;t create employee engagement without designing employee experiences first. It&#8217;s time to rethink your strategy and implement a real-world framework that focuses on how to create an organization where people want to show up to work. The Employee Experience Advantage shows you how to do just that.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-employee-experience-advantage-how-to-win-the-war-for-talent-by-giving-employees-the-workspaces-they-want-the-tools-they-need-and-a-culture-they-can-celebrate-jacob-morgan-foreword-by-m/">The Employee Experience Advantage : How to Win the War for Talent by Giving Employees the Workspaces they Want, the Tools they Need, and a Culture They Can Celebrate &#8211; Jacob Morgan, Foreword by Marshall Goldsmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Programming / Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221; Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term? While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221;<br />
                     Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb    </p>
<p>                    How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term?  While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments of creation and conclusion, The Messy Middle argues that the real key to success is how you navigate the ups-and-downs after initial investment is secured. It will give you all the insights you need to build and optimize your team, improve your product and develop your own capacity to lead covering:<br />
                    *         Coping with uncertainty and conflict<br />
                    *         Playing the long game<br />
                    *         Optimising your team<br />
                    *         Problem solving through the ups and downs<br />
                    *         Adapting your strategy<br />
                    *         When to quit<br />
                    Building on seven years&#8217; of meticulous research with entrepreneurs, small agencies, start-ups and billion-dollar companies, Scott Belsky offers indispensable lessons on how to endure and thrive in the long term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joy, Inc : How We Built a Workplace People Love &#8211; Richard Sheridan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A guidebook for how leaders can motivate, engage, and recognize their people all the while growing the business profitably.&#8221; &#8211;Forbes.com Every year, thousands of visitors come from around the world to visit Menlo Innovations, a small software company in Ann Arbor, Michigan. They make the trek not to learn about technology but to witness a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/">Joy, Inc : How We Built a Workplace People Love &#8211; Richard Sheridan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A guidebook for how leaders can motivate, engage, and recognize their people all the while growing the business profitably.&#8221; &#8211;Forbes.com     </p>
<p>                    Every year, thousands of visitors come from around the world to visit Menlo Innovations, a small software company in Ann Arbor, Michigan. They make the trek not to learn about technology but to witness a radically different approach to company culture.     </p>
<p>                    CEO Rich Sheridan removed the fear and ambiguity that typically make a workplace miserable. With joy as the explicit goal, he and his team changed everything about how the company was run. The results blew away all expectations. Menlo has won numerous growth awards and was named an Inc. magazine &#8220;audacious small company.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Joy, Inc. offers an inside look at how Menlo created its culture, and shows how any organization can follow their methods for a more passionate team and sustainable, profitable results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/">Joy, Inc : How We Built a Workplace People Love &#8211; Richard Sheridan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Productivity Project : Proven Ways to Become More Awesome &#8211; Chris Bailey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-productivity-project-proven-ways-to-become-more-awesome-chris-bailey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-productivity-project-proven-ways-to-become-more-awesome-chris-bailey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fun, interesting, and useful read!&#8217; David Allen, bestselling author of Getting Things Done Nearly all of us want to be more productive, but finding the method that works for you among the hundreds and hundreds of different tips, tricks and hacks can be a daunting prospect. After graduating college, Chris Bailey decided to dedicate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-productivity-project-proven-ways-to-become-more-awesome-chris-bailey-abridged/">The Productivity Project : Proven Ways to Become More Awesome &#8211; Chris Bailey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fun, interesting, and useful read!&#8217; David Allen, bestselling author of Getting Things Done    </p>
<p>                    Nearly all of us want to be more productive, but finding the method that works for you among the hundreds and hundreds of different tips, tricks and hacks can be a daunting prospect. After graduating college, Chris Bailey decided to dedicate a whole year to doing just that &#8211; experimenting with as many of the techniques as he could, and finding the things that work. Among the experiments that he undertook are: going several weeks on little to no sleep; cutting out caffeine and sugar; taking a daily siesta; living in total isolation for 10 days; stretching his workweek to 90 hours; and getting up at 5:30 every morning,  all the while monitoring the impact of his experiments on the quality and quantity of his work. The results were often surprising!     </p>
<p>                    This book is the result of Chris&#8217;s year-long journey, distilling the lessons he learned into a few core truths about how we get things done (or, indeed, don&#8217;t).  Among the many counterintuitive insights Chris discovered that had the biggest impact on his productivity were striving for imperfection; scheduling less time for important tasks; the 20 second rule to distract yourself from distractions; and the concept of productive procrastination.     </p>
<p>                    In this accessible and fun guide, Chris Bailey offers over 30 tried-and-tested best practices that will help everyone to accomplish more &#8211; and become more awesome.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-productivity-project-proven-ways-to-become-more-awesome-chris-bailey-abridged/">The Productivity Project : Proven Ways to Become More Awesome &#8211; Chris Bailey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cubed : The Secret History of the Workplace &#8211; Nikil Saval (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Buildings: Civic, Commercial, Industrial, Etc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book &#8211; Daily Beast Best Nonfiction of 2014 &#8211; Inc. Magazine&#8217;s Most Thought-Provoking Books of the Year &#8220;Man is born free, but he is everywhere in cubicles.&#8221; How did we get from Scrooge&#8217;s office to &#8220;Office Space&#8221;? From bookkeepers in dark countinghouses to freelancers in bright cafes? What would the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/">Cubed : The Secret History of the Workplace &#8211; Nikil Saval (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book &#8211; Daily Beast Best Nonfiction of 2014 &#8211; Inc. Magazine&#8217;s Most Thought-Provoking Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Man is born free, but he is everywhere in cubicles.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    How did we get from Scrooge&#8217;s office to &#8220;Office Space&#8221;? From bookkeepers in dark countinghouses to freelancers in bright cafes? What would the world be like without the vertical file cabinet? What would the world be like without the office at all? In Cubed, Nikil Saval chronicles the evolution of the office in a fascinating, often funny, and sometimes disturbing anatomy of the white-collar world and how it came to be the way it is. Drawing on the history of architecture and business, as well as a host of pop culture artifacts&#8211;from Mad Men to Dilbert (and, yes, The Office)&#8211;and ranging in time from the earliest clerical houses to the surprisingly utopian origins of the cubicle to the funhouse campuses of Silicon Valley, Cubed is an all-encompassing investigation into the way we work, why we do it the way we do (and often don&#8217;t like it), and how we might do better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/">Cubed : The Secret History of the Workplace &#8211; Nikil Saval (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Morning Routine : How Successful People Start Every Day Inspired &#8211; Benjamin Spall, Michael Xander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-morning-routine-how-successful-people-start-every-day-inspired-benjamin-spall-michael-xander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-morning-routine-how-successful-people-start-every-day-inspired-benjamin-spall-michael-xander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ONE OF AMAZON&#8217;S BEST BUSINESS BOOKS OF 2018 SO FAR ONE OF THE FINANCIAL TIMES&#8217; BUSINESS BOOKS OF THE MONTH UPON RELEASE ONE OF BUSINESS INSIDER&#8217;S BEST BUSINESS BOOKS TO READ THIS SUMMER &#8216;This small book carries the irresistible implicit promise that if you follow the morning routines of famous, important and successful people, you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-morning-routine-how-successful-people-start-every-day-inspired-benjamin-spall-michael-xander-abridged/">My Morning Routine : How Successful People Start Every Day Inspired &#8211; Benjamin Spall, Michael Xander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ONE OF AMAZON&#8217;S BEST BUSINESS BOOKS OF 2018 SO FAR<br />
                    ONE OF THE FINANCIAL TIMES&#8217; BUSINESS BOOKS OF THE MONTH UPON RELEASE<br />
                    ONE OF BUSINESS INSIDER&#8217;S BEST BUSINESS BOOKS TO READ THIS SUMMER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This small book carries the irresistible implicit promise that if you follow the morning routines of famous, important and successful people, you will become famous, important and successful yourself.&#8217; Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    How are you spending your most valuable hours? The first few choices you make each morning can unlock greater productivity, creativity, and calm &#8211; or bring out your worst self.    </p>
<p>                    Marie Kondo performs a quick tidying ritual to quiet her mind before leaving the house. The president of Pixar and Walt Disney Animation Studios, Ed Catmull, mixes three shots of espresso with three scoops of cocoa powder and two sweeteners. Retired U.S.Army Four-Star General Stanley McChrystal works out at 4:00 AM every day for at least an hour.     </p>
<p>                     Part instruction manual, part someone else&#8217;s diary, My Morning Routine interviews sixty-four of today&#8217;s most successful people &#8211; including Biz Stone, the co-founder of Twitter; Arianna Huffington, founder of The Huffington Post; and Michael Acton Smith, the CEO of Calm &#8211; and offers timeless advice on creating a routine of your own.    </p>
<p>                     Some routines are all about early-morning exercise and spartan living; others are more leisurely and self-indulgent. Whether you want to boost your productivity, implement a workout or meditation routine, or learn to roll with the punches in the morning, this book has you covered.     </p>
<p>                    Once you land on the right routine, you&#8217;ll look forward to waking up.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    From inside the book:     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A big part of my morning routine is about what I don&#8217;t do: when I wake up, I don&#8217;t start the day by looking at my phone&#8217; &#8211; ARIANNA HUFFINGTON, founder of the Huffington Post and Thrive Global    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;I travel a lot for work, so my days are always different. Having a morning routine really means fitting things in around everything else&#8217; &#8211; CAMERON RUSSELL, fashion model and cultural activist I    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;if I don&#8217;t get a chance to play with my son in the morning I feel like I missed something that I&#8217;ll never get back&#8217; &#8211; BIZ STONE, cofounder of Twitter    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Find certain things you know you should do, don&#8217;t like to do, or make excuses to avoid, and then do them every day&#8217; &#8211; STANLEY McCHRYSTAL, retired U.S. Army four-star general    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;    </p>
<p>                     BENJAMIN SPALL AND MICHAEL XANDER are the founders of mymorningroutine.com. Spall has written for outlets including The Huffington Post, 99U, and The Next Web. Xander is a product designer and engineer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-morning-routine-how-successful-people-start-every-day-inspired-benjamin-spall-michael-xander-abridged/">My Morning Routine : How Successful People Start Every Day Inspired &#8211; Benjamin Spall, Michael Xander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Infinite Game : From the bestselling author of Start With Why &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER The New York Times-bestselling author of Start With Why, Leaders Eat Last, and Together Is Better offers a bold new approach to business strategy by asking one question: are you playing the finite game or the infinite game? In The Infinite Game, Sinek applies game theory to explore how great businesses [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/">The Infinite Game : From the bestselling author of Start With Why &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The New York Times-bestselling author of Start With Why, Leaders Eat Last, and Together Is Better offers a bold new approach to business strategy by asking one question: are you playing the finite game or the infinite game?     </p>
<p>                    In The Infinite Game, Sinek applies game theory to explore how great businesses achieve long-lasting success. He finds that building long-term value and healthy, enduring growth &#8211; that playing the infinite game &#8211; is the only thing that matters to your business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/">The Infinite Game : From the bestselling author of Start With Why &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Change The Culture, Change The &#8211; Roger Connors, Tom Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/change-the-culture-change-the-roger-connors-tom-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/change-the-culture-change-the-roger-connors-tom-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fully revised and updated installment from the bestselling author of The Oz Principle Series. Two-time New York Times bestselling authors Roger Connors and Tom Smith show how leaders can achieve record-breaking results by quickly and effectively shaping their organizational culture to capitalize on their greatest asset-their people. Change the Culture, Change the Game joins [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/change-the-culture-change-the-roger-connors-tom-smith-abridged/">Change The Culture, Change The &#8211; Roger Connors, Tom Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fully revised and updated installment from the bestselling author of The Oz Principle Series.   Two-time New York Times bestselling authors Roger Connors and Tom Smith show how leaders can achieve record-breaking results by quickly and effectively shaping their organizational culture to capitalize on their greatest asset-their people.  Change the Culture, Change the Game joins their classic book, The Oz Principle, and their recent bestseller, How Did That Happen?, to complete the most comprehensive series ever written on workplace accountability. Based on an earlier book, Journey to the Emerald City, this fully revised installment captures what the authors have learned while working with the hundreds of thousands of people on using organizational culture as a strategic advantage.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/change-the-culture-change-the-roger-connors-tom-smith-abridged/">Change The Culture, Change The &#8211; Roger Connors, Tom Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indistractable : How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life &#8211; Nir Eyal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A must-read&#8217; Mark Manson We are living through a crisis of distraction. Plans get sidetracked, friends are ignored, work never seems to get done. Why does it feel like we&#8217;re distracting our lives away? In Indistractable, behavioural designer Nir Eyal reveals the hidden psychology driving you to distraction. Empowering and optimistic, this is the book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/">Indistractable : How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life &#8211; Nir Eyal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A must-read&#8217; Mark Manson    </p>
<p>                    We are living through a crisis of distraction. Plans get sidetracked, friends are ignored, work never seems to get done.     </p>
<p>                    Why does it feel like we&#8217;re distracting our lives away?    </p>
<p>                    In Indistractable, behavioural designer Nir Eyal reveals the hidden psychology driving you to distraction. Empowering and optimistic, this is the book that will help you design your time, realise your ambitions, and live the life you really want.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you value your time, your focus or your relationships, this book is essential reading&#8217; Jonathan Haidt, author of The Righteous Mind    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A guide to staying focused in an age of constant distraction&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Exactly what most of us need in order to focus on what is important, rather than the dazzling, illuminated, unsatisfying distractions of modern life&#8217; Matt Haig    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Does exactly as it promises. Amazing&#8217; Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The best guide I&#8217;ve read for reclaiming our attention, our focus and our lives&#8217; Arianna Huffington</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/">Indistractable : How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life &#8211; Nir Eyal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Take a break and read Rest: you&#8217;ll make smarter decisions, have better relationships, and be happier and more creative&#8221; James Wallman, author of Stuffocation Do you regularly find yourself too tired after a long day at your desk to do anything other than binge TV, or scroll mindlessly through social media? Do you go on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/">Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Take a break and read Rest: you&#8217;ll make smarter decisions, have better relationships, and be happier and more creative&#8221; James Wallman, author of Stuffocation    </p>
<p>                     Do you regularly find yourself too tired after a long day at your desk to do anything other than binge TV, or scroll mindlessly through social media? Do you go on holiday and still compulsively check your email? Do you work through your lunch-break, often not even leaving your desk to get some fresh air?    </p>
<p>                     For most of us, overwork is the new norm, and we never truly take the time to rest and recharge. But as Silicon Valley consultant Alex Soojung-Kim Pang explains in this groundbreaking book, rest needs to be taken seriously and to be done properly, because when you rest better you work better.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on emerging neuroscience, Rest is packed with easy practical tips for incorporating rest into our everyday:    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Go for a long walk to stimulate and sustain creativity<br />
                     &#8211; Schedule deliberate active rest periods into your diary to try out new activities like painting or learning a language<br />
                     &#8211; Stop working on a task when you know what the next step will be, this will make it easier to get started the next day<br />
                    &#8211; Establish clear boundaries between work and rest time<br />
                     &#8211; Take a nap during the day to increase alertness, boost your concentration and decrease fatigue<br />
                     &#8211; Get good quality sleep at night to stay healthy, solidify memories and generate new ideas    </p>
<p>                     When you rest better you&#8217;ll find that it won&#8217;t just be your work which improves &#8211; you&#8217;ll have more time for hobbies, stronger relationships and you&#8217;ll sleep better, too.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;An incredibly timely read for my own increasingly rest-starved life. This might be the book to finally persuade us that downtime isn&#8217;t in conflict with good work; rather, it&#8217;s an essential ingredient of it&#8221; Oliver Burkeman, Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/">Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Organized Mind : Thinking Straight in the Age of Information Overload &#8211; Daniel Levitin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-organized-mind-thinking-straight-in-the-age-of-information-overload-daniel-levitin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-organized-mind-thinking-straight-in-the-age-of-information-overload-daniel-levitin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Organized Mind, New York Times and Sunday Times bestselling author and neuroscientist Daniel Levitin offers solutions for the problems of information overload. ___________________________________________________ Overwhelmed by demands on your time? Baffled by the sheer volume of data? You&#8217;re not alone. Even the smartest mind can&#8217;t beat the organized mind &#8211; when we&#8217;re unable to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-organized-mind-thinking-straight-in-the-age-of-information-overload-daniel-levitin-abridged/">The Organized Mind : Thinking Straight in the Age of Information Overload &#8211; Daniel Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Organized Mind, New York Times and Sunday Times bestselling author and neuroscientist Daniel Levitin offers solutions for the problems of information overload.<br />
                    ___________________________________________________<br />
                     Overwhelmed by demands on your time? Baffled by the sheer volume of data?<br />
                    You&#8217;re not alone. Even the smartest mind can&#8217;t beat the organized mind &#8211; when we&#8217;re unable to make sense of it all, our creativity plummets, our decision making suffers and we grow absent-minded. Nowadays, we drown under emails, forever juggle six tasks at once and try to make complex decisions ever more quickly. This is information overload.    </p>
<p>                     Using a combination of academic research and examples from daily life, Daniel Levitin explains how to take back control of your life, from healthcare to online dating to raising kids, showing that the secret to success is always organization. You&#8217;ll discover life-changing facts about:    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; How to make the most of your brain&#8217;s daily processing limit<br />
                     &#8211; Why pressing Send or clicking Like are addictive<br />
                     &#8211; Why daydreaming is your brain at its most productive<br />
                     &#8211; What the most successful people keep in their drawer<br />
                     &#8211; Why multitasking is a bad way to do nearly everything    </p>
<p>                     In a world where information is power, The Organized Mind holds the key to harnessing that information and making it work for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-organized-mind-thinking-straight-in-the-age-of-information-overload-daniel-levitin-abridged/">The Organized Mind : Thinking Straight in the Age of Information Overload &#8211; Daniel Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Joy of Work : The No.1 Sunday Times Business Bestseller &#8211; 30 Ways to Fix Your Work Culture and Fall in Love with Your Job Again &#8211; Bruce Daisley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>__________________________ &#8216;Bruce Daisley is on a mission to change the world of work.&#8217; The Times __________________________ From the creator of hit podcast Eat Sleep Work Repeat comes a revolutionary re-envisioning of how to enjoy your job. Do you want to get more done, feel less stressed and love your job again? Sometimes having a job [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/">The Joy of Work : The No.1 Sunday Times Business Bestseller &#8211; 30 Ways to Fix Your Work Culture and Fall in Love with Your Job Again &#8211; Bruce Daisley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>__________________________<br />
                    &#8216;Bruce Daisley is on a mission to change the world of work.&#8217; The Times<br />
                    __________________________    </p>
<p>                    From the creator of hit podcast Eat Sleep Work Repeat comes a revolutionary re-envisioning of how to enjoy your job.    </p>
<p>                    Do you want to get more done, feel less stressed and love your job again?    </p>
<p>                    Sometimes having a job can feel like hard work. But between Monk Mode mornings, silent meetings and crisp Thursdays, the solutions are at your fingertips.    </p>
<p>                    Bruce Daisley knows a thing or two about the workplace. In the course of a career that has taken him from some of the world&#8217;s biggest media companies to Twitter, via Google and YouTube, he has become a leading expert on how we work now. And in his hugely popular podcast Eat Sleep Work Repeat, he has explored ways to fix it. Now he shares 30 brilliant &#8211; and refreshingly simple &#8211; tips on how to make your job more productive, more rewarding &#8211; and much, much more enjoyable.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;With just 30 changes, you can transform your work experience from bland and boring (or worse) to fulfilling, fun, and even joyful.&#8217; Daniel Pink, author of When and Drive    </p>
<p>                    __________________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is a warm, wise and funny book which provides a terrific summary of some of the science &#8211; and stories &#8211; behind what makes work a positive part of people&#8217;s lives. From the importance of lunch to the value of laughter, this book gives witty and practical advice. I loved it and I&#8217;ve already started changing some of the things I do at work, as a result!&#8221; &#8211; Professor Sophie Scott    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Don&#8217;t quit yet! In this book, Bruce shares remarkable advice that may well have you laughing while you work and truly loving your job.&#8221; &#8211; Biz Stone, Twitter co-founder    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Bruce Daisley&#8217;s The Joy of Work is a joy to read. It translates the best of workplace psychology research into practical ways of establishing creative and liveable cultures at work-a must read for all of us 9-5ers!&#8221; &#8211; Professor Sir Cary Cooper, ALLIANCE Manchester Business School, University of Manchester    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Bruce&#8217;s The Joy of Work is an important reminder of simple everyday practices to improve how we all work together, which will lead to greater team and individual happiness and performance. Great results will follow.&#8221; &#8211; Jack Dorsey, CEO of Twitter and Square    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;With just 30 changes, you can transform your work experience from bland and boring (or worse) to fulfilling, fun, and even joyful. Bruce Daisley has pulled together threads of research and woven them into a tapestry of strategies that actually work, and that don&#8217;t depend on the CEO&#8217;s sign-off for implementation. You can begin changing your work culture today at the individual, team, and organisational levels with these tactics that increase creativity, productivity, and satisfaction.&#8221; &#8211; Daniel Pink, author of WHEN and DRIVE</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/">The Joy of Work : The No.1 Sunday Times Business Bestseller &#8211; 30 Ways to Fix Your Work Culture and Fall in Love with Your Job Again &#8211; Bruce Daisley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability. Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability.    </p>
<p>                    Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more rewarding and productive life. He no longer has to contend with an environment that constantly demands more productivity, more output and more growth.    </p>
<p>                    In Company of One, Jarvis explains how you can do the same, including:    </p>
<p>                    *         Planning to set up<br />
                    *         Determining desired revenues<br />
                    *         Keeping clients happy<br />
                    *         And, of course, doing all this on your own.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jarvis makes a compelling case for making your business better instead of bigger. A must-read for any entrepreneur who prioritizes a rich life over riches.&#8221;<br />
                     -CAL NEWPORT, bestselling author of DEEP WORK and DIGITAL MINIMALISM    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You&#8217;re not a machine, so why would you run your business like one? Company of One shows you another way. If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how to have a business that works for you-instead of the other way around-you need this book.&#8221;<br />
                    -CHRIS GUILLEBEAU, bestselling author of SIDE HUSTLE and THE $100 STARTUP</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Awakening Compassion at Work : The Quiet Power That Elevates People and Organizations (16pt Large Print Edition) &#8211; Monica C Worline, Jane E Dutton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Caring Is a Competitive Advantage Suffering in the workplace can rob our colleagues and coworkers of humanity, dignity, and motivation and is an unrecognized and costly drain on organizational potential. Marshaling evidence from two decades of field research, scholars and consultants Monica Worline and Jane Dutton show that alleviating such suffering confers measurable competitive advantages [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/">Awakening Compassion at Work : The Quiet Power That Elevates People and Organizations (16pt Large Print Edition) &#8211; Monica C Worline, Jane E Dutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Caring Is a Competitive Advantage Suffering in the workplace can rob our colleagues and coworkers of humanity, dignity, and motivation and is an unrecognized and costly drain on organizational potential. Marshaling evidence from two decades of field research, scholars and consultants Monica Worline and Jane Dutton show that alleviating such suffering confers measurable competitive advantages in areas like innovation, collaboration, service quality, and talent attraction and retention. They outline four steps for meeting suffering with compassion and show how to build a capacity for compassion into the structures and practices of an organization-because ultimately, as they write, Compassion is an irreplaceable dimension of excellence for any organization that wants to make the most of its human capabilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/">Awakening Compassion at Work : The Quiet Power That Elevates People and Organizations (16pt Large Print Edition) &#8211; Monica C Worline, Jane E Dutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Robots Are Coming! : The Future of Jobs in the Age of Automation &#8211; Andres Oppenheimer, Translated by Ezra E. Fitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-robots-are-coming-the-future-of-jobs-in-the-age-of-automation-andres-oppenheimer-translated-by-ezra-e-fitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations & Safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-robots-are-coming-the-future-of-jobs-in-the-age-of-automation-andres-oppenheimer-translated-by-ezra-e-fitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Staying true to his trademark journalistic approach, Andrés Oppenheimer takes his readers on yet another journey, this time across the globe, in a thought-provoking search to understand what the future holds for today&#8217;s jobs in the foreseeable age of automation. The Robots Are Coming! centers around the issue of jobs and their future in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-robots-are-coming-the-future-of-jobs-in-the-age-of-automation-andres-oppenheimer-translated-by-ezra-e-fitz-abridged/">The Robots Are Coming! : The Future of Jobs in the Age of Automation &#8211; Andres Oppenheimer, Translated by Ezra E. Fitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Staying true to his trademark journalistic approach, Andrés Oppenheimer takes his readers on yet another journey, this time across the globe, in a thought-provoking search to understand what the future holds for today&#8217;s jobs in the foreseeable age of automation.     </p>
<p>                    The Robots Are Coming! centers around the issue of jobs and their future in the context of rapid automation and the growth of online products and services. As two of Oppenheimer&#8217;s interviewees &#8212; both experts in technology and economics from Oxford University &#8212; indicate, forty-seven percent of existing jobs are at risk of becoming automated or rendered obsolete by other technological changes in the next twenty years. Oppenheimer examines current changes in several fields, including the food business, legal work, banking, and medicine, speaking with experts in the field, and citing articles and literature on automation in various areas of the workforce. He contrasts the perspectives of techno-optimists with those of techno-negativists and generally attempts to find a middle ground between an alarmist vision of the future, and one that is too uncritical. A self-described cautious optimist, Oppenheimer believes that technology will not create massive unemployment, but rather will drastically change what work looks like.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-robots-are-coming-the-future-of-jobs-in-the-age-of-automation-andres-oppenheimer-translated-by-ezra-e-fitz-abridged/">The Robots Are Coming! : The Future of Jobs in the Age of Automation &#8211; Andres Oppenheimer, Translated by Ezra E. Fitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mastery : The Keys to Success and Long-Term Fulfillment &#8211; George Leonard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mastery-the-keys-to-success-and-long-term-fulfillment-george-leonard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mastery-the-keys-to-success-and-long-term-fulfillment-george-leonard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Drawing on Zen philosophy and his expertise in the martial art of aikido, bestselling author George Leonard shows how the process of mastery can help us attain a higher level of excellence and a deeper sense of satisfaction and fulfillment in our daily lives. Whether you&#8217;re seeking to improve your career or your intimate relationships, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mastery-the-keys-to-success-and-long-term-fulfillment-george-leonard-abridged/">Mastery : The Keys to Success and Long-Term Fulfillment &#8211; George Leonard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Drawing on Zen philosophy and his expertise in the martial art of aikido, bestselling author George Leonard shows how the process of mastery can help us attain a higher level of excellence and a deeper sense of satisfaction and fulfillment in our daily lives.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re seeking to improve your career or your intimate relationships, increase self-esteem or create harmony within yourself, this inspiring prescriptive guide will help you master anything you choose and achieve success in all areas of your life. In Mastery, you&#8217;ll discover:    </p>
<p>                    * The 5 Essential Keys to Mastery<br />
                    * Tools for Mastery<br />
                    * How to Master Your Athletic Potential<br />
                    * The 3 Personality Types That Are Obstacles to Mastery<br />
                    * How to Avoid Pitfalls Along the Path<br />
                    * and more&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mastery-the-keys-to-success-and-long-term-fulfillment-george-leonard-abridged/">Mastery : The Keys to Success and Long-Term Fulfillment &#8211; George Leonard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Measure : The Big Impact of Small Changes &#8211; Margaret Heffernan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-measure-the-big-impact-of-small-changes-margaret-heffernan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-measure-the-big-impact-of-small-changes-margaret-heffernan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A powerful manifesto for CEOs and employees alike: Influential and award-winning business leader Margaret Heffernan reveals how organizations can build ideal workplace cultures and create seismic shifts by making deceptively small changes. By implementing sweeping changes, businesses often think it&#8217;s possible to do better, to earn more, and have happier employees. So why does engagement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-measure-the-big-impact-of-small-changes-margaret-heffernan-abridged/">Beyond Measure : The Big Impact of Small Changes &#8211; Margaret Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A powerful manifesto for CEOs and employees alike: Influential and award-winning business leader Margaret Heffernan reveals how organizations can build ideal workplace cultures and create seismic shifts by making deceptively small changes.     </p>
<p>                    By implementing sweeping changes, businesses often think it&#8217;s possible to do better, to earn more, and have happier employees. So why does engagement prove so difficult and productivity so elusive?     </p>
<p>                    In Beyond Measure, Margaret Heffernan looks back over her decades spent overseeing different organizations and comes to a counterintuitive conclusion: it&#8217;s the small shifts that have the greatest impact. Heffernan argues that building the strongest organization can be accelerated by implementing seemingly small changes, such as embracing conflict as a creative catalyst; using every mind on the team; celebrating mistakes; speaking up and listening more; and encouraging time off from work.     </p>
<p>                    Packed with incredible anecdotes and startling statistics, Beyond Measure takes us on a fascinating tour across the globe, highlighting disparate businesses and revealing how they&#8217;ve managed to change themselves in big ways through incremental shifts. How did the CIA revolutionize their intelligence gathering with one simple question? How did one organization increase their revenue by $15 million by instituting a short coffee break? How can a day-long hackathon change the culture of a company? Told with wry wit and knowing humor, Heffernan proves that it&#8217;s often the small changes that make the greatest, most lasting impact.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-measure-the-big-impact-of-small-changes-margaret-heffernan-abridged/">Beyond Measure : The Big Impact of Small Changes &#8211; Margaret Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Berkshire Hathaway, the $300 billion conglomerate that Warren Buffett built, is among the world&#8217;s largest and most famous corporations. Yet, for all its power and celebrity, few people understand Berkshire, and many assume it cannot survive without Buffett. This book proves them wrong. In a comprehensive portrait of the corporate culture that unites Berkshire&#8217;s subsidiaries, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/">Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Berkshire Hathaway, the $300 billion conglomerate that Warren Buffett built, is among the world&#8217;s largest and most famous corporations. Yet, for all its power and celebrity, few people understand Berkshire, and many assume it cannot survive without Buffett. This book proves them wrong. In a comprehensive portrait of the corporate culture that unites Berkshire&#8217;s subsidiaries, Lawrence A. Cunningham unearths the traits that assure the conglomerate&#8217;s continued prosperity. Riveting stories of each subsidiary&#8217;s origins, triumphs, and journey to Berkshire reveal how managers generate economic value from intangibles like thrift, integrity, entrepreneurship, autonomy, and a sense of permanence. Rich with lessons for those wishing to profit from the Berkshire model, this engaging book is a valuable read for entrepreneurs, business owners, managers, family business members, and investors, and it is an important resource for scholars of corporate stewardship. General readers will enjoy learning how an iconoclastic businessman transformed a struggling textile company into a corporate legacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/">Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reboot : Leadership and the Art of Growing Up &#8211; Jerry Colonna (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reboot-leadership-and-the-art-of-growing-up-jerry-colonna-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reboot-leadership-and-the-art-of-growing-up-jerry-colonna-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the start-up world&#8217;s most in-demand executive coaches-hailed as the &#8220;CEO Whisperer&#8221; (Gimlet Media)-reveals why radical self-inquiry is critical to professional success and healthy relationships in all realms of life. Jerry Colonna helps start-up CEOs make peace with their demons, the psychological habits and behavioral patterns that have helped them to succeed-molding them into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reboot-leadership-and-the-art-of-growing-up-jerry-colonna-abridged/">Reboot : Leadership and the Art of Growing Up &#8211; Jerry Colonna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the start-up world&#8217;s most in-demand executive coaches-hailed as the &#8220;CEO Whisperer&#8221; (Gimlet Media)-reveals why radical self-inquiry is critical to professional success and healthy relationships in all realms of life.    </p>
<p>                    Jerry Colonna helps start-up CEOs make peace with their demons, the psychological habits and behavioral patterns that have helped them to succeed-molding them into highly accomplished individuals-yet have been detrimental to their relationships and ultimate well-being. Now, this venture capitalist turned executive coach shares his unusual yet highly effective blend of Buddhism, Jungian therapy, and entrepreneurial straight talk to help leaders overcome their own psychological traumas. Reboot is a journey of radical self-inquiry, helping you to reset your life by sorting through the emotional baggage that is holding you back professionally, and even more important, in your relationships.    </p>
<p>                    Jerry has taught CEOs and their top teams to realize their potential by using the raw material of their lives to find meaning, to build healthy interpersonal bonds, and to become more compassionate and bold leaders. In Reboot, he inspires everyone to hold themselves responsible for their choices and for the possibility of truly achieving their dreams.    </p>
<p>                    Work does not have to destroy us. Work can be the way in which we achieve our fullest self, Jerry firmly believes. What we need, sometimes, is a chance to reset our goals and to reconnect with our deepest selves and with each other. Reboot moves and empowers us to begin this journey.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reboot-leadership-and-the-art-of-growing-up-jerry-colonna-abridged/">Reboot : Leadership and the Art of Growing Up &#8211; Jerry Colonna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Too Fast to Think : How to Reclaim Your Creativity in a Hyper-connected Work Culture &#8211; Chris Lewis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/too-fast-to-think-how-to-reclaim-your-creativity-in-a-hyper-connected-work-culture-chris-lewis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/too-fast-to-think-how-to-reclaim-your-creativity-in-a-hyper-connected-work-culture-chris-lewis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our lives are getting faster and faster. We are engulfed in constant distraction from email, social media and our &#8216;always on&#8217; work culture. We are too busy, too overloaded with information and too focused on analytical left-brain thinking processes to be creative. Too Fast to Think exposes how our current work practices, media culture and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/too-fast-to-think-how-to-reclaim-your-creativity-in-a-hyper-connected-work-culture-chris-lewis-abridged/">Too Fast to Think : How to Reclaim Your Creativity in a Hyper-connected Work Culture &#8211; Chris Lewis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our lives are getting faster and faster. We are engulfed in constant distraction from email, social media and our &#8216;always on&#8217; work culture. We are too busy, too overloaded with information and too focused on analytical left-brain thinking processes to be creative. Too Fast to Think exposes how our current work practices, media culture and education systems are detrimental to innovation. The speed and noise of modern life is undermining the clarity and quiet that is essential to power individual thought. Our best ideas are often generated when we are free to think diffusely, in an uninterrupted environment, which is why moments of inspiration so often occur in places completely separate to our offices.     </p>
<p>                    To reclaim creativity, Too Fast to Think teaches you how to retrain your brain into allowing creative ideas to emerge, before they are shut down by interruption, distraction or the self-doubt of your over-rational brain. This is essential reading for anyone who wants to maximize their creative potential, as well as that of their team. Supported by cutting-edge research from the University of the Arts London and insightful interviews with business leaders, academics, artists, politicians and psychologists, Chris Lewis takes a holistic approach to explain the 8 crucial traits that are inherently linked to creation and innovation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/too-fast-to-think-how-to-reclaim-your-creativity-in-a-hyper-connected-work-culture-chris-lewis-abridged/">Too Fast to Think : How to Reclaim Your Creativity in a Hyper-connected Work Culture &#8211; Chris Lewis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Outward Mindset &#8211; Arbinger Institute (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-outward-mindset-arbinger-institute-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-outward-mindset-arbinger-institute-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The new edition of an international bestseller helps individuals and organizations shift to a new mindset that will improve performance, spark collaboration, accelerate innovation, and make your life and the lives of everyone around you better. Without even being aware of it, many of us operate from an inward mindset, a single-minded focus on our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-outward-mindset-arbinger-institute-abridged/">The Outward Mindset &#8211; Arbinger Institute (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The new edition of an international bestseller helps individuals and organizations shift to a new mindset that will improve performance, spark collaboration, accelerate innovation, and make your life and the lives of everyone around you better.     </p>
<p>                     Without even being aware of it, many of us operate from an inward mindset, a single-minded focus on our own goals and objectives. This book points out the many ways, some quite subtle and deceptive, that this mindset invites tension and conflict. But incredible things happen when people switch to an outward mindset. They intuitively understand what coworkers, colleagues, family, and friends need to be successful and happy. Their organizations thrive, and astonishingly, by focusing on others they become happier and more successful themselves! This new mindset brings about deep and far-reaching changes.     </p>
<p>                     The Outward Mindset presents compelling true stories to illustrate the gaps that individuals and organizations typically experience between their actual inward mindsets and their needed outward mindsets. And it provides simple yet profound guidance and tools to help bridge this mindset gap. This new edition includes a new preface, updated case studies, and new material covering Arbinger&#8217;s latest research on mindsets. In the long run, changing negative behavior without changing one&#8217;s mindset doesn&#8217;t last&#8211;the old behaviors always reassert themselves. But changing the mindset that causes the behavior changes everything.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-outward-mindset-arbinger-institute-abridged/">The Outward Mindset &#8211; Arbinger Institute (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
