<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Natural History Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/natural-history-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/natural-history-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Natural History Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/natural-history-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic In the two years after the 1939 publication of Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful The Grapes of Wrath, Steinbeck and his novel increasingly became the center of intense controversy and censorship. In search of a respite from the national stage, Steinbeck and his close friend, biologist Ed Ricketts, embarked on a month long marine specimen-collecting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/">The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic     </p>
<p>                    In the two years after the 1939 publication of Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful The Grapes of Wrath, Steinbeck and his novel increasingly became the center of intense controversy and censorship. In search of a respite from the national stage, Steinbeck and his close friend, biologist Ed Ricketts, embarked on a month long marine specimen-collecting expedition in the Gulf of California, which resulted in their collaboration on the Sea of Cortez. In 1951, after Ricketts&#8217; death, Steinbeck reissued his narrative portion of the work in memory of his friend and the inspiration for Cannery Row&#8217;s &#8220;Doc&#8221;. This exciting day-by-day account of their journey together is a rare blend of science, philosophy, and high-spirited adventure. This edition features an introduction by Richard Astro.     </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/">The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized  the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much more besides. In it, Dawkins extended the gene&#8217;s eye view to argue that the genes that sit within an organism have an<br />
                    influence that reaches out beyond the visible traits in that body &#8211; the phenotype &#8211; to the wider environment, which can include other individuals. So, for instance, the genes of the beaver drive it to gather twigs to produce the substantial physical structure of a dam; and the genes of the cuckoo chick produce effects that<br />
                    manipulate the behaviour of the host bird, making it nurture the intruder as one of its own. This notion of the extended phenotype has proved to be highly influential in the way we understand evolution and the natural world. It represents a key scientific contribution to evolutionary biology, and it continues to play an important role in research in the life sciences.    </p>
<p>                    The Extended Phenotype is a conceptually deep book that forms important reading for biologists and students. But Dawkins&#8217; clear exposition is accessible to all who are prepared to put in a little effort.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Magic of Reality : How we know what&#8217;s really true &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-magic-of-reality-how-we-know-whats-really-true-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-magic-of-reality-how-we-know-whats-really-true-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Magic takes many forms. The ancient Egyptians explained the night by suggesting that the goddess Nut swallowed the sun. The Vikings believed a rainbow was the gods&#8217; bridge to earth. These are magical, extraordinary tales. But there is another kind of magic, and it lies in the exhilaration of discovering the real answers to these [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-magic-of-reality-how-we-know-whats-really-true-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Magic of Reality : How we know what&#8217;s really true &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Magic takes many forms. The ancient Egyptians explained the night by suggesting that the goddess Nut swallowed the sun. The Vikings believed a rainbow was the gods&#8217; bridge to earth. These are magical, extraordinary tales. But there is another kind of magic, and it lies in the exhilaration of discovering the real answers to these questions. It is the magic of reality &#8211; science.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with inspiring explanations of space, time and evolution, laced with humour and clever thought experiments, The Magic of Reality explores a stunningly wide range of natural phenomena. What is stuff made of? How old is the universe? What causes tsunamis? Who was the first man, or woman? This is a page-turning, inspirational detective story that not only mines all the sciences for its clues but primes the reader to think like a scientist too.    </p>
<p>                    Richard Dawkins elucidates the wonders of the natural world to all ages with his inimitable clarity and exuberance in a text that will enlighten and inform for generations to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-magic-of-reality-how-we-know-whats-really-true-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Magic of Reality : How we know what&#8217;s really true &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walden: Or, Life in the Woods &#8211; Henry David Thoreau (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nature was a form of religion for naturalist, essayist, and early environmentalist Henry David Thoreau (1817-62). In communing with the natural world, he wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and &#8230; learn what it had to teach. Toward that end Thoreau built a cabin in the spring of 1845 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/">Walden: Or, Life in the Woods &#8211; Henry David Thoreau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nature was a form of religion for naturalist, essayist, and early environmentalist Henry David Thoreau (1817-62). In communing with the natural world, he wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and &#8230; learn what it had to teach. Toward that end Thoreau built a cabin in the spring of 1845 on the shores of Walden Pond &#8212; on land owned by Ralph Waldo Emerson &#8212; outside Concord, Massachusetts. There he observed nature, farmed, built fences, surveyed, and wrote in his journal.<br />
                    One product of his two-year sojourn was this book &#8212; a great classic of American letters. Interwoven with accounts of Thoreau&#8217;s daily life (he received visitors and almost daily walked into Concord) are mediations on human existence, society, government, and other topics, expressed with wisdom and beauty of style.<br />
                    Walden offers abundant evidence of Thoreau&#8217;s ability to begin with observations on a mundane incident or the minutiae of nature and then develop these observations into profound ruminations on the most fundamental human concerns. Credited with influencing Tolstoy, Gandhi, and other thinkers, the volume remains a masterpiece of philosophical reflection.<br />
                    A selection of the Common Core State Standards Initiative.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/">Walden: Or, Life in the Woods &#8211; Henry David Thoreau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mosquito : A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator &#8211; Timothy C. Winegard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Butterflies, Other Insects & Spiders]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**The instant New York Times bestseller** *An international bestseller* &#8220;Hugely impressive, a major work.&#8221;&#8211;NPR A pioneering and groundbreaking work of narrative nonfiction that offers a dramatic new perspective on the history of humankind, showing how through millennia, the mosquito has been the single most powerful force in determining humanity&#8217;s fate. Why was gin and tonic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/">The Mosquito : A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator &#8211; Timothy C. Winegard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**The instant New York Times bestseller**<br />
                    *An international bestseller*     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hugely impressive, a major work.&#8221;&#8211;NPR    </p>
<p>                    A pioneering and groundbreaking work of narrative nonfiction that offers a dramatic new perspective on the history of humankind, showing how through millennia, the mosquito has been the single most powerful force in determining humanity&#8217;s fate.     </p>
<p>                     Why was gin and tonic the cocktail of choice for British colonists in India and Africa? What does Starbucks have to thank for its global domination? What has protected the lives of popes for millennia? Why did Scotland surrender its sovereignty to England? What was George Washington&#8217;s secret weapon during the American Revolution?     </p>
<p>                     The answer to all these questions, and many more, is the mosquito.     </p>
<p>                     Across our planet since the dawn of humankind, this nefarious pest, roughly the size and weight of a grape seed, has been at the frontlines of history as the grim reaper, the harvester of human populations, and the ultimate agent of historical change. As the mosquito transformed the landscapes of civilization, humans were unwittingly required to respond to its piercing impact and universal projection of power.     </p>
<p>                     The mosquito has determined the fates of empires and nations, razed and crippled economies, and decided the outcome of pivotal wars, killing nearly half of humanity along the way. She (only females bite) has dispatched an estimated 52 billion people from a total of 108 billion throughout our relatively brief existence. As the greatest purveyor of extermination we have ever known, she has played a greater role in shaping our human story than any other living thing with which we share our global village.     </p>
<p>                     Imagine for a moment a world without deadly mosquitoes, or any mosquitoes, for that matter? Our history and the world we know, or think we know, would be completely unrecognizable.     </p>
<p>                     Driven by surprising insights and fast-paced storytelling, The Mosquito is the extraordinary untold story of the mosquito&#8217;s reign through human history and her indelible impact on our modern world order.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/">The Mosquito : A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator &#8211; Timothy C. Winegard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Origin Story : A Big History of Everything &#8211; David Christian (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/origin-story-a-big-history-of-everything-david-christian-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Earliest Times To Present Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/origin-story-a-big-history-of-everything-david-christian-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>David Christian, creator of Big History (&#8216;My favourite course of all time&#8217; Bill Gates), brings us the epic story of the universe and our place in it, from 13.8 billion years ago to the remote future &#8216;Nails home the point: Life is a miracle &#8230; A compelling history of everything&#8217; Washington Post &#8216;Spectacular&#8217; Carlo Rovelli [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/origin-story-a-big-history-of-everything-david-christian-abridged/">Origin Story : A Big History of Everything &#8211; David Christian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>David Christian, creator of Big History (&#8216;My favourite course of all time&#8217; Bill Gates), brings us the epic story of the universe and our place in it, from 13.8 billion years ago to the remote future    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Nails home the point: Life is a  miracle &#8230; A compelling history of everything&#8217; Washington Post<br />
                     &#8216;Spectacular&#8217; Carlo Rovelli    </p>
<p>                    How  did we get from the Big Bang to today&#8217;s staggering complexity, in which  seven billion humans are connected into networks powerful enough to  transform the planet? And why, in comparison, are our closest primate  relatives reduced to near-extinction?     </p>
<p>                    Big History creator David  Christian gives the answers in a mind-expanding cosmological detective  story told on the grandest possible scale. He traces how, during eight  key thresholds, the right conditions have allowed new forms of  complexity to arise, from stars to galaxies, Earth to homo sapiens,  agriculture to fossil fuels. This last mega-innovation gave us an energy  bonanza that brought huge benefits to mankind, yet also threatens to  shake apart everything we have created.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rather like the Big Bang, the book is awe-inspiring &#8230; Superb&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;With   fascinating ideas on every page and the page-turning energy of a good   thriller, this is a landmark work&#8217; Sir Ken Robinson, author of The Element</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/origin-story-a-big-history-of-everything-david-christian-abridged/">Origin Story : A Big History of Everything &#8211; David Christian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geographical Discovery & Exploration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geology & The Lithosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Geography & Topography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** Winner of Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books 2015 ** We live in epoch-making times. The changes we humans have made in recent decades have altered our world beyond anything it has experienced in its 4.6 billion-year history. As a result, our planet is said to be crossing into the Anthropocene &#8211; the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/">Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** Winner of Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books 2015 **    </p>
<p>                    We live in epoch-making times. The changes we humans have made in recent decades have altered our world beyond anything it has experienced in its 4.6 billion-year history. As a result, our planet is said to be crossing into the Anthropocene &#8211; the Age of Humans.     </p>
<p>                     Gaia Vince decided to travel the world at the start of this new age to see what life is really like for the people on the frontline of the planet we&#8217;ve made.  From artificial glaciers in the Himalayas to painted mountains in Peru, electrified reefs in the Maldives to garbage islands in the Caribbean, Gaia found people doing the most extraordinary things to solve the problems that we ourselves have created.    </p>
<p>                     These stories show what the Anthropocene means for all of us &#8211; and they illuminate how we might engineer Earth for our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/">Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Walk in the Woods : Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Outdoor Survival Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Walking, Hiking, Trekking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Appalachian Trail trail stretches from Georgia to Maine and covers some of the most breathtaking terrain in America-majestic mountains, silent forests, sparking lakes. If you&#8217;re going to take a hike, it&#8217;s probably the place to go. And Bill Bryson is surely the most entertaining guide you&#8217;ll find. He introduces us to the history and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/">A Walk in the Woods : Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Appalachian Trail trail stretches from Georgia to Maine and covers some of the most breathtaking terrain in America-majestic mountains, silent forests, sparking lakes. If you&#8217;re going to take a hike, it&#8217;s probably the place to go. And Bill Bryson is surely the most entertaining guide you&#8217;ll find. He introduces us to the history and ecology of the trail and to some of the other hardy (or just foolhardy) folks he meets along the way-and a couple of bears. Already a classic, A Walk in the Woods  will make you long for the great outdoors (or at least a comfortable chair to sit and read in).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/">A Walk in the Woods : Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Planet of Viruses : Second Edition &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The past year has been one of viral panic-panic about viruses, that is. Through headlines, public health warnings, and at least one homemade hazmat suit, we were reminded of the powerful force of viruses. They are the smallest living things known to science, yet they can hold the entire planet in their sway. A Planet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/">A Planet of Viruses : Second Edition &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past year has been one of viral panic-panic about viruses, that is. Through headlines, public health warnings, and at least one homemade hazmat suit, we were reminded of the powerful force of viruses. They are the smallest living things known to science, yet they can hold the entire planet in their sway. A Planet of Viruses is Carl Zimmer&#8217;s eye-opening look at the hidden world of viruses. Zimmer, the popular science writer and author of National Geographic&#8217;s award-winning blog The Loom, has updated this edition to include the stories of new outbreaks, such as Ebola, MERS, and chikungunya virus; new scientific discoveries, such as a hundred-million-year-old virus that infected the common ancestor of armadillos, elephants, and humans; and new findings that show why climate change may lead to even deadlier outbreaks. Zimmer&#8217;s lucid explanations and fascinating stories demonstrate how deeply humans and viruses are intertwined. Viruses helped give rise to the first life-forms, are responsible for many of our most devastating diseases, and will continue to control our fate for centuries.<br />
                    Thoroughly readable, and as reassuring as it is frightening, A Planet of Viruses is a fascinating tour of a formidable hidden world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/">A Planet of Viruses : Second Edition &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Braiding Sweetgrass : Indigenous Wisdom, Scientific Knowledge and the Teachings of Plants &#8211; Robin Wall Kimmerer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Botany & Plant Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees, Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A hymn of love to the world &#8230; A journey that is every bit as mythic as it is scientific, as sacred as it is historical, as clever as it is wise&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert, author of Eat, Pray, Love As a botanist, Robin Wall Kimmerer has been trained to ask questions of nature with the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/">Braiding Sweetgrass : Indigenous Wisdom, Scientific Knowledge and the Teachings of Plants &#8211; Robin Wall Kimmerer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A hymn of love to the world &#8230; A journey that is every bit as mythic as it is scientific, as sacred as  it is historical, as clever as it is wise&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert, author of Eat, Pray, Love    </p>
<p>                    As a botanist, Robin Wall Kimmerer has been trained to ask questions of nature with the tools of science. As a member of the Citizen Potawatomi Nation, she embraces the notion that plants and animals are our oldest teachers. In Braiding Sweetgrass, Kimmerer brings these two ways of knowledge together.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on her life as an indigenous scientist, a mother, and a woman, Kimmerer shows how other living beings &#8211; asters and goldenrod, strawberries and squash, salamanders, algae, and sweetgrass &#8211; offer us gifts and lessons, even if we&#8217;ve forgotten how to hear their voices. In a rich braid of reflections that range from the creation of Turtle Island to the forces that threaten its flourishing today, she circles toward a central argument: that the awakening of a wider ecological consciousness requires the acknowledgment and celebration of our reciprocal relationship with the rest of the living world. For only when we can hear the languages of other beings will we be capable of understanding the generosity of the earth, and learn to give our own gifts in return.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/">Braiding Sweetgrass : Indigenous Wisdom, Scientific Knowledge and the Teachings of Plants &#8211; Robin Wall Kimmerer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Triumph of Seeds : How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees, Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We live in a world of seeds. From our morning toast to the cotton in our clothes, they are quite literally the stuff and staff of life: supporting diets, economies, and civilizations around the globe. Just as the search for nutmeg and pepper drove the Age of Discovery, coffee beans fueled the Enlightenment and cottonseed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/">The Triumph of Seeds : How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We live in a world of seeds. From our morning toast to the cotton in our clothes, they are quite literally the stuff and staff of life: supporting diets, economies, and civilizations around the globe. Just as the search for nutmeg and pepper drove the Age of Discovery, coffee beans fueled the Enlightenment and cottonseed sparked the Industrial Revolution. Seeds are fundamental objects of beauty, evolutionary wonders, and simple fascinations. Yet, despite their importance, seeds are often seen as commonplace, their extraordinary natural and human histories overlooked. Thanks to this stunning new book, they can be overlooked no more. This is a book of knowledge, adventure, and wonder, spun by an award-winning writer with both the charm of a fireside story-teller and the hard-won expertise of a field biologist. A fascinating scientific adventure, it is essential reading for anyone who loves to see a plant grow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/">The Triumph of Seeds : How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cannibalism: a Perfectly Natural History &#8211; Bill Schutt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cannibalism-a-perfectly-natural-history-bill-schutt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cannibalism-a-perfectly-natural-history-bill-schutt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Surprising. Impressive. Cannibalism restores my faith in humanity.&#8221; &#8211;Sy Montgomery, The New York Times Book Review For centuries scientists have written off cannibalism as a bizarre phenomenon with little biological significance. Its presence in nature was dismissed as a desperate response to starvation or other life-threatening circumstances, and few spent time studying it. A taboo [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cannibalism-a-perfectly-natural-history-bill-schutt-abridged/">Cannibalism: a Perfectly Natural History &#8211; Bill Schutt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Surprising. Impressive. Cannibalism restores my faith in humanity.&#8221; &#8211;Sy Montgomery, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                     For centuries scientists have written off cannibalism as a bizarre phenomenon with little biological significance. Its presence in nature was dismissed as a desperate response to starvation or other life-threatening circumstances, and few spent time studying it. A taboo subject in our culture, the behavior was portrayed mostly through horror movies or tabloids sensationalizing the crimes of real-life flesh-eaters. But the true nature of cannibalism&#8211;the role it plays in evolution as well as human history&#8211;is even more intriguing (and more normal) than the misconceptions we&#8217;ve come to accept as fact.    </p>
<p>                     In Cannibalism: A Perfectly Natural History,  zoologist Bill Schutt sets the record straight, debunking common myths and investigating our new understanding of cannibalism&#8217;s role in biology, anthropology, and history in the most fascinating account yet written on this complex topic. Schutt takes readers from Arizona&#8217;s Chiricahua Mountains, where he wades through ponds full of tadpoles devouring their siblings, to the Sierra Nevadas, where he joins researchers who are shedding new light on what happened to the Donner Party&#8211;the most infamous episode of cannibalism in American history. He even meets with an expert on the preparation and consumption of human placenta (and, yes, it goes well with Chianti).    </p>
<p>                     Bringing together the latest cutting-edge science, Schutt answers questions such as why some amphibians consume their mother&#8217;s skin; why certain insects bite the heads off their partners after sex; why, up until the end of the twentieth century, Europeans regularly ate human body parts as medical curatives; and how cannibalism might be linked to the extinction of the Neanderthals. He takes us into the future as well, investigating whether, as climate change causes famine, disease, and overcrowding, we may see more outbreaks of cannibalism in many more species&#8211;including our own.    </p>
<p>                     Cannibalism places a perfectly natural occurrence into a vital new context and invites us to explore why it both enthralls and repels us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cannibalism-a-perfectly-natural-history-bill-schutt-abridged/">Cannibalism: a Perfectly Natural History &#8211; Bill Schutt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feathers : The Evolution of a Natural Miracle &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Birds (ornithology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dinosaurs & The Prehistoric World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Birds & Birdwatching]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Feathers are an evolutionary marvel: aerodynamic, insulating, beguiling. They date back more than 100 million years. Yet their story has never been fully told. In Feathers , biologist Thor Hanson details a sweeping natural history, as feathers have been used to fly, protect, attract, and adorn through time and place. Applying the research of paleontologists, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/">Feathers : The Evolution of a Natural Miracle &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Feathers are an evolutionary marvel: aerodynamic, insulating, beguiling. They date back more than 100 million years. Yet their story has never been fully told. In  Feathers , biologist Thor Hanson details a sweeping natural history, as feathers have been used to fly, protect, attract, and adorn through time and place. Applying the research of paleontologists, ornithologists, biologists, engineers, and even art historians, Hanson asks: What are feathers? How did they evolve? What do they mean to us? Engineers call feathers the most efficient insulating material ever discovered, and they are at the root of biology&#8217;s most enduring debate. They silence the flight of owls and keep penguins dry below the ice. They have decorated queens, jesters, and priests. And they have inked documents from the Constitution to the novels of Jane Austen.  Feathers  is a captivating and beautiful exploration of this most enchanting object.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/">Feathers : The Evolution of a Natural Miracle &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Geography & Topography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel With Children / Family Holidays]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>By the beloved and wildly popular host of the PBS Kids show Dinosaur Train, here is the book every parent needs: a rousing call to connect our kids to the natural world, filled with tips and advice. The average North American child now spends about seven hours a day staring at screens and mere minutes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/">How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By the beloved and wildly popular host of the PBS Kids show Dinosaur Train, here is the book every parent needs: a rousing call to connect our kids to the natural world, filled with tips and advice.    </p>
<p>                    The average North American child now spends about seven hours a day staring at screens and mere minutes engaged in unstructured play outdoors. Yet recent research indicates that experiences in nature are essential for healthy growth.     </p>
<p>                    Regular exposure to nature can help relieve stress, depression, and attention deficits. It can reduce bullying, combat obesity, and boost academic scores. Most critical of all, abundant time in natural settings seems to yield long-term benefits in kids&#8217; cognitive, emotional, and social development.     </p>
<p>                    How to Raise a Wild Child is a timely and engaging antidote, offering teachers, parents, and other caregivers the necessary tools to engender a meaningful, lasting connection between children and the natural world.     </p>
<p>                    Distilling the latest research in multiple disciplines, Sampson reveals how adults can help kids fall in love with nature&#8211;enlisting technology as an ally, taking advantage of urban nature, and instilling a sense of place along the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In a time when the connection between humans and the rest of nature is most vulnerable, Scott offers parents and teachers a book of encouragement and knowledge, and to children, the priceless gift of wonder.&#8221;&#8211;Richard Louv, author of Last Child in the Woods and The Nature Principle</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/">How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
