<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Small Businesses &amp; Self-employed Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/small-businesses-self-employed/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/small-businesses-self-employed/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Small Businesses &amp; Self-employed Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/small-businesses-self-employed/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crush It! : Why NOW Is the Time to Cash In on Your Passion &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</title>
		<link>/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a hobby you wish you could do all day? An obsession that keeps you up at night? Now is the perfect time to take those passions and make a living doing what you love. In Crush It! Why Now Is The Time To Cash In On Your Passion, Gary Vaynerchuk shows you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/">Crush It! : Why NOW Is the Time to Cash In on Your Passion &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a hobby you wish you could do all day? An obsession that keeps you up at night? Now is the perfect time to take those passions and make a living doing what you love. In Crush It! Why Now Is The Time To Cash In On Your Passion, Gary Vaynerchuk shows you how to use the power of the Internet to turn your real interests into real businesses. Gary spent years building his family business from a local wine shop into a national industry leader. Then one day he turned on a video camera, and by using the secrets revealed in this book, transformed his entire life and earning potential by building his personal brand. By the end of this book, any reader will have learned how to harness the power of the Internet to make their entrepreneurial dreams come true. Step by step, Crush It! is the ultimate driver&#8217;s manual for modern business. Gary Vaynerchuk has captured attention with his pioneering, multi-faceted approach to personal branding and business.<br />
                    After primarily utilizing traditional advertising techniques to build his family&#8217;s local retail wine business into a national industry leader, Gary rapidly leveraged social media tools such as Twitter and Facebook to promote Wine Library TV. Gary has always had an early-to-market approach, launching Wine Library&#8217;s retail website in 1997 and Wine Library TV in February of 2006. His lessons on social media, passion, transparency, and reactionary business are not to be missed!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/">Crush It! : Why NOW Is the Time to Cash In on Your Passion &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We&#8217;re All Marketers : 20 Go-To Principles To Help You Market Like a Marketer &#8211; Nico de Bruyn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/were-all-marketers-20-go-to-principles-to-help-you-market-like-a-marketer-nico-de-bruyn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/were-all-marketers-20-go-to-principles-to-help-you-market-like-a-marketer-nico-de-bruyn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Did you know that you&#8217;re a marketer? That&#8217;s right. In today&#8217;s consumerist, always-digital, interconnected environment, it&#8217;s almost become a necessity to be a marketer. We have all adapted to survive, whether that be to wade through the nearly 4,000 advertisements many of us see everyday, or to help convince friends and family to attend that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-all-marketers-20-go-to-principles-to-help-you-market-like-a-marketer-nico-de-bruyn-abridged/">We&#8217;re All Marketers : 20 Go-To Principles To Help You Market Like a Marketer &#8211; Nico de Bruyn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Did you know that you&#8217;re a marketer? That&#8217;s right. In today&#8217;s consumerist, always-digital, interconnected environment, it&#8217;s almost become a necessity to be a marketer. We have all adapted to survive, whether that be to wade through the nearly 4,000 advertisements many of us see everyday, or to help convince friends and family to attend that get-together we hold every year. Everyday we craft messages. Messages that we hope are persuasive and authentic. Messages that we hope help others see the world the way that we do. Every single person that has access to the internet now has the opportunity of a lifetime. But how can you use it to your advantage, where do you even start and is there a simple way to get from where you are today to where you want to go? We&#8217;re All Marketers consists of 20 go-to principles to help you market like a marketer! It breaks down the principles that have made the top marketers successful and explains how you can utilize these principles to market you, your company or organization in a more impactful way.Inside this book you&#8217;ll learn: * The 20 foundational principles of marketing* The new rules of digital marketing and how understanding them will set you apart* How experts have applied them in their careers as well as case studies and examples* How to use the marketing principles from the tailored checklists in your marketing strategy todayThe digital era has brought nearly limitless possibilities for the average digital citizen. However, due to the pace of innovation and the complexity of information, too many people continue to struggle to understand basic marketing principles. We&#8217;re All Marketers is designed to be a straightforward and easy-to-read guide for the average person. If you&#8217;ve ever wanted to get started in digital marketing, wanted to effectively share your stories on social media, or just want to understand more about how you can grow your digital world into something strategic and amazing, this book is for you!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-all-marketers-20-go-to-principles-to-help-you-market-like-a-marketer-nico-de-bruyn-abridged/">We&#8217;re All Marketers : 20 Go-To Principles To Help You Market Like a Marketer &#8211; Nico de Bruyn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ReWork : Change the Way You Work Forever &#8211; David Heinemeier Hansson, Jason Fried (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rework-change-the-way-you-work-forever-david-heinemeier-hansson-jason-fried-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rework-change-the-way-you-work-forever-david-heinemeier-hansson-jason-fried-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the founders of the trailblazing software company 37signals, here is a different kind of business book &#8211; one that explores a new reality. Today, anyone can be in business. Tools that used to be out of reach are now easily accessible. Technology that cost thousands is now just a few pounds or even free. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rework-change-the-way-you-work-forever-david-heinemeier-hansson-jason-fried-abridged/">ReWork : Change the Way You Work Forever &#8211; David Heinemeier Hansson, Jason Fried (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the founders of the trailblazing software company 37signals, here is a different kind of business book &#8211; one that explores a new reality. Today, anyone can be in business. Tools that used to be out of reach are now easily accessible. Technology that cost thousands is now just a few pounds or even free. Stuff that was impossible just a few years ago is now simple.     </p>
<p>                    That means anyone can start a business. And you can do it without working miserable 80-hour weeks or depleting your life savings. You can start it on the side while your day job provides all the cash flow you need. Forget about business plans, meetings, office space &#8211; you don&#8217;t need them.    </p>
<p>                    With its straightforward language and easy-is-better approach, Rework is the perfect playbook for anyone who&#8217;s ever dreamed of doing it on their own. Hardcore entrepreneurs, small-business owners, people stuck in day jobs who want to get out, and artists who don&#8217;t want to starve anymore will all find valuable inspiration and guidance in these pages.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s time to rework work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rework-change-the-way-you-work-forever-david-heinemeier-hansson-jason-fried-abridged/">ReWork : Change the Way You Work Forever &#8211; David Heinemeier Hansson, Jason Fried (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Help take your startup to the next step with the new and revised edition of the popular book on the VC deal process-from the co-founders of the Foundry Group How do venture capital deals come together? This is one of the most frequent questions asked by each generation of new entrepreneurs. Surprisingly, there is little [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/">Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Help take your startup to the next step with the new and revised edition of the popular book on the VC deal process-from the co-founders of the Foundry Group    </p>
<p>                     How do venture capital deals come together? This is one of the most frequent questions asked by each generation of new entrepreneurs. Surprisingly, there is little reliable information on the subject. No one understands this better than Brad Feld and Jason Mendelson. The founders and driving force behind the Foundry Group-a venture capital firm focused on investing in early-stage information technology companies-Brad and Jason have been involved in hundreds of venture capital financings. Their investments range from small startups to large Series A venture financing rounds. The new edition of Venture Deals continues to show fledgling entrepreneurs the inner-workings of the VC process, from the venture capital term sheet and effective negotiating strategies to the initial seed and the later stages of development.    </p>
<p>                     Fully updated to reflect the intricacies of startups and entrepreneurship in today&#8217;s dynamic economic environment, this new edition includes revisions and updates to coverage on negotiating, gender issues, ICO&#8217;s, and economic terms. New chapters examine legal and procedural considerations relevant to fundraising, bank debt, equity and convertible debt, how to hire an investment banker to sell a company, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Provides valuable, real-world insights into venture capital structure and strategy<br />
                    Explains and clarifies the VC term sheet and other misunderstood aspects of capital funding<br />
                    Helps to build collaborative and supportive relationships between entrepreneurs and investors<br />
                    Draws from the author&#8217;s years of practical experience in the VC arena<br />
                    Includes extensively revised and updated content throughout to increase readability and currency    </p>
<p>                     Venture Deals: Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist is a must-have resource for Any aspiring entrepreneur, venture capitalist, or lawyer involved in VC deals as well as students and instructors in related areas of study.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/">Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startup Playbook &#8211; David Kidder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/startup-playbook-david-kidder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/startup-playbook-david-kidder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Startup Playbook, Clickable CEO and NY Times best-selling author David Kidder reveals the rules and guiding principles of successful entrepreneurs, investors and CEOs. Built on some of the most dramatic success stories in today&#8217;s marketplace (Spandex, TED, etc), this is a no-nonsense guide to starting a company.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-playbook-david-kidder-abridged/">Startup Playbook &#8211; David Kidder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Startup Playbook, Clickable CEO and NY Times best-selling author David Kidder reveals the rules and guiding principles of successful entrepreneurs, investors and CEOs. Built on some of the most dramatic success stories in today&#8217;s marketplace (Spandex, TED, etc), this is a no-nonsense guide to starting a company.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-playbook-david-kidder-abridged/">Startup Playbook &#8211; David Kidder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Entrepreneur Roller Coaster : It&#8217;s Your Turn to #jointheride &#8211; Darren Hardy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-entrepreneur-roller-coaster-its-your-turn-to-jointheride-darren-hardy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-entrepreneur-roller-coaster-its-your-turn-to-jointheride-darren-hardy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Entrepreneur Roller Coaster you will learn the best strategies Darren has ever collected from the most successful people on the planet, covering the four essential skills necessary for entrepreneurial success: sales, recruiting, leadership, and productivity. This essential guidebook will prepare you for the wild ride of entrepreneurship. It will warn you (of forthcoming fears, doubts, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-entrepreneur-roller-coaster-its-your-turn-to-jointheride-darren-hardy-abridged/">The Entrepreneur Roller Coaster : It&#8217;s Your Turn to #jointheride &#8211; Darren Hardy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Entrepreneur Roller Coaster you will learn the best strategies Darren has ever collected from the most successful people on the planet, covering the four essential skills necessary for entrepreneurial success: sales, recruiting, leadership, and productivity.    This essential guidebook will prepare you for the wild ride of entrepreneurship. It will warn you (of forthcoming fears, doubts, and the self-defeating conditioning of your upbringing and past), inoculate you (from the naysayers, dream-stealers, and pains of rejection and failure), and guide you (as you build those underdeveloped skills of independence, self-motivation, and self-accountability) safely past the landmines that blow up and cause the failure of 66 percent of all new businesses.    Discover why NOW is the best time to #JOINTHERIDE.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-entrepreneur-roller-coaster-its-your-turn-to-jointheride-darren-hardy-abridged/">The Entrepreneur Roller Coaster : It&#8217;s Your Turn to #jointheride &#8211; Darren Hardy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secrets to Writing a Successful Business Plan : A Pro Shares A Step-by-Step Guide to Creating a Plan That Gets Results &#8211; Hal Shelton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secrets-to-writing-a-successful-business-plan-a-pro-shares-a-step-by-step-guide-to-creating-a-plan-that-gets-results-hal-shelton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secrets-to-writing-a-successful-business-plan-a-pro-shares-a-step-by-step-guide-to-creating-a-plan-that-gets-results-hal-shelton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Secrets to Writing a Successful Business Plan: A Pro Shares a Step-by-Step Guide to Creating a Plan that Gets Results by Hal Shelton will open your eyes to insider tips, hints, and techniques for creating a winning business plan and attaining funding. This second edition maintains the original laser focus on writing the plan. It [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secrets-to-writing-a-successful-business-plan-a-pro-shares-a-step-by-step-guide-to-creating-a-plan-that-gets-results-hal-shelton-abridged/">The Secrets to Writing a Successful Business Plan : A Pro Shares A Step-by-Step Guide to Creating a Plan That Gets Results &#8211; Hal Shelton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Secrets to Writing a Successful Business Plan: A Pro Shares a Step-by-Step Guide to Creating a Plan that Gets Results by Hal Shelton will open your eyes to insider tips, hints, and techniques for creating a winning business plan and attaining funding. This second edition maintains the original laser focus on writing the plan. It also adds much material on the vibrant crowdfunding platforms as well as providing a new section on issues faced by early stage companies. Nearly 50 percent of new businesses fail within five years. A well-thought-out business plan can dramatically turn the odds in your favor. With this easy-to-follow guide, you will (1) Discover why you need a business plan and the best style for you, (2) Receive step-by-step guidance for creating each section of your plan, (3) Get proven strategies for obtaining bank loans and attracting investors, (4) Spend less time writing your plan and more time setting up your business, and (5) Learn how to create a business plan for a nonprofit This book is for entrepreneurs who are thinking of starting a small business or nonprofit, and for small business owners who want to grow an existing business or solve an operating problem. This book will also help if you are looking for assurance that you are headed in the right direction, seeking help with a section of your business plan that you do not understand, feeling that a section of your business plan is not robust enough and want pointers, or wanting to learn where and how to apply for funding. Entrepreneurs should always surround themselves with mentors and advisors, so you will also find ideas on where to find these valuable resources. The Secrets to Writing a Successful Business Plan is packed with actionable advice and real-life examples from Shelton&#8217;s experience as a senior executive, SCORE small business mentor, and angel investor.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secrets-to-writing-a-successful-business-plan-a-pro-shares-a-step-by-step-guide-to-creating-a-plan-that-gets-results-hal-shelton-abridged/">The Secrets to Writing a Successful Business Plan : A Pro Shares A Step-by-Step Guide to Creating a Plan That Gets Results &#8211; Hal Shelton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return. Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return.    </p>
<p>                    Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last two decades by way of real-world case studies. Through revealing interviews, readers are introduced to Mark Suster, Catherine Mott, Christopher Mirabile, Brad Feld, Allan May, Joanne Wilson, and many other accomplished angel investors and venture capitalists. In these interviews you&#8217;ll learn:<br />
                     &#8211; How the best investors think about identifying companies, negotiating terms, and partnering with founders and other investors<br />
                     &#8211; How angel investing can involve many different successful approaches<br />
                     &#8211; What the best investors have learned from their largest successes and failures<br />
                     &#8211; How investors design their portfolios and work with companies to achieve the most successful results.    </p>
<p>                    STARTUP WEALTH is an insightful and useful tool for anyone seeking to make better investments, select great investors, or raise early-stage capital for their business.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There is nothing better when it comes to learning &#8216;best practices&#8217; than hearing from successful people in the trenches. Josh&#8217;s book captures the best of the best, as they reveal both what worked and what didn&#8217;t for them as angel investors and entrepreneurs. Required reading whatever side of the investing fence you&#8217;re on!&#8221;&#8211;Gerry Langeler, Managing Director at OVP Venture Partners. Co-founder of Mentor Graphics (NASDAQ: MENT). Author of The Success Matrix and Take the Money and Run! An Insider&#8217;s Guide to Venture Capital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the international bestseller Business Model Generation explain how to create value propositions customers can&#8217;t resist Value Proposition Design helps you tackle the core challenge of every business &#8211; creating compelling products and services customers want to buy. This highly practical book, paired with its online companion, will teach you the processes and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/">Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the international bestseller Business Model Generation explain how to create value propositions customers can&#8217;t resist    </p>
<p>                     Value Proposition Design helps you tackle the core challenge of every business &#8211; creating compelling products and services customers want to buy. This highly practical book, paired with its online companion, will teach you the processes and tools you need to create products that sell.    </p>
<p>                    Using the same stunning visual format as the authors&#8217; global bestseller, Business Model Generation, this sequel explains how to use the &#8220;Value Proposition Canvas&#8221; to design, test, create, and manage products and services customers actually want.    </p>
<p>                    Value Proposition Design is for anyone who has been frustrated by new product meetings based on hunches and intuitions; it&#8217;s for anyone who has watched an expensive new product launch fail in the market. The book will help you understand the patterns of great value propositions, get closer to customers, and avoid wasting time with ideas that won&#8217;t work. You&#8217;ll learn the simple process of designing and testing value propositions, that perfectly match customers&#8217; needs and desires.    </p>
<p>                    In addition the book gives you exclusive access to an online companion on Strategyzer.com. You will be able to assess your work, learn from peers, and download pdfs, checklists, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Value Proposition Design is an essential companion to the &#8220;Business Model Canvas&#8221; from Business Model Generation, a tool embraced globally by startups and large corporations such as MasterCard, 3M, Coca Cola, GE, Fujitsu, LEGO, Colgate-Palmolive, and many more.<br />
                    Value Proposition Design gives you a proven methodology for success, with value propositions that sell, embedded in profitable business models.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/">Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Hero Factor : How Great Leaders Transform Organizations and Create Winning Cultures &#8211; Jeffrey W. Hayzlett, With Jim Eber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-hero-factor-how-great-leaders-transform-organizations-and-create-winning-cultures-jeffrey-w-hayzlett-with-jim-eber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-hero-factor-how-great-leaders-transform-organizations-and-create-winning-cultures-jeffrey-w-hayzlett-with-jim-eber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not profit over people that will make your business successful-it&#8217;s when you combine people and profits that you become A HERO LEADERToday&#8217;s leaders need to engage, connect with, listen to and include their employees and customers in the conversation surrounding the business. The Hero Factor discusses the importance of a strong company culture as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hero-factor-how-great-leaders-transform-organizations-and-create-winning-cultures-jeffrey-w-hayzlett-with-jim-eber-abridged/">The Hero Factor : How Great Leaders Transform Organizations and Create Winning Cultures &#8211; Jeffrey W. Hayzlett, With Jim Eber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not profit over people that will make your business successful-it&#8217;s when you combine people and profits that you become A HERO LEADERToday&#8217;s leaders need to engage, connect with, listen to and include their employees and customers in the conversation surrounding the business. The Hero Factor discusses the importance of a strong company culture as the backbone of any successful business. Companies with leadership that dismisses the importance of transparency in today&#8217;s world are more likely to be called out for not living up to the mission statements on their websites.    </p>
<p>                    Dive in and learn how to implement the traits that will help them become a hero entrepreneur, change their organization, live their values, and create a winning culture where they:    </p>
<p>                    Invest in people as a path to more inclusion<br />
                    Recast the role of business leadership beyond politics<br />
                    Serve others/the common good<br />
                    Avoid failure, reasons why not, and the lure of the dark side when things get tough<br />
                    Know the line between hero and martyr<br />
                    Create the next generation of hero leaders</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hero-factor-how-great-leaders-transform-organizations-and-create-winning-cultures-jeffrey-w-hayzlett-with-jim-eber-abridged/">The Hero Factor : How Great Leaders Transform Organizations and Create Winning Cultures &#8211; Jeffrey W. Hayzlett, With Jim Eber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oversubscribed : How To Get People Lining Up To Do Business With You &#8211; Daniel Priestley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to get your business oversubscribed in a crowded marketplace to make your business stand out and get people lining up to do business with you Are you constantly chasing customers? Why does it seem like some businesses have their customers begging to purchase their goods or services? Think about it for a moment. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/">Oversubscribed : How To Get People Lining Up To Do Business With You &#8211; Daniel Priestley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to get your business oversubscribed in a crowded marketplace to make your business stand out and get people lining up to do business with you     </p>
<p>                     Are you constantly chasing customers? Why does it seem like some businesses have their customers begging to purchase their goods or services? Think about it for a moment. When a new iPhone is released, why do customers camp overnight to be the first through the door? In cities with thousands of great restaurants, why do some restaurants require reservations months in advance? Why is it that some consultants, accountants, lawyers and healthcare professionals can charge exponentially more than others? In the modern marketplace, consumer options are virtually endless, intense competition is rife and so much is given away for free online.  Often businesses are left scrambling to attract enough customers to make a small profit. Yet the opposite is true for a small number of businesses that do things differently-customers chase them. They have buyers who gladly queue up, pay more, and eagerly wait for the chance to hand over their money for the next thing. How do these businesses do it? More importantly, how can you become one of them?     </p>
<p>                     Oversubscribed is the guide to transforming your business into one which customers fight over! Author Daniel Priestley, a successful entrepreneur who has built and sold businesses around the world, shares proven, real-world methods that will not only grab customers&#8217; attention, but will also have them lining up to buy from you. This invaluable guide will teach you how to drive demand for your products or services far beyond supply and will dramatically increase the success of your business. Now in its second edition, this updated version offers new insights and motivating examples that are right for the 2020s. This book will show you:    </p>
<p>                    The principles and philosophies Oversubscribed businesses live by that are often the opposite of what most businesses do<br />
                    Specific steps for getting into the mind of your customer so they only want to buy from your business<br />
                    How to structure campaigns and product launches that systematically get your business Oversubscribed<br />
                    How to implement a process of signalling to market, and collect signals back from market to build up desire and demand for your products and services    </p>
<p>                     The new edition of Oversubscribed: How to get people lining up to do business with you is a must-read for entrepreneurs, marketers, business leaders and owners, team managers, and business students.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/">Oversubscribed : How To Get People Lining Up To Do Business With You &#8211; Daniel Priestley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With roughly 95,000 blogs launched worldwide every 24 hours (BlogPulse), making a fledgling site stand out isn&#8217;t easy. This authoritative handbook gives creative hopefuls a leg up. Joy Cho, of the award-winning Oh Joy!, offers expert advice on starting and growing a blog, from design and finance to overcoming blogger&#8217;s block, attracting readers, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/">Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With roughly 95,000 blogs launched worldwide every 24 hours (BlogPulse), making a fledgling site stand out isn&#8217;t easy. This authoritative handbook gives creative hopefuls a leg up. Joy Cho, of the award-winning Oh Joy!, offers expert advice on starting and growing a blog, from design and finance to overcoming blogger&#8217;s block, attracting readers, and more. With a foreword from Grace Bonney of Design*Sponge plus expert interviews, this book will fine-tune what the next generation of bloggers shares with the world. Learn how to design your site, choose the right platform, attract a fan base, finance your blog, maintain work/life balance, manage comments, find content inspiration, overcome blogger&#8217;s block, choose the right ads, develop a voice, protect your work, create a media kit, leverage your social network, take better photographs, set up an affiliate program, partner with sponsors, build community, go full-time with your blog, and more!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/">Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of FORTUNE Magazine&#8217;s Top 5 Business Book Must-Reads How do you cut through the noise, commotion, and bad information that is right now cluttering up your customers&#8217; digital space? EPIC CONTENT MARKETINGOne of the world&#8217;s leading experts on content marketing, Joe Pulizzi explains how to attract prospects and customers by creating information and content [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of FORTUNE Magazine&#8217;s Top 5 Business Book Must-Reads How do you cut through the noise, commotion, and bad information that is right now cluttering up your customers&#8217; digital space?    </p>
<p>                    EPIC CONTENT MARKETINGOne of the world&#8217;s leading experts on content marketing, Joe Pulizzi explains how to attract prospects and customers by creating information and content they actually want to engage with. No longer can we interrupt our customers with mediocre content and sales messages they don&#8217;t care about.    </p>
<p>                    Epic Content Marketing takes you step-by-stepthrough the process of developing stories that inform and entertain and compel customers to act&#8211;without actually telling them to. Epic content, distributed to the right person at the right time, is the way to truly capture the hearts and minds of customers. It&#8217;s how to position your business as a trusted expert in its industry. It&#8217;s what customers share and talk about.    </p>
<p>                    Once we hook customers with epic content, they reward us by sending our sales through the roof.    </p>
<p>                    Epic Content Marketing provides everything youneed to:    </p>
<p>                    Determine what your content niche should be to attract and retain customersDiscover and develop your content marketing mission statementSet up a process for creating and curating epic contentLearn how to leverage social and e-mail channels to create&#8211;and grow&#8211;your audienceMeasure the performance of your content&#8211;and increase your content marketing budget    </p>
<p>                    With in-depth case studies of how John Deere, LEGO, Coca-Cola, and other leading corporations are using content to drive epic sales, this groundbreaking guide gives you all the tools to start creating and disseminating content that leads directly to greater profits and growth.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re the CMO of a Fortune 500, a digital marketer, or an entrepreneur, Epic Content Marketing gives you the tools you need to vanquish the competition. Start your epic journey now!    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR EPIC CONTENT MARKETING&#8221;From the man who invented content marketing. Listen to this guy. He really understands the new world of marketing. The concepts in Epic Content Marketing are usable all over the world&#8211;instantly usable and useful for any business.&#8221; &#8212; Don Schultz, the &#8220;father of integrated marketing,&#8221; Professor Emeritus at Northwestern University&#8217;s Medill School of Journalism, and author of 13 books    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi&#8217;s ideas are so consistently . . . well, epic (!) that they really don&#8217;t need any endorsement by anyone. But here&#8217;s mine anyway: You don&#8217;t need MORE content. You need the right kind of content,strategically applied. For those organizations struggling to create a content marketing program that drives results, Joe delivers. Again.&#8221; &#8212; Ann Handley, coauthor of Content Rules and Chief Content Officer, MarketingProfs    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;As Joe shows us in his wonderful Epic Content Marketing, you must unlearn interrupting people with your nonsense. Instead, publish the valuable content they want to consume and are eager to share.&#8221; &#8212; David Meerman Scott, marketing strategist and bestselling author ofThe New Rules of Marketing and PR    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is a brilliant canter through the rapid and ever-changing world of content marketing. Joe has managed to capture the right blend of art and science as he plots the major trends impacting all marketers right now.&#8221; &#8212; Jonathan Mildenhall, VP, Global Advertising Strategy and Creative Excellence, Coca-Cola Company    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You could say that Joe Pulizzi wrote the book on content marketing, but now it&#8217;s more than just a saying.It&#8217;s what you&#8217;re holding in your hands. If you truly want to be successful at content marketing, Pulizzi is one of the few who can show you the way.&#8221; &#8212; Mitch Joel, President, Twist Image, and author of Six Pixels of Separation and CTRL ALT Delete    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi may know more about content marketing than any person alive. He proves it in these pages.&#8221; &#8212; Jay Baer, New York Times bestselling author of Youtility: Why Smart Marketing is About Help Not Hype    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The future of successful brand building, and especially the art of solidifying the emotional connection between people and brands, will require expertise in Content Marketing. Epic Content Marketing gives all the details practitioners need without overcomplicating.&#8221; &#8212; Professor JoAnn Sciarrino, Knight Chair, Digital Advertising and Marketing, UNC Chapel Hill    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi is the godfather of our burgeoning profession of Content Marketing. He lays out the objectives, principles, and core strategies of our field in a way that&#8217;s easy-to-understand, inspiring, and entertaining. If your company doesn&#8217;t yet realize that it&#8217;s a media company, with all the challenges and advantages that implies, you&#8217;re missing the most powerful way to connect with your customers.&#8221; &#8212; Julie Fleischer, Director, Media &#038; Consumer Engagement, Kraft Foods</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do More Faster : Techstars Lessons to Accelerate Your Startup &#8211; Brad Feld, David G. Cohen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-more-faster-techstars-lessons-to-accelerate-your-startup-brad-feld-david-g-cohen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-more-faster-techstars-lessons-to-accelerate-your-startup-brad-feld-david-g-cohen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Refreshed, updated, and expanded. Do More Faster provides time-tested advice, tips, and experiences by founders and mentors of Techstars to help entrepreneurs succeed! David Cohen and Brad Feld, leading advocates for entrepreneurs and startups, team up to provide first-time entrepreneurs with the tools, insights, and experiences to help them do more faster. The authors share [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-more-faster-techstars-lessons-to-accelerate-your-startup-brad-feld-david-g-cohen-abridged/">Do More Faster : Techstars Lessons to Accelerate Your Startup &#8211; Brad Feld, David G. Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Refreshed, updated, and expanded. Do More Faster provides time-tested advice, tips, and experiences by founders and mentors of Techstars to help entrepreneurs succeed!    </p>
<p>                     David Cohen and Brad Feld, leading advocates for entrepreneurs and startups, team up to provide first-time entrepreneurs with the tools, insights, and experiences to help them do more faster. The authors share their decades of experience working with thousands of startup founders and have enlisted the advice of dozens of Techstars startup founders and mentors. Contributors include Tim Ferriss, Eric Ries, Matt Mullenweg (WordPress), Isaac Saldana (SendGrid), and other successful entrepreneurs.    </p>
<p>                     Co-founders of Techstars, the worldwide network that helps entrepreneurs succeed, Cohen and Feld recognize the daunting task of creating a sustainable business and have seen first-hand the common mistakes first-time entrepreneurs make over and over. The authors take the complexity and uncertainty of starting a business and distill the critical factors into seven themes: Ideas and Vision, People, Working Effectively, Product, Fundraising, Legal and Structure, and Work and Life Harmony. They share their hard-won successes, failures, and advice for anyone with an idea who wants to create a business.    </p>
<p>                     Throughout the book crucial questions are raised and addressed from multiple perspectives.    </p>
<p>                            How important is it to have an original idea?    </p>
<p>                            How is founder conflict handled?    </p>
<p>                            What are the tradeoffs between bootstrapping and financing?    </p>
<p>                     Make-or-break decisions like company structure, hiring, and legal consequences are presented in an easy-to-understand style. Do More Faster will elevate your thinking on a range of important topics, help you avoid costly mistakes, and provide you with a resource to consult as you go from idea to successful business.    </p>
<p>                     If you have the drive and desire to start a business, need to create a vibrant entrepreneurial ecosystem in your community, or want to spark greater innovation in your organization-don&#8217;t go it alone. Use the advice, tips, and tactics found throughout Do More Faster to give yourself the best chance of succeeding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-more-faster-techstars-lessons-to-accelerate-your-startup-brad-feld-david-g-cohen-abridged/">Do More Faster : Techstars Lessons to Accelerate Your Startup &#8211; Brad Feld, David G. Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever. From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business     </p>
<p>                    Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever.    </p>
<p>                    From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the go-to guide to building a solid small-business by establishing a loyal audience before you sell any products or services. In these pages, Joe Pulizzi provides a lower-risk, better way to build a successful business by re-engineering the process that so often leads to failure: You&#8217;ll learn how to develop valuable content, build an audience around that content-and then create a product for that audience. Content Inc. walks you through the entire process, showing how to    </p>
<p>                    Identify the intersection of your expertise and your future customer&#8217;s needs<br />
                    Determine how to &#8220;tilt&#8221; your sweet spot to find a place where little or no competition exists<br />
                    Establish your number-one channel for disseminating content (blog, podcast, YouTube, etc.)<br />
                    Use social-media and SEO to convert one-time visitors into long-term subscribers<br />
                    Grow your business by expanding into multiple delivery channels<br />
                    Monetize your product or service for ultimate business success<br />
                    Understand how to sell your content asset for millions or build the business into a large enterprise    </p>
<p>                    This fully updated edition includes new and enhanced coverage of platforms like TikTok, SnapChat, and Instagram, a new section about the exit strategy for the model, more practical how-tos, and current examples of companies that have successfully implemented these strategies.      </p>
<p>                    Apply the methods laid out for you in Content Inc., and before you know it, you&#8217;ll be running your own profitable, scalable business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Content Marketing: How to Create Great Content, Reach More Customers, and Build a Worldwide Marketing Strategy that Works &#8211; Pam Didner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Engage Customers Around the World with Cross-Regional Content MarketingTechnology has virtually erased national borders, forever transforming the way we reach and engage customers, as well as the way we search for and consumecontent. Global Content Marketing takes you step-by-step through the process of creating and refining your strategies to meet this new reality. LEARN HOW [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/">Global Content Marketing: How to Create Great Content, Reach More Customers, and Build a Worldwide Marketing Strategy that Works &#8211; Pam Didner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Engage Customers Around the World with Cross-Regional Content MarketingTechnology has virtually erased national borders, forever transforming the way we reach and engage customers, as well as the way we search for and consumecontent. Global Content Marketing takes you step-by-step through the process of creating and refining your strategies to meet this new reality.    </p>
<p>                    LEARN HOW TO:    </p>
<p>                    Create content that engages people&#8211;regardless of their country and cultureIdentify key actions and strategies to apply to your projectsConnect &#8220;dots&#8221; that others don&#8217;t see and connect them in ways you never thought of before    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Content marketing across geographies is a diff erent animal. In this smart, practical, and authoritative book, Pam Didner has tamed this animal for all of us.&#8221; &#8212; DOUG KESSLER, Creative Director, Velocity    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable guide to developing and distributing your global content effectively.&#8221; &#8212; NANCY BHAGAT, former VP, Global Marketing Strategy, Intel, and current Divisional CMO, TE Connectivity    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book is the blueprint for engineering a modern scalable content marketing operation.&#8221; &#8212; PAWAN DESHPANDE, CEO, Curata    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Finally the book that explores all critical aspects of global content marketing! Whether you are a small business or a Fortune 500 company, it is essential to understand the 4P&#8217;s developed by Pam Didner. Read it and take your content strategy to the whole new level.&#8221;  &#8212; EKATERINA WALTER, author of Think Like Zuck and coauthor of The Power of Visual Storytelling</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/">Global Content Marketing: How to Create Great Content, Reach More Customers, and Build a Worldwide Marketing Strategy that Works &#8211; Pam Didner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fortune Cookie Principle : The 20 Keys to a Great Brand Story and Why Your Business Needs One &#8211; Bernadette Jiwa (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not how good you are. It&#8217;s how well you tell your story. Big corporations might have huge marketing and advertising budgets but you&#8217;ve got a story. Your brand story isn&#8217;t just what you tell people. It&#8217;s what they believe about you based on the signals your brand sends. The Fortune Cookie Principle is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/">The Fortune Cookie Principle : The 20 Keys to a Great Brand Story and Why Your Business Needs One &#8211; Bernadette Jiwa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not how good you are. It&#8217;s how well you tell your story. Big corporations might have huge marketing and advertising budgets but you&#8217;ve got a story. Your brand story isn&#8217;t just what you tell people. It&#8217;s what they believe about you based on the signals your brand sends. The Fortune Cookie Principle is a brand building framework and communication strategy consisting of 20 keys that enable you to begin telling your brand&#8217;s story from the inside out. It&#8217;s the foundation upon which you can differentiate your brand and make emotional connections with the kind of clients and customers you want to serve. The most successful brands in the world don&#8217;t behave like commodities and neither should you. A great brand story will make you stand out, increase brand awareness, create customer loyalty and power profits. Isn&#8217;t it time to gave your customers a story to tell? The Fortune Cookie Principle will show you how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/">The Fortune Cookie Principle : The 20 Keys to a Great Brand Story and Why Your Business Needs One &#8211; Bernadette Jiwa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Programming / Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221; Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term? While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221;<br />
                     Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb    </p>
<p>                    How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term?  While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments of creation and conclusion, The Messy Middle argues that the real key to success is how you navigate the ups-and-downs after initial investment is secured. It will give you all the insights you need to build and optimize your team, improve your product and develop your own capacity to lead covering:<br />
                    *         Coping with uncertainty and conflict<br />
                    *         Playing the long game<br />
                    *         Optimising your team<br />
                    *         Problem solving through the ups and downs<br />
                    *         Adapting your strategy<br />
                    *         When to quit<br />
                    Building on seven years&#8217; of meticulous research with entrepreneurs, small agencies, start-ups and billion-dollar companies, Scott Belsky offers indispensable lessons on how to endure and thrive in the long term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lean Analytics &#8211; Alistair Croll (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lean-analytics-alistair-croll-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lean-analytics-alistair-croll-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Whether you&#8217;re a startup founder trying to disrupt an industry or an intrapreneur trying to provoke change from within, your biggest challenge is creating a product people actually want. Lean Analytics steers you in the right direction. This book shows you how to validate your initial idea, find the right customers, decide what to build, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-analytics-alistair-croll-abridged/">Lean Analytics &#8211; Alistair Croll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Whether you&#8217;re a startup founder trying to disrupt an industry or an intrapreneur trying to provoke change from within, your biggest challenge is creating a product people actually want. Lean Analytics steers you in the right direction. This book shows you how to validate your initial idea, find the right customers, decide what to build, how to monetize your business, and how to spread the word. Packed with more than thirty case studies and insights from over a hundred business experts, Lean Analytics provides you with hard-won, real-world information no entrepreneur can afford to go without. Understand Lean Startup, analytics fundamentals, and the data-driven mindset  Look at six sample business models and how they map to new ventures of all sizes  Find the One Metric That Matters to you  Learn how to draw a line in the sand, so you&#8217;ll know it&#8217;s time to move forward  Apply Lean Analytics principles to large enterprises and established products</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-analytics-alistair-croll-abridged/">Lean Analytics &#8211; Alistair Croll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ultimate Guide to Local Business Marketing &#8211; Perry Marshall, Talor Zamir (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ultimate-guide-to-local-business-marketing-perry-marshall-talor-zamir-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ultimate-guide-to-local-business-marketing-perry-marshall-talor-zamir-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MASTER LOCAL SEO AND REACH THE RIGHT CUSTOMERS EVERY TIME With Google, Yahoo!, and Bing returning local businesses as results on more than a billion daily searches, Google Adwords expert Perry Marshall and lead generation expert Talor Zamir introduce you to the basic framework behind a successful local SEO campaign. From defining local search&#8211;often confused [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-guide-to-local-business-marketing-perry-marshall-talor-zamir-abridged/">Ultimate Guide to Local Business Marketing &#8211; Perry Marshall, Talor Zamir (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MASTER LOCAL SEO AND REACH THE RIGHT CUSTOMERS EVERY TIME  With Google, Yahoo!, and Bing returning local businesses as results on more than a billion daily searches, Google Adwords expert Perry Marshall and lead generation expert Talor Zamir introduce you to the basic framework behind a successful local SEO campaign.  From defining local search&#8211;often confused with paid search and search engine marketing&#8211;to local listing and reviews to social outreach and effective content development, this guide delivers the tools to build an entire local marketing campaign. You&#8217;ll learn how to: Capture high-quality leads from Google AdWords and Bing in 48 hours Master the components of a high-converting campaign and get the most bang for your buck Harness mobile search advertising and Facebook ads for maximum results</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-guide-to-local-business-marketing-perry-marshall-talor-zamir-abridged/">Ultimate Guide to Local Business Marketing &#8211; Perry Marshall, Talor Zamir (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello, My Name is Awesome : How to Create Brand Names That Stick &#8211; Alexandra Watkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The ultimate guide to naming your product or business has been updated throughout with twice as many resources as before, new stories (of both hits and flops), and an entirely new chapter on the power of names in the workplace. Too many new companies and products have names that look like the results of a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/">Hello, My Name is Awesome : How to Create Brand Names That Stick &#8211; Alexandra Watkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ultimate guide to naming your product or business has been updated throughout with twice as many resources as before, new stories (of both hits and flops), and an entirely new chapter on the power of names in the workplace.     </p>
<p>                     Too many new companies and products have names that look like the results of a drunken Scrabble game (Xobni, Svbtle, Doostang). In this entertaining and engaging book, ace-naming consultant Alexandra Watkins explains how anyone&#8211;even noncreative types&#8211;can create memorable and effective brand names. No degree in linguistics required.     </p>
<p>                     The heart of the book is Watkins&#8217;s proven SMILE and SCRATCH Test. A great name makes you SMILE because it is Suggestive&#8211;evokes something about your brand; is Memorable&#8211;makes an association with the familiar; uses Imagery&#8211;aids memory through evocative visuals; has Legs&#8211;lends itself to a theme for extended mileage; and is Emotional&#8211;moves people.     </p>
<p>                     A bad name, on the other hand, makes you SCRATCH your head because it is Spelling challenged&#8211;looks like a typo; is a Copycat&#8211;similar to competitors&#8217; names; is Restrictive&#8211;limits future growth; is Annoying&#8211;seems forced and frustrates customers; is Tame&#8211;feels flat, merely descriptive, and uninspired; suffers from the Curse of Knowledge&#8211;speaks only to insiders; and is Hard to pronounce&#8211;confuses and distances customers.     </p>
<p>                     This 50 percent-new second edition has double the number of brainstorming tools and techniques, even more secrets and strategies to nab an available domain name, a brand-new chapter on how companies are using creative names around the office to add personality to everything from cafeterias to conference rooms, and much more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/">Hello, My Name is Awesome : How to Create Brand Names That Stick &#8211; Alexandra Watkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wealth of Nations : The Economics Classic &#8211; A Selected Edition for the Contemporary Reader &#8211; Adam Smith, Introduction by Tom Butler-Bowdon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wealth-of-nations-the-economics-classic-a-selected-edition-for-the-contemporary-reader-adam-smith-introduction-by-tom-butler-bowdon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wealth-of-nations-the-economics-classic-a-selected-edition-for-the-contemporary-reader-adam-smith-introduction-by-tom-butler-bowdon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE MOST INFLUENTIAL BOOK ON MODERN ECONOMICS The Wealth of Nations is an economics book like no other. First published in 1776, Adam Smith&#8217;s groundbreaking theories provide a recipe for national prosperity that has not been bettered since. It assumes no prior knowledge of its subject, and over 200 years on, still provides valuable lessons [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wealth-of-nations-the-economics-classic-a-selected-edition-for-the-contemporary-reader-adam-smith-introduction-by-tom-butler-bowdon-abridged/">The Wealth of Nations : The Economics Classic &#8211; A Selected Edition for the Contemporary Reader &#8211; Adam Smith, Introduction by Tom Butler-Bowdon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE MOST INFLUENTIAL BOOK ON MODERN ECONOMICS     </p>
<p>                    The Wealth of Nations is an economics book like no other. First published in 1776, Adam Smith&#8217;s groundbreaking theories provide a recipe for national prosperity that has not been bettered since. It assumes no prior knowledge of its subject, and over 200 years on, still provides valuable lessons on the fundamentals of economics.     </p>
<p>                    This keepsake edition is a selected abridgement of all five books, and includes an Introduction by Tom Butler-Bowdon, drawing out lessons for the contemporary reader, a Foreword from Eamonn Butler, Director of the Adam Smith Institute, and a Preface from Dr. Razeen Sally of the London School of Economics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wealth-of-nations-the-economics-classic-a-selected-edition-for-the-contemporary-reader-adam-smith-introduction-by-tom-butler-bowdon-abridged/">The Wealth of Nations : The Economics Classic &#8211; A Selected Edition for the Contemporary Reader &#8211; Adam Smith, Introduction by Tom Butler-Bowdon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Freelance Mum : A Flexible Career Guide for Better Work-Life Balance &#8211; Annie Ridout (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-freelance-mum-a-flexible-career-guide-for-better-work-life-balance-annie-ridout-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-freelance-mum-a-flexible-career-guide-for-better-work-life-balance-annie-ridout-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More time with your kids, making the money you know you&#8217;re worth and a better work/life balance. No wonder more women than ever are choosing to be become freelance mums. In the last decade, 70% more mums have chosen to go freelance. Annie Ridout was one of them. And in her enlightening new book, she [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-freelance-mum-a-flexible-career-guide-for-better-work-life-balance-annie-ridout-abridged/">The Freelance Mum : A Flexible Career Guide for Better Work-Life Balance &#8211; Annie Ridout (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More time with your kids, making the money you know you&#8217;re worth and a better work/life balance. No wonder more women than ever are choosing to be become freelance mums.     </p>
<p>                              In the last decade, 70% more mums have chosen to go freelance. Annie Ridout was one of them. And in her enlightening new book, she shares the tips and tricks that helped her build a better working life around her family.     </p>
<p>                    From choosing a career and launching a website, to getting your name out there and perfecting your brand, to the nitty gritty of childcare options and daily routines, The Freelance Mum is a comprehensive guide to setting out on your own path.    </p>
<p>                    Using her own experience, alongside advice from other mums that make it work, including Arianna Huffington, Scummy Mummies, Carrie-Anne Roberts, Robyn Wilder, Zoe de Pass, Cherry Healey, Sali Hughes and Anna Jones, Annie will show that with hard work and determination, any mother can thrive as a freelancer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-freelance-mum-a-flexible-career-guide-for-better-work-life-balance-annie-ridout-abridged/">The Freelance Mum : A Flexible Career Guide for Better Work-Life Balance &#8211; Annie Ridout (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crafts & Hobbies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge &#8211; over one million copies sold** Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge  &#8211; over one million copies sold**    </p>
<p>                    Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness    </p>
<p>                    Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. In The Little Book of Lykke, he reveals what he has found.    </p>
<p>                    This captivating read features case studies from Bhutan to Australia, South Korea to Canada, France to Denmark, taking the reader on a happiness treasure hunt. Written in the same warm tone as Meik&#8217;s phenomenal bestseller The Little Book of Hygge, this easy-to-understand book will change the way you think about how you relate to your neighbours, the rituals around cooking and eating dinner, and when to book your next holiday &#8211; and is guaranteed to put a smile on your face.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is a happy book about happiness, written with a twinkle and packaged with Danish style&#8217; (John Helliwell, Economist and Editor of the World Happiness Report)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Giants : Companies That Choose to be Great Instead of Big &#8211; Bo Burlingham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-giants-companies-that-choose-to-be-great-instead-of-big-bo-burlingham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-giants-companies-that-choose-to-be-great-instead-of-big-bo-burlingham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s widely accepted in business that great companies grow their revenues and profits year after year &#8211; but bigger is not necessarily better. In Small Giants, journalist Bo Burlingham takes us deep inside fourteen remarkable privately held companies, from a brewery to a record label, that chose a different path to success. These organizations quietly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-giants-companies-that-choose-to-be-great-instead-of-big-bo-burlingham-abridged/">Small Giants : Companies That Choose to be Great Instead of Big &#8211; Bo Burlingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s widely accepted in business that great companies grow their revenues and profits year after year &#8211; but bigger is not necessarily better. In Small Giants, journalist Bo Burlingham takes us deep inside fourteen remarkable privately held companies, from a brewery to a record label, that chose a different path to success.     </p>
<p>                    These organizations quietly rejected the pressure of endless growth, deciding to focus more on satisfying business goals &#8211; being the best at what they do, creating a stimulating place to work, providing perfect customer service and making important contributions to their communities.    </p>
<p>                    But what are the magic ingredients that make these companies unique? Why and how does their approach work in such widely varying industries? And what lessons can we learn from them? A fresh, inspirational guide to business strategy, Small Giants will help any entrepeneur consider new directions to make their company great.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-giants-companies-that-choose-to-be-great-instead-of-big-bo-burlingham-abridged/">Small Giants : Companies That Choose to be Great Instead of Big &#8211; Bo Burlingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New to Big : How Companies Can Create Like Entrepreneurs, Invest Like VCs, and Install a Permanent Operating System for Growth &#8211; David Kidder, Christina Wallace (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/new-to-big-how-companies-can-create-like-entrepreneurs-invest-like-vcs-and-install-a-permanent-operating-system-for-growth-david-kidder-christina-wallace-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/new-to-big-how-companies-can-create-like-entrepreneurs-invest-like-vcs-and-install-a-permanent-operating-system-for-growth-david-kidder-christina-wallace-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Serial entrepreneurs David Kidder and Christina Wallace reveal their revolutionary playbook for igniting growth inside established companies. Most established companies face a key survival challenge, says David Kidder, CEO of Bionic, lifelong entrepreneur, and angel investor in more than thirty startups: operational efficiency and outdated bureaucracy are at war with new growth. Legacy companies are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-to-big-how-companies-can-create-like-entrepreneurs-invest-like-vcs-and-install-a-permanent-operating-system-for-growth-david-kidder-christina-wallace-abridged/">New to Big : How Companies Can Create Like Entrepreneurs, Invest Like VCs, and Install a Permanent Operating System for Growth &#8211; David Kidder, Christina Wallace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Serial entrepreneurs David Kidder and Christina Wallace reveal their revolutionary playbook for igniting growth inside established companies.     </p>
<p>                    Most established companies face a key survival challenge, says David Kidder, CEO of Bionic, lifelong entrepreneur, and angel investor in more than thirty startups: operational efficiency and outdated bureaucracy are at war with new growth. Legacy companies are skilled at growing big businesses into even bigger ones. But they are less adept at discovering new opportunities and turning them into big businesses, the way entrepreneurs and early-stage investors must. In New to Big, Kidder and Wallace reveal their proprietary blueprint for installing a permanent growth capability inside any company&#8211;the Growth Operating System.     </p>
<p>                    The Growth OS borrows the best tools, systems, and mind-sets from entrepreneurship and venture capital and adapts them for established organizations, leveraging these two distinct skills as a form of management for building in a future that is uncertain. By focusing on what consumers do rather than what they say, celebrating productive failure, embracing a portfolio approach, and learning from the outside-in, Kidder and Wallace argue any company can go on offense and win the future.     </p>
<p>                    This isn&#8217;t about a one-off innovation moonshot. It&#8217;s about building a permanent ladder to the moon.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-to-big-how-companies-can-create-like-entrepreneurs-invest-like-vcs-and-install-a-permanent-operating-system-for-growth-david-kidder-christina-wallace-abridged/">New to Big : How Companies Can Create Like Entrepreneurs, Invest Like VCs, and Install a Permanent Operating System for Growth &#8211; David Kidder, Christina Wallace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simple Numbers, Straight Talk, Big Profits! &#8211; Greg Crabtree, Beverly Herzog (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/simple-numbers-straight-talk-big-profits-greg-crabtree-beverly-herzog-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/simple-numbers-straight-talk-big-profits-greg-crabtree-beverly-herzog-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Simple Numbers can guide you to increased business profitability Take the mystery out of small business finance with this no-frills guide to understanding the numbers that will guide your business out of any financial black hole. Author Greg Crabtree, a successful accountant, small business advisor, and popular presenter, shows you how to use your firm&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simple-numbers-straight-talk-big-profits-greg-crabtree-beverly-herzog-abridged/">Simple Numbers, Straight Talk, Big Profits! &#8211; Greg Crabtree, Beverly Herzog (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Simple Numbers can guide you to increased business profitability Take the mystery out of small business finance with this no-frills guide to understanding the numbers that will guide your business out of any financial black hole. Author Greg Crabtree, a successful accountant, small business advisor, and popular presenter, shows you how to use your firm&#8217;s key financial indicators as a basis for smart business decisions as you grow your firm from startup to $5 million (and, more ) in annual revenue. Jargon free, and presented in an easy-to-follow, step-by-step format, with plenty of real-world examples, Crabtree&#8217;s down-to-earth discussion highlights the most common financial errors committed by small businesses, and how to avoid them. You&#8217;ll be fascinated to learn: Why your numbers are lying to you (and why you are the cause ) How labor productivity is the key to profitability and simplifying human resource decisions Why the amount of tax you pay is your #1 key performance indicator Take advantage of Crabtree&#8217;s years of experience teaching clients how to build successful businesses by &#8221;seeing beyond numbers&#8221; with this step-by-step guide to increasing your businesses profitability.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simple-numbers-straight-talk-big-profits-greg-crabtree-beverly-herzog-abridged/">Simple Numbers, Straight Talk, Big Profits! &#8211; Greg Crabtree, Beverly Herzog (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Building Your Business the Right-Brain Way : Sustainable Success for the Creative Entrepreneur &#8211; Jennifer Lee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/building-your-business-the-right-brain-way-sustainable-success-for-the-creative-entrepreneur-jennifer-lee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crafts & Hobbies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hobby and Gaming Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/building-your-business-the-right-brain-way-sustainable-success-for-the-creative-entrepreneur-jennifer-lee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;ve started a business, you know that the journey toward success can be both invigorating and confusing, so where can you find advice that is practical and focused but still as playful and passionate as you are? Look no further than this book, which combines solid business expertise with a right-brain perspective that inspires [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-your-business-the-right-brain-way-sustainable-success-for-the-creative-entrepreneur-jennifer-lee-abridged/">Building Your Business the Right-Brain Way : Sustainable Success for the Creative Entrepreneur &#8211; Jennifer Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;ve started a business, you know that the journey toward success can be both invigorating and confusing, so where can you find advice that is practical and focused but still as playful and passionate as you are? Look no further than this book, which combines solid business expertise with a right-brain perspective that inspires creativity and innovation. Jennifer Lee&#8217;s fresh, empowering approach emphasizes taking action and continually improving to achieve extraordinary long-term results. Building Your Business the Right-Brain Way offers real-world-tested techniques that can benefit all sorts of businesses, whether you&#8217;re a sole proprietor running a coaching practice, a crafter looking to license products, a wellness professional with a team of employees, or any creative soul making a meaningful difference with your work. You&#8217;ll discover how to: * assess your business&#8217;s unique &#8220;ecosystem&#8221;<br />
                    * build your brand and attract, engage, and keep ideal customers<br />
                    * develop new income streams that better leverage your time and resources<br />
                    * promote your products and services with authenticity and ease<br />
                    * grow your team (virtual and in-person) and manage staff and vendors<br />
                    * establish infrastructure and procedures to keep operations running smoothly<br />
                    * carve out vital white space to pause, reflect, and celebrate</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-your-business-the-right-brain-way-sustainable-success-for-the-creative-entrepreneur-jennifer-lee-abridged/">Building Your Business the Right-Brain Way : Sustainable Success for the Creative Entrepreneur &#8211; Jennifer Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traction : How Any Startup Can Achieve Explosive Customer Growth &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Justin Mares (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/traction-how-any-startup-can-achieve-explosive-customer-growth-gabriel-weinberg-justin-mares-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/traction-how-any-startup-can-achieve-explosive-customer-growth-gabriel-weinberg-justin-mares-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Traction, serial entrepreneurs Gabriel Weinberg and Justin Mares give startups the tools for generating explosive customer growth &#8216;Anyone trying to break through to new customers can use this smart, ambitious book&#8217; Eric Ries, author of The Lean Startup Most startups don&#8217;t fail because they can&#8217;t build a product. Most startups fail because they can&#8217;t [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/traction-how-any-startup-can-achieve-explosive-customer-growth-gabriel-weinberg-justin-mares-abridged/">Traction : How Any Startup Can Achieve Explosive Customer Growth &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Justin Mares (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Traction, serial entrepreneurs Gabriel Weinberg and Justin Mares give startups the tools for generating explosive customer growth    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Anyone trying to break through to new customers can use this smart, ambitious book&#8217;<br />
                    Eric Ries, author of The Lean Startup    </p>
<p>                    Most startups don&#8217;t fail because they can&#8217;t build a product. Most startups fail because they can&#8217;t get traction.    </p>
<p>                    Building a successful company is hard. Smart entrepreneurs know that the key to success isn&#8217;t the originality of your offering, the brilliance of your team, or how much money you raise. It&#8217;s how consistently you can grow and acquire new customers.     </p>
<p>                    Traction will teach you the nineteen channels you can use to build a customer base, and offers a three-step framework to figure out which ones will work best for your business. No matter how you apply them, the lessons and examples in Traction will help you create and sustain the growth your business desperately needs.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Here is the inside scoop, the latest, most specific tactics from the red-hot centre of the Internet marketing universe. From someone who has done it. Twice&#8217;<br />
                    Seth Godin, author of Linchpin</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/traction-how-any-startup-can-achieve-explosive-customer-growth-gabriel-weinberg-justin-mares-abridged/">Traction : How Any Startup Can Achieve Explosive Customer Growth &#8211; Gabriel Weinberg, Justin Mares (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value. Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value.    </p>
<p>                     Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this revolution and provides the first &#8220;owner&#8217;s manual&#8221; for creating a platform marketplace. It provides the essential guide to unlocking the potential of an economic landscape transformed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not To Worry : The Remarkable Truth of How a Small Change Can Help You Stress Less and Enjoy Life More &#8211; Paul McGee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-worry-the-remarkable-truth-of-how-a-small-change-can-help-you-stress-less-and-enjoy-life-more-paul-mcgee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-worry-the-remarkable-truth-of-how-a-small-change-can-help-you-stress-less-and-enjoy-life-more-paul-mcgee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to defeat stress, worry, and anxiety to achieve more in business and life. From the international bestselling author of Self-Confidence. Are You A Worrier? Do you seem to worry more than most? Do you find that insignificant things stress you out? Do you sweat the small stuff and the big stuff too? Well, now [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-worry-the-remarkable-truth-of-how-a-small-change-can-help-you-stress-less-and-enjoy-life-more-paul-mcgee-abridged/">How Not To Worry : The Remarkable Truth of How a Small Change Can Help You Stress Less and Enjoy Life More &#8211; Paul McGee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to defeat stress, worry, and anxiety to achieve more in business and life. From the international bestselling author of Self-Confidence. Are You A Worrier? Do you seem to worry more than most? Do you find that insignificant things stress you out? Do you sweat the small stuff and the big stuff too? Well, now s the time to stop worrying and start living. Worry, stress, anxiety whichever label you prefer to use can have consequences that impact not only our lives, but the lives of others around us. When we worry it s like the engine of our mind is constantly being revved up. It doesn t allow us time to switch off and rest. It tires you out. And when you re tired you re less likely to think straight. And when you re not thinking straight it s easy to make stupid mistakes and confuse priorities&#8230;But relax. There is a way forward. In How Not to Worry Paul McGee shows us that there is a way to tackle life s challenges in a calmer and more considered way. It is possible to use a certain degree of worry and anxiety to spur us on towards positive, constructive action, and then leave the rest behind.<br />
                    With down to earth, real life advice, How Not to Worry helps us understand why worrying is such a big deal and the reasons for it, exposing the behavioural traps we fall into when faced with challenges. It then helps us to move on with tools and ideas to deal with our worries in a more constructive way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-worry-the-remarkable-truth-of-how-a-small-change-can-help-you-stress-less-and-enjoy-life-more-paul-mcgee-abridged/">How Not To Worry : The Remarkable Truth of How a Small Change Can Help You Stress Less and Enjoy Life More &#8211; Paul McGee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that philosophy and illustrates how successful businesses have redefined themselves in the new customer universe.    </p>
<p>                    Personality Not Included is a powerhouse resource packed with bold new insights that show you how to shed the lifeless armor of your business and rediscover the soul of your brand. Sharing stories from the ethos of the world&#8217;s weirdest city, to how Manga has taken the comic book industry by storm, to showcasing brands like Intel, Boeing, ING, and Dyson, Bhargava shows you why personality matters from the inside out.    </p>
<p>                    In Part One, you&#8217;ll be introduced to the key components to building a personality and learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    Recognize the greatest myth that most marketers blindly follow, and how to get past itUse the &#8220;UAT Filter&#8221; to understand the personality of your organization and products in order to develop a communication strategy that drives your marketingCreate your company&#8217;s &#8220;marketing backstory&#8221; using techniques pioneered by Hollywood screenwritersHarness the influence of &#8220;accidental spokespeople&#8221; and use it to your advantageNavigate the roadblocks of using personality that come from bosses, peers, investors, and lawyers, without getting fired or flamedPinpoint and capitalize on the moments where personality can make a difference<br />
                    Part Two is packed with guides, tools, and techniques to help you flawlessly implement your plan. It features practical, step-by-step lessons that help you effectively move from theory to action, and includes a valuable collection of guides, checklists, question forms, printable resources, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Don&#8217;t be another faceless company-learn the new rules for succeeding in the social media era with Personality Not Included.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave : 50 Everyday Acts of Courage to Thrive in Work, Love and Life &#8211; Margie Warrell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brave-50-everyday-acts-of-courage-to-thrive-in-work-love-and-life-margie-warrell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-50-everyday-acts-of-courage-to-thrive-in-work-love-and-life-margie-warrell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Live every day with greater clarity, confidence and courage. Brave is a handbook for being more courageous. Written for busy people on the go, its short, focused chapters provide practical tools and empowering perspectives to help you build your &#8216;courage muscles&#8217; in your work, relationships and life. Drawing on her background in business, psychology and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-50-everyday-acts-of-courage-to-thrive-in-work-love-and-life-margie-warrell-abridged/">Brave : 50 Everyday Acts of Courage to Thrive in Work, Love and Life &#8211; Margie Warrell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Live every day with greater clarity, confidence and courage. Brave is a handbook for being more courageous. Written for busy people on the go, its short, focused chapters provide practical tools and empowering perspectives to help you build your &#8216;courage muscles&#8217; in your work, relationships and life.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on her background in business, psychology and coaching, author Margie Warrell will guide you in moving past the fears, doubts and beliefs that keep you from making the changes, and taking the chances, you need to enjoy the fulfillment and success you desire.    </p>
<p>                     Courage is a habit. Practicing it daily, even in quiet small ways, unlocks new possibilities, creates new opportunities, grows your influence and enables you to meet your challenges with more resilience and self-assurance. So whether you&#8217;re stuck in a rut, struggling in a relationship, overwhelmed by your daily juggling act or uninspired about your future, Brave will provide you with a regular dose of positive and practical inspiration to:    </p>
<p>                    Clarify what &#8216;success&#8217; truly means to you, and be more purposeful in your daily efforts to achieve it<br />
                    Speak up with greater confidence, and be more assertive in dealing with difficult people, getting what you want and changing what you don&#8217;t<br />
                    Define the person and leader you aspire to be, become more resilient under pressure, decisive in uncertainty and adaptable to change<br />
                    Scrap the excuses (your age, education, gender, busyness or children) that sabotage your future actions<br />
                    Dare more boldly, passionately pursuing the goals that inspire you most, no matter how daunting    </p>
<p>                     Courage begets courage. You build it every time you choose to leave the safety of your comfort zone for the sake of something more important. Day by day, brave action by brave action, you can Brave within you to create a life rich in all that you seek. If you want to live your life more powerfully and purposefully, this book will become your trusted companion.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-50-everyday-acts-of-courage-to-thrive-in-work-love-and-life-margie-warrell-abridged/">Brave : 50 Everyday Acts of Courage to Thrive in Work, Love and Life &#8211; Margie Warrell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Systems Analysis & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You won&#8217;t find a more honest, raw and helpful look into the trenches of founding a tech startup than this book&#8217; Nir Eyal, author of Hooked &#8216;Rand Fishkin is the real deal&#8217; Seth Godin, entrepreneur and author &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; Everyone knows how a startup story is supposed to go: a young, brilliant entrepreneur has an cool [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/">Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You won&#8217;t find a more honest, raw and helpful look into the trenches of founding a tech startup than this book&#8217; Nir Eyal, author of Hooked    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rand Fishkin is the real deal&#8217; Seth Godin, entrepreneur and author     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    Everyone knows how a startup story is supposed to go: a young, brilliant entrepreneur has an cool idea, drops out of college, defies the doubters, overcomes all odds, makes billions and becomes the envy of the technology world.     </p>
<p>                    This is not that story.    </p>
<p>                    Rand Fishkin, the founder and former CEO of Moz, is one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on SEO. Moz is now a $45 million a year business, but Fishkin&#8217;s business and reputation took 15 years to grow, and his startup began not in a Harvard dorm room but as a mother-and-son family business that fell deeply into debt.     </p>
<p>                    Now Fishkin pulls back the curtain on tech startup mythology, exposing the ups and downs of startup life that most CEOs would rather keep secret. For instance: a minimally viable product can be destructive if you launch at the wrong moment. Growth hacking may be the buzzword du jour, but initiatives to your business can fizzle quickly. Revenue and profitability won&#8217;t protect you from layoffs. And venture capital always comes with strings attached.     </p>
<p>                    In Lost and Founder Fishkin reveals the mostly awful, sometimes awesome truth about startup culture with the transparency and humour that his hundreds of thousands of blog readers have come to love. Fishkin&#8217;s hard-won lessons are applicable to any kind of business environment and this book can help solve your problems, and make you feel less alone for having them.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is a truly courageous book. It&#8217;s one part business-building guide and two parts Indiana Jones-style adventure memoir&#8217; Chris Guillebeau, author of Side Hustle and The $100 Startup    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rand Fishkin is like the industry friend we all wish we had &#8211; funny, warm, and refreshingly honest about the rollercoaster ride that is founding your own company&#8217; Julie Zhou, VP of Product Design at Facebook</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/">Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crossing the Chasm, 3rd Edition : Marketing and Selling Disruptive Products to Mainstream Customers &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bible for bringing cutting-edge products to larger markets&#8211;now revised and updated with new insights into the realities of high-tech marketing In Crossing the Chasm, Geoffrey A. Moore shows that in the Technology Adoption Life Cycle&#8211;which begins with innovators and moves to early adopters, early majority, late majority, and laggards&#8211;there is a vast chasm between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/">Crossing the Chasm, 3rd Edition : Marketing and Selling Disruptive Products to Mainstream Customers &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bible for bringing cutting-edge products to larger markets&#8211;now revised and updated with new insights into the realities of high-tech marketing    </p>
<p>                    In Crossing the Chasm, Geoffrey A. Moore shows that in the Technology Adoption Life Cycle&#8211;which begins with innovators and moves to early adopters, early majority, late majority, and laggards&#8211;there is a vast chasm between the early adopters and the early majority. While early adopters are willing to sacrifice for the advantage of being first, the early majority waits until they know that the technology actually offers improvements in productivity. The challenge for innovators and marketers is to narrow this chasm and ultimately accelerate adoption across every segment.     </p>
<p>                    This third edition brings Moore&#8217;s classic work up to date with dozens of new examples of successes and failures, new strategies for marketing in the digital world, and Moore&#8217;s most current insights and findings. He also includes two new appendices, the first connecting the ideas in Crossing the Chasm to work subsequently published in his Inside the Tornado, and the second presenting his recent groundbreaking work for technology adoption models for high-tech consumer markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/">Crossing the Chasm, 3rd Edition : Marketing and Selling Disruptive Products to Mainstream Customers &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave New Work : Are You Ready to Reinvent Your Organization? &#8211; Aaron Dignan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s stopping you from doing the best work of your life? The way we work is broken. It takes forever to get anything done. Meetings and emails are incessant. Bureaucracy stifles talent and creativity. Is this really the best we can do? Aaron Dignan teaches companies how to eliminate red tape, tap into collective intelligence, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/">Brave New Work : Are You Ready to Reinvent Your Organization? &#8211; Aaron Dignan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s stopping you from doing the best work of your life?    </p>
<p>                    The way we work is broken. It takes forever to get anything done. Meetings and emails are incessant. Bureaucracy stifles talent and creativity.  Is this really the best we can do?    </p>
<p>                    Aaron Dignan teaches companies how to eliminate red tape, tap into collective intelligence, and rethink long-held traditions that no longer make sense. In Brave New Work, he shows you how to revolutionize the way you, your team and your company works forever.     </p>
<p>                    *         Have fewer but better meetings<br />
                    *         Create a culture of honesty, transparency and trust<br />
                    *         Cut down on rules to be more efficient<br />
                    *         Be more agile and adaptive<br />
                    *         Reignite passion and energy throughout your organisation    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Clear, powerful and urgent, it&#8217;s a must read for anyone who cares about where they work and how they work&#8221; &#8211; Seth Godin, author of This is Marketing and Purple Cow</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-work-are-you-ready-to-reinvent-your-organization-aaron-dignan-abridged/">Brave New Work : Are You Ready to Reinvent Your Organization? &#8211; Aaron Dignan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Polymath : Unlocking the Power of Human Versatility &#8211; Waqas Ahmed (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-polymath-unlocking-the-power-of-human-versatility-waqas-ahmed-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-polymath-unlocking-the-power-of-human-versatility-waqas-ahmed-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every human is born with multifarious potential. Why, then, do parents, schools and employers insist that we restrict our many talents and interests; that we &#8216;specialise&#8217; in just one? We&#8217;ve been sold a myth, that to &#8216;specialise&#8217; is the only way to pursue truth, identity, or even a livelihood. Yet specialisation is nothing but an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-polymath-unlocking-the-power-of-human-versatility-waqas-ahmed-abridged/">The Polymath : Unlocking the Power of Human Versatility &#8211; Waqas Ahmed (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every human is born with multifarious potential. Why, then, do parents, schools and employers insist that we restrict our many talents and interests; that we &#8216;specialise&#8217; in just one?     </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve been sold a myth, that to &#8216;specialise&#8217; is the only way to pursue truth, identity, or even a livelihood. Yet specialisation is nothing but an outdated system that fosters ignorance, exploitation and disillusionment and thwarts creativity, opportunity and progress.     </p>
<p>                    Following a series of exchanges with the world&#8217;s greatest historians, futurists, philosophers and scientists, Waqas Ahmed has weaved together a narrative of history and a vision for the future that seeks to disrupt this prevailing system of unwarranted &#8216;hyper-specialisation.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    In The Polymath, Waqas shows us that there is another way of thinking and being. Through an approach that is both philosophical and practical, he sets out a cognitive journey towards reclaiming your innate polymathic state. Going further, he proposes nothing less than a cultural revolution in our education and professional structures, whereby everyone is encouraged to express themselves in multiple ways and fulfil their many-sided potential.     </p>
<p>                    Not only does this enhance individual fulfilment, but in doing so, facilitates a conscious and creative society that is both highly motivated and well equipped to address the complexity of 21st century challenges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-polymath-unlocking-the-power-of-human-versatility-waqas-ahmed-abridged/">The Polymath : Unlocking the Power of Human Versatility &#8211; Waqas Ahmed (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smart Teams : How to Work Better Together &#8211; Dermot Crowley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smart-teams-how-to-work-better-together-dermot-crowley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smart-teams-how-to-work-better-together-dermot-crowley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Communicate, congregate and collaborate more effectively than ever Smart Teams will help your team to go beyond personal productivity to enhance team productivity. Building on the concepts presented in Smart Work, which focuses on personal productivity, this book shows you how to turn unproductive team behaviours that create friction into &#8216;superproductive&#8217; behaviours that promote flow. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smart-teams-how-to-work-better-together-dermot-crowley-abridged/">Smart Teams : How to Work Better Together &#8211; Dermot Crowley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Communicate, congregate and collaborate more effectively than ever    </p>
<p>                     Smart Teams will help your team to go beyond personal productivity to enhance team productivity. Building on the concepts presented in Smart Work, which focuses on personal productivity, this book shows you how to turn unproductive team behaviours that create friction into &#8216;superproductive&#8217; behaviours that promote flow. Productivity is, at its core, a leadership issue &#8211; and this book provides practical guidelines that help you build a culture where productivity thrives.    </p>
<p>                     Working together can be a drag &#8211; literally. Email noise, unproductive meetings and poorly organised projects can stifle creativity and disrupt everyone&#8217;s workflow. But by creating team agreements that raise awareness of the negative impact of our behaviours, you build the desire and capability to change. This book is packed with tips, guidelines and expert insights for leaders and managers at any level.    </p>
<p>                    Foster a culture of &#8216;superproductivity&#8217;<br />
                    Create a set of Smart Team principles to guide cooperation<br />
                    Run fewer, shorter and more effective meetings<br />
                    Collaborate more productively on projects<br />
                    Reduce urgency, interruptions and email noise    </p>
<p>                     People want their work to matter, they want to make an impact and they want to do it all with a healthy work-life balance &#8211; productivity is the key to making it all happen.  Smart Teams shows you how to implement the culture shift that will allow your team to flourish.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smart-teams-how-to-work-better-together-dermot-crowley-abridged/">Smart Teams : How to Work Better Together &#8211; Dermot Crowley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job : How to Dump Your Boss, Build a Business and Not Go Broke &#8211; Scott Gerber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/never-get-a-real-job-how-to-dump-your-boss-build-a-business-and-not-go-broke-scott-gerber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/never-get-a-real-job-how-to-dump-your-boss-build-a-business-and-not-go-broke-scott-gerber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Young serial entrepreneur Scott Gerber is not the product of a wealthy family or storied entrepreneurial heritage. Nor is he the outcome of a traditional business school education or a corporate executive turned entrepreneur. Rather, he is a hard-working, self-taught 26-year-old hustler, rainmaker, and bootstrapper who has survived and thrived despite never having held the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-get-a-real-job-how-to-dump-your-boss-build-a-business-and-not-go-broke-scott-gerber-abridged/">Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job : How to Dump Your Boss, Build a Business and Not Go Broke &#8211; Scott Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Young serial entrepreneur Scott Gerber is not the product of a wealthy family or storied entrepreneurial heritage. Nor is he the outcome of a traditional business school education or a corporate executive turned entrepreneur. Rather, he is a hard-working, self-taught 26-year-old hustler, rainmaker, and bootstrapper who has survived and thrived despite never having held the proverbial &#8220;real job. In  Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job: How to Dump Your Boss, Build a Business, and Not Go Broke, Gerber challenges the social conventions behind the &#8220;real&#8221; job and empowers young people to take control of their lives and dump their nine-to-fives or their quest to attain them. Drawing upon case studies, experiences, and observations, Scott dissects failures, shares hard-learned lessons, and presents practical, affordable, and systematic action steps to building, managing, and marketing a successful business on a shoestring budget. The proven, no-b.s. methodology presented in  Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job teaches unemployed and underemployed Gen-Yers, aspiring small business owners, students, and recent college graduates how to quit 9-to-5s, become their own bosses, and achieve financial independence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-get-a-real-job-how-to-dump-your-boss-build-a-business-and-not-go-broke-scott-gerber-abridged/">Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job : How to Dump Your Boss, Build a Business and Not Go Broke &#8211; Scott Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Side Hustle : Build a Side Business and Make Extra Money &#8211; Without Quitting Your Day Job &#8211; Chris Guillebeau (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/side-hustle-build-a-side-business-and-make-extra-money-without-quitting-your-day-job-chris-guillebeau-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/side-hustle-build-a-side-business-and-make-extra-money-without-quitting-your-day-job-chris-guillebeau-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of $100 Startup comes this accessible guide to building a side business from scratch &#8211; without having to give up your day job. Side Hustle is about much more than just making some extra cash; it&#8217;s about freedom and job security in today&#8217;s unstable business environment. That&#8217;s because [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/side-hustle-build-a-side-business-and-make-extra-money-without-quitting-your-day-job-chris-guillebeau-abridged/">Side Hustle : Build a Side Business and Make Extra Money &#8211; Without Quitting Your Day Job &#8211; Chris Guillebeau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of $100 Startup comes this accessible guide to building a side business from scratch &#8211; without having to give up your day job.    </p>
<p>                    Side Hustle is about much more than just making some extra cash; it&#8217;s about freedom and job security in today&#8217;s unstable business environment. That&#8217;s because when you receive income from multiple different sources, you are no longer dependent on the whims of a single employer. It affords you choices and options.    </p>
<p>                    In the style of $100 Startup, full of practical exercises and peppered with inspiring stories, Chris Guillebeau&#8217;s Side Hustle shows readers how to brainstorm, choose, implement, launch and refine their side business in just 27 days &#8211; with little to no budget and without having to quit their current job.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/side-hustle-build-a-side-business-and-make-extra-money-without-quitting-your-day-job-chris-guillebeau-abridged/">Side Hustle : Build a Side Business and Make Extra Money &#8211; Without Quitting Your Day Job &#8211; Chris Guillebeau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW* In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement. &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW*    </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New York Magazine    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compellingly motivational read&#8217; The Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book you need in your life&#8217; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                    *Winner of the 2014 Goodreads Choice Award for Best Business Book*    </p>
<p>                    In the space of ten years, Sophia Amoruso has gone from high-school dropout to founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal, one of the fastest-growing retailers in the world.     </p>
<p>                    Sophia&#8217;s never been a typical executive, or a typical anything, and she&#8217;s written #GIRLBOSS for other girls like her: outsiders (and insiders) seeking a unique path to success.    </p>
<p>                    Filled with brazen wake-up calls, cunning and frank observations, and behind-the-scenes stories from Nasty Gal&#8217;s meteoric rise, #GIRLBOSS covers a lot of ground. It proves that success doesn&#8217;t come from where you went to college or how popular you were in school. Success is about trusting your instincts and following your gut, knowing which rules to follow and which to break.    </p>
<p>                    Inspiring, motivating and empowering, #GIRLBOSS will give you the kick up the ass you need to reach your potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stories and advice for creating a business out of the food you love. Do you have a passion for delicious food and want to create your own business out of it, but have no idea where to start? Cooking Up a Business is essential reading for aspiring entrepreneurs and gives you a real-world, up-close-and-personal preview [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/">Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stories and advice for creating a business out of the food you love.      </p>
<p>                    Do you have a passion for delicious food and want to create your own business out of it, but have no idea where to start? Cooking Up a Business is essential reading for aspiring entrepreneurs and gives you a real-world, up-close-and-personal preview of the exciting journey. Through profiles and interviews with nationally known food entrepreneurs from Popchips, Vosges Haut-Chocolat, Hint Water, Mary&#8217;s Gone Crackers, Love Grown Foods, Kopali Organics, Tasty, Evol, Justin&#8217;s Nut Butters, Cameron Hughes Wine, and more, you will gain applicable, practical guidance that teaches you how to succeed today:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; How to create a national brand&#8211;with no connections or experience<br />
                    &#8211; The secret to getting meetings with grocery store buyers<br />
                    &#8211; The number one thing you need to know about food safety regulations<br />
                    &#8211; Why a grassroots budget might actually help you succeed<br />
                    &#8211; Specific advice for gluten-free, organic, wine, and beverage companies<br />
                    &#8211; What every entrepreneur wishes someone had told them at the beginning &#8211; Why doing what you love is always a good idea</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/">Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?) The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect. Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?)    </p>
<p>                    The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect.    </p>
<p>                    Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover exactly what people want to buy, and how to give it to them &#8211; and in a way that makes people fall in love with you and your company.     </p>
<p>                    The proven, repeatable (yet slightly counterintuitive) Ask Method has quietly generated over $100 million in online sales across 23 different industries, and counting. In this tell-all book, Ryan Levesque reveals this exact method step-by-step, as well as the unusual story behind its discovery.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re an aspiring Internet entrepreneur, advanced online marketer, or established business owner, this book will both inspire you and show you how to skyrocket your online income-while creating a mass of raving fans in the process-simply by asking the right questions in a surprisingly different way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ryan has uncovered some enormous misunderstandings about human buying behavior and then utilized his neuroscience background to create this game-changing marketing and survey strategy. Before you finish the first third of the book, you&#8217;ll be eager to jump ahead and implement his process immediately &#8211; it&#8217;s that powerful!&#8217; &#8211; Annie Hyman Pratt, former CEO of The Coffee Bean and Tea Leaf and CEO of IMPAQ Entrepreneur Business Execution Systems    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ask may be the most important book written for anyone who sells products or services directly to consumers since Breakthrough Advertising was published in 1966. Like that masterpiece, Ask gives us a new paradigm for understanding human behavior at the deepest level, which gives rise to a more intelligent and profitable way to sell almost anything. Ryan Levsque will go down in history as the marketer who used his background to change the way products and services are sold online.&#8217; &#8211; Brian Kurtz, business builder of Boardroom Inc. and serial direct marketer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making Ideas Happen : Overcoming the Obstacles Between Vision and Reality &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-ideas-happen-overcoming-the-obstacles-between-vision-and-reality-scott-belsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-ideas-happen-overcoming-the-obstacles-between-vision-and-reality-scott-belsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Edison famously said that genius is 1% inspiration, 99% perspiration. Every day new solutions, revolutionary cures, and artistic breakthroughs are conceived and squandered by smart people. Along with the gift of creativity come the obstacles to making ideas happen: lack of organisation, lack of accountability and a lack of community support. Scott Belsky has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-ideas-happen-overcoming-the-obstacles-between-vision-and-reality-scott-belsky-abridged/">Making Ideas Happen : Overcoming the Obstacles Between Vision and Reality &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Edison famously said that genius is 1% inspiration, 99% perspiration. Every day new solutions, revolutionary cures, and artistic breakthroughs are conceived and squandered by smart people. Along with the gift of creativity come the obstacles to making ideas happen: lack of organisation, lack of accountability and a lack of community support.    </p>
<p>                    Scott Belsky has interviewsed hundreds of the most productive creative people and teams in the world, revealing one common trait: a carefully trained capacity for executing ideas. Implementing your ideas is a skill that can be taught, and Belsky distills the core principles in this book.    </p>
<p>                    While many of us obsess about discovering great new ideas, Belsky shows why it is better to develop the capacity to make ideas happen &#8211; using old-fashioned passion and perspiration. Making Ideas Happen reveals the practical yet counterintuitive techniques of &#8216;serial creatives&#8217; &#8211; those few who make their visions a reality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-ideas-happen-overcoming-the-obstacles-between-vision-and-reality-scott-belsky-abridged/">Making Ideas Happen : Overcoming the Obstacles Between Vision and Reality &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability. Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability.    </p>
<p>                    Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more rewarding and productive life. He no longer has to contend with an environment that constantly demands more productivity, more output and more growth.    </p>
<p>                    In Company of One, Jarvis explains how you can do the same, including:    </p>
<p>                    *         Planning to set up<br />
                    *         Determining desired revenues<br />
                    *         Keeping clients happy<br />
                    *         And, of course, doing all this on your own.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jarvis makes a compelling case for making your business better instead of bigger. A must-read for any entrepreneur who prioritizes a rich life over riches.&#8221;<br />
                     -CAL NEWPORT, bestselling author of DEEP WORK and DIGITAL MINIMALISM    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You&#8217;re not a machine, so why would you run your business like one? Company of One shows you another way. If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how to have a business that works for you-instead of the other way around-you need this book.&#8221;<br />
                    -CHRIS GUILLEBEAU, bestselling author of SIDE HUSTLE and THE $100 STARTUP</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Four Steps to the Epiphany : Successful Strategies for Products that Win &#8211; Steve Blank (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling classic that launched 10,000 startups and new corporate ventures &#8211; The Four Steps to the Epiphany is one of the most influential and practical business books of all time. The Four Steps to the Epiphany launched the Lean Startup approach to new ventures. It was the first book to offer that startups are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/">The Four Steps to the Epiphany : Successful Strategies for Products that Win &#8211; Steve Blank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling classic that launched 10,000 startups and new corporate ventures &#8211; The Four Steps to the Epiphany is one of the most influential and practical business books of all time.<br />
                    The Four Steps to the Epiphany launched the Lean Startup approach to new ventures. It was the first book to offer that startups are not smaller versions of large companies and that new ventures are different than existing ones. Startups search for business models while existing companies execute them.    </p>
<p>                    The book offers the practical and proven four-step Customer Development process for search and offers insight into what makes some startups successful and leaves others selling off their furniture.<br />
                    Rather than blindly execute a plan, The Four Steps helps uncover flaws in product and business plans and correct them before they become costly. Rapid iteration, customer feedback, testing your assumptions are all explained in this book.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with concrete examples of what to do, how to do it and when to do it, the book will leave you with new skills to organize sales, marketing and your business for success.<br />
                    If your organization is starting a new venture, and you&#8217;re thinking how to successfully organize sales, marketing and business development you need The Four Steps to the Epiphany.<br />
                    Essential reading for anyone starting something new.     </p>
<p>                     The Four Steps to the Epiphany  was originally published by K&#038;S Ranch Publishing Inc. and is now available from Wiley. The cover, design, and content are the same as the prior release and should not be considered a new or updated product.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/">The Four Steps to the Epiphany : Successful Strategies for Products that Win &#8211; Steve Blank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital When you connect with the right angel [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital    </p>
<p>                    When you connect with the right angel investor, it&#8217;s like finding a new best friend&#8211;you just have to know what makes him or her happy.    </p>
<p>                    Smart funding is waiting for smart founders. Raising funds is all about connecting with the investor who&#8217;s right for you&#8211;and What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know shows you exactly how to succeed.    </p>
<p>                    Veteran early-stage investor Brian Cohen knows how to spot a great company destined for success, and in this groundbreaking book he offers soup-to-nuts guidance for anyentrepreneur seeking to launch an invention, a product, or a great new idea into a receptive marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    As chairman of the board of directors of the New York Angels, Cohen is one of the most engaged angel investors out there today. The first investor in Pinterest, he describes exactly what angels want to see, hear, and feelbefore they take out their checkbooks:    </p>
<p>                    A clear exit strategy before the startup even launchesFacts that turn &#8220;due&#8221; diligence into &#8220;do&#8221; diligenceAuthenticity&#8211;&#8220;save your spinning for the fitness center&#8221;Proof that you &#8220;live inside the customer&#8217;s head&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Cohen gives invaluable insight into how the most successful angels view due diligence, friends and family money, crowdfunding, team building, scalability, iteration, exit strategies&#8211;and much more.    </p>
<p>                    This one-of-a-kind book provides a rare look inside the minds of people who are in the business of funding businesses just like yours.    </p>
<p>                    Read What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know to get your best shot at funding for your product after your very first pitch.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR WHAT EVERY ANGEL INVESTOR WANTS YOU TO KNOW:&#8221;Brian Cohen is truly the entrepreneur&#8217;s best friend. Cohen and Kador haven distilled their first-hand experiences into an intensely personal, highly readablejourney into the mind of angels that should be kept at the bedside of every startup CEO.&#8221; &#8212; DAVID S. ROSE, founder, New York Angels, and CEO, Gust    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Meet one of the fundamental building blocks of the entrepreneurial scene. In one easy-to-read package, readers now have the wisdom of Brian Cohen, perhaps themost well-connected investor/entrepreneur in New York.&#8221; &#8212; MURAT AKTIHANOGLU, founder and managing director, Entrepreneurs Roundtable Accelerator    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know gives you an actionable checklist for success in fund-raising and entrepreneurship. Cohen and Kador provide anexhilarating ride for those who want to pilot their own business.&#8221; &#8212; REED HOLDEN, serial entrepreneur and author of Negotiating with Backbone    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Personal insights from a seasoned angel investor. An important addition to the reading list for today&#8217;s entrepreneurs.&#8221; &#8212; SCOTT CASE, CEO, Startup America Partnership    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know is a must-read for entrepreneurs and investors who want to fi nance startup dreams&#8211;an accessible, jargon-free,practical primer.&#8221; &#8212; WHITNEY JOHNSON, author of Dare, Dream, Do: Remarkable Things Happen When You Dare to Dream and cofounder, Rose Park Advisors    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;While [this] book is anecdotal, [the authors] discuss in depth how angels view a potential investment as well as how they evaluate its prospects. This is the book&#8217;s strength. Recommended. All levels of students, entrepreneurs, practitioners.&#8221; &#8212; CHOICE</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With must-have updates, a new edition of the bestselling method that shows how anyone can turn their one simple idea into millions &#8211; without lifting a finger! Stephen Key is an award-winning inventor who has licensed more than 20 product ideas. In 2011, he shared the secrets to his success in the bestselling book One [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/">One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With must-have updates, a new edition of the bestselling method that shows how anyone can turn their one simple idea into millions &#8211; without lifting a finger!    </p>
<p>                     Stephen Key is an award-winning inventor who has licensed more than 20 product ideas. In 2011, he shared the secrets to his success in the bestselling book One Simple Idea. Since that time, many changes have occurred in the entrepreneurial world.    </p>
<p>                    One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition has been revised and updated to reflect current trends and practices in the industry. In addition to teaching readers how to turn their ideas into marketable products that companies will want to license, Key expands upon his cutting-edge product development, sales, and negotiation strategies, making note of the new opportunities and technologies available to creative people today. The book also features real-life success stories from people who have used the author&#8217;s strategies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/">One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Jobs : Money, Meaning and Freedom Without the 9-to-5 &#8211; Taylor Pearson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Amazon Bestseller in Business and Money, Small Business, Entrepreneurship, and International Economics A Top 3 &#8216;Start Your Own Business&#8217; Book -Inc Magazine The rapid development of technology and globalization has changed the leverage points in accumulating wealth: money, meaning and freedom. Those that don&#8217;t adapt are becoming trapped in the downward spiral of a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/">The End of Jobs : Money, Meaning and Freedom Without the 9-to-5 &#8211; Taylor Pearson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Amazon Bestseller in Business and Money, Small Business, Entrepreneurship, and International Economics    </p>
<p>                    A Top 3 &#8216;Start Your Own Business&#8217; Book -Inc Magazine    </p>
<p>                    The rapid development of technology and globalization has changed the leverage points in accumulating wealth: money, meaning and freedom. Those that don&#8217;t adapt are becoming trapped in the downward spiral of a dying middle class &#8211; working harder and earning less. Entrepreneurs that understand the new paradigm, have created unprecedented wealth in their lives and the lives of those they love.    </p>
<p>                    In This Book You&#8217;ll Learn:     </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why the century-long growth in wages came to a halt in 2000.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why MBAs and JDs can&#8217;t get jobs and what that means for the future of work and your job.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why The Theory of Constraints and a shift into the Fourth Economy has made entrepreneurship the highest-leveraged career path for the young and ambitious.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why The Turkey Problem means accounting may be the riskiest profession in the 21st century while entrepreneurship may be the safest.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; How entrepreneurs with second-rate degrees are leveraging the radical democracy of the Long Tail to get rich.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; How the Stair Step Method and return of apprenticeships have transformed the &#8220;entrepreneurial leap&#8221; to make entrepreneurship at large, and small business entrepreneurship in particular, more accessible than ever.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; The scientific research on how giving up balanced living and embracing integrated living leads to more money, more meaning, and more freedom.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why a 20th century world view to career search questions like &#8220;What career is right for me?&#8221; and &#8220;How do I find a career?&#8221; could be the source of your frustration (and a better way to think about it)    </p>
<p>                    Included (Free) Resources:     </p>
<p>                    Get access by visiting http: //taylorpearson.me/eoj    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Full Recorded Interviews with the Ten Entrepreneurs featured in The End of Jobs detailing how they launched their own successful businesses.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Taylor&#8217;s 67 must-read business books and the best entrepreneur books to fuel your entrepreneurial career.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; 49 tools and templates to save you hundreds of hours when launching and growing a business.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; A Ninety-Day goal setting template to translate the book into actionable steps    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Access to a private community to discuss the book and get support from a community of like-minded individuals to inspire, motivate, and assist each other in seeking out apprenticeships, your career search and other elements around &#8220;how to find a career&#8221; and other career guidance questions like &#8220;what career is right for me</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/">The End of Jobs : Money, Meaning and Freedom Without the 9-to-5 &#8211; Taylor Pearson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The E-Myth Revisited : Why Most Small Businesses Don&#8217;t Work and What to Do About It &#8211; Michael E. Gerber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>E-Myth &#8216;e-,&#8217;mith n 1: the entrepreneurial myth: the myth that most people who start small businesses are entrepreneurs 2: the fatal assumption that an individual who understands the technical work of a business can successfully run a business that does that technical work Voted #1 business book by Inc. 500 CEOs. An instant classic, this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/">The E-Myth Revisited : Why Most Small Businesses Don&#8217;t Work and What to Do About It &#8211; Michael E. Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>E-Myth  &#8216;e-,&#8217;mith n 1: the entrepreneurial myth: the myth that most people who start small businesses are entrepreneurs 2: the fatal assumption that an individual who understands the technical work of a business can successfully run a business that does that technical work  Voted #1 business book by Inc. 500 CEOs.  An instant classic, this revised and updated edition of the phenomenal bestseller dispels the myths about starting your own business. Small business consultant and author Michael E. Gerber, with sharp insight gained from years of experience, points out how common assumptions, expectations, and even technical expertise can get in the way of running a successful business.  Gerber walks you through the steps in the life of a business-from entrepreneurial infancy through adolescent growing pains to the mature entrepreneurial perspective: the guiding light of all businesses that succeed-and shows how to apply the lessons of franchising to any business, whether or not it is a franchise. Most importantly, Gerber draws the vital, often overlooked distinction between working on your business and working in your business.<br />
                    The E-Myth Revisited will help you grow your business in a productive, assured way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/">The E-Myth Revisited : Why Most Small Businesses Don&#8217;t Work and What to Do About It &#8211; Michael E. Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fixer : My Adventures Saving Startups from Death by Politics &#8211; Bradley Tusk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Service & Public Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The famed political advisor to Uber, FanDuel, Lemonade, Tesla and other startups reveals what really happens at the intersection of politics, tech and business Most new startups today are in highly regulated industries with strong incumbents &#8211; transportation, hotels, drones, energy, gaming, education, health care, cannabis, finance, liquor, insurance. The more startups try to snatch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/">The Fixer : My Adventures Saving Startups from Death by Politics &#8211; Bradley Tusk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The famed political advisor to Uber, FanDuel, Lemonade, Tesla and other startups reveals what really happens at the intersection of politics, tech and business Most new startups today are in highly regulated industries with strong incumbents &#8211; transportation, hotels, drones, energy, gaming, education, health care, cannabis, finance, liquor, insurance. The more startups try to snatch a piece of the establishment&#8217;s pie, the more they risk running into a political wall. That&#8217;s where Bradley Tusk comes in. Described as Silicon Valley&#8217;s Political Savior (Fast Company) Uber&#8217;s Political Genius (Vanity Fair) and Silicon Valley&#8217;s Favorite Fixer (TechCrunch) Tusk deploys the skills and knowledge he developed working with Chuck Schumer, Michael Bloomberg, Rod Blagojevich, and other political and business legends to help startups fight back. This book goes behind the scenes on how he helped stop the taxi industry from killing Uber in its infancy, how he held insurance companies at bay while startup Lemonade launched in each state, and how he helped online sports betting sites FanDuel and Draft Kings escape the regulatory death grip casinos tried to put on them. As Tusk writes, Every new company is essentially a tech startup. And when you disrupt someone in any industry, they don&#8217;t say thank you. They punch you in the nose. These are the lessons startups need to learn to punch back and survive the clutches of politics. Combining a firsthand glimpse behind the curtain with tangible advice for how any new venture can play the political game, THE FIXER is a must-read for aspiring entrepreneurs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/">The Fixer : My Adventures Saving Startups from Death by Politics &#8211; Bradley Tusk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this new paperback edition of the classic bestseller, you&#8217;ll be taken on a hilarious, fast-paced ride through the history of ideas. Author Scott Berkun will show you how to transcend the false stories that many business experts, scientists, and much of pop culture foolishly use to guide their thinking about how ideas change the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/">The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this new paperback edition of the classic bestseller, you&#8217;ll be taken on a hilarious, fast-paced ride through the history of ideas. Author Scott Berkun will show you how to transcend the false stories that many business experts, scientists, and much of pop culture foolishly use to guide their thinking about how ideas change the world. With four new chapters on putting the ideas in the book to work, updated references and over 50 corrections and improvements, now is the time to get past the myths, and change the world. You&#8217;ll have fun while you learn:  * Where ideas come from * The true history of history * Why most people don&#8217;t like ideas * How great managers make ideas thrive * The importance of problem finding * The simple plan (new for paperback)  Since its initial publication, this classic bestseller has been discussed on NPR, MSNBC, CNBC, and at Yale University, MIT, Carnegie Mellon University, Microsoft, Apple, Intel, Google, Amazon.com, and other major media, corporations, and universities around the world. It has changed the way thousands of leaders and creators understand the world.<br />
                    Now in an updated and expanded paperback edition, it&#8217;s a fantastic time to explore or rediscover this powerful view of the world of ideas. &#8220;Sets us free to try and change the world.&#8221; &#8211;Guy Kawasaki, Author of Art of The Start &#8220;Small, simple, powerful: an innovative book about innovation.&#8221; &#8211;Don Norman, author of Design of Everyday Things &#8220;Insightful, inspiring, evocative, and just plain fun to read. It&#8217;s totally great.&#8221; &#8211;John Seely Brown, Former Director, Xerox Palo Alto Research Center (PARC) &#8220;Methodically and entertainingly dismantling the cliches that surround the process of innovation.&#8221; &#8211;Scott Rosenberg, author of Dreaming in Code; cofounder of Salon.com &#8220;Will inspire you to come up with breakthrough ideas of your own.&#8221; &#8211;Alan Cooper, Father of Visual Basic and author of The Inmates are Running the Asylum &#8220;Brimming with insights and historical examples, Berkun&#8217;s book not only debunks widely held myths about innovation, it also points the ways toward making your new ideas stick.&#8221; &#8211;Tom Kelley, GM, IDEO; author of The Ten Faces of Innovation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/">The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Science of Intelligent Achievement : How Smart People Focus, Create and Grow Their Way to Success &#8211; Isaiah Hankel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-science-of-intelligent-achievement-how-smart-people-focus-create-and-grow-their-way-to-success-isaiah-hankel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-science-of-intelligent-achievement-how-smart-people-focus-create-and-grow-their-way-to-success-isaiah-hankel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Smart strategies for pragmatic, science-based growth and sustainable achievement. The Science of Intelligent Achievement teaches you the scientific process of finding success through your most valuable assets: * Selective focus &#8211; how selective are you with who and what you let into your life? * Creative ownership &#8211; how dependent are you on others for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-intelligent-achievement-how-smart-people-focus-create-and-grow-their-way-to-success-isaiah-hankel-abridged/">The Science of Intelligent Achievement : How Smart People Focus, Create and Grow Their Way to Success &#8211; Isaiah Hankel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Smart strategies for pragmatic, science-based growth and sustainable achievement. The Science of Intelligent Achievement teaches you the scientific process of finding success through your most valuable assets:    </p>
<p>                     *      Selective focus &#8211; how selective are you with who and what you let into your life?    </p>
<p>                     *      Creative ownership &#8211; how dependent are you on others for your happiness and success?    </p>
<p>                     *      Pragmatic growth &#8211; how consistently and practically are you growing daily?    </p>
<p>                     First, this book will show you how to develop your focus by being very selective with where you spend your mental energy. If you&#8217;ve failed to reach an important goal because you were distracted, misinformed, or overcommitted, then you know the role focus and selectivity play in achievement. Second, you will learn how to stop allowing your happiness and success to be dependent on other people and instead, start taking ownership over your life through creative work. Finally, you will learn the art of changing your life through pragmatic decisions and actions. Self-improvement is not the result of dramatic changes. Instead, science has shown that personal and professional change is initiated and sustained by consistent, practical changes. To grow, you must leverage the power of micro-decisions, personality responsibility, and mini-habits. Your own biology will not let you improve your life in any other way.    </p>
<p>                     What do you currently value? What are working to attain? Have you been taught to value your job title or your relationship with some other person above all else? Have you been convinced that the most valuable things in life are your paycheck, the number of people who say &#8216;hello&#8217; to you at the office, and the number of people who say &#8216;I need you&#8217; at home? Or, have you become so passive in what you value that you let anyone and anything into your life, as long as whatever you let in allows you to stay disconnected from the cold hard truth that when things really go wrong in your life, the only person who will be able to fix it and the only person will be responsible for it is you. If so&#8230;welcome to fake success. Passivity, dependence, and the sacrifice of practical thinking and personal responsibility to fuzzy, grandiose ideals and temporary feelings &#8211; these are markers of fake success.    </p>
<p>                     Intelligent Achievement, on the other hand, is not a moving target. It&#8217;s not empty either. Instead, it&#8217;s sturdy, full, and immovable. It&#8217;s not something that&#8217;s just handed to you. It&#8217;s not something you&#8217;re nudged to chase or coerced into wanting. Intelligent Achievement comes from within you. It&#8217;s a collection of values that are aligned with who you are-values you have to protect and nurture. These values do not increase your dependence on other people and things. Instead, they relieve you of dependence. This kind of achievement is something that you have a part in building from the ground up-you know what&#8217;s in it-you chose it, someone else didn&#8217;t choose it for you.    </p>
<p>                     Achieving real success means you must focus, create, and grow daily. The Science of Intelligent Achievement will show you how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-intelligent-achievement-how-smart-people-focus-create-and-grow-their-way-to-success-isaiah-hankel-abridged/">The Science of Intelligent Achievement : How Smart People Focus, Create and Grow Their Way to Success &#8211; Isaiah Hankel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on building a product that people will actually buy and use. By rigorously following the techniques described in Running Lean, you can eliminate waste &#8211; whether it&#8217;s time, money, effort, or all of the above &#8211; and get your product to market quickly. Refined through the real-world experiences of dozens of startup companies, these techniques are part of Eric Ries&#8217; Lean Startup methodology. Principles covered in this book include: * Find a problem worth solving, then define a solution * Demo before building * Pricing is part of the product * Maximize for speed, learning, and focus * Build a continuous feedback loop with customers throughout the product development cycle * Right Action, Right Time * Build a path to customers from day one</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Write Your Business Plan : Get Your Plan in Place and Your Business off the Ground &#8211; The Staff of Entrepreneur Media (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive companion to Entrepreneur&#8217;s long-time bestseller Start Your Own Business, this essential guide leads you through the most critical startup step next to committing to your business vision&#8211;defining how to achieve it. Coached by a diverse group of experts and successful business owners, gain an in-depth understanding of what&#8217;s essential to any business plan, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/">Write Your Business Plan : Get Your Plan in Place and Your Business off the Ground &#8211; The Staff of Entrepreneur Media (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive companion to Entrepreneur&#8217;s long-time bestseller Start Your Own Business, this essential guide leads you through the most critical startup step next to committing to your business vision&#8211;defining how to achieve it.  Coached by a diverse group of experts and successful business owners, gain an in-depth understanding of what&#8217;s essential to any business plan, what&#8217;s appropriate for your venture, and what it takes ensure success. Plus, learn from real-world examples of plans that worked, helping to raise money, hone strategy, and build a solid business.  Whether you&#8217;re just starting out or already running a business, to successfully build a company, you need a plan. One that lays out your product, your strategy, your market, your team, and your opportunity. It is the blueprint for your business. The experts at Entrepreneur show you how to create it.  Includes sample business plans, resources and worksheets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/">Write Your Business Plan : Get Your Plan in Place and Your Business off the Ground &#8211; The Staff of Entrepreneur Media (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to get to the stage &#8211; soon &#8211; where you are truly financially independent, able to use your money in the way you&#8217;d like, and be completely confident in your ability to take care of yourself and your family? That is a universal desire, but many of us regard wealth and financial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/">Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to get to the stage &#8211; soon &#8211; where you are truly financially independent, able to use your money in the way you&#8217;d like, and be completely confident in your ability to take care of yourself and your family?     </p>
<p>                    That is a universal desire, but many of us regard wealth and financial independence as a goal which we&#8217;ll likely never achieve &#8211; there are just too many bills that need paying and there is a widespread belief that the money game is rigged. Even people who win the lottery or inherit money often seem to wind up losing it. The evidence suggests you can&#8217;t win a game that you don&#8217;t understand &#8211; even if you start out winning &#8211; because you never understood the game in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    So how can you win with money? How can you create independent wealth and hold on to it? This inspiring book by self-made multi-millionaire Rob Moore explains the rules of the game, shares simple tricks for managing money better, details how to create a plan for an ambitious future, and shows you the very best way to become a millionaire &#8211; to think and behave like one!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/">Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Prepare a Business Plan : Your Guide to Creating an Excellent Strategy, Forecasting Your Finances and Producing a Persuasive Plan &#8211; Edward Blackwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An excellent business plan impresses financial backers, provides a clear blueprint for the future of your company and functions as a benchmark against which to measure future growth. How to Prepare a Business Plan explains the process of creating an excellent business plan in an engaging and accessible way. It includes essential coverage of producing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/">How to Prepare a Business Plan : Your Guide to Creating an Excellent Strategy, Forecasting Your Finances and Producing a Persuasive Plan &#8211; Edward Blackwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An excellent business plan impresses financial backers, provides a clear blueprint for the future of your company and functions as a benchmark against which to measure future growth. How to Prepare a Business Plan explains the process of creating an excellent business plan in an engaging and accessible way. It includes essential coverage of producing cash flow forecasts, planning a business expansion, planning your borrowing and monitoring business progress.     </p>
<p>                    Global case studies containing real business plans provide inspiration and real-life practical insight by analyzing the plans, monitoring the business&#8217; progress and discussing their problems. Sample business plans also show you the process in action and provide useful examples for creating your own. How to Prepare a Business Plan helps new business owners to consider what they really want out of their business, and to map their own journey and gain a new understanding of their product&#8217;s place in the market, as well as writing a business plan with the clarity, brevity and logic to keep bank managers interested and convinced.     </p>
<p>                    Whether looking to start up or expand, this practical advice will help anyone to prepare a plan that is tailored to the requirements of their business &#8211; one that will get the financial backing they need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/">How to Prepare a Business Plan : Your Guide to Creating an Excellent Strategy, Forecasting Your Finances and Producing a Persuasive Plan &#8211; Edward Blackwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Automatic Customer : Creating a Subscription Business in Any Industry &#8211; John Warrillow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-automatic-customer-creating-a-subscription-business-in-any-industry-john-warrillow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-automatic-customer-creating-a-subscription-business-in-any-industry-john-warrillow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Automatic Customer, John Warrillow provides the essential blueprint for turning your customers into subscribers The lifeblood of your business is repeat customers. But customers can be fickle, markets shift and competitors are ruthless. So how do you ensure a steady flow of business? The secret &#8211; no matter what industry you&#8217;re in &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-automatic-customer-creating-a-subscription-business-in-any-industry-john-warrillow-abridged/">The Automatic Customer : Creating a Subscription Business in Any Industry &#8211; John Warrillow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Automatic Customer, John Warrillow provides the essential blueprint for turning your customers into subscribers    </p>
<p>                    The lifeblood of your business is repeat customers. But customers can be fickle, markets shift and competitors are ruthless. So how do you ensure a steady flow of business? The secret &#8211; no matter what industry you&#8217;re in &#8211; is finding and keeping automatic customers.    </p>
<p>                    These days virtually anything you need can come through a subscription. Far beyond Spotify and Netflix, companies in nearly any industry, from home contractors to florists, can build subscriptions into their business.    </p>
<p>                    Subscription is the key to increasing cash flow, igniting growth and boosting the value of your company. Whether you want to transform your entire business into a recurring revenue engine or just pick up an extra 5 per cent of sales growth, The Automatic Customer will be your secret weapon.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Read, apply and watch your bank deposits grow every month&#8217;  Chris Guillebeau, bestselling author of The $100 Startup    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you have a business, or are thinking about starting one, this book will be the best investment you&#8217;ve ever made&#8217;  Bo Burlingham, editor-at-large of Inc. and author of Small Giants and Finish Big    </p>
<p>                    John Warrillow, the author of Built to Sell, is the founder of The Value Builder System (TM) where advisors help company owners increase the value of their business. Previously, he founded Warrillow &#038; Co., a subscription-based research business dedicated to helping Fortune 500 companies market to small business owners. A sought-after speaker and popular Inc.com columnist, he lives in Toronto.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-automatic-customer-creating-a-subscription-business-in-any-industry-john-warrillow-abridged/">The Automatic Customer : Creating a Subscription Business in Any Industry &#8211; John Warrillow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Scale : A Road Map to Growing Your Company &#8211; Les Mckeown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-scale-a-road-map-to-growing-your-company-les-mckeown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-scale-a-road-map-to-growing-your-company-les-mckeown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Scaling up is something most founders aspire to, especially once the tricky start-up phase has been navigated. It can increase your reach and future proof your business. But how do you scale ? And how does it differ from flipping for a quick profit or slower organic growth? Les McKeown advises industry leaders on how [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-scale-a-road-map-to-growing-your-company-les-mckeown-abridged/">Do Scale : A Road Map to Growing Your Company &#8211; Les Mckeown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Scaling up is something most founders aspire to, especially once the tricky start-up phase has been navigated. It can increase your reach and future proof your business. But how do you scale ? And how does it differ from flipping for a quick profit or slower organic growth?     </p>
<p>                    Les McKeown advises industry leaders on how to achieve scalable, sustainable growth. In Do Scale, he draws from his decades of experience to provide a clear understanding of what&#8217;s involved, and the strategies needed to take your business (or not-for-profit) to the next level. You&#8217;ll find out: What it means to scale and if now is the right time; Why founders need to get out of their own way; How to develop winning teams; Your secret weapon for decision making.     </p>
<p>                    With practical advice and clear guidance, Do Scale is an essential manual for anyone looking to grow a successful and sustainable organisation and turn it into something truly remarkable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-scale-a-road-map-to-growing-your-company-les-mckeown-abridged/">Do Scale : A Road Map to Growing Your Company &#8211; Les Mckeown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Build a thriving consultancy with the updated edition of this classic bestseller Having inspired generations of consultants and entrepreneurs around the world, the &#8220;Rock Star of Consulting&#8221; Alan Weiss returns with a revised and completely updated edition of his authoritative guide to consulting success. Weiss provides his time-tested model on creating a flourishing consulting business, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/">Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Build a thriving consultancy with the updated edition of this classic bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Having inspired generations of consultants and entrepreneurs around the world, the &#8220;Rock Star of Consulting&#8221; Alan Weiss returns with a revised and completely updated edition of his authoritative guide to consulting success.      </p>
<p>                    Weiss provides his time-tested model on creating a flourishing consulting business, while incorporating and focusing on the many dynamic changes in solo and boutique consulting, coaching, and entrepreneurship. In addition to guidance on raising capital, attracting clients, and creating a marketing plan, he also gives brand new step-by-step advice on:    </p>
<p>                    * Harnessing today&#8217;s global opportunities<br />
                    * Developing brands across markets<br />
                    * Creating and licensing intellectual property<br />
                    * Avoiding the pitfalls of social media<br />
                    * Landing unsolicited referrals through counterintuitive methods<br />
                    * Managing and organizing your time wisely<br />
                    * Succeeding in the face of continuing turbulence    </p>
<p>                    Find out why this book has been the classic go-to for consultants for nearly twenty-five years, and learn how to grow your business into a $1 million-per-year firm today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/">Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Broke : How Empty Pockets, a Tight Budget, and a Hunger for Success Can Become Your Greatest Competitive Advantage &#8211; Daymond John, Daniel Paisner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-broke-how-empty-pockets-a-tight-budget-and-a-hunger-for-success-can-become-your-greatest-competitive-advantage-daymond-john-daniel-paisner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-broke-how-empty-pockets-a-tight-budget-and-a-hunger-for-success-can-become-your-greatest-competitive-advantage-daymond-john-daniel-paisner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The instant New York Times bestseller from Shark Tank star and Fubu Founder Daymond John on why starting a business on a limited budget can be an entrepreneur&#8217;s greatest competitive advantage. Daymond John has been practicing the power of broke ever since he started selling his home-sewn t-shirts on the streets of Queens. With a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-broke-how-empty-pockets-a-tight-budget-and-a-hunger-for-success-can-become-your-greatest-competitive-advantage-daymond-john-daniel-paisner-abridged/">The Power of Broke : How Empty Pockets, a Tight Budget, and a Hunger for Success Can Become Your Greatest Competitive Advantage &#8211; Daymond John, Daniel Paisner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The instant New York Times bestseller from Shark Tank star and Fubu Founder Daymond John on why starting a business on a limited budget can be an entrepreneur&#8217;s greatest competitive advantage. Daymond John has been practicing the power of broke ever since he started selling his home-sewn t-shirts on the streets of Queens. With a $40 budget, Daymond had to strategize out-of-the-box ways to promote his products. Luckily, desperation breeds innovation, and so he hatched an idea for a creative campaign that eventually launched the FUBU brand into a $6 billion dollar global phenomenon. But it might not have happened if he hadn&#8217;t started out broke &#8211; with nothing but hope and a ferocious drive to succeed by any means possible.  Here, the FUBU founder and star of ABC&#8217;s Shark Tank shows that, far from being a liability, broke can actually be your greatest competitive advantage as an entrepreneur. Why? Because starting a business from broke forces you to think more creatively. It forces you to use your resources more efficiently. It forces you to connect with your customers more authentically, and market your ideas more imaginatively. It forces you to be true to yourself, stay laser focused on your goals, and come up with those innovative solutions required to make a meaningful mark. Drawing his own experiences as an entrepreneur and branding consultant, peeks behind-the scenes from the set of Shark Tank, and stories of dozens of other entrepreneurs who have hustled their way to wealth, John shows how we can all leverage the power of broke to phenomenal success. You&#8217;ll meet: &#8211; Steve Aoki, the electronic dance music (EDM) deejay who managed to parlay a series of $100 gigs into becoming a global superstar who has redefined the music industry<br />
                     &#8211; Gigi Butler, a cleaning lady from Nashville who built cupcake empire on the back of a family recipe, her maxed out credit cards, and a heaping dose of faith<br />
                     &#8211; 11-year old Shark Tank guest Mo Bridges who stitched together a winning clothing line with just his grandma&#8217;s sewing machine, a stash of loose fabric, and his unique sartorial flair When your back is up against the wall, your bank account is empty, and creativity and passion are the only resources you can afford, success is your only option. Here you&#8217;ll learn how to tap into that Power of Broke to scrape, hustle, and dream your way to the top.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-broke-how-empty-pockets-a-tight-budget-and-a-hunger-for-success-can-become-your-greatest-competitive-advantage-daymond-john-daniel-paisner-abridged/">The Power of Broke : How Empty Pockets, a Tight Budget, and a Hunger for Success Can Become Your Greatest Competitive Advantage &#8211; Daymond John, Daniel Paisner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
