<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sleep Disorders &amp; Therapy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sleep-disorders-therapy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sleep-disorders-therapy/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sleep Disorders &amp; Therapy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sleep-disorders-therapy/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone struggles with sleep from time to time, but when sleepless nights and overtired days become the norm, your well-being is compromised, and frustration and worry increase-including concerns about what&#8217;s stopping you from getting the sleep you need, and what can be done about it. So, how do you stop the cycle of relentless worries [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/">End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone struggles with sleep from time to time, but when sleepless nights and overtired days become the norm, your well-being is compromised, and frustration and worry increase-including concerns about what&#8217;s stopping you from getting the sleep you need, and what can be done about it. So, how do you stop the cycle of relentless worries and restless nights?    </p>
<p>                    End the Insomnia Struggle offers a comprehensive, medication-free program that can be individually tailored for anyone who struggles with insomnia. Integrating the physiology of sleep, and proven-effective approaches from cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I) and acceptance and commitment therapy (ACT), this book provides step-by-step guidance for developing your own treatment plan according to your particular challenges with insomnia.    </p>
<p>                    With this book, you&#8217;ll have everything you need to overcome the relentless thoughts, ruminations, and stress of insomnia. Utilizing these evidence-based strategies and easy-to-use tools, you&#8217;ll finally get to sleep, stay asleep, and wake up rested and ready to face the world as your best self, day after day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/">End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Can&#8217;t Sleep : Generation X Women&#8217;s New Midlife Crisis &#8211; Ada Calhoun (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-cant-sleep-generation-x-womens-new-midlife-crisis-ada-calhoun-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-cant-sleep-generation-x-womens-new-midlife-crisis-ada-calhoun-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Ada Calhoun found herself in the throes of a midlife crisis, she thought that she had no right to complain. She was married with children and a good career. So why did she feel miserable? And why did it seem that the women around her were miserable, too? Calhoun decided to find some answers. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-cant-sleep-generation-x-womens-new-midlife-crisis-ada-calhoun-abridged/">Why We Can&#8217;t Sleep : Generation X Women&#8217;s New Midlife Crisis &#8211; Ada Calhoun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Ada Calhoun found herself in the throes of a midlife crisis, she thought that she had no right to complain. She was married with children and a good career. So why did she feel miserable? And why did it seem that the women around her were miserable, too?    </p>
<p>                    Calhoun decided to find some answers. She looked into housing costs, HR trends, credit card debt averages and divorce data. At every turn, she saw a pattern: sandwiched between the Boomers and the Millennials, Gen X women were facing new problems as they entered middle age, problems that were largely overlooked. Speaking with women across America about their experiences as the generation raised to &#8216;have it all,&#8217; Calhoun found that most were exhausted, terrified about money, under-employed, and overwhelmed. Instead of being heard, they were told instead to lean in, take &#8216;me-time&#8217;, or make a chore chart to get their lives and homes in order.    </p>
<p>                    In Why We Can&#8217;t Sleep, Calhoun opens up the cultural and political contexts of this predicament and offers solutions for how to pull oneself out of the abyss-and keep the next generation of women from falling in. The result is reassuring, empowering and essential reading for all middle-aged women, and anyone who hopes to understand them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-cant-sleep-generation-x-womens-new-midlife-crisis-ada-calhoun-abridged/">Why We Can&#8217;t Sleep : Generation X Women&#8217;s New Midlife Crisis &#8211; Ada Calhoun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep & Dreams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all. Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all.    </p>
<p>                    Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising solutions for insomnia and other sleep disturbances, empowering readers to stop taking sleeping pills and enjoy the best sleep of their lives.    </p>
<p>                    Written in a clear and entertaining way, The Sleep Solution contains tips, tricks, exercises, and illustrations throughout. Dr Winter is an international expert on sleep and has helped thousands of patients &#8211; including professional athletes &#8211; rest better at night. Now, he&#8217;s ready to help you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sleep Smarter : 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to a Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success &#8211; Shawn Stevenson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your body&#8217;s natural ability to sleep soundly and learn how to boost your energy, lose weight, and improve your overall health and wellbeing. When it comes to health, there is one criminally overlooked element: sleep. Good sleep helps you shed fat for good, stave off disease, stay productive and improve virtually every function of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/">Sleep Smarter : 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to a Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success &#8211; Shawn Stevenson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your body&#8217;s natural ability to sleep soundly and learn how to boost your energy, lose weight, and improve your overall health and wellbeing.    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to health, there is one criminally overlooked element: sleep. Good sleep helps you shed fat for good, stave off disease, stay productive and improve virtually every function of your mind and body. When a degenerative bone disease crushed Shawn Stevenson&#8217;s dream of becoming a professional athlete and restricted his ability to function normally in daily life, Shawn took his health into his own hands. Through better sleep and optimized nutrition, he not only healed his body but also achieved fitness and business goals he never thought possible.    </p>
<p>                    Now in Sleep Smarter, Shawn shares easy tips and tricks to discover the best sleep and best health of your life. With a 14-Day Sleep Makeover, you&#8217;ll learn:<br />
                    &#8211; How to create the ideal sleep sanctuary<br />
                    &#8211; How to hack sunlight to regulate your circadian rhythms<br />
                    &#8211; Which clinically proven sleep nutrients and supplements you need and why<br />
                    &#8211; Stress-reduction exercises and fitness tips to keep you mentally and physically sharp&#8230; and more!    </p>
<p>                    Sleep Smarter is the much-needed guide for achieving the rest, energy and life you truly deserve.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/">Sleep Smarter : 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to a Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success &#8211; Shawn Stevenson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
