<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Monetary Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/monetary-economics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/monetary-economics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Monetary Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/monetary-economics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE MONTH FROM THE WALL STREET JOURNAL: &#8220;Nothing Mr. Gilder says or writes is ever delivered at anything less than the fullest philosophical decibel&#8230; Mr. Gilder sounds less like a tech guru than a poet, and his words tumble out in a romantic cascade.&#8221; &#8220;Google&#8217;s algorithms assume the world&#8217;s future [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/">Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE MONTH      </p>
<p>                     FROM THE WALL STREET JOURNAL: &#8220;Nothing Mr. Gilder says or writes is ever delivered at anything less than the fullest philosophical decibel&#8230; Mr. Gilder sounds less like a tech guru than a poet, and his words tumble out in a romantic cascade.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Google&#8217;s algorithms assume the world&#8217;s future is nothing more than the next moment in a random process. George Gilder shows how deep this assumption goes, what motivates people to make it, and why it&#8217;s wrong: the future depends on human action.&#8221; &#8212; Peter Thiel, founder of PayPal and Palantir Technologies and author of Zero to One: Notes on Startups, or How to Build the Future     </p>
<p>                     The Age of Google, built on big data and machine intelligence, has been an awesome era. But it&#8217;s coming to an end. In Life after Google, George Gilder&#8211;the peerless visionary of technology and culture&#8211;explains why Silicon Valley is suffering a nervous breakdown and what to expect as the post-Google age dawns.     </p>
<p>                     Google&#8217;s astonishing ability to &#8220;search and sort&#8221; attracts the entire world to its search engine and countless other goodies&#8211;videos, maps, email, calendars&#8230;.And everything it offers is free, or so it seems. Instead of paying directly, users submit to advertising. The system of &#8220;aggregate and advertise&#8221; works&#8211;for a while&#8211;if you control an empire of data centers, but a market without prices strangles entrepreneurship and turns the Internet into a wasteland of ads.     </p>
<p>                     The crisis is not just economic. Even as advances in artificial intelligence induce delusions of omnipotence and transcendence, Silicon Valley has pretty much given up on security. The Internet firewalls supposedly protecting all those passwords and personal information have proved hopelessly permeable.     </p>
<p>                     The crisis cannot be solved within the current computer and network architecture. The future lies with the &#8220;cryptocosm&#8221;&#8211;the new architecture of the blockchain and its derivatives. Enabling cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin and ether, NEO and Hashgraph, it will provide the Internet a secure global payments system, ending the aggregate-and-advertise Age of Google.     </p>
<p>                     Silicon Valley, long dominated by a few giants, faces a &#8220;great unbundling,&#8221; which will disperse computer power and commerce and transform the economy and the Internet.     </p>
<p>                     Life after Google is almost here.     </p>
<p>                     For fans of &#8220;Wealth and Poverty,&#8221; &#8220;Knowledge and Power,&#8221; and &#8220;The Scandal of Money.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/">Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge    </p>
<p>                    With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. This clear, concise, and accessible guide from two industry insiders shows you how to navigate this brave new blockchain world-and how to invest in these emerging assets to secure your financial future.    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets gives you all the tools you need:    </p>
<p>                    * An actionable framework for investigating and valuing cryptoassets     </p>
<p>                    * Portfolio management techniques to maximize returns while managing risk    </p>
<p>                    * Historical context and tips to navigate inevitable bubbles and manias    </p>
<p>                    * Practical guides to exchanges, wallets, capital market vehicles, and ICOs    </p>
<p>                    * Predictions on how blockchain technology may disrupt current portfolios    </p>
<p>                    In addition to offering smart investment strategies, this authoritative resource will help you understand how these assets were created, how they work, and how they are evolving amid the blockchain revolution. The authors define a clear and original cryptoasset taxonomy, composed of cryptocurrencies, cryptocommodities, and cryptotokens, with insights into how each subset is blending technology and markets. You&#8217;ll find a variety of methods to invest in these assets, whether through global exchanges that trade 24/7 or initial cryptoasset offerings (ICOs). By sequentially building on the concepts of each prior chapter, the book will provide you with a full understanding of the cryptoasset economy and the opportunities that await the innovative investor .    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets represent the future of money and markets. This book is your guide to that future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When to Rob a Bank : A Rogue Economist&#8217;s Guide to the World &#8211; Steven D. Levitt, Stephen J. Dubner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/when-to-rob-a-bank-a-rogue-economists-guide-to-the-world-steven-d-levitt-stephen-j-dubner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/when-to-rob-a-bank-a-rogue-economists-guide-to-the-world-steven-d-levitt-stephen-j-dubner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is the ultimate guide to the world of the Freak. Renegade thinkers and bestselling sensations Levitt and Dubner have carefully curated the very best of their blogs, conversations, wisecracks and advice from the last decade to reveal the outlandish truth about everything from lying to bankrobbing, fast food to sex taxes. &#8216;We are all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-to-rob-a-bank-a-rogue-economists-guide-to-the-world-steven-d-levitt-stephen-j-dubner-abridged/">When to Rob a Bank : A Rogue Economist&#8217;s Guide to the World &#8211; Steven D. Levitt, Stephen J. Dubner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the ultimate guide to the world of the Freak. Renegade thinkers  and bestselling sensations Levitt and Dubner have carefully curated the  very best of their blogs, conversations, wisecracks and advice from the  last decade to reveal the outlandish truth about everything from lying  to bankrobbing, fast food to sex taxes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We are all Freakonomists now&#8217; Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A phenomenon &#8230; their approach has won them a cult following&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Lie back and let Levitt and Dubner&#8217;s bouncy prose style carry you along from one peculiarity to the next&#8217; Sunday Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You are guaranteed a good time&#8217; Financial Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-to-rob-a-bank-a-rogue-economists-guide-to-the-world-steven-d-levitt-stephen-j-dubner-abridged/">When to Rob a Bank : A Rogue Economist&#8217;s Guide to the World &#8211; Steven D. Levitt, Stephen J. Dubner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age. Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award    </p>
<p>                    A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age.    </p>
<p>                    Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and engrossing history of Bitcoin, the landmark digital money and financial technology that has spawned a global social movement.    </p>
<p>                    The notion of a new currency, maintained by the computers of users around the world, has been the butt of many jokes, but that has not stopped it from growing into a technology worth billions of dollars, supported by the hordes of followers who have come to view it as the most important new idea since the creation of the Internet. Believers from Beijing to Buenos Aires see the potential for a financial system free from banks and governments. More than just a tech industry fad, Bitcoin has threatened to decentralize some of society&#8217;s most basic institutions.    </p>
<p>                    An unusual tale of group invention, Digital Gold charts the rise of the Bitcoin technology through the eyes of the movement&#8217;s colorful central characters, including an Argentinian millionaire, a Chinese entrepreneur, Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, and Bitcoin&#8217;s elusive creator, Satoshi Nakamoto. Already, Bitcoin has led to untold riches for some, and prison terms for others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, Airbnb, Kickstarter, and other innovators, and that we understand money&#8217;s transition from hard currencies to cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin if we are to access their cooperative potential.  The Evolution of Money illuminates this fascinating reality, focusing on the tension between currency&#8217;s real and abstract properties and advancing a vital theory of money rooted in this dual exchange. It begins with the debt tablets of Mesopotamia and follows with the development of coin money in ancient Greece and Rome, gold-backed currencies in medieval Europe, and monetary economics in Victorian England. The book ends in the digital era, with the cryptocurrencies and service providers that are making the most of money&#8217;s virtual side and that suggest a tectonic shift in what we call money.<br />
                    By building this organic time line, The Evolution of Money helps us anticipate money&#8217;s next, transformative role.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since its hardcover publication in August of 1995, Buffett has appeared on the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, San Francisco Chronicle, Los Angeles Times, Seattle Times, Newsday and Business Week bestseller lists. Starting from scratch, simply by picking stocks and companies for investment, Warren Buffett amassed one of the epochal fortunes of the twentieth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since its hardcover publication in August of 1995, Buffett has appeared on the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, San Francisco Chronicle, Los Angeles Times, Seattle Times, Newsday and Business Week bestseller lists. Starting from scratch, simply by picking stocks and companies for investment, Warren Buffett amassed one of the epochal fortunes of the twentieth century&#8211;an astounding net worth of $10 billion, and counting. His awesome investment record has made him a cult figure popularly known for his seeming contradictions: a billionaire who has a modest lifestyle, a phenomenally successful investor who eschews the revolving-door trading of modern Wall Street, a brilliant dealmaker who cultivates a homespun aura. Journalist Roger Lowenstein draws on three years of unprecedented access to Buffett&#8217;s family, friends, and colleagues to provide the first definitive, inside account of the life and career of this American original. Buffett explains Buffett&#8217;s investment strategy&#8211;a long-term philosophy grounded in buying stock in companies that are undervalued on the market and hanging on until their worth invariably surfaces&#8211;and shows how it is a reflection of his inner self.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Square and the Tower : Networks, Hierarchies and the Struggle for Global Power &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Silicon Valley needed a history lesson and Ferguson has provided it&#8217; Eric Schmidt Most history is about the people at the top of the towers of power. But what if the real action is in the social networks down below, in the town squares? Niall Ferguson, the international bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The Square and the Tower : Networks, Hierarchies and the Struggle for Global Power &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    &#8216;Silicon Valley needed a history lesson and Ferguson has provided it&#8217;  Eric Schmidt    </p>
<p>                    Most history is about the people at the top of the towers of power. But what if the real action is in the social networks down below, in the town squares? Niall Ferguson, the international bestselling author of Empire, The Ascent of Money and Civilization,  brilliantly recasts past and present as an unending contest between hierarchies and networks.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Provocative, snappy, a rare book &#8230; fasten your seatbelts&#8217; Peter Frankopan, Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Immensely stimulating, absorbing, illuminating &#8230; sends ideas blazing all over the place &#8230; one of the best popular historians of our time&#8217; David Goodhart, Prospect    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Powerful, fast-paced &#8230; a pull-yourself-together warning to the present by way of arresting historical precedent&#8217; Andrew Anthony, Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captivating and compelling&#8217; Jonathan A. Knee, The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The Square and the Tower : Networks, Hierarchies and the Struggle for Global Power &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Selected as a Financial Times Best Book of 2013 Governments today in both Europe and the United States have succeeded in casting government spending as reckless wastefulness that has made the economy worse. In contrast, they have advanced a policy of draconian budget cuts-austerity-to solve the financial crisis. We are told that we have all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/">Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Selected as a Financial Times Best Book of 2013    </p>
<p>                    Governments today in both Europe and the United States have succeeded in casting government spending as reckless wastefulness that has made the economy worse. In contrast, they have advanced a policy of draconian budget cuts-austerity-to solve the financial crisis. We are told that we have all lived beyond our means and now need to tighten our belts. This view conveniently forgets where all that debt came from. Not from an orgy of government spending, but as the direct result of bailing out,<br />
                    recapitalizing, and adding liquidity to the broken banking system. Through these actions private debt was rechristened as government debt while those responsible for generating it walked away scot free, placing the blame on the state, and the burden on the taxpayer.     </p>
<p>                    That burden now takes the form of a global turn to austerity, the policy of reducing domestic wages and prices to restore competitiveness and balance the budget. The problem, according to political economist Mark Blyth, is that austerity is a very dangerous idea. First of all, it doesn&#8217;t work. As the past four years and countless historical examples from the last 100 years show, while it makes sense for any one state to try and cut its way to growth, it simply cannot work when all states try it<br />
                    simultaneously: all we do is shrink the economy. In the worst case, austerity policies worsened the Great Depression and created the conditions for seizures of power by the forces responsible for the Second World War: the Nazis and the Japanese military establishment. As Blyth amply demonstrates,<br />
                    the arguments for austerity are tenuous and the evidence thin. Rather than expanding growth and opportunity, the repeated revival of this dead economic idea has almost always led to low growth along with increases in wealth and income inequality. Austerity demolishes the conventional wisdom, marshaling an army of facts to demand that we austerity for what it is, and what it costs us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/">Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When a pseudonymous programmer introduced &#8220;a new electronic cash system that&#8217;s fully peer-to-peer, with no trusted third party&#8221; to a small online mailing list in 2008, very few paid attention. Ten years later, and against all odds, this upstart autonomous decentralized software offers an unstoppable and globally-accessible hard money alternative to modern central banks. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/">The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When a pseudonymous programmer introduced &#8220;a new electronic cash system that&#8217;s fully peer-to-peer, with no trusted third party&#8221; to a small online mailing list in 2008, very few paid attention. Ten years later, and against all odds, this upstart autonomous decentralized software offers an unstoppable and globally-accessible hard money alternative to modern central banks. The Bitcoin Standard analyzes the historical context to the rise of Bitcoin, the economic properties that have allowed it to grow quickly, and its likely economic, political, and social implications.    </p>
<p>                     While Bitcoin is a new invention of the digital age, the problem it purports to solve is as old as human society itself: transferring value across time and space. Ammous takes the reader on an engaging journey through the history of technologies performing the functions of money, from primitive systems of trading limestones and seashells, to metals, coins, the gold standard, and modern government debt. Exploring what gave these technologies their monetary role, and how most lost it, provides the reader with a good idea of what makes for sound money, and sets the stage for an economic discussion of its consequences for individual and societal future-orientation, capital accumulation, trade, peace, culture, and art. Compellingly, Ammous shows that it is no coincidence that the loftiest achievements of humanity have come in societies enjoying the benefits of sound monetary regimes, nor is it coincidental that monetary collapse has usually accompanied civilizational collapse.    </p>
<p>                     With this background in place, the book moves on to explain the operation of Bitcoin in a functional and intuitive way. Bitcoin is a decentralized, distributed piece of software that converts electricity and processing power into indisputably accurate records, thus allowing its users to utilize the Internet to perform the traditional functions of money without having to rely on, or trust, any authorities or infrastructure in the physical world. Bitcoin is thus best understood as the first successfully implemented form of digital cash and digital hard money. With an automated and perfectly predictable monetary policy, and the ability to perform final settlement of large sums across the world in a matter of minutes, Bitcoin&#8217;s real competitive edge might just be as a store of value and network for final settlement of large payments-a digital form of gold with a built-in settlement infrastructure.    </p>
<p>                     Ammous&#8217; firm grasp of the technological possibilities as well as the historical realities of monetary evolution provides for a fascinating exploration of the ramifications of voluntary free market money. As it challenges the most sacred of government monopolies, Bitcoin shifts the pendulum of sovereignty away from governments in favor of individuals, offering us the tantalizing possibility of a world where money is fully extricated from politics and unrestrained by borders.    </p>
<p>                     The final chapter of the book explores some of the most common questions surrounding Bitcoin: Is Bitcoin mining a waste of energy? Is Bitcoin for criminals? Who controls Bitcoin, and can they change it if they please? How can Bitcoin be killed? And what to make of all the thousands of Bitcoin knock-offs, and the many supposed applications of Bitcoin&#8217;s &#8216;blockchain technology&#8217;? The Bitcoin Standard is the essential resource for a clear understanding of the rise of the Internet&#8217;s decentralized, apolitical, free-market alternative to national central banks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/">The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
