<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hobby and Gaming Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/hobby-and-gaming-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/hobby-and-gaming-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Hobby and Gaming Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/hobby-and-gaming-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Wonderland : How Play Made the Modern World &#8211; Steven Johnson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wonderland-how-play-made-the-modern-world-steven-johnson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hobby and Gaming Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wonderland-how-play-made-the-modern-world-steven-johnson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The book is a house of wonders&#8217; The New York Times &#8216;Steven Johnson is the Darwin of technology&#8217; Walter Issacson, author of Steve Jobs What connects Paleolithic bone flutes to the invention of computer software? Or the Murex sea snail to the death of the great American city? How does the bag of crisps you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wonderland-how-play-made-the-modern-world-steven-johnson-abridged/">Wonderland : How Play Made the Modern World &#8211; Steven Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The book is a house of wonders&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Steven Johnson is the Darwin of technology&#8217; Walter Issacson, author of Steve Jobs    </p>
<p>                    What connects Paleolithic bone flutes to the invention of computer software? Or the Murex sea snail to the death of the great American city? How does the bag of crisps you hold in your hand help tell the story of humanity itself?     </p>
<p>                    In his brilliant new work on the history of innovation, international bestseller Steven Johnson argues that the pursuit of novelty and wonder has always been a powerful driver of world-shaping technological change. He finds that  that throughout history, the cutting edge of innovation lies wherever people are working the hardest to keep themselves and others amused.     </p>
<p>                    Johnson&#8217;s storytelling is just as delightful as the inventions he describes, full of surprising stops along the journey from simple concepts to complex modern systems. He introduces us to the colourful innovators of leisure: the explorers, proprietors, showmen, and artists who changed the trajectory of history with their luxurious wares, exotic meals, taverns, gambling tables, and magic shows.    </p>
<p>                    Johnson compellingly argues that observers of technological and social trends should be looking for clues in novel amusements. You&#8217;ll find the future wherever people are having the most fun.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wonderland-how-play-made-the-modern-world-steven-johnson-abridged/">Wonderland : How Play Made the Modern World &#8211; Steven Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Building Your Business the Right-Brain Way : Sustainable Success for the Creative Entrepreneur &#8211; Jennifer Lee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/building-your-business-the-right-brain-way-sustainable-success-for-the-creative-entrepreneur-jennifer-lee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crafts & Hobbies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hobby and Gaming Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/building-your-business-the-right-brain-way-sustainable-success-for-the-creative-entrepreneur-jennifer-lee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;ve started a business, you know that the journey toward success can be both invigorating and confusing, so where can you find advice that is practical and focused but still as playful and passionate as you are? Look no further than this book, which combines solid business expertise with a right-brain perspective that inspires [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-your-business-the-right-brain-way-sustainable-success-for-the-creative-entrepreneur-jennifer-lee-abridged/">Building Your Business the Right-Brain Way : Sustainable Success for the Creative Entrepreneur &#8211; Jennifer Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;ve started a business, you know that the journey toward success can be both invigorating and confusing, so where can you find advice that is practical and focused but still as playful and passionate as you are? Look no further than this book, which combines solid business expertise with a right-brain perspective that inspires creativity and innovation. Jennifer Lee&#8217;s fresh, empowering approach emphasizes taking action and continually improving to achieve extraordinary long-term results. Building Your Business the Right-Brain Way offers real-world-tested techniques that can benefit all sorts of businesses, whether you&#8217;re a sole proprietor running a coaching practice, a crafter looking to license products, a wellness professional with a team of employees, or any creative soul making a meaningful difference with your work. You&#8217;ll discover how to: * assess your business&#8217;s unique &#8220;ecosystem&#8221;<br />
                    * build your brand and attract, engage, and keep ideal customers<br />
                    * develop new income streams that better leverage your time and resources<br />
                    * promote your products and services with authenticity and ease<br />
                    * grow your team (virtual and in-person) and manage staff and vendors<br />
                    * establish infrastructure and procedures to keep operations running smoothly<br />
                    * carve out vital white space to pause, reflect, and celebrate</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-your-business-the-right-brain-way-sustainable-success-for-the-creative-entrepreneur-jennifer-lee-abridged/">Building Your Business the Right-Brain Way : Sustainable Success for the Creative Entrepreneur &#8211; Jennifer Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
