<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ownership &amp; Organization Of Enterprises Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/ownership-organization-of-enterprises/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/ownership-organization-of-enterprises/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Ownership &amp; Organization Of Enterprises Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/ownership-organization-of-enterprises/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Help take your startup to the next step with the new and revised edition of the popular book on the VC deal process-from the co-founders of the Foundry Group How do venture capital deals come together? This is one of the most frequent questions asked by each generation of new entrepreneurs. Surprisingly, there is little [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/">Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Help take your startup to the next step with the new and revised edition of the popular book on the VC deal process-from the co-founders of the Foundry Group    </p>
<p>                     How do venture capital deals come together? This is one of the most frequent questions asked by each generation of new entrepreneurs. Surprisingly, there is little reliable information on the subject. No one understands this better than Brad Feld and Jason Mendelson. The founders and driving force behind the Foundry Group-a venture capital firm focused on investing in early-stage information technology companies-Brad and Jason have been involved in hundreds of venture capital financings. Their investments range from small startups to large Series A venture financing rounds. The new edition of Venture Deals continues to show fledgling entrepreneurs the inner-workings of the VC process, from the venture capital term sheet and effective negotiating strategies to the initial seed and the later stages of development.    </p>
<p>                     Fully updated to reflect the intricacies of startups and entrepreneurship in today&#8217;s dynamic economic environment, this new edition includes revisions and updates to coverage on negotiating, gender issues, ICO&#8217;s, and economic terms. New chapters examine legal and procedural considerations relevant to fundraising, bank debt, equity and convertible debt, how to hire an investment banker to sell a company, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Provides valuable, real-world insights into venture capital structure and strategy<br />
                    Explains and clarifies the VC term sheet and other misunderstood aspects of capital funding<br />
                    Helps to build collaborative and supportive relationships between entrepreneurs and investors<br />
                    Draws from the author&#8217;s years of practical experience in the VC arena<br />
                    Includes extensively revised and updated content throughout to increase readability and currency    </p>
<p>                     Venture Deals: Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist is a must-have resource for Any aspiring entrepreneur, venture capitalist, or lawyer involved in VC deals as well as students and instructors in related areas of study.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/">Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startup Playbook &#8211; David Kidder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/startup-playbook-david-kidder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/startup-playbook-david-kidder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Startup Playbook, Clickable CEO and NY Times best-selling author David Kidder reveals the rules and guiding principles of successful entrepreneurs, investors and CEOs. Built on some of the most dramatic success stories in today&#8217;s marketplace (Spandex, TED, etc), this is a no-nonsense guide to starting a company.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-playbook-david-kidder-abridged/">Startup Playbook &#8211; David Kidder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Startup Playbook, Clickable CEO and NY Times best-selling author David Kidder reveals the rules and guiding principles of successful entrepreneurs, investors and CEOs. Built on some of the most dramatic success stories in today&#8217;s marketplace (Spandex, TED, etc), this is a no-nonsense guide to starting a company.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-playbook-david-kidder-abridged/">Startup Playbook &#8211; David Kidder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Idea to Execution : How to Optimize, Automate, and Outsource Everything in Your Business &#8211; Nick Sonnenberg, Ari Meisel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/idea-to-execution-how-to-optimize-automate-and-outsource-everything-in-your-business-nick-sonnenberg-ari-meisel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/idea-to-execution-how-to-optimize-automate-and-outsource-everything-in-your-business-nick-sonnenberg-ari-meisel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nick Sonnenberg and Ari Meisel recently launched a profitable Virtual Assistant (VA) business in just one day &#8211; challenging the startup mentality that every new venture requires months of planning and a large investment of capital. Their VA business was born from scribbled notes on a cocktail napkin during dinner and was an up-and-running less [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/idea-to-execution-how-to-optimize-automate-and-outsource-everything-in-your-business-nick-sonnenberg-ari-meisel-abridged/">Idea to Execution : How to Optimize, Automate, and Outsource Everything in Your Business &#8211; Nick Sonnenberg, Ari Meisel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nick Sonnenberg and Ari Meisel recently launched a profitable Virtual Assistant (VA) business in just one day &#8211; challenging the startup mentality that every new venture requires months of planning and a large investment of capital. Their VA business was born from scribbled notes on a cocktail napkin during dinner and was an up-and-running less than 24 hours later. By following their 3 step process: Optimize, Automate, Outsource, they leveraged free, readily available digital tools and apps with no outlay of cash whatsoever.Meisel and Sonnenberg reveal tactics for building a scalable business in today&#8217;s world. This fascinating and informative book chronicles their first year in business together. An essential read for any entrepreneur. It follows their journey from idea to execution, detailing a bold new approach to 21st century business based on a fearless ingenuity and a willingness to rewrite the rules.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/idea-to-execution-how-to-optimize-automate-and-outsource-everything-in-your-business-nick-sonnenberg-ari-meisel-abridged/">Idea to Execution : How to Optimize, Automate, and Outsource Everything in Your Business &#8211; Nick Sonnenberg, Ari Meisel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scaling up Excellence &#8211; Hayagreeva Rao, Robert I. Sutton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/scaling-up-excellence-hayagreeva-rao-robert-i-sutton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance (QA) & Total Quality Management (TQM)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/scaling-up-excellence-hayagreeva-rao-robert-i-sutton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Scaling up excellence is the key to creating a great organisation. It&#8217;s how a small enterprise expands without losing focus. It&#8217;s how a brilliant new idea or plan developed by the few goes on to be adopted by the many. And, in hard times and tough situations, it&#8217;s how pockets of smart new thinking overcome [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scaling-up-excellence-hayagreeva-rao-robert-i-sutton-abridged/">Scaling up Excellence &#8211; Hayagreeva Rao, Robert I. Sutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Scaling up excellence is the key to creating a great organisation. It&#8217;s how a small enterprise expands without losing focus. It&#8217;s how a brilliant new idea or plan developed by the few goes on to be adopted by the many. And, in hard times and tough situations, it&#8217;s how pockets of smart new thinking overcome cultures of indifference  or negativity. An organisation that doesn&#8217;t know how to scale up what is best within it won&#8217;t achieve long-term success.     </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author Robert Sutton and his Stanford colleague Huggy Rao have devoted nearly a decade to uncovering what it takes to create and spread outstanding performance, and in Scaling Up Excellence they share the fruits of their research. Drawing on case studies that range from Silicon Valley enterprises to non-profit organisations, they provide crucial insights into corporate cultures, both good and bad, and offer a road map for establishing and stimulating excellence. In the process, they show how to use &#8216;premortems&#8217; when making big decisions about change. They reveal why seven is so often the magic number when it comes to team size. They examine successful and unsuccessful quests for improvement &#8211; in hospitals, schools and elsewhere. And they discuss when a single corporate mindset is best (&#8216;Catholicism&#8217;) and when local variation is preferable (&#8216;Buddhism&#8217;).     </p>
<p>                    Scaling Up Excellence is the first management book devoted to what is  &#8211; or should be  &#8211;  a core priority for every organisation. As such it is destined to become the standard bearer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scaling-up-excellence-hayagreeva-rao-robert-i-sutton-abridged/">Scaling up Excellence &#8211; Hayagreeva Rao, Robert I. Sutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Intel Trinity : How Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove Built the World&#8217;s Most Important Company &#8211; Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Based on unprecedented access to the corporation&#8217;s archives, The Intel Trinity is the first full history of Intel Corporation-the essential company of the digital age- told through the lives of the three most important figures in the company&#8217;s history: Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove. Often hailed the &#8220;most important company in the world,&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/">The Intel Trinity : How Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove Built the World&#8217;s Most Important Company &#8211; Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Based on unprecedented access to the corporation&#8217;s archives, The Intel Trinity is the first full history of Intel Corporation-the essential company of the digital age- told through the lives of the three most important figures in the company&#8217;s history: Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove.  Often hailed the &#8220;most important company in the world,&#8221; Intel remains, more than four decades after its inception, a defining company of the global digital economy. The legendary inventors of the microprocessor-the single most important product in the modern world-Intel today builds the tiny &#8220;engines&#8221; that power almost every intelligent electronic device on the planet.  But the true story of Intel is the human story of the trio of geniuses behind it. Michael S. Malone reveals how each brought different things to Intel, and at different times. Noyce, the most respected high tech figure of his generation, brought credibility (and money) to the company&#8217;s founding; Moore made Intel the world&#8217;s technological leader; and Grove, has relentlessly driven the company to ever-higher levels of success and competitiveness.<br />
                    Without any one of these figures, Intel would never have achieved its historic success; with them, Intel made possible the personal computer, Internet, telecommunications, and the personal electronics revolutions.  The Intel Trinity is not just the story of Intel&#8217;s legendary past; it also offers an analysis of the formidable challenges that lie ahead as the company struggles to maintain its dominance, its culture, and its legacy.  With eight pages of black-and-white photos.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/">The Intel Trinity : How Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove Built the World&#8217;s Most Important Company &#8211; Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do More Faster : Techstars Lessons to Accelerate Your Startup &#8211; Brad Feld, David G. Cohen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-more-faster-techstars-lessons-to-accelerate-your-startup-brad-feld-david-g-cohen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-more-faster-techstars-lessons-to-accelerate-your-startup-brad-feld-david-g-cohen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Refreshed, updated, and expanded. Do More Faster provides time-tested advice, tips, and experiences by founders and mentors of Techstars to help entrepreneurs succeed! David Cohen and Brad Feld, leading advocates for entrepreneurs and startups, team up to provide first-time entrepreneurs with the tools, insights, and experiences to help them do more faster. The authors share [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-more-faster-techstars-lessons-to-accelerate-your-startup-brad-feld-david-g-cohen-abridged/">Do More Faster : Techstars Lessons to Accelerate Your Startup &#8211; Brad Feld, David G. Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Refreshed, updated, and expanded. Do More Faster provides time-tested advice, tips, and experiences by founders and mentors of Techstars to help entrepreneurs succeed!    </p>
<p>                     David Cohen and Brad Feld, leading advocates for entrepreneurs and startups, team up to provide first-time entrepreneurs with the tools, insights, and experiences to help them do more faster. The authors share their decades of experience working with thousands of startup founders and have enlisted the advice of dozens of Techstars startup founders and mentors. Contributors include Tim Ferriss, Eric Ries, Matt Mullenweg (WordPress), Isaac Saldana (SendGrid), and other successful entrepreneurs.    </p>
<p>                     Co-founders of Techstars, the worldwide network that helps entrepreneurs succeed, Cohen and Feld recognize the daunting task of creating a sustainable business and have seen first-hand the common mistakes first-time entrepreneurs make over and over. The authors take the complexity and uncertainty of starting a business and distill the critical factors into seven themes: Ideas and Vision, People, Working Effectively, Product, Fundraising, Legal and Structure, and Work and Life Harmony. They share their hard-won successes, failures, and advice for anyone with an idea who wants to create a business.    </p>
<p>                     Throughout the book crucial questions are raised and addressed from multiple perspectives.    </p>
<p>                            How important is it to have an original idea?    </p>
<p>                            How is founder conflict handled?    </p>
<p>                            What are the tradeoffs between bootstrapping and financing?    </p>
<p>                     Make-or-break decisions like company structure, hiring, and legal consequences are presented in an easy-to-understand style. Do More Faster will elevate your thinking on a range of important topics, help you avoid costly mistakes, and provide you with a resource to consult as you go from idea to successful business.    </p>
<p>                     If you have the drive and desire to start a business, need to create a vibrant entrepreneurial ecosystem in your community, or want to spark greater innovation in your organization-don&#8217;t go it alone. Use the advice, tips, and tactics found throughout Do More Faster to give yourself the best chance of succeeding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-more-faster-techstars-lessons-to-accelerate-your-startup-brad-feld-david-g-cohen-abridged/">Do More Faster : Techstars Lessons to Accelerate Your Startup &#8211; Brad Feld, David G. Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fortune Cookie Principle : The 20 Keys to a Great Brand Story and Why Your Business Needs One &#8211; Bernadette Jiwa (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not how good you are. It&#8217;s how well you tell your story. Big corporations might have huge marketing and advertising budgets but you&#8217;ve got a story. Your brand story isn&#8217;t just what you tell people. It&#8217;s what they believe about you based on the signals your brand sends. The Fortune Cookie Principle is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/">The Fortune Cookie Principle : The 20 Keys to a Great Brand Story and Why Your Business Needs One &#8211; Bernadette Jiwa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not how good you are. It&#8217;s how well you tell your story. Big corporations might have huge marketing and advertising budgets but you&#8217;ve got a story. Your brand story isn&#8217;t just what you tell people. It&#8217;s what they believe about you based on the signals your brand sends. The Fortune Cookie Principle is a brand building framework and communication strategy consisting of 20 keys that enable you to begin telling your brand&#8217;s story from the inside out. It&#8217;s the foundation upon which you can differentiate your brand and make emotional connections with the kind of clients and customers you want to serve. The most successful brands in the world don&#8217;t behave like commodities and neither should you. A great brand story will make you stand out, increase brand awareness, create customer loyalty and power profits. Isn&#8217;t it time to gave your customers a story to tell? The Fortune Cookie Principle will show you how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/">The Fortune Cookie Principle : The 20 Keys to a Great Brand Story and Why Your Business Needs One &#8211; Bernadette Jiwa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Built to Last : Successful Habits of Visionary Companies &#8211; James C. Collins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/built-to-last-successful-habits-of-visionary-companies-james-c-collins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance (QA) & Total Quality Management (TQM)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/built-to-last-successful-habits-of-visionary-companies-james-c-collins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Drawing upon a six-year research project at the Stanford University Graduate School of Business, James C. Collins and Jerry I. Porras took eighteen truly exceptional and long-lasting companies and studied each in direct comparison to one of its top competitors. They examined the companies from their very beginnings to the present day &#8212; as start-ups, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/built-to-last-successful-habits-of-visionary-companies-james-c-collins-abridged/">Built to Last : Successful Habits of Visionary Companies &#8211; James C. Collins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Drawing upon a six-year research project at the Stanford University Graduate School of Business, James C. Collins and Jerry I. Porras took eighteen truly exceptional and long-lasting companies and studied each in direct comparison to one of its top competitors. They examined the companies from their very beginnings to the present day &#8212; as start-ups, as midsize companies, and as large corporations. Throughout, the authors asked: What makes the truly exceptional companies different from the comparison companies and what were the common practices these enduringly great companies followed throughout their history?     </p>
<p>                    Filled with hundreds of specific examples and organized into a coherent framework of practical concepts that can be applied by managers and entrepreneurs at all levels, Built to Last provides a master blueprint for building organizations that will prosper long into the 21st century and beyond.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/built-to-last-successful-habits-of-visionary-companies-james-c-collins-abridged/">Built to Last : Successful Habits of Visionary Companies &#8211; James C. Collins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello, My Name is Awesome : How to Create Brand Names That Stick &#8211; Alexandra Watkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The ultimate guide to naming your product or business has been updated throughout with twice as many resources as before, new stories (of both hits and flops), and an entirely new chapter on the power of names in the workplace. Too many new companies and products have names that look like the results of a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/">Hello, My Name is Awesome : How to Create Brand Names That Stick &#8211; Alexandra Watkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ultimate guide to naming your product or business has been updated throughout with twice as many resources as before, new stories (of both hits and flops), and an entirely new chapter on the power of names in the workplace.     </p>
<p>                     Too many new companies and products have names that look like the results of a drunken Scrabble game (Xobni, Svbtle, Doostang). In this entertaining and engaging book, ace-naming consultant Alexandra Watkins explains how anyone&#8211;even noncreative types&#8211;can create memorable and effective brand names. No degree in linguistics required.     </p>
<p>                     The heart of the book is Watkins&#8217;s proven SMILE and SCRATCH Test. A great name makes you SMILE because it is Suggestive&#8211;evokes something about your brand; is Memorable&#8211;makes an association with the familiar; uses Imagery&#8211;aids memory through evocative visuals; has Legs&#8211;lends itself to a theme for extended mileage; and is Emotional&#8211;moves people.     </p>
<p>                     A bad name, on the other hand, makes you SCRATCH your head because it is Spelling challenged&#8211;looks like a typo; is a Copycat&#8211;similar to competitors&#8217; names; is Restrictive&#8211;limits future growth; is Annoying&#8211;seems forced and frustrates customers; is Tame&#8211;feels flat, merely descriptive, and uninspired; suffers from the Curse of Knowledge&#8211;speaks only to insiders; and is Hard to pronounce&#8211;confuses and distances customers.     </p>
<p>                     This 50 percent-new second edition has double the number of brainstorming tools and techniques, even more secrets and strategies to nab an available domain name, a brand-new chapter on how companies are using creative names around the office to add personality to everything from cafeterias to conference rooms, and much more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/">Hello, My Name is Awesome : How to Create Brand Names That Stick &#8211; Alexandra Watkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New to Big : How Companies Can Create Like Entrepreneurs, Invest Like VCs, and Install a Permanent Operating System for Growth &#8211; David Kidder, Christina Wallace (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/new-to-big-how-companies-can-create-like-entrepreneurs-invest-like-vcs-and-install-a-permanent-operating-system-for-growth-david-kidder-christina-wallace-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/new-to-big-how-companies-can-create-like-entrepreneurs-invest-like-vcs-and-install-a-permanent-operating-system-for-growth-david-kidder-christina-wallace-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Serial entrepreneurs David Kidder and Christina Wallace reveal their revolutionary playbook for igniting growth inside established companies. Most established companies face a key survival challenge, says David Kidder, CEO of Bionic, lifelong entrepreneur, and angel investor in more than thirty startups: operational efficiency and outdated bureaucracy are at war with new growth. Legacy companies are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-to-big-how-companies-can-create-like-entrepreneurs-invest-like-vcs-and-install-a-permanent-operating-system-for-growth-david-kidder-christina-wallace-abridged/">New to Big : How Companies Can Create Like Entrepreneurs, Invest Like VCs, and Install a Permanent Operating System for Growth &#8211; David Kidder, Christina Wallace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Serial entrepreneurs David Kidder and Christina Wallace reveal their revolutionary playbook for igniting growth inside established companies.     </p>
<p>                    Most established companies face a key survival challenge, says David Kidder, CEO of Bionic, lifelong entrepreneur, and angel investor in more than thirty startups: operational efficiency and outdated bureaucracy are at war with new growth. Legacy companies are skilled at growing big businesses into even bigger ones. But they are less adept at discovering new opportunities and turning them into big businesses, the way entrepreneurs and early-stage investors must. In New to Big, Kidder and Wallace reveal their proprietary blueprint for installing a permanent growth capability inside any company&#8211;the Growth Operating System.     </p>
<p>                    The Growth OS borrows the best tools, systems, and mind-sets from entrepreneurship and venture capital and adapts them for established organizations, leveraging these two distinct skills as a form of management for building in a future that is uncertain. By focusing on what consumers do rather than what they say, celebrating productive failure, embracing a portfolio approach, and learning from the outside-in, Kidder and Wallace argue any company can go on offense and win the future.     </p>
<p>                    This isn&#8217;t about a one-off innovation moonshot. It&#8217;s about building a permanent ladder to the moon.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-to-big-how-companies-can-create-like-entrepreneurs-invest-like-vcs-and-install-a-permanent-operating-system-for-growth-david-kidder-christina-wallace-abridged/">New to Big : How Companies Can Create Like Entrepreneurs, Invest Like VCs, and Install a Permanent Operating System for Growth &#8211; David Kidder, Christina Wallace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value. Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value.    </p>
<p>                     Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this revolution and provides the first &#8220;owner&#8217;s manual&#8221; for creating a platform marketplace. It provides the essential guide to unlocking the potential of an economic landscape transformed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Purpose : The Starting Point of Great Companies &#8211; Nikos Mourkogiannis, Foreword by Roger Fisher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/purpose-the-starting-point-of-great-companies-nikos-mourkogiannis-foreword-by-roger-fisher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/purpose-the-starting-point-of-great-companies-nikos-mourkogiannis-foreword-by-roger-fisher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Purpose, world-renowned thought leader Nikos Mourkogiannis turns the entire idea of leadership on its head and shows that the choice between values and success is no choice at all. Mourkogiannis argues that companies must satisfy the need for purpose &#8211; a set of values that defines an organization and inspires and motivates its employees. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purpose-the-starting-point-of-great-companies-nikos-mourkogiannis-foreword-by-roger-fisher-abridged/">Purpose : The Starting Point of Great Companies &#8211; Nikos Mourkogiannis, Foreword by Roger Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Purpose, world-renowned thought leader Nikos Mourkogiannis turns the entire idea of leadership on its head and shows that the choice between values and success is no choice at all. Mourkogiannis argues that companies must satisfy the need for purpose &#8211; a set of values that defines an organization and inspires and motivates its employees. Rather than organization and structure, ideas are what cause companies to go from good to great. Drawing on examples from across multiple industries, Mourkogiannis demonstrates how a strong purpose is the essential first step toward lasting success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purpose-the-starting-point-of-great-companies-nikos-mourkogiannis-foreword-by-roger-fisher-abridged/">Purpose : The Starting Point of Great Companies &#8211; Nikos Mourkogiannis, Foreword by Roger Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crossing the Chasm, 3rd Edition : Marketing and Selling Disruptive Products to Mainstream Customers &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bible for bringing cutting-edge products to larger markets&#8211;now revised and updated with new insights into the realities of high-tech marketing In Crossing the Chasm, Geoffrey A. Moore shows that in the Technology Adoption Life Cycle&#8211;which begins with innovators and moves to early adopters, early majority, late majority, and laggards&#8211;there is a vast chasm between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/">Crossing the Chasm, 3rd Edition : Marketing and Selling Disruptive Products to Mainstream Customers &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bible for bringing cutting-edge products to larger markets&#8211;now revised and updated with new insights into the realities of high-tech marketing    </p>
<p>                    In Crossing the Chasm, Geoffrey A. Moore shows that in the Technology Adoption Life Cycle&#8211;which begins with innovators and moves to early adopters, early majority, late majority, and laggards&#8211;there is a vast chasm between the early adopters and the early majority. While early adopters are willing to sacrifice for the advantage of being first, the early majority waits until they know that the technology actually offers improvements in productivity. The challenge for innovators and marketers is to narrow this chasm and ultimately accelerate adoption across every segment.     </p>
<p>                    This third edition brings Moore&#8217;s classic work up to date with dozens of new examples of successes and failures, new strategies for marketing in the digital world, and Moore&#8217;s most current insights and findings. He also includes two new appendices, the first connecting the ideas in Crossing the Chasm to work subsequently published in his Inside the Tornado, and the second presenting his recent groundbreaking work for technology adoption models for high-tech consumer markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/">Crossing the Chasm, 3rd Edition : Marketing and Selling Disruptive Products to Mainstream Customers &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rebel Rules : Daring to be Yourself in Business &#8211; Chip Conley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rebel-rules-daring-to-be-yourself-in-business-chip-conley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rebel-rules-daring-to-be-yourself-in-business-chip-conley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When he was 26, Chip Conley broke the two cardinal rules of starting a business: he invested in an industry about which he knew nothing and he ignored the mantra location, location, location. He bought a notorious pay-by-the-hour motel in a seedy San Francisco neighborhood. A dozen years later, Chip is the boy wonder of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rebel-rules-daring-to-be-yourself-in-business-chip-conley-abridged/">The Rebel Rules : Daring to be Yourself in Business &#8211; Chip Conley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When he was 26, Chip Conley broke the two cardinal rules of starting a business: he invested in an industry about which he knew nothing and he ignored the mantra location, location, location. He bought a notorious pay-by-the-hour motel in a seedy San Francisco neighborhood.<br />
                     A dozen years later, Chip is the boy wonder of the American travel industry, famous for his entrepreneurial genius, creativity, and sense of fun.<br />
                     In The Rebel Rules,  Conley shares his success secrets. He focuses on the primary traits &#8212; vision, passion, instinct, and agility &#8212; that characterize today&#8217;s fast company leaders. His guidebook doubles as a toolbox for anyone &#8212; whether a virgin entrepreneur or a corporate manager &#8212; who wants to walk in step with today&#8217;s business innovators.<br />
                     The Rebel Rules will show you how to:<br />
                      Tap into your natural talents and focus on what you can control<br />
                     Build a fanatical customer base and create great buzz<br />
                     Engage employees and encourage them to break the rules<br />
                     Kick butt in business and still have a life    </p>
<p>                     With exercises and activities that will develop these and other business skills, The Rebel Rules will transform the way you approach your career.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rebel-rules-daring-to-be-yourself-in-business-chip-conley-abridged/">The Rebel Rules : Daring to be Yourself in Business &#8211; Chip Conley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job : How to Dump Your Boss, Build a Business and Not Go Broke &#8211; Scott Gerber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/never-get-a-real-job-how-to-dump-your-boss-build-a-business-and-not-go-broke-scott-gerber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/never-get-a-real-job-how-to-dump-your-boss-build-a-business-and-not-go-broke-scott-gerber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Young serial entrepreneur Scott Gerber is not the product of a wealthy family or storied entrepreneurial heritage. Nor is he the outcome of a traditional business school education or a corporate executive turned entrepreneur. Rather, he is a hard-working, self-taught 26-year-old hustler, rainmaker, and bootstrapper who has survived and thrived despite never having held the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-get-a-real-job-how-to-dump-your-boss-build-a-business-and-not-go-broke-scott-gerber-abridged/">Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job : How to Dump Your Boss, Build a Business and Not Go Broke &#8211; Scott Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Young serial entrepreneur Scott Gerber is not the product of a wealthy family or storied entrepreneurial heritage. Nor is he the outcome of a traditional business school education or a corporate executive turned entrepreneur. Rather, he is a hard-working, self-taught 26-year-old hustler, rainmaker, and bootstrapper who has survived and thrived despite never having held the proverbial &#8220;real job. In  Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job: How to Dump Your Boss, Build a Business, and Not Go Broke, Gerber challenges the social conventions behind the &#8220;real&#8221; job and empowers young people to take control of their lives and dump their nine-to-fives or their quest to attain them. Drawing upon case studies, experiences, and observations, Scott dissects failures, shares hard-learned lessons, and presents practical, affordable, and systematic action steps to building, managing, and marketing a successful business on a shoestring budget. The proven, no-b.s. methodology presented in  Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job teaches unemployed and underemployed Gen-Yers, aspiring small business owners, students, and recent college graduates how to quit 9-to-5s, become their own bosses, and achieve financial independence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-get-a-real-job-how-to-dump-your-boss-build-a-business-and-not-go-broke-scott-gerber-abridged/">Never Get a &#8220;Real&#8221; Job : How to Dump Your Boss, Build a Business and Not Go Broke &#8211; Scott Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Side Hustle : Build a Side Business and Make Extra Money &#8211; Without Quitting Your Day Job &#8211; Chris Guillebeau (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/side-hustle-build-a-side-business-and-make-extra-money-without-quitting-your-day-job-chris-guillebeau-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/side-hustle-build-a-side-business-and-make-extra-money-without-quitting-your-day-job-chris-guillebeau-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of $100 Startup comes this accessible guide to building a side business from scratch &#8211; without having to give up your day job. Side Hustle is about much more than just making some extra cash; it&#8217;s about freedom and job security in today&#8217;s unstable business environment. That&#8217;s because [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/side-hustle-build-a-side-business-and-make-extra-money-without-quitting-your-day-job-chris-guillebeau-abridged/">Side Hustle : Build a Side Business and Make Extra Money &#8211; Without Quitting Your Day Job &#8211; Chris Guillebeau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of $100 Startup comes this accessible guide to building a side business from scratch &#8211; without having to give up your day job.    </p>
<p>                    Side Hustle is about much more than just making some extra cash; it&#8217;s about freedom and job security in today&#8217;s unstable business environment. That&#8217;s because when you receive income from multiple different sources, you are no longer dependent on the whims of a single employer. It affords you choices and options.    </p>
<p>                    In the style of $100 Startup, full of practical exercises and peppered with inspiring stories, Chris Guillebeau&#8217;s Side Hustle shows readers how to brainstorm, choose, implement, launch and refine their side business in just 27 days &#8211; with little to no budget and without having to quit their current job.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/side-hustle-build-a-side-business-and-make-extra-money-without-quitting-your-day-job-chris-guillebeau-abridged/">Side Hustle : Build a Side Business and Make Extra Money &#8211; Without Quitting Your Day Job &#8211; Chris Guillebeau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disrupted : Ludicrous Misadventures in the Tech Start-up Bubble &#8211; Dan Lyons (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dan Lyons was Technology Editor at Newsweek Magazine for years, a magazine writer at the top of his profession. One Friday morning he received a phone call: his job no longer existed. Fifty years old and with a wife and two young kids, Dan was unemployed and facing financial oblivion. Then an idea hit. Dan [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/">Disrupted : Ludicrous Misadventures in the Tech Start-up Bubble &#8211; Dan Lyons (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dan Lyons was Technology Editor at Newsweek Magazine for years, a magazine writer at the top of his profession. One Friday morning he received a phone call: his job no longer existed. Fifty years old and with a wife and two young kids, Dan was unemployed and facing financial oblivion. Then an idea hit. Dan had long reported on Silicon Valley and the tech explosion. Why not join it? HubSpot, a Boston start-up, was flush with $100 million in venture capital. They offered Dan a pile of stock options for the nebulous role of &#8220;marketing fellow.&#8221; What could possibly go wrong?     </p>
<p>                     What follows is a hilarious and excoriating account of Dan&#8217;s time at the start-up and a revealing window onto the dysfunctional culture that prevails in a world flush with cash and devoid of experience. Filled with stories of meaningless jargon, teddy bears at meetings, push-up competitions and all-night parties, this uproarious tale is also a trenchant analysis of the dysfunctional start-up world, a de facto conspiracy between those who start companies and those who fund them. It is a world where bad ideas are rewarded with hefty investments, where companies blow money lavishing perks on their post-collegiate workforces, and where everybody is trying to hang on just long enough to cash out with a fortune.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/">Disrupted : Ludicrous Misadventures in the Tech Start-up Bubble &#8211; Dan Lyons (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Mathematics & Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Engineering: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How do today&#8217;s most successful tech companies-Amazon, Google, Facebook, Netflix, Tesla-design, develop, and deploy the products that have earned the love of literally billions of people around the world? Perhaps surprisingly, they do it very differently than most tech companies. In INSPIRED, technology product management thought leader Marty Cagan provides readers with a master class [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/">Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do today&#8217;s most successful tech companies-Amazon, Google, Facebook, Netflix, Tesla-design, develop, and deploy the products that have earned the love of literally billions of people around the world?    </p>
<p>                     Perhaps surprisingly, they do it very differently than most tech companies.    </p>
<p>                     In INSPIRED, technology product management thought leader Marty Cagan provides readers with a master class in how to structure and staff a vibrant and successful product organization, and how to discover and deliver technology products that your customers will love-and that will work for your business.    </p>
<p>                     With sections on assembling the right people and skillsets, discovering the right product, embracing an effective yet lightweight process, and creating a strong product culture, readers can take the information they learn and immediately leverage it within their own organizations-dramatically improving their own product efforts.    </p>
<p>                     Whether you&#8217;re an early stage startup working to get to product/market fit, or a growth-stage company working to scale your product organization, or a large, long-established company trying to regain your ability to consistently deliver new value for your customers, INSPIRED will take you and your product organization to a new level of customer engagement, consistent innovation, and business success.    </p>
<p>                     Filled with the author&#8217;s own personal stories-and profiles of some of today&#8217;s most-successful product managers and technology-powered product companies, including Adobe, Apple, BBC, Google, Microsoft, and Netflix-INSPIRED will show you how to turn up the dial of your own product efforts, creating technology products your customers love.    </p>
<p>                     The first edition of INSPIRED, published ten years ago, established itself as the primary reference for technology product managers, and can be found on the shelves of nearly every successful technology product company worldwide. This thoroughly updated second edition shares the same objective of being the most valuable resource for technology product managers, yet it is completely new-sharing the latest practices and techniques of today&#8217;s most-successful tech product companies, and the men and women behind every great product.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/">Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Four Steps to the Epiphany : Successful Strategies for Products that Win &#8211; Steve Blank (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling classic that launched 10,000 startups and new corporate ventures &#8211; The Four Steps to the Epiphany is one of the most influential and practical business books of all time. The Four Steps to the Epiphany launched the Lean Startup approach to new ventures. It was the first book to offer that startups are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/">The Four Steps to the Epiphany : Successful Strategies for Products that Win &#8211; Steve Blank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling classic that launched 10,000 startups and new corporate ventures &#8211; The Four Steps to the Epiphany is one of the most influential and practical business books of all time.<br />
                    The Four Steps to the Epiphany launched the Lean Startup approach to new ventures. It was the first book to offer that startups are not smaller versions of large companies and that new ventures are different than existing ones. Startups search for business models while existing companies execute them.    </p>
<p>                    The book offers the practical and proven four-step Customer Development process for search and offers insight into what makes some startups successful and leaves others selling off their furniture.<br />
                    Rather than blindly execute a plan, The Four Steps helps uncover flaws in product and business plans and correct them before they become costly. Rapid iteration, customer feedback, testing your assumptions are all explained in this book.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with concrete examples of what to do, how to do it and when to do it, the book will leave you with new skills to organize sales, marketing and your business for success.<br />
                    If your organization is starting a new venture, and you&#8217;re thinking how to successfully organize sales, marketing and business development you need The Four Steps to the Epiphany.<br />
                    Essential reading for anyone starting something new.     </p>
<p>                     The Four Steps to the Epiphany  was originally published by K&#038;S Ranch Publishing Inc. and is now available from Wiley. The cover, design, and content are the same as the prior release and should not be considered a new or updated product.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/">The Four Steps to the Epiphany : Successful Strategies for Products that Win &#8211; Steve Blank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital When you connect with the right angel [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital    </p>
<p>                    When you connect with the right angel investor, it&#8217;s like finding a new best friend&#8211;you just have to know what makes him or her happy.    </p>
<p>                    Smart funding is waiting for smart founders. Raising funds is all about connecting with the investor who&#8217;s right for you&#8211;and What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know shows you exactly how to succeed.    </p>
<p>                    Veteran early-stage investor Brian Cohen knows how to spot a great company destined for success, and in this groundbreaking book he offers soup-to-nuts guidance for anyentrepreneur seeking to launch an invention, a product, or a great new idea into a receptive marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    As chairman of the board of directors of the New York Angels, Cohen is one of the most engaged angel investors out there today. The first investor in Pinterest, he describes exactly what angels want to see, hear, and feelbefore they take out their checkbooks:    </p>
<p>                    A clear exit strategy before the startup even launchesFacts that turn &#8220;due&#8221; diligence into &#8220;do&#8221; diligenceAuthenticity&#8211;&#8220;save your spinning for the fitness center&#8221;Proof that you &#8220;live inside the customer&#8217;s head&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Cohen gives invaluable insight into how the most successful angels view due diligence, friends and family money, crowdfunding, team building, scalability, iteration, exit strategies&#8211;and much more.    </p>
<p>                    This one-of-a-kind book provides a rare look inside the minds of people who are in the business of funding businesses just like yours.    </p>
<p>                    Read What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know to get your best shot at funding for your product after your very first pitch.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR WHAT EVERY ANGEL INVESTOR WANTS YOU TO KNOW:&#8221;Brian Cohen is truly the entrepreneur&#8217;s best friend. Cohen and Kador haven distilled their first-hand experiences into an intensely personal, highly readablejourney into the mind of angels that should be kept at the bedside of every startup CEO.&#8221; &#8212; DAVID S. ROSE, founder, New York Angels, and CEO, Gust    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Meet one of the fundamental building blocks of the entrepreneurial scene. In one easy-to-read package, readers now have the wisdom of Brian Cohen, perhaps themost well-connected investor/entrepreneur in New York.&#8221; &#8212; MURAT AKTIHANOGLU, founder and managing director, Entrepreneurs Roundtable Accelerator    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know gives you an actionable checklist for success in fund-raising and entrepreneurship. Cohen and Kador provide anexhilarating ride for those who want to pilot their own business.&#8221; &#8212; REED HOLDEN, serial entrepreneur and author of Negotiating with Backbone    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Personal insights from a seasoned angel investor. An important addition to the reading list for today&#8217;s entrepreneurs.&#8221; &#8212; SCOTT CASE, CEO, Startup America Partnership    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know is a must-read for entrepreneurs and investors who want to fi nance startup dreams&#8211;an accessible, jargon-free,practical primer.&#8221; &#8212; WHITNEY JOHNSON, author of Dare, Dream, Do: Remarkable Things Happen When You Dare to Dream and cofounder, Rose Park Advisors    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;While [this] book is anecdotal, [the authors] discuss in depth how angels view a potential investment as well as how they evaluate its prospects. This is the book&#8217;s strength. Recommended. All levels of students, entrepreneurs, practitioners.&#8221; &#8212; CHOICE</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zone to Win : Organizing to Compete in an Age of Disruption &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zone-to-win-organizing-to-compete-in-an-age-of-disruption-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zone-to-win-organizing-to-compete-in-an-age-of-disruption-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the last 25 years, Geoffrey Moore has established himself as one of the most influential high-tech advisors in the world-once prompting Conan O&#8217;Brien to ask &#8220;Who is Geoffrey Moore and why is he more famous than me?&#8221; Following up on the ferociously innovative ESCAPE VELOCITY, which served as the basis for Moore&#8217;s consulting work [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zone-to-win-organizing-to-compete-in-an-age-of-disruption-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/">Zone to Win : Organizing to Compete in an Age of Disruption &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over the last 25 years, Geoffrey Moore has established himself as one of the most influential high-tech advisors in the world-once prompting Conan O&#8217;Brien to ask &#8220;Who is Geoffrey Moore and why is he more famous than me?&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Following up on the ferociously innovative ESCAPE VELOCITY, which served as the basis for Moore&#8217;s consulting work to such companies as Salesforce, Microsoft, and Intel, ZONE TO WIN serves as the companion playbook for his landmark guide, offering a practical manual to address the challenge large enterprises face when they seek to add a new line of business to their established portfolio. Focused on spurring next-generation growth, guiding mergers and acquisitions, and embracing disruption and innovation, ZONE TO WIN is a high-powered tool for driving your company above and beyond its limitations, its definitions of success, and ultimately, its competitors.    </p>
<p>                    Moore&#8217;s classic bestseller, CROSSING THE CHASM, has sold more than one million copies by addressing the challenges faced by start-up companies. Now ZONE TO WIN is set to guide established enterprises through the same journey.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;For any company, regardless of size or industry, ZONE TO WIN is the playbook for succeeding in today&#8217;s disruptive, connected, fast-paced business world.&#8221; -Marc Benioff, CEO, Salesforce    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Once again Geoffrey Moore weighs in with a prescient examination of what it takes to win in today&#8217;s competitive, disruptive business environment.&#8221; -Satya Nadella, CEO, Microsoft    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;With this book, Geoffrey Moore continues to lead us all through ever-changing times&#8230;His work has changed the game of changing the game!&#8221; -Gary Kovacs, CEO, AVG    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;ZONE TO WIN uses crystal-clear language to describe the management plays necessary to win in an ever-disrupting marketplace. Regardless of your level of management experience, you will find this book an invaluable tool for building long-term success for your business.&#8221; -Lip-Bu Tan, President and CEO, Cadence Design Systems</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zone-to-win-organizing-to-compete-in-an-age-of-disruption-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/">Zone to Win : Organizing to Compete in an Age of Disruption &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How the Mighty Fall : And Why Some Companies Never Give in &#8211; Jim Collins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-the-mighty-fall-and-why-some-companies-never-give-in-jim-collins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-the-mighty-fall-and-why-some-companies-never-give-in-jim-collins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Decline can be avoided. Decline can be detected. Decline can be reversed. Amidst the desolate landscape of fallen great companies, Jim Collins began to wonder: How do the mighty fall? Can decline be detected early and avoided? How far can a company fall before the path toward doom becomes inevitable and unshakable? How can companies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-the-mighty-fall-and-why-some-companies-never-give-in-jim-collins-abridged/">How the Mighty Fall : And Why Some Companies Never Give in &#8211; Jim Collins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decline can be avoided.     </p>
<p>                    Decline can be detected.     </p>
<p>                    Decline can be reversed.     </p>
<p>                    Amidst the desolate landscape of fallen great companies, Jim Collins began to wonder: How do the mighty fall? Can decline be detected early and avoided? How far can a company fall before the path toward doom becomes inevitable and unshakable? How can companies reverse course?     </p>
<p>                    In How the Mighty Fall, Collins confronts these questions, offering leaders the well-founded hope that they can learn how to stave off decline and, if they find themselves falling, reverse their course. Collins&#8217; research project&#8211;more than four years in duration&#8211;uncovered five step-wise stages of decline:     </p>
<p>                    Stage 1: Hubris Born of Success     </p>
<p>                    Stage 2: Undisciplined Pursuit of More     </p>
<p>                    Stage 3: Denial of Risk and Peril     </p>
<p>                    Stage 4: Grasping for Salvation     </p>
<p>                    Stage 5: Capitulation to Irrelevance or Death     </p>
<p>                    By understanding these stages of decline, leaders can substantially reduce their chances of falling all the way to the bottom.     </p>
<p>                    Great companies can stumble, badly, and recover.     </p>
<p>                    Every institution, no matter how great, is vulnerable to decline. There is no law of nature that the most powerful will inevitably remain at the top. Anyone can fall and most eventually do. But, as Collins&#8217; research emphasizes, some companies do indeed recover&#8211;in some cases, coming back even stronger&#8211;even after having crashed into the depths of Stage 4.     </p>
<p>                    Decline, it turns out, is largely self-inflicted, and the path to recovery lies largely within our own hands. We are not imprisoned by our circumstances, our history, or even our staggering defeats along the way. As long as we never get entirely knocked out of the game, hope always remains. The mighty can fall, but they can often rise again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-the-mighty-fall-and-why-some-companies-never-give-in-jim-collins-abridged/">How the Mighty Fall : And Why Some Companies Never Give in &#8211; Jim Collins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With must-have updates, a new edition of the bestselling method that shows how anyone can turn their one simple idea into millions &#8211; without lifting a finger! Stephen Key is an award-winning inventor who has licensed more than 20 product ideas. In 2011, he shared the secrets to his success in the bestselling book One [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/">One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With must-have updates, a new edition of the bestselling method that shows how anyone can turn their one simple idea into millions &#8211; without lifting a finger!    </p>
<p>                     Stephen Key is an award-winning inventor who has licensed more than 20 product ideas. In 2011, he shared the secrets to his success in the bestselling book One Simple Idea. Since that time, many changes have occurred in the entrepreneurial world.    </p>
<p>                    One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition has been revised and updated to reflect current trends and practices in the industry. In addition to teaching readers how to turn their ideas into marketable products that companies will want to license, Key expands upon his cutting-edge product development, sales, and negotiation strategies, making note of the new opportunities and technologies available to creative people today. The book also features real-life success stories from people who have used the author&#8217;s strategies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/">One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mom Test : How to talk to customers &#038; learn if your business is a good idea when everyone is lying to you &#8211; Rob Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-mom-test-how-to-talk-to-customers-learn-if-your-business-is-a-good-idea-when-everyone-is-lying-to-you-rob-fitzpatrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mom-test-how-to-talk-to-customers-learn-if-your-business-is-a-good-idea-when-everyone-is-lying-to-you-rob-fitzpatrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Mom Test is a quick, practical guide that will save you time, money, and heartbreak. They say you shouldn&#8217;t ask your mom whether your business is a good idea, because she loves you and will lie to you. This is technically true, but it misses the point. You shouldn&#8217;t ask anyone if your business [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mom-test-how-to-talk-to-customers-learn-if-your-business-is-a-good-idea-when-everyone-is-lying-to-you-rob-fitzpatrick-abridged/">The Mom Test : How to talk to customers &#038; learn if your business is a good idea when everyone is lying to you &#8211; Rob Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Mom Test is a quick, practical guide that will save you time, money, and heartbreak.    </p>
<p>                    They say you shouldn&#8217;t ask your mom whether your business is a good idea, because she loves you and will lie to you. This is technically true, but it misses the point. You shouldn&#8217;t ask anyone  if your business is a good idea. It&#8217;s a bad question and everyone will lie to you at least a little . As a matter of fact, it&#8217;s not their responsibility to tell you the truth. It&#8217;s your responsibility to find it and it&#8217;s worth doing right .    </p>
<p>                    Talking to customers is one of the foundational skills of both Customer Development and Lean Startup. We all know we&#8217;re supposed to do it, but nobody seems willing to admit that it&#8217;s easy to screw up and hard to do right. This book is going to show you how customer conversations go wrong and how you can do better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mom-test-how-to-talk-to-customers-learn-if-your-business-is-a-good-idea-when-everyone-is-lying-to-you-rob-fitzpatrick-abridged/">The Mom Test : How to talk to customers &#038; learn if your business is a good idea when everyone is lying to you &#8211; Rob Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fixer : My Adventures Saving Startups from Death by Politics &#8211; Bradley Tusk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Service & Public Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The famed political advisor to Uber, FanDuel, Lemonade, Tesla and other startups reveals what really happens at the intersection of politics, tech and business Most new startups today are in highly regulated industries with strong incumbents &#8211; transportation, hotels, drones, energy, gaming, education, health care, cannabis, finance, liquor, insurance. The more startups try to snatch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/">The Fixer : My Adventures Saving Startups from Death by Politics &#8211; Bradley Tusk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The famed political advisor to Uber, FanDuel, Lemonade, Tesla and other startups reveals what really happens at the intersection of politics, tech and business Most new startups today are in highly regulated industries with strong incumbents &#8211; transportation, hotels, drones, energy, gaming, education, health care, cannabis, finance, liquor, insurance. The more startups try to snatch a piece of the establishment&#8217;s pie, the more they risk running into a political wall. That&#8217;s where Bradley Tusk comes in. Described as Silicon Valley&#8217;s Political Savior (Fast Company) Uber&#8217;s Political Genius (Vanity Fair) and Silicon Valley&#8217;s Favorite Fixer (TechCrunch) Tusk deploys the skills and knowledge he developed working with Chuck Schumer, Michael Bloomberg, Rod Blagojevich, and other political and business legends to help startups fight back. This book goes behind the scenes on how he helped stop the taxi industry from killing Uber in its infancy, how he held insurance companies at bay while startup Lemonade launched in each state, and how he helped online sports betting sites FanDuel and Draft Kings escape the regulatory death grip casinos tried to put on them. As Tusk writes, Every new company is essentially a tech startup. And when you disrupt someone in any industry, they don&#8217;t say thank you. They punch you in the nose. These are the lessons startups need to learn to punch back and survive the clutches of politics. Combining a firsthand glimpse behind the curtain with tangible advice for how any new venture can play the political game, THE FIXER is a must-read for aspiring entrepreneurs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fixer-my-adventures-saving-startups-from-death-by-politics-bradley-tusk-abridged/">The Fixer : My Adventures Saving Startups from Death by Politics &#8211; Bradley Tusk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Founder&#8217;s Dilemmas : Anticipating and Avoiding the Pitfalls That Can Sink a Startup &#8211; Noam Wasserman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-founders-dilemmas-anticipating-and-avoiding-the-pitfalls-that-can-sink-a-startup-noam-wasserman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-founders-dilemmas-anticipating-and-avoiding-the-pitfalls-that-can-sink-a-startup-noam-wasserman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Often downplayed in the excitement of starting up a new business venture is one of the most important decisions entrepreneurs will face: should they go it alone, or bring in cofounders, hires, and investors to help build the business? More than just financial rewards are at stake. Friendships and relationships can suffer. Bad decisions at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-founders-dilemmas-anticipating-and-avoiding-the-pitfalls-that-can-sink-a-startup-noam-wasserman-abridged/">The Founder&#8217;s Dilemmas : Anticipating and Avoiding the Pitfalls That Can Sink a Startup &#8211; Noam Wasserman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Often downplayed in the excitement of starting up a new business venture is one of the most important decisions entrepreneurs will face: should they go it alone, or bring in cofounders, hires, and investors to help build the business? More than just financial rewards are at stake. Friendships and relationships can suffer. Bad decisions at the inception of a promising venture lay the foundations for its eventual ruin. The Founder&#8217;s Dilemmas is the first book to examine the early decisions by entrepreneurs that can make or break a startup and its team. Drawing on a decade of research, Noam Wasserman reveals the common pitfalls founders face and how to avoid them. He looks at whether it is a good idea to cofound with friends or relatives, how and when to split the equity within the founding team, and how to recognize when a successful founder-CEO should exit or be fired. Wasserman explains how to anticipate, avoid, or recover from disastrous mistakes that can splinter a founding team, strip founders of control, and leave founders without a financial payoff for their hard work and innovative ideas.<br />
                    He highlights the need at each step to strike a careful balance between controlling the startup and attracting the best resources to grow it, and demonstrates why the easy short-term choice is often the most perilous in the long term. The Founder&#8217;s Dilemmas draws on the inside stories of founders like Evan Williams of Twitter and Tim Westergren of Pandora, while mining quantitative data on almost ten thousand founders. People problems are the leading cause of failure in startups. This book offers solutions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-founders-dilemmas-anticipating-and-avoiding-the-pitfalls-that-can-sink-a-startup-noam-wasserman-abridged/">The Founder&#8217;s Dilemmas : Anticipating and Avoiding the Pitfalls That Can Sink a Startup &#8211; Noam Wasserman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Measure : The Big Impact of Small Changes &#8211; Margaret Heffernan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-measure-the-big-impact-of-small-changes-margaret-heffernan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-measure-the-big-impact-of-small-changes-margaret-heffernan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A powerful manifesto for CEOs and employees alike: Influential and award-winning business leader Margaret Heffernan reveals how organizations can build ideal workplace cultures and create seismic shifts by making deceptively small changes. By implementing sweeping changes, businesses often think it&#8217;s possible to do better, to earn more, and have happier employees. So why does engagement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-measure-the-big-impact-of-small-changes-margaret-heffernan-abridged/">Beyond Measure : The Big Impact of Small Changes &#8211; Margaret Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A powerful manifesto for CEOs and employees alike: Influential and award-winning business leader Margaret Heffernan reveals how organizations can build ideal workplace cultures and create seismic shifts by making deceptively small changes.     </p>
<p>                    By implementing sweeping changes, businesses often think it&#8217;s possible to do better, to earn more, and have happier employees. So why does engagement prove so difficult and productivity so elusive?     </p>
<p>                    In Beyond Measure, Margaret Heffernan looks back over her decades spent overseeing different organizations and comes to a counterintuitive conclusion: it&#8217;s the small shifts that have the greatest impact. Heffernan argues that building the strongest organization can be accelerated by implementing seemingly small changes, such as embracing conflict as a creative catalyst; using every mind on the team; celebrating mistakes; speaking up and listening more; and encouraging time off from work.     </p>
<p>                    Packed with incredible anecdotes and startling statistics, Beyond Measure takes us on a fascinating tour across the globe, highlighting disparate businesses and revealing how they&#8217;ve managed to change themselves in big ways through incremental shifts. How did the CIA revolutionize their intelligence gathering with one simple question? How did one organization increase their revenue by $15 million by instituting a short coffee break? How can a day-long hackathon change the culture of a company? Told with wry wit and knowing humor, Heffernan proves that it&#8217;s often the small changes that make the greatest, most lasting impact.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-measure-the-big-impact-of-small-changes-margaret-heffernan-abridged/">Beyond Measure : The Big Impact of Small Changes &#8211; Margaret Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this new paperback edition of the classic bestseller, you&#8217;ll be taken on a hilarious, fast-paced ride through the history of ideas. Author Scott Berkun will show you how to transcend the false stories that many business experts, scientists, and much of pop culture foolishly use to guide their thinking about how ideas change the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/">The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this new paperback edition of the classic bestseller, you&#8217;ll be taken on a hilarious, fast-paced ride through the history of ideas. Author Scott Berkun will show you how to transcend the false stories that many business experts, scientists, and much of pop culture foolishly use to guide their thinking about how ideas change the world. With four new chapters on putting the ideas in the book to work, updated references and over 50 corrections and improvements, now is the time to get past the myths, and change the world. You&#8217;ll have fun while you learn:  * Where ideas come from * The true history of history * Why most people don&#8217;t like ideas * How great managers make ideas thrive * The importance of problem finding * The simple plan (new for paperback)  Since its initial publication, this classic bestseller has been discussed on NPR, MSNBC, CNBC, and at Yale University, MIT, Carnegie Mellon University, Microsoft, Apple, Intel, Google, Amazon.com, and other major media, corporations, and universities around the world. It has changed the way thousands of leaders and creators understand the world.<br />
                    Now in an updated and expanded paperback edition, it&#8217;s a fantastic time to explore or rediscover this powerful view of the world of ideas. &#8220;Sets us free to try and change the world.&#8221; &#8211;Guy Kawasaki, Author of Art of The Start &#8220;Small, simple, powerful: an innovative book about innovation.&#8221; &#8211;Don Norman, author of Design of Everyday Things &#8220;Insightful, inspiring, evocative, and just plain fun to read. It&#8217;s totally great.&#8221; &#8211;John Seely Brown, Former Director, Xerox Palo Alto Research Center (PARC) &#8220;Methodically and entertainingly dismantling the cliches that surround the process of innovation.&#8221; &#8211;Scott Rosenberg, author of Dreaming in Code; cofounder of Salon.com &#8220;Will inspire you to come up with breakthrough ideas of your own.&#8221; &#8211;Alan Cooper, Father of Visual Basic and author of The Inmates are Running the Asylum &#8220;Brimming with insights and historical examples, Berkun&#8217;s book not only debunks widely held myths about innovation, it also points the ways toward making your new ideas stick.&#8221; &#8211;Tom Kelley, GM, IDEO; author of The Ten Faces of Innovation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/">The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smartest Places on Earth : Why Rustbelts Are the Emerging Hotspots of Global Innovation &#8211; Antoine van Agtmael, Fred Bakker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smartest-places-on-earth-why-rustbelts-are-the-emerging-hotspots-of-global-innovation-antoine-van-agtmael-fred-bakker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smartest-places-on-earth-why-rustbelts-are-the-emerging-hotspots-of-global-innovation-antoine-van-agtmael-fred-bakker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Antoine van Agtmael coined the term &#8220;emerging markets&#8221; and built a career and a multibillion-dollar investing firm centered on these surging economies that would, over time, supplant the West as engines of wealth and prosperity. The trend held for decades, but a few years ago van Agtmael and Alfred Bakker, a renowned European journalist, began [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-places-on-earth-why-rustbelts-are-the-emerging-hotspots-of-global-innovation-antoine-van-agtmael-fred-bakker-abridged/">The Smartest Places on Earth : Why Rustbelts Are the Emerging Hotspots of Global Innovation &#8211; Antoine van Agtmael, Fred Bakker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Antoine van Agtmael coined the term &#8220;emerging markets&#8221; and built a career and a multibillion-dollar investing firm centered on these surging economies that would, over time, supplant the West as engines of wealth and prosperity. The trend held for decades, but a few years ago van Agtmael and Alfred Bakker, a renowned European journalist, began seeing signs that the tide might be turning. For example, during a visit to an enormously successful chip company in Taiwan, the company&#8217;s leaders told them that their American competitors were now eating their lunch. And Taiwan was not the only place giving them this message.    </p>
<p>                    Thus began a remarkable two-year journey to reassess the conventional wisdom that the United States and Europe are yesterday&#8217;s story and to determine whether there something profound is happening that points the way to the creation of the next economy.     </p>
<p>                    In The Smartest Places on Earth, van Agtmael and Bakker present a truly hopeful and inspiring investigation into the emerging sources of a new era of competitiveness for America and Europe that are coming from unlikely places&#8211;those cities and areas once known as &#8220;rustbelts&#8221; that have, from an economic perspective, been written off. Take Akron, Ohio, whose economy for decades was dependent on industries such as tire manufacturing, a product now made cheaply elsewhere. In Akron and other such communities, a combination of forces&#8211;including visionary thinkers, government initiatives, start-ups making real products, and even big corporations&#8211;have succeeded in creating what van Agtmael and Bakker call a &#8220;brainbelt.&#8221; These brainbelts depend on a collaborative work style that is unique to the societies and culture of America and Europe, since they involve levels of trust and freedom of thinking that can&#8217;t be replicated elsewhere. They are producing products and technologies that are transforming industries such as vehicles and transportation, farming and food production, medical devices and health care.    </p>
<p>                    For several decades, American and European industry focused on cost by outsourcing production to those emerging markets that can make things cheaper. The tide has now turned toward being smart, as van Agtmael and Bakker report, and the next emerging market, may, in fact, be the West.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-places-on-earth-why-rustbelts-are-the-emerging-hotspots-of-global-innovation-antoine-van-agtmael-fred-bakker-abridged/">The Smartest Places on Earth : Why Rustbelts Are the Emerging Hotspots of Global Innovation &#8211; Antoine van Agtmael, Fred Bakker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Bang Disruption : Business Survival in the Age of Constant Innovation &#8211; Larry Downes, Paul Nunes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/big-bang-disruption-business-survival-in-the-age-of-constant-innovation-larry-downes-paul-nunes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/big-bang-disruption-business-survival-in-the-age-of-constant-innovation-larry-downes-paul-nunes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A stimulating read&#8230;carefully researched and accessibly written&#8230;the case studies on disruption alone are worth the cover price&#8217; -Financial Times &#8216;Everything you need from business school in one very direct book&#8217; -Dick Costolo, CEO, Twitter It used to take years for new products and services to dethrone industry leaders. Now any busi ness can be instantly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-bang-disruption-business-survival-in-the-age-of-constant-innovation-larry-downes-paul-nunes-abridged/">Big Bang Disruption : Business Survival in the Age of Constant Innovation &#8211; Larry Downes, Paul Nunes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A stimulating read&#8230;carefully researched and accessibly written&#8230;the case studies on disruption alone are worth the cover price&#8217; -Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Everything you need from business school in one very direct book&#8217; -Dick Costolo, CEO, Twitter    </p>
<p>                    It used to take years for new products and services to dethrone industry leaders. Now any busi ness can be instantly devastated by something better and cheaper. How can you protect yourself, and harness the power of Big Bang Disruption?    </p>
<p>                    No matter what your industry, start-ups can change the market before you even begin to grasp what&#8217;s happening. The good news is that any business can mas ter the strategy of the start-ups.    </p>
<p>                    In Big Bang Disruption, Larry Downes and Paul Nunes show you how to spot the next big thing &#8211; before the next start-up does. Based on extensive research by the Accenture Institute for High Performance and interviews from over 30 industries, this essential bookwill give you with the tools to take control of your future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-bang-disruption-business-survival-in-the-age-of-constant-innovation-larry-downes-paul-nunes-abridged/">Big Bang Disruption : Business Survival in the Age of Constant Innovation &#8211; Larry Downes, Paul Nunes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on building a product that people will actually buy and use. By rigorously following the techniques described in Running Lean, you can eliminate waste &#8211; whether it&#8217;s time, money, effort, or all of the above &#8211; and get your product to market quickly. Refined through the real-world experiences of dozens of startup companies, these techniques are part of Eric Ries&#8217; Lean Startup methodology. Principles covered in this book include: * Find a problem worth solving, then define a solution * Demo before building * Pricing is part of the product * Maximize for speed, learning, and focus * Build a continuous feedback loop with customers throughout the product development cycle * Right Action, Right Time * Build a path to customers from day one</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Write Your Business Plan : Get Your Plan in Place and Your Business off the Ground &#8211; The Staff of Entrepreneur Media (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive companion to Entrepreneur&#8217;s long-time bestseller Start Your Own Business, this essential guide leads you through the most critical startup step next to committing to your business vision&#8211;defining how to achieve it. Coached by a diverse group of experts and successful business owners, gain an in-depth understanding of what&#8217;s essential to any business plan, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/">Write Your Business Plan : Get Your Plan in Place and Your Business off the Ground &#8211; The Staff of Entrepreneur Media (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive companion to Entrepreneur&#8217;s long-time bestseller Start Your Own Business, this essential guide leads you through the most critical startup step next to committing to your business vision&#8211;defining how to achieve it.  Coached by a diverse group of experts and successful business owners, gain an in-depth understanding of what&#8217;s essential to any business plan, what&#8217;s appropriate for your venture, and what it takes ensure success. Plus, learn from real-world examples of plans that worked, helping to raise money, hone strategy, and build a solid business.  Whether you&#8217;re just starting out or already running a business, to successfully build a company, you need a plan. One that lays out your product, your strategy, your market, your team, and your opportunity. It is the blueprint for your business. The experts at Entrepreneur show you how to create it.  Includes sample business plans, resources and worksheets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/">Write Your Business Plan : Get Your Plan in Place and Your Business off the Ground &#8211; The Staff of Entrepreneur Media (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Prepare a Business Plan : Your Guide to Creating an Excellent Strategy, Forecasting Your Finances and Producing a Persuasive Plan &#8211; Edward Blackwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An excellent business plan impresses financial backers, provides a clear blueprint for the future of your company and functions as a benchmark against which to measure future growth. How to Prepare a Business Plan explains the process of creating an excellent business plan in an engaging and accessible way. It includes essential coverage of producing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/">How to Prepare a Business Plan : Your Guide to Creating an Excellent Strategy, Forecasting Your Finances and Producing a Persuasive Plan &#8211; Edward Blackwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An excellent business plan impresses financial backers, provides a clear blueprint for the future of your company and functions as a benchmark against which to measure future growth. How to Prepare a Business Plan explains the process of creating an excellent business plan in an engaging and accessible way. It includes essential coverage of producing cash flow forecasts, planning a business expansion, planning your borrowing and monitoring business progress.     </p>
<p>                    Global case studies containing real business plans provide inspiration and real-life practical insight by analyzing the plans, monitoring the business&#8217; progress and discussing their problems. Sample business plans also show you the process in action and provide useful examples for creating your own. How to Prepare a Business Plan helps new business owners to consider what they really want out of their business, and to map their own journey and gain a new understanding of their product&#8217;s place in the market, as well as writing a business plan with the clarity, brevity and logic to keep bank managers interested and convinced.     </p>
<p>                    Whether looking to start up or expand, this practical advice will help anyone to prepare a plan that is tailored to the requirements of their business &#8211; one that will get the financial backing they need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/">How to Prepare a Business Plan : Your Guide to Creating an Excellent Strategy, Forecasting Your Finances and Producing a Persuasive Plan &#8211; Edward Blackwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make Your Mark : The Creative&#8217;s Guide to Building a Business with Impact &#8211; Jocelyn K. Glei (Editor) (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/make-your-mark-the-creatives-guide-to-building-a-business-with-impact-jocelyn-k-glei-editor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/make-your-mark-the-creatives-guide-to-building-a-business-with-impact-jocelyn-k-glei-editor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Finally, a business book for makers, not managers. Are you ready to &#8220;make a dent in the universe&#8221;? As a creative, you no longer have to take a backseat. In fact, stepping up and embracing entrepreneurship is the fastest route to impact. But where do you start? And what sets the businesses that succeed apart? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-mark-the-creatives-guide-to-building-a-business-with-impact-jocelyn-k-glei-editor-abridged/">Make Your Mark : The Creative&#8217;s Guide to Building a Business with Impact &#8211; Jocelyn K. Glei (Editor) (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Finally, a business book for makers, not managers.     </p>
<p>                    Are you ready to &#8220;make a dent in the universe&#8221;? As a creative, you no longer have to take a backseat. In fact, stepping up and embracing entrepreneurship is the fastest route to impact. But where do you start? And what sets the businesses that succeed apart?     </p>
<p>                    To find out, we asked the bright minds behind companies like Google X, Warby Parker, Facebook, O&#8217;Reilly Media, and more to share their startup wisdom. Featuring hard-won wisdom from 20 leading entrepreneurs and designers, 99U&#8217;s Make Your Mark will arm you with practical insights for launching a purpose-driven business, refining your product, delighting your customers, inspiring your team&#8211;and ultimately&#8211;making something that matters.     </p>
<p>                    Make Your Mark features contributions from: Will Allen, Rich Armstrong, Warren Berger, Sean Blanda, Neil Blumenthal, Craig Dalton, Jane ni Dhulchaointigh, Aaron Dignan, Andy Dunn, Joel Gascoigne, Seth Godin, Chris Guillebeau, Emily Heyward, John Maeda, David Marquet, Tim O&#8217;Reilly, Shane Snow, Sebastian Thrun, Keith Yamashita, and Julie Zhuo. Plus, a foreword from Behance founder Scott Belsky</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-mark-the-creatives-guide-to-building-a-business-with-impact-jocelyn-k-glei-editor-abridged/">Make Your Mark : The Creative&#8217;s Guide to Building a Business with Impact &#8211; Jocelyn K. Glei (Editor) (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will It Fly? : How to Test Your Next Business Idea So You Don&#8217;t Waste Your Time and Money &#8211; Pat Flynn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/will-it-fly-how-to-test-your-next-business-idea-so-you-dont-waste-your-time-and-money-pat-flynn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/will-it-fly-how-to-test-your-next-business-idea-so-you-dont-waste-your-time-and-money-pat-flynn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stop rushing into businesses born from half-baked ideas, misguided theories, and other forms of self-delusion. A lack of proper validation kills more businesses than anything else. As Joel Barker says, &#8216;Speed is only useful if you re running in the right direction.&#8217; Will It Fly? will help you make sure you are clear for takeoff. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/will-it-fly-how-to-test-your-next-business-idea-so-you-dont-waste-your-time-and-money-pat-flynn-abridged/">Will It Fly? : How to Test Your Next Business Idea So You Don&#8217;t Waste Your Time and Money &#8211; Pat Flynn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stop rushing into businesses born from half-baked ideas, misguided theories, and other forms of self-delusion. A lack of proper validation kills more businesses than anything else. As Joel Barker says, &#8216;Speed is only useful if you re running in the right direction.&#8217; Will It Fly? will help you make sure you are clear for takeoff.    </p>
<p>                     It answers questions like:  Does your business idea have merit? Will it succeed in the market you re trying to serve, or will it just be a waste of time and resources? Is it a good idea for YOU?     </p>
<p>                     In other words, will it fly?    </p>
<p>                     Chock-full of practical suggestions you can apply to your business idea today, Will It Fly? combines action-based exercises, small-scale &#8216;litmus tests&#8217;, and real-world case studies with anecdotes from the author s personal experience of making money online, hosting successful podcasts, testing niche sites, and launching several online businesses.    </p>
<p>                     Will It Fly? will challenge you to think critically, act deliberately, and dare greatly. You can think of the book as your business flight manual, something you can refer to for honest and straight-forward advice as you begin to test your idea and build a business that takes off and soars.    </p>
<p>                     In five parts, Will It Fly? will guide you through the validation of your next business idea:     </p>
<p>                     Part one, Mission Design, helps you make sure your target idea aligns with and supports your goals. Part two, Development Lab, walks you through uncovering important details about your idea that you haven&#8217;t even thought about. Part three, Flight Planning, is all about assessing current market conditions. Part four, Flight Simulator, focuses on the actual validating and testing of an idea with a small segment of a target market. Finally, Part five, All Systems Go, is for final analysis to help you make sure your idea is one you are ready to move forward with.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/will-it-fly-how-to-test-your-next-business-idea-so-you-dont-waste-your-time-and-money-pat-flynn-abridged/">Will It Fly? : How to Test Your Next Business Idea So You Don&#8217;t Waste Your Time and Money &#8211; Pat Flynn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Broke : How Empty Pockets, a Tight Budget, and a Hunger for Success Can Become Your Greatest Competitive Advantage &#8211; Daymond John, Daniel Paisner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-broke-how-empty-pockets-a-tight-budget-and-a-hunger-for-success-can-become-your-greatest-competitive-advantage-daymond-john-daniel-paisner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-broke-how-empty-pockets-a-tight-budget-and-a-hunger-for-success-can-become-your-greatest-competitive-advantage-daymond-john-daniel-paisner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The instant New York Times bestseller from Shark Tank star and Fubu Founder Daymond John on why starting a business on a limited budget can be an entrepreneur&#8217;s greatest competitive advantage. Daymond John has been practicing the power of broke ever since he started selling his home-sewn t-shirts on the streets of Queens. With a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-broke-how-empty-pockets-a-tight-budget-and-a-hunger-for-success-can-become-your-greatest-competitive-advantage-daymond-john-daniel-paisner-abridged/">The Power of Broke : How Empty Pockets, a Tight Budget, and a Hunger for Success Can Become Your Greatest Competitive Advantage &#8211; Daymond John, Daniel Paisner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The instant New York Times bestseller from Shark Tank star and Fubu Founder Daymond John on why starting a business on a limited budget can be an entrepreneur&#8217;s greatest competitive advantage. Daymond John has been practicing the power of broke ever since he started selling his home-sewn t-shirts on the streets of Queens. With a $40 budget, Daymond had to strategize out-of-the-box ways to promote his products. Luckily, desperation breeds innovation, and so he hatched an idea for a creative campaign that eventually launched the FUBU brand into a $6 billion dollar global phenomenon. But it might not have happened if he hadn&#8217;t started out broke &#8211; with nothing but hope and a ferocious drive to succeed by any means possible.  Here, the FUBU founder and star of ABC&#8217;s Shark Tank shows that, far from being a liability, broke can actually be your greatest competitive advantage as an entrepreneur. Why? Because starting a business from broke forces you to think more creatively. It forces you to use your resources more efficiently. It forces you to connect with your customers more authentically, and market your ideas more imaginatively. It forces you to be true to yourself, stay laser focused on your goals, and come up with those innovative solutions required to make a meaningful mark. Drawing his own experiences as an entrepreneur and branding consultant, peeks behind-the scenes from the set of Shark Tank, and stories of dozens of other entrepreneurs who have hustled their way to wealth, John shows how we can all leverage the power of broke to phenomenal success. You&#8217;ll meet: &#8211; Steve Aoki, the electronic dance music (EDM) deejay who managed to parlay a series of $100 gigs into becoming a global superstar who has redefined the music industry<br />
                     &#8211; Gigi Butler, a cleaning lady from Nashville who built cupcake empire on the back of a family recipe, her maxed out credit cards, and a heaping dose of faith<br />
                     &#8211; 11-year old Shark Tank guest Mo Bridges who stitched together a winning clothing line with just his grandma&#8217;s sewing machine, a stash of loose fabric, and his unique sartorial flair When your back is up against the wall, your bank account is empty, and creativity and passion are the only resources you can afford, success is your only option. Here you&#8217;ll learn how to tap into that Power of Broke to scrape, hustle, and dream your way to the top.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-broke-how-empty-pockets-a-tight-budget-and-a-hunger-for-success-can-become-your-greatest-competitive-advantage-daymond-john-daniel-paisner-abridged/">The Power of Broke : How Empty Pockets, a Tight Budget, and a Hunger for Success Can Become Your Greatest Competitive Advantage &#8211; Daymond John, Daniel Paisner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
