<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Service Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/service-industries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/service-industries/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Service Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/service-industries/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>This is Service Design Thinking : Basics, Tools, Cases &#8211; Marc Stickdorn, Jakob Schneider (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to design and market services to create outstanding customer experiences Service design thinking is the designing and marketing of services that improve the customer experience, and the interactions between the service providers and the customers. If you have two coffee shops right next to each other, and each sell the exact same coffee at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/">This is Service Design Thinking : Basics, Tools, Cases &#8211; Marc Stickdorn, Jakob Schneider (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to design and market services to create outstanding customer experiences Service design thinking is the designing and marketing of services that improve the customer experience, and the interactions between the service providers and the customers. If you have two coffee shops right next to each other, and each sell the exact same coffee at the exact same price, service design is what makes you walk into one and not the other. Maybe one plays music and the other doesn&#8217;t. Maybe one takes credit cards and the other is cash only. Maybe you like the layout of one over the other, or one has more comfortable seating. Maybe the staff at one is friendlier, or draws fun shapes on the top of their lattes. All of these nuances relate to service design.<br />
                    This Is Service Design Thinking combines the knowledge of twenty-three international authors and even more online contributors from the global service design community and is divided into three sections: * Basics: outlines service design thinking along five basic principles * Tools: describing a variety of tools and methods used in Service Design Thinking * Cases: vivid examples for the introduced fundamentals with real-life case studies from 5 companies that did inspiring projects within the field of Service Design At the end, a one-page &#8220;Customer Journey Canvas&#8221; is included, which can be used to quickly sketch any service on a single sheet of paper capturing different stakeholder concerns: e.g. customers, front-line staff and management.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/">This is Service Design Thinking : Basics, Tools, Cases &#8211; Marc Stickdorn, Jakob Schneider (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212; Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International    </p>
<p>                      &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! There, I learned the fundamentals of guest service that consistently gave Disney a tremendous advantage in the marketplace. Now, anyone can know these secrets of success thanks to Doug Lipp&#8217;s informative book. No matter what your business, the lessons taught at DisneyUniversity will prove invaluable.&#8221; &#8212; Michael Eisner, Former CEO and Chairman, The Walt Disney Company    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to world-class employees, few organizations rival Disney. Famous for their friendliness, knowledge, passion, and superior customer service, Disney&#8217;s employees have been fueling the iconic brand&#8217;s wild success for more than 50 years.    </p>
<p>                    How has Disney succeeded in maintaining such a powerful workforce for so many years? Why are so many corporations and executives drawn to study how Disney continues to exemplify service and leadership standards?    </p>
<p>                    The Disney University, founded by Van France, trains the supporting cast that helps create the world-famous Disney Magic. Now, for the first time, the secrets of this exemplary institution are revealed. In Disney U, Doug Lipp examines how Van perpetuated Walt Disney&#8217;s timeless company values and leadership lessons, creating a training and development dynasty. It contains never-before-told stories from numerous Disney legends. These pioneers share behind-the-scenes success stories of how they helped bring Walt Disney&#8217;s dream to life.    </p>
<p>                    Disney U reveals the heart of the Disney culture and describes the company&#8217;s values and operational philosophies that support the iconic brand. Doug Lipp lays out 13 timeless lessons Disney has used to drive profits and growth worldwide for more than half a century.    </p>
<p>                    To this day, the Disney University continues to turn out some of the most engaged, loyal, and customer-centered employees the business world has ever seen. Using the lessons outlined in Disney U will set your organization on a path of sustained success.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR Disney U:    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I highly recommend Disney U to anyone interested in building an enduring market presence and brand.&#8221; &#8212; Stephen Cannon, President and Chief Executive Officer, Mercedes-Benz USA    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lipp&#8217;s narratives reveal how Van and other Disney visionaries set the stage for a world-class organization by skillfully balancing both &#8216;people&#8217; and &#8216;technology.'&#8221; &#8212; Debi Aubee, Vice President of Sales, Bose Corporation    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every leader should have the equivalent of a Van France at his or her side. Thanks to Doug Lipp, we can now tap into the brilliance of a man who helped Walt createThe Happiest Place on Earth.&#8221; &#8212; David Overton, Founder and Chief Executive Officer, The Cheesecake Factory    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;How does Disney University create such enthusiastic, loyal, and customer-centered employees, year after year? Now, for the first time, Doug Lipp takes us on a journey backstage to answer this pivotal question.&#8221; &#8212; John G. Veres III, Ph.D., Chancellor, Auburn University at Montgomery    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Doug Lipp shares terrific stories about Disney that underscore the importance of creating an organizational culture with an unwavering dedication to superlativeservice and exceptional quality, both for employees and customers. He then takes it a step further by explaining how to bring these values to life for your organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Christine A. Morena, Executive Vice President of Human Resources, Saks Incorporated</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selling The Invisible : A Field Guide to Modern Marketing &#8211; Harry Beckwith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SELLING THE INVISIBLE is a succinct and often entertaining look at the unique characteristics of services and their prospects, and how any service, from a home-based consultancy to a multinational brokerage, can turn more prospects into clients and keep them. SELLING THE INVISIBLE covers service marketing from start to finish. Filled with wonderful insights and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/">Selling The Invisible : A Field Guide to Modern Marketing &#8211; Harry Beckwith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SELLING THE INVISIBLE is a succinct and often entertaining look at the unique characteristics of services and their prospects, and how any service, from a home-based consultancy to a multinational brokerage, can turn more prospects into clients and keep them. SELLING THE INVISIBLE covers service marketing from start to finish. Filled with wonderful insights and written in a roll-up-your-sleeves, jargon-free, accessible style, such as:    </p>
<p>                    Greatness May Get You Nowhere; Focus Groups Don&#8217;ts; The More You Say, the Less People Hear; Seeing the Forest Around the Falling Trees</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/">Selling The Invisible : A Field Guide to Modern Marketing &#8211; Harry Beckwith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Be Our Guest (10th Anniversary Updated Edition) : Perfecting the Art of Customer Service &#8211; Ted Kinni, Edited by Wendy Lefkon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exceeding expectations rather than simply satisfying them is the cornerstone of the Disney approach to customer service. Disney Institute specializes in helping professionals see new possibilities through concepts not found in the typical workplace, is revealing even more of the business behind the magic of quality service. During the last twenty-five years, thousands of professionals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/">Be Our Guest (10th Anniversary Updated Edition) : Perfecting the Art of Customer Service &#8211; Ted Kinni, Edited by Wendy Lefkon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exceeding expectations rather than simply satisfying them is the cornerstone of the Disney approach to customer service.<br />
                    Disney Institute specializes in helping professionals see new possibilities through concepts not found in the typical workplace, is revealing even more of the business behind the magic of quality service. During the last twenty-five years, thousands of professionals from more than thirty-five countries and more than forty industries have attended business programs at Disney Institute and learned how to adapt the Disney approach for their own organizations.Be Our Guest highlights the successes many of these companies have achieved, plus the key processes and best practices that have made Disney a trusted and revered brand around the world for more than eighty-five years.<br />
                    Want more insight on The Walt Disney Company, its founder, and its driving creative forces? Explore these behind-the-scenes stories from Disney Editions: Travels with Figment: On the Road in Search of Disney Dreams (By Disney Legend Marty Sklar)<br />
                    One Little Spark! Mickey&#8217;s Ten Commandments and The Road to Imagineering (By Disney Legend Marty Sklar)<br />
                    Magic Journey: My Fantastical Walt Disney Imagineering Career (By Kevin Rafferty)<br />
                    Travels with Walt Disney: A Photographic Voyage Around the World (By Jeff Kurtti)<br />
                    Eat Like Walt: The Wonderful World of Disney Food (By Marcy Carriker Smothers)<br />
                    Walt Disney: An American Original (By Bob Thomas)<br />
                    Disney A to Z: The Official Encyclopedia, Fifth Edition (By Disney Legend Dave Smith)<br />
                    Disney Facts Revealed: Answers to Fans&#8217; Curious Questions (By Disney Legend Dave Smith)<br />
                    Disney Trivia from the Vault: Secrets Revealed and Questions Answered (By Disney Legend Dave Smith)<br />
                    My Pride: Mastering Life&#8217;s Daily Performance from Broadway&#8217;s Record-Breaking Lion King (By Alton Fitzgerald White)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/">Be Our Guest (10th Anniversary Updated Edition) : Perfecting the Art of Customer Service &#8211; Ted Kinni, Edited by Wendy Lefkon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now the subject of a film by Richard Linklater, Eric Schlosser&#8217;s explosive bestseller Fast Food Nation: What the All-American Meal is Doing to the World tells the story of our love affair with fast food. Britain eats more fast food than any other country in Europe. It looks good, tastes good, and it&#8217;s cheap. But [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now the subject of a film by Richard Linklater, Eric Schlosser&#8217;s explosive bestseller Fast Food Nation: What the All-American Meal is Doing to the World tells the story of our love affair with fast food.    </p>
<p>                      Britain eats more fast food than any other country in Europe. It looks good, tastes good, and it&#8217;s cheap. But the real cost never appears on the menu.    </p>
<p>                      Eric Schlosser visits the lab that re-creates the smell of strawberries; examines the safety records of abattoirs; reveals why the fries really taste so good and what lurks between the sesame buns &#8211; and shows how fast food is transforming not only our diets but our world.    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Fast Food Nation has lifted the polystyrene lid on the global fast food industry &#8230; and sparked a storm&#8217;<br />
                      Observer    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Has wiped that smirk off the Happy Meal &#8230; Thanks to this man, you&#8217;ll never eat a burger again&#8217;<br />
                      Evening Standard    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Startling &#8230; Junk food, we learn, is just that &#8230; left this reader vowing never to set foot in one of those outlets again&#8217;<br />
                      Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;This book tells you more than you really want to know when you&#8217;re chomping on that hamburger &#8230; Have a nice day? Listen &#8211; you should live so long&#8217;<br />
                      The Times    </p>
<p>                      Eric Schlosser is a correspondent for the Atlantic Monthly. His first book, Fast Food Nation, was a major international bestseller. His work has appeared in the Atlantic Monthly, Rolling Stone and the Guardian. He has received a number of journalistic honours, including a National Magazine Award for an Atlantic Review article on the drug trade, which was later adapted into the book Reefer Madness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related to the way managers treat employees.    </p>
<p>                    Kelsey Young is an optimistic but disillusioned sales associate working her way through college. Her world opens up when one of her professors challenges her to create a culture of service at her workplace by putting the five components of Legendary Service into practice. AlthoughFerguson&#8217;s, the store where Kelsey works, certainly isn&#8217;t known for service excellence, Kelsey believes she can make a positive difference. She quickly learns that culture change isn&#8217;t easy&#8211;and that her role as a frontline employee is more significant than she ever could have imagined.    </p>
<p>                    In characteristic Blanchard style, Legendary Service: The Key Is to Care is a quick and entertainingread for people at all organizational levels in every industry. When applied, its lessons will have a profound impact on the service experience your customers will receive. Whether a CEO or a part-time employee, every person can make a difference&#8211;and customer service iseveryone&#8217;s job.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR LEGENDARY SERVICE:&#8221;Read this book and establish a service culture in your organization.&#8221; &#8212; Horst Schulze, Chairman/CEO, Capella Hotel Group    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Legendary Service has great learnings for people at all organizational levels: for executives and managers, the value of a service culture; and for frontlinestaff, the reality that they are the face of the company and can make a difference. Legendary service&#8211;it&#8217;s everyone, always.&#8221; &#8212; Mark King, CEO and President, TaylorMade Golf    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Everything I know about service I learned from my career at Hilton Hotels, Marriott International, The Walt Disney Company, and Ken Blanchard. The One Minute Manager dramatically changed my thinking 32 years ago. LegendaryService will teach the next generation how to deliver sensational service. Buy it, study it, implement it.&#8221; &#8212; Lee Cockerell, Executive Vice President, Walt Disney World (Retired &#038; Inspired), and author of Creating Magic and The Customer Rules    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Kathy Cuff and Vicki Halsey have created a fantastic customer service model called ICARE. When you add their voices to that of the master storyteller KenBlanchard, you have a masterpiece entitled Legendary Service. It is a must-read for everyone who, like me, has a passion for service.&#8221; &#8212; Colleen Barrett, President Emeritus, Southwest Airlines, and coauthor of Lead with LUV    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken Blanchard has done it again and delivered the right book at the right time. Legendary Service provides the essentials of hospitality and servant leadership in a way that everyone can adopt&#8211;right now&#8211;today!&#8221; &#8212; John Caparella, President and COO,The Venetian, The Palazzo, and Sands Expo    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken, Kathy, and Vicki show us how to change everyday service events into memorable experiences. Their book is a must-read for anyone unwilling to acceptmediocrity.&#8221; &#8212; Leonardo Inghilleri, coauthor ofExceptional Service, Exceptional Profit</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
