<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Clinical Psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/clinical-psychology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/clinical-psychology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Clinical Psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/clinical-psychology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson</title>
		<link>/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 Sunday Times bestseller from &#8216;the most influential public intellectual in the Western world right now&#8217; (New York Times) &#8211; now in paperback. How should we live properly in a world of chaos and uncertainty? Jordan Peterson has helped millions of people, young and old, men and women, aim at a life of responsibility [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson/">12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 Sunday Times bestseller from &#8216;the most influential public intellectual in the Western world right now&#8217; (New York Times) &#8211; now in paperback.    </p>
<p>                    How should we live properly in a world of chaos and uncertainty?    </p>
<p>                    Jordan Peterson has helped millions of people, young and old, men and women, aim at a life of responsibility and meaning. Now he can help you.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own work as a clinical psychologist and on lessons from humanity&#8217;s oldest myths and stories, Peterson offers twelve profound and realistic principles to live by. After all, as he reminds us, we each have a vital role to play in the unfolding destiny of the world.    </p>
<p>                    Deep, rewarding and enlightening, 12 Rules for Life is a lifeboat built solidly for stormy seas: ancient wisdom applied to our contemporary problems.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson/">12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circe : The No. 1 Bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles &#8211; Madeline Miller</title>
		<link>/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The international Number One bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles, shortlisted for the Women&#8217;s Prize for Fiction Woman. Witch. Myth. Mortal. Outcast. Lover. Destroyer. Survivor. CIRCE. In the house of Helios, god of the sun and mightiest of the Titans, a daughter is born. Circe is a strange child &#8211; not powerful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/">Circe : The No. 1 Bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles &#8211; Madeline Miller</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The international Number One bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles, shortlisted for the Women&#8217;s Prize for Fiction</p>
<p>                    Woman. Witch. Myth. Mortal. Outcast. Lover. Destroyer. Survivor. CIRCE.</p>
<p>                     In the house of Helios, god of the sun and mightiest of the Titans, a daughter is born. Circe is a strange child &#8211; not powerful and terrible, like her father, nor gorgeous and mercenary like her mother. Scorned and rejected, Circe grows up in the shadows, at home in neither the world of gods or mortals. But Circe has a dark power of her own: witchcraft. When her gift threatens the gods, she is banished to the island of Aiaia where she hones her occult craft, casting spells, gathering strange herbs and taming wild beasts. Yet a woman who stands alone will never be left in peace for long &#8211; and among her island&#8217;s guests is an unexpected visitor: the mortal Odysseus, for whom Circe will risk everything. </p>
<p>                     So Circe sets forth her tale, a vivid, mesmerizing epic of family rivalry, love and loss &#8211; the defiant, inextinguishable song of woman burning hot and bright through the darkness of a man&#8217;s world.</p>
<p>                    THE NUMBER ONE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER </p>
<p>                    CHOSEN AS A BOOK OF THE YEAR BY THE GUARDIAN, TELEGRAPH, SUNDAY TELEGRAPH, I PAPER, SUNDAY EXPRESS, IRISH TIMES, TIMES LITERARY SUPPLEMENT, AMAZON, AUDIBLE, BUZZFEED, REFINERY 29, WASHINGTON POST, BOSTON GLOBE, SEATTLE TIMES, TIME MAGAZINE, NEWSWEEK, PEOPLE, ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY, KIRKUS, PUBLISHERS WEEKLY AND GOODREADS</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/">Circe : The No. 1 Bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles &#8211; Madeline Miller</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Drive : The Surprising Truth About What Motivates Us &#8211; Daniel H. Pink</title>
		<link>/drive-the-surprising-truth-about-what-motivates-us-daniel-h-pink/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/drive-the-surprising-truth-about-what-motivates-us-daniel-h-pink/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A book that will change how you think and transform how you live Forget everything you thought you knew about how to motivate people &#8211; at work, at school, at home. It is wrong. As Daniel H. Pink explains in his paradigm-shattering book Drive, the secret to high performance and satisfaction in today&#8217;s world is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drive-the-surprising-truth-about-what-motivates-us-daniel-h-pink/">Drive : The Surprising Truth About What Motivates Us &#8211; Daniel H. Pink</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A book that will change how you think and transform how you live     </p>
<p>                    Forget everything you thought you knew about how to motivate people &#8211; at work, at school, at home. It is wrong. As Daniel H. Pink explains in his paradigm-shattering book Drive, the secret to high performance and satisfaction in today&#8217;s world is the deeply human need to direct our own lives, to learn and create new things, and to do better by ourselves and the world.    </p>
<p>                    Along the way, he takes us to companies that are enlisting new approaches to motivation, and introduces us to the scientists and entrepreneurs who are pointing a bold way forward.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drive-the-surprising-truth-about-what-motivates-us-daniel-h-pink/">Drive : The Surprising Truth About What Motivates Us &#8211; Daniel H. Pink</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Client Centered Therapy (New Ed) &#8211; Carl Rogers</title>
		<link>/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Counselling & Advice Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Presenting the non-directive and related points of view in counselling and therapy, this book defines the progress recently made in the development of the techniques and basic philosophy of counselling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/">Client Centered Therapy (New Ed) &#8211; Carl Rogers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Presenting the non-directive and related points of view in counselling  and therapy, this book defines the progress recently made in the  development of the techniques and basic philosophy of counselling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/">Client Centered Therapy (New Ed) &#8211; Carl Rogers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creative Confidence : Unleashing the Creative Potential within Us All &#8211; David Kelley, Tom Kelley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A powerful and inspiring book from the founders of IDEO, the award-winning design firm, on unleashing the creativity that lies within each and every one of us. Too often, companies and individuals assume that creativity and innovation are the domain of the &#8216;creative types&#8217;. But two of the foremost experts in innovation, design and creativity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/">Creative Confidence : Unleashing the Creative Potential within Us All &#8211; David Kelley, Tom Kelley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A powerful and inspiring book from the founders of IDEO, the award-winning design firm, on unleashing the creativity that lies within each and every one of us.    </p>
<p>                              Too often, companies and individuals assume that creativity and innovation are the domain of the &#8216;creative types&#8217;. But two of the foremost experts in innovation, design and creativity on the planet show us that each and every one of us is creative.    </p>
<p>                              In an entertaining and inspiring narrative that draws on countless stories from their work at IDEO, and with many of the world&#8217;s top companies and design firms, David and Tom Kelley identify the principles and strategies that will allow us to tap into our creative potential in our work lives, and in our personal lives, allow us to think outside the box in terms of how we approach and solve problems.    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;Creative Confidence&#8217; is a book that will help each of us be more productive and successful in our lives and in our careers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/">Creative Confidence : Unleashing the Creative Potential within Us All &#8211; David Kelley, Tom Kelley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Twenty-four Hour Mind : The Role of Sleep and Dreaming in Our Emotional Lives &#8211; Rosalind D. Cartwright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-twenty-four-hour-mind-the-role-of-sleep-and-dreaming-in-our-emotional-lives-rosalind-d-cartwright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Respiratory Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep & Dreams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-twenty-four-hour-mind-the-role-of-sleep-and-dreaming-in-our-emotional-lives-rosalind-d-cartwright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In January of 1999, an otherwise nonviolent man under great stress at work brutally murdered his wife in their backyard. He then went back to bed, awakening only when police entered his home. He claimed to have no memory of the event because, while his body was awake at the time, his mind was not. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-twenty-four-hour-mind-the-role-of-sleep-and-dreaming-in-our-emotional-lives-rosalind-d-cartwright-abridged/">The Twenty-four Hour Mind : The Role of Sleep and Dreaming in Our Emotional Lives &#8211; Rosalind D. Cartwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In January of 1999, an otherwise nonviolent man under great stress at work brutally murdered his wife in their backyard. He then went back to bed, awakening only when police entered his home. He claimed to have no memory of the event because, while his body was awake at the time, his mind was not. He had been sleepwalking.    </p>
<p>                    In The Twenty-four Hour Mind, sleep scientist Rosalind Cartwright brings together decades of research into the bizarre sleep disorders known as parasomnias to propose a new theory of how the human mind works consistently throughout waking and sleeping hours. Thanks to increasingly sophisticated EEG and brain imaging technologies, we now know that our minds do not simply &#8220;turn off&#8221; during sleep. Rather, they continue to be active, and research has indicated that one of the primary<br />
                    purposes of sleep is to aid in regulating emotions and processing experiences that occur during preceding waking hours. As such, when sleep is neurologically or genetically impaired or just too short, the processes that good sleep facilitates-those that usually have a positive effect on our mood and<br />
                    performance-can short circuit, with negative results that occasionally reach tragic proportions. Examining the interactions between conscious and unconscious forms of thinking as they proceed throughout the cycles of sleeping, dreaming, and waking, Cartwright demystifies the inner workings of the human mind that trigger sleep problems, how researchers are working to control them, and how they can apply what they learn to further our understanding of the brain. Along the way, she provides a<br />
                    lively account of the history of sleep research and the birth of sleep medicine that will initiate readers into this fascinating field of inquiry and the far-reaching implications it will have on the future of neuroscience. The Twenty-four Hour Mind offers a unique look at a relatively new area of study<br />
                    that will be of interest to those with and without sleep problems, as well as anyone captivated by the mysteries of the brain-and what sleep continues to teach us about the waking mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-twenty-four-hour-mind-the-role-of-sleep-and-dreaming-in-our-emotional-lives-rosalind-d-cartwright-abridged/">The Twenty-four Hour Mind : The Role of Sleep and Dreaming in Our Emotional Lives &#8211; Rosalind D. Cartwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in their working lives.    </p>
<p>                    Overcoming Mobbing is an informative, comprehensive guidebook written for the victims of mobbing and their families who often can&#8217;t make sense of the experience or mobilize resources for recovery. In an engaging, reader-friendly style, the book distinguishes mobbing from bullying in that it takes place within organizational or institutional settings and involves organizational dynamics. Mobbing is not about the occasional negative experience at work; it is ongoing negative acts, both<br />
                    overt and covert, over time, that erode workers&#8217; confidence in themselves and in their workplaces and that no amount of sophistication or maturity can make sense of.  Duffy and Sperry, leading authorities on this special type of aggression, provide effective strategies for recovery from mobbing as well as for<br />
                    prevention, and they demystify the experience through the use of case vignettes. More than a simple self-help book, this volume brings the concept and terminology relating to mobbing into the public vocabulary by virtue of its strong foundation in psychological and organizational research. It offers a detailed presentation of the causes and consequences of mobbing, helps readers avoid falling into the trap of misplacing blame, and holds organizations at the center of responsibility for<br />
                    preventing the abuse. In addition to those who have experienced mobbing themselves, this book is an invaluable resource for workplace managers and human resources personnel who wish to prevent or reverse mobbing within their own professional settings.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Upward Spiral : Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time &#8211; Alex Korb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Depression doesn&#8217;t happen all at once. It starts gradually and builds momentum over time. If you go through a difficult experience, you may stop taking care of yourself. You may stop exercising and eating healthy, which will end up making you feel even worse as time goes on. You are caught in a downward spiral, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/">The Upward Spiral : Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time &#8211; Alex Korb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Depression doesn&#8217;t happen all at once. It starts gradually and builds momentum over time. If you go through a difficult experience, you may stop taking care of yourself. You may stop exercising and eating healthy, which will end up making you feel even worse as time goes on. You are caught in a downward spiral, but you may feel too tired, too overwhelmed, and too scared to try and pull yourself back up. The good news is that just one small step can be a step in the right direction.    </p>
<p>                    In The Upward Spiral, neuroscientist Alex Korb demystifies the neurological processes in the brain that cause depression and offers effective ways to get better-one little step at a time. In the book, you&#8217;ll discover that there isn&#8217;t &#8220;one big solution&#8221; that will solve your depression. Instead, there are dozens of small, practical things you can do to alleviate your symptoms and start healing. Some are as simple as relaxing certain muscles to reduce feelings of anxiety, while others involve making small efforts toward more positive social interactions. Small steps in the right direction can have profound effects-giving you the power to literally &#8220;reshape&#8221; your brain.    </p>
<p>                    Like most people, you probably didn&#8217;t wake up one day and find yourself completely depressed. Instead, it probably happened over time, as a series of reactions to difficult situations and negative thinking. But if you are ready to reverse the trajectory of your depression and find lasting happiness, this book will show you how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/">The Upward Spiral : Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time &#8211; Alex Korb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cure : A Journey Into the Science of Mind over Body &#8211; Jo Marchant (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cure-a-journey-into-the-science-of-mind-over-body-jo-marchant-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cure-a-journey-into-the-science-of-mind-over-body-jo-marchant-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER SHORTLISTED FOR THE ROYAL SOCIETY SCIENCE BOOK PRIZE LONGLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME PRIZE ALL IN THE MIND? &#8211; Can meditation fend off dementia? &#8211; Can the smell of lavender affect the immune system? &#8211; Can your thoughts ease physical pain? In Cure, award-winning science writer Jo Marchant travels the world [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cure-a-journey-into-the-science-of-mind-over-body-jo-marchant-abridged/">Cure : A Journey Into the Science of Mind over Body &#8211; Jo Marchant (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE ROYAL SOCIETY SCIENCE BOOK PRIZE<br />
                    LONGLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME PRIZE    </p>
<p>                    ALL IN THE MIND?    </p>
<p>                      &#8211;       Can meditation fend off dementia?<br />
                      &#8211;       Can the smell of lavender affect the immune system?<br />
                      &#8211;       Can your thoughts ease physical pain?    </p>
<p>                     In Cure, award-winning science writer Jo Marchant travels the world to meet the physicians, patients and researchers on the cutting edge of mind-body medicine, asking how the brain can heal the body and how we can all make changes to keep ourselves healthier.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cure-a-journey-into-the-science-of-mind-over-body-jo-marchant-abridged/">Cure : A Journey Into the Science of Mind over Body &#8211; Jo Marchant (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 Sunday Times bestseller from &#8216;the most influential public intellectual in the Western world right now&#8217; (New York Times) &#8211; now in paperback. How should we live properly in a world of chaos and uncertainty? Jordan Peterson has helped millions of people, young and old, men and women, aim at a life of responsibility [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson-abridged/">12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 Sunday Times bestseller from &#8216;the most influential public intellectual in the Western world right now&#8217; (New York Times) &#8211; now in paperback.    </p>
<p>                    How should we live properly in a world of chaos and uncertainty?    </p>
<p>                    Jordan Peterson has helped millions of people, young and old, men and women, aim at a life of responsibility and meaning. Now he can help you.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own work as a clinical psychologist and on lessons from humanity&#8217;s oldest myths and stories, Peterson offers twelve profound and realistic principles to live by. After all, as he reminds us, we each have a vital role to play in the unfolding destiny of the world.    </p>
<p>                    Deep, rewarding and enlightening, 12 Rules for Life is a lifeboat built solidly for stormy seas: ancient wisdom applied to our contemporary problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson-abridged/">12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm : The One Stop Guide: Practical Advice for Anybody Affected by Self-Harm &#8211; Allan House (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Self-harm is increasingly prevalent in our society. But few of us understand why, or know what to do to help ourselves, friends or family in such situations. It can be very isolating. Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm aims to fill this gap, providing practical information and advice for anyone who has an experience of self-harm. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/">Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm : The One Stop Guide: Practical Advice for Anybody Affected by Self-Harm &#8211; Allan House (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Self-harm is increasingly prevalent in our society. But few of us understand why, or know what to do to help ourselves, friends or family in such situations. It can be very isolating.    </p>
<p>                    Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm aims to fill this gap, providing practical information and advice for anyone who has an experience of self-harm.    </p>
<p>                    Showing the various forms self-harm can take, this book explores the reasons behind it, and offers advice on self-management, support to others, and what services are available. Full of clear, thoughtful advice for those who may be thinking of harming themselves, or have already done so, as well as guidance for families and friends on helpful strategies and responses &#8211; and ones to avoid &#8211; it uses evidence from research and direct experience to provide an essential resource.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/">Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm : The One Stop Guide: Practical Advice for Anybody Affected by Self-Harm &#8211; Allan House (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Miracle Of Mindfulness : The Classic Guide to Meditation by the World&#8217;s Most Revered Master &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-the-classic-guide-to-meditation-by-the-worlds-most-revered-master-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-the-classic-guide-to-meditation-by-the-worlds-most-revered-master-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this beautifully written book, Buddhist monk and Nobel Peace Prize nominee Thich Nhat Hanh explains how to acquire the skills of mindfulness. Once we have these skills, we can slow our lives down and discover how to live in the moment &#8211; even simple acts like washing the dishes or drinking a cup of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-the-classic-guide-to-meditation-by-the-worlds-most-revered-master-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/">The Miracle Of Mindfulness : The Classic Guide to Meditation by the World&#8217;s Most Revered Master &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this beautifully written book, Buddhist monk and Nobel Peace Prize nominee Thich Nhat Hanh explains how to acquire the skills of mindfulness. Once we have these skills, we can slow our lives down and discover how to live in the moment &#8211; even simple acts like washing the dishes or drinking a cup of tea may be transformed into acts of meditation.    </p>
<p>                    Thich Nhat Hanh&#8217;s gentle anecdotes and practical exercises help us to arrive at greater self-understanding and peacefulness, whether we are beginners or advanced students. Irrespective of our particular religious beliefs, we can begin to reap the immense benefits that meditation has been scientifically proven to offer. We can all learn how to be mindful and experience the miracle of mindfulness for ourselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-the-classic-guide-to-meditation-by-the-worlds-most-revered-master-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/">The Miracle Of Mindfulness : The Classic Guide to Meditation by the World&#8217;s Most Revered Master &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trauma & Shock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;An astonishing and important book. The trauma Bible. I cannot recommend it enough for anyone struggling with&#8230;well&#8230;anything&#8217; Tara Westover The effects of trauma can be devastating for sufferers, their families and future generations. Here one of the world&#8217;s experts on traumatic stress offers a bold new paradigm for treatment, moving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/">The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An astonishing and important book. The trauma Bible. I  cannot recommend it enough for anyone struggling with&#8230;well&#8230;anything&#8217; Tara Westover    </p>
<p>                    The effects of trauma can be devastating for sufferers, their families and future generations. Here one of the world&#8217;s experts on traumatic stress offers a bold new paradigm for treatment, moving away from standard talking and drug therapies and towards an alternative approach that heals mind, brain and body.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Dr. van der Kolk&#8217;s masterpiece combines the boundless curiosity of the scientist, the erudition of the scholar, and the passion of the truth teller&#8217; Judith Herman, author of Trauma and Recovery</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/">The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
