<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Dogs As Pets Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/dogs-as-pets/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/dogs-as-pets/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Dogs As Pets Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/dogs-as-pets/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Art of Racing in the Rain &#8211; Garth Stein</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogs As Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major motion picture, this heart-warming and inspirational tale follows Enzo, a loyal family dog, tells the story of his human family, how they nearly fell apart, and what he did to bring them back together. Enzo knows he is different from other dogs: he thinks and feels in nearly human ways. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/">The Art of Racing in the Rain &#8211; Garth Stein</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major motion picture, this heart-warming and inspirational tale follows Enzo, a loyal family dog, tells the story of his human family, how they nearly fell apart, and what he did to bring them back together.    </p>
<p>                              Enzo knows he is different from other dogs: he thinks and feels in nearly human ways. He has educated himself by watching extensive television, and by listening very closely to the words of his master, Denny Swift, an up-and-coming race car driver. Through Denny, Enzo realizes that racing is a metaphor: that by applying the techniques a driver would apply on the race track, one can successfully navigate the ordeals and travails one encounters in life.    </p>
<p>                              Enzo relates the story of his human family, sharing their tragedies and triumphs. In the end, despite what he sees as his own limitations as a dog, Enzo comes through heroically to preserve the Swift family.    </p>
<p>                              The Art of Racing in the Rain is a testament to a man&#8217;s life, given by his dog. But it is also a testament to the dog, himself. Though Enzo cannot speak, he understands everything that happens around him as he bears witness to his master&#8217;s problems. His enforced muteness only refines his listening ability, and allows him to understand many of life&#8217;s nuances that are lost on most humans. With humour, sharp observation, and a courageous heart, Enzo guides the reader to the bittersweet yet ultimately satisfying conclusion: there are no limitations to what we can achieve, if we truly know where we want to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-racing-in-the-rain-garth-stein/">The Art of Racing in the Rain &#8211; Garth Stein</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Genius of Dogs : Discovering the Unique Intelligence of Man&#8217;s Best Friend &#8211; Brian Hare, Vanessa Woods (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-genius-of-dogs-discovering-the-unique-intelligence-of-mans-best-friend-brian-hare-vanessa-woods-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dog Obedience & Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogs As Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Animals & Pets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-genius-of-dogs-discovering-the-unique-intelligence-of-mans-best-friend-brian-hare-vanessa-woods-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The international bestseller that reveals the amazing mind of your favourite friend Is your dog purposefully disobeying you? Probably, and usually behind your back. Should you act like &#8216;top dog&#8217; to maintain control? No, you&#8217;re better off displaying your friendliness &#8211; and not just to your dog. Which breed is the cleverest? That&#8217;s the wrong [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-genius-of-dogs-discovering-the-unique-intelligence-of-mans-best-friend-brian-hare-vanessa-woods-abridged/">The Genius of Dogs : Discovering the Unique Intelligence of Man&#8217;s Best Friend &#8211; Brian Hare, Vanessa Woods (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The international bestseller that reveals the amazing mind of your favourite friend    </p>
<p>                    Is your dog purposefully disobeying you? Probably, and usually behind your back. Should you act like &#8216;top dog&#8217; to maintain control? No, you&#8217;re better off displaying your friendliness &#8211; and not just to your dog. Which breed is the cleverest? That&#8217;s the wrong question to ask.    </p>
<p>                    These are just some of the extraordinary insights to be found in The Genius of Dogs &#8211; the seminal book on how dogs evolved their unique intelligence by award-winning scientist Dr Brian Hare. He shares more than two decades of startling discoveries about the mysteries of the dog mind and how you can use his groundbreaking work to build a better relationship with your own dog.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-genius-of-dogs-discovering-the-unique-intelligence-of-mans-best-friend-brian-hare-vanessa-woods-abridged/">The Genius of Dogs : Discovering the Unique Intelligence of Man&#8217;s Best Friend &#8211; Brian Hare, Vanessa Woods (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
