<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Guidebooks Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/guidebooks/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/guidebooks/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Guidebooks Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/guidebooks/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</title>
		<link>/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Home Renovation & Extension]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV Tie-in Humour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE ENTERTAINING AND HEARTWARMING SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER. Like many couples, Dick and Angel had long dreamed of living in France, but where others might settle for a modest bolthole in the French countryside, the Strawbridges fell in love with a 19th-century fairytale chateau, complete with 45 rooms, seven outbuildings, 12 acres of land and its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/">A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE ENTERTAINING AND HEARTWARMING SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER.</p>
<p>                    Like many couples, Dick and Angel had long dreamed of living in France, but where others might settle for a modest bolthole in the French countryside, the Strawbridges fell in love with a 19th-century fairytale chateau, complete with 45 rooms, seven outbuildings, 12 acres of land and its own moat.</p>
<p>                    Throwing caution to the wind, Dick and Angel swapped their two-bedroom flat in East London for an abandoned and derelict castle in the heart of the Loire valley and embarked on the adventure of a lifetime with their two young children Arthur and Dorothy.</p>
<p>                    Sharing their full journey for the first time, A Year at the Chateau follows Dick and Angel from when they first moved to France in the depths of winter and found bedrooms infested with flies, turrets inhabited by bats, the wind rattling through cracked windows, and just one working toilet, which flushed into the moat, through to the monumental efforts that went into readying the chateau for their unforgettable wedding and their incredibly special first Christmas.</p>
<p>                    Along the way we&#8217;ll read glorious descriptions of rural life in France, with charming characters, delicious food and wonderful seasonal produce, together with the extraordinary list of renovations and restorations Dick and Angel completed, many of which were never shown on TV.</p>
<p>                    As warm and entertaining as their much-loved show, A Year at the Chateau is a truly irresistible story of adventure and heart, epic ambitions and a huge amount of hard graft.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/">A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Long Petal of the Sea : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Isabel Allende</title>
		<link>/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spanish Civil War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller &#8216;One of the strongest and most affecting works in Allende&#8217;s long career&#8217; New York Times Book Review &#8216;A defiantly warm and funny novel, by somebody who has earned the right to argue that love and optimism can survive whatever history might throw at us&#8217; Daily Telegraph September 3, 1939, the day [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/">A Long Petal of the Sea : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Isabel Allende</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the strongest and most affecting works in Allende&#8217;s long career&#8217; New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A defiantly warm and funny novel, by somebody who has earned the right to argue that love and optimism can survive whatever history might throw at us&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>                    September 3, 1939, the day of the Spanish exiles&#8217; splendid arrival in Chile, the Second World War broke out in Europe.</p>
<p>                    Victor Dalmau is a young doctor when he is caught up in the Spanish Civil War, a tragedy that leaves his life &#8211; and the fate of his country &#8211; forever changed. Together with his sister-in-law, the pianist Roser, he is forced out of his beloved Barcelona and into exile. </p>
<p>                    When opportunity to seek refuge arises, they board a ship chartered by the poet Pablo Neruda to Chile, the promised &#8216;long petal of sea and wine and snow&#8217;. There, they find themselves enmeshed in a rich web of characters who come together in love and tragedy over the course of four generations, destined to witness the battle between freedom and repression as it plays out across the world.</p>
<p>                    A masterful work of historical fiction that soars from the Spanish Civil War to the rise and fall of Pinochet, A Long Petal of the Sea is Isabel Allende at the height of her powers.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An epic that starts in 1939 and spans decades and continents . . . A masterful work of historical fiction about hope, exile and belonging, and one that sheds light on the way we live now&#8217; Independent.co.uk</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Full of ambition and humanity&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Allende knows that all stories are love stories, and the greatest love stories are told by time&#8217; Colum McCann</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Allende&#8217;s style is impressively Olympian and the payoff is remarkable&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Epic in scope, yet intimate in execution&#8217; i</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/">A Long Petal of the Sea : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Isabel Allende</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck and Capa&#8217;s account of their journey through Cold War Russia is a classic piece of reportage and travel writing. A Penguin Classic Just after the Iron Curtain fell on Eastern Europe, Pulitzer Prize-winning author John Steinbeck and acclaimed war photographer Robert Capa ventured into the Soviet Union to report for the New York Herald [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/">A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck and Capa&#8217;s account of their journey through Cold War Russia is a classic piece of reportage and travel writing. </p>
<p>                    A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    Just after the Iron Curtain fell on Eastern Europe, Pulitzer Prize-winning author John Steinbeck and acclaimed war photographer Robert Capa ventured into the Soviet Union to report for the New York Herald Tribune. This rare opportunity took the famous travelers not only to Moscow and Stalingrad &#8211; now Volgograd &#8211; but through the countryside of the Ukraine and the Caucasus. Hailed by the New York Times as superb when it first appeared in 1948, A Russian Journal is the distillation of their journey and remains a remarkable memoir and unique historical document.</p>
<p>                    What they saw and movingly recorded in words and on film was what Steinbeck called the great other side there &#8230; the private life of the Russian people. Unlike other Western reporting about Russia at the time, A Russian Journal is free of ideological obsessions. Rather, Steinbeck and Capa recorded the grim realities of factory workers, government clerks, and peasants, as they emerged from the rubble of World War II&#8211;represented here in Capa&#8217;s stirring photographs alongside Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful prose. Through it all, we are given intimate glimpses of two artists at the height of their powers, answering their need to document human struggle. This edition features an introduction by Steinbeck scholar Susan Shillinglaw.</p>
<p>                     For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/">A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Children of the Night : The Strange and Epic Story of Modern Romania &#8211; Paul Kenyon</title>
		<link>/children-of-the-night-the-strange-and-epic-story-of-modern-romania-paul-kenyon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/children-of-the-night-the-strange-and-epic-story-of-modern-romania-paul-kenyon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A vivid, brilliant, darkly humorous and horrifying history of some of the strangest dictators that Europe has ever seen. &#8216;A witty and page-turning narrative full of grotesque characters&#8217; Misha Glenny &#8216;Kenyon relates all this with verve [and] humour&#8230; He patiently untangles the complicated webs of loyalty and enmity&#8217; Literary Review &#8216;Absolutely essential reading for anyone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/children-of-the-night-the-strange-and-epic-story-of-modern-romania-paul-kenyon/">Children of the Night : The Strange and Epic Story of Modern Romania &#8211; Paul Kenyon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A vivid, brilliant, darkly humorous and horrifying history of some of the strangest dictators that Europe has ever seen. &#8216;A witty and page-turning narrative full of grotesque characters&#8217; Misha Glenny</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Kenyon relates all this with verve [and] humour&#8230; He patiently untangles the complicated webs of loyalty and enmity&#8217; Literary Review</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Absolutely essential reading for anyone interested in Romania past and present&#8217; John Simpson</p>
<p>                    Balanced precariously on the shifting fault line between East and West, Romania&#8217;s schizophrenic, often violent past is one of the great untold stories of modern Europe.</p>
<p>                    The country that gave us Vlad Dracula, and whose citizens consider themselves descendants of ancient Rome, has traditionally preferred the status of enigmatic outsider. But this beautiful and unexplored land has experienced some of the most disastrous leaderships of the last century.</p>
<p>                    After a relatively benign period led by a dutiful King and his vivacious British-born Queen, the country oscillated wildly. Its interwar rulers form a gallery of bizarre characters and extreme movements: the corrupt and mentally unbalanced King Carol; the fascist death cult led by Corneliu Codreanu; the vain General Ion Antonescu, who seized power in 1940 and led the country into a catastrophic alliance with Nazi Germany. After 1945 power was handed to Romania&#8217;s tiny communist party, under which it experienced severe repression, purges and collectivisation.</p>
<p>                    Then in 1965, Nicolae Ceausescu came to power. And thus began the strangest dictatorship of all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/children-of-the-night-the-strange-and-epic-story-of-modern-romania-paul-kenyon/">Children of the Night : The Strange and Epic Story of Modern Romania &#8211; Paul Kenyon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel With Children / Family Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* NOW WITH A NEW CHAPTER * &#8216;A hugely enjoyable romp through the pleasures and pitfalls of setting up home in a foreign land.&#8217;- Guardian Given the opportunity of a new life in rural Jutland, Helen Russell discovered a startling statistic: Denmark, land of long dark winters, cured herring, Lego and pastries, was the happiest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/">The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* NOW WITH A NEW CHAPTER *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A hugely enjoyable romp through the pleasures and pitfalls of setting up home in a foreign land.&#8217;- Guardian    </p>
<p>                    Given the opportunity of a new life in rural Jutland, Helen Russell discovered a startling statistic: Denmark, land of long dark winters, cured herring, Lego and pastries, was the happiest place on earth.    </p>
<p>                    Keen to know their secrets, Helen gave herself a year to uncover the formula for Danish happiness.    </p>
<p>                    From childcare, education, food and interior design to SAD and taxes, The Year of Living Danishly records a funny, poignant journey, showing us what the Danes get right, what they get wrong, and how we might all live a little more Danishly ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    In this new edition, six years on Helen reveals how her life and family have changed, and explores how Denmark, too &#8211; or. her understanding of it &#8211; has shifted. It&#8217;s a messy and flawed place, she concludes &#8211; but can still be a model for a better way of living.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/">The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food    </p>
<p>                    There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; whole grains are healthy, whole grains are a disaster; eat everything in moderation; eat only certain foods&#8212;and on and on. In 100 Million Years of Food, biological anthropologist Stephen Le explains how cuisines of different cultures are a result of centuries of evolution, finely tuned to our biology and surroundings. Today many cultures have strayed from their ancestral diets, relying instead on mass-produced food often made with chemicals that may be contributing to a rise in so-called Western diseases, such as cancer, heart disease, and obesity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Colour : Travels Through the Paintbox &#8211; Victoria Finlay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paintings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A rare and wonderful book&#8230; I could not be more enthusiastic.&#8217; Simon Winchester &#8216;A treasure trove of human history and obsession&#8230;the breadth of research and insight is dazzling.&#8217; Glasgow Herald Colour unlocks the history of the colours of the rainbow, and reveals how paints came to be invented, discovered, traded and used. This remarkable and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/">Colour : Travels Through the Paintbox &#8211; Victoria Finlay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A rare and wonderful book&#8230; I could not be more enthusiastic.&#8217; Simon Winchester    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A treasure trove of human history and obsession&#8230;the breadth of research and insight is dazzling.&#8217; Glasgow Herald    </p>
<p>                    Colour unlocks the history of the colours of the rainbow, and reveals how paints came to be invented, discovered, traded and used. This remarkable and beautifully written book, part travelogue part narrative history, remembers a time when red paint was really the colour of blood, when orange was the poison pigment, blue as expensive as gold, and yellow made from the urine of cows force-fed with mangoes. It looks at how green was carried by yaks along the silk road, and how an entire nation was founded on the colour purple.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A highly companionable guide, adventurous and romantic&#8217; Independent on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    Exciting, richly informative, and always surprising, Colour lifts the lid on the historical palette and unearths an astonishing wealth of stories about the quest for colours, and our efforts to understand them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/">Colour : Travels Through the Paintbox &#8211; Victoria Finlay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Geography of Genius : Lessons from the World&#8217;s Most Creative Places &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tag along on this New York Times bestselling &#8220;witty, entertaining romp&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) as Eric Winer travels the world, from Athens to Silicon Valley&#8211;and back through history, too&#8211;to show how creative genius flourishes in specific places at specific times. In this &#8220;intellectual odyssey, traveler&#8217;s diary, and comic novel all rolled into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/">The Geography of Genius : Lessons from the World&#8217;s Most Creative Places &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tag along on this New York Times bestselling &#8220;witty, entertaining romp&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) as Eric Winer travels the world, from Athens to Silicon Valley&#8211;and back through history, too&#8211;to show how creative genius flourishes in specific places at specific times.     </p>
<p>                    In this &#8220;intellectual odyssey, traveler&#8217;s diary, and comic novel all rolled into one&#8221; (Daniel Gilbert, author of Stumbling on Happiness), acclaimed travel writer Weiner sets out to examine the connection between our surroundings and our most innovative ideas. A &#8220;superb travel guide: funny, knowledgeable, and self-deprecating&#8221; (The Washington Post), he explores the history of places like Vienna of 1900, Renaissance Florence, ancient Athens, Song Dynasty Hangzhou, and Silicon Valley to show how certain urban settings are conducive to ingenuity. With his trademark insightful humor, this &#8220;big-hearted humanist&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal) walks the same paths as the geniuses who flourished in these settings to see if the spirit of what inspired figures like Socrates, Michelangelo, and Leonardo remains. In these places, Weiner asks, &#8220;What was in the air, and can we bottle it?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Fun and thought provoking&#8221; (Miami Herald), The Geography of Genius reevaluates the importance of culture in nurturing creativity and &#8220;offers a practical map for how we can all become a bit more inventive&#8221; (Adam Grant, author of Originals).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geography-of-genius-lessons-from-the-worlds-most-creative-places-eric-weiner-abridged/">The Geography of Genius : Lessons from the World&#8217;s Most Creative Places &#8211; Eric Weiner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Maps & Atlases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from the foreword     </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s nothing like vagabonding: taking time off from your normal life&#8211;from six weeks to four months to two years&#8211;to discover and experience the world on your own terms. In this one-of-a-kind handbook, veteran travel writer Rolf Potts explains how anyone armed with an independent spirit can achieve the dream of extended overseas travel. Now completely revised and updated, Vagabonding is an accessible and inspiring guide to     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; financing your travel time<br />
                     &#8211; determining your destination<br />
                     &#8211; adjusting to life on the road<br />
                     &#8211; working and volunteering overseas<br />
                     &#8211; handling travel adversity<br />
                     &#8211; re-assimilating back into ordinary life     </p>
<p>                     Praise for Vagabonding    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A crucial reference for any budget wanderer.&#8221;&#8211;Time    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The book is a meditation on the joys of hitting the road. . . . It&#8217;s also a primer for those with a case of pent-up wanderlust seeking to live the dream.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I couldn&#8217;t put this book down. It&#8217;s a whole different ethic of travel. . . . [Potts&#8217;s] practical advice might just convince you to enjoy that open-ended trip of a lifetime.&#8221;&#8211;Rick Steves     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Potts wants us to wander, to explore, to embrace the unknown, and, finally, to take our own damn time about it. I think this is the most sensible book of travel-related advice ever written.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Cahill, founding editor of Outside</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feng Shui]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Be more Zen in 2022 with this little book of 100 tips and activities to soothe the soul &#8216;Brings the spirit of Zen Buddhism to everyday life . . . 100 snack-size Zen activities you can do daily to add more calm to your life&#8217; Daily Telegraph _______ Zen is the perfect antidote to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/">Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Be more Zen in 2022 with this little book of 100 tips and activities to soothe the soul    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brings the spirit of Zen Buddhism to everyday life . . . 100 snack-size Zen activities you can do daily to add more calm to your life&#8217; Daily Telegraph<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    Zen is the perfect antidote to the stress and uncertainty of modern life . . .    </p>
<p>                    In clear, practical and easy to follow lessons &#8211; one a day for 100 days &#8211; renowned Buddhist monk Shunmyo Masuno draws on centuries of wisdom to show you how to apply the essence of Zen to modern life.    </p>
<p>                    You will learn how to exhale deeply to eliminate negative emotions, to arrange your house simply to clear your thinking, to line up your shoes at night to bring order to your mind, to plant a single flower and watch it grow, to worry less about what you cannot control, and so much more . . .    </p>
<p>                    You will even make time to think about nothing at all.    </p>
<p>                    Simplify your life with the art of Zen, and learn how to feel more relaxed, fulfilled, and with a renewed sense of peace.<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Full of the simplest yet richest rituals to adopt in order to live a long and happy life, this book of wisdom is a soothing balm of peace for anyone living in the busy modern world&#8217; Psychologies    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Does for mental clutter what Marie Kondo has done for household clutter&#8217; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This little treasure needs to be at every bedside&#8217; llan Lokos, author of Through the Flames, Patience, and Pocket Peace    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Zen: The Art of Simple Living makes the wisdom of the Buddha radically accessible&#8217; Dzogchen Ponlop Rinpoche, author of Emotional Rescue and Rebel Buddha</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/">Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When Women Ruled the World : Six Queens of Egypt &#8211; Kara Cooney (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/when-women-ruled-the-world-six-queens-of-egypt-kara-cooney-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/when-women-ruled-the-world-six-queens-of-egypt-kara-cooney-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This riveting narrative explores the lives of six remarkable female pharaohs, from Hatshepsut to Cleopatra&#8211;women who ruled with real power&#8211;and shines a piercing light on our own perceptions of women in power today. Female rulers are a rare phenomenon&#8211;but thousands of years ago in ancient Egypt, women reigned supreme. Regularly, repeatedly, and with impunity, queens [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-women-ruled-the-world-six-queens-of-egypt-kara-cooney-abridged/">When Women Ruled the World : Six Queens of Egypt &#8211; Kara Cooney (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This riveting narrative explores the lives of six remarkable female pharaohs, from Hatshepsut to Cleopatra&#8211;women who ruled with real power&#8211;and shines a piercing light on our own perceptions of women in power today.    </p>
<p>                     Female rulers are a rare phenomenon&#8211;but thousands of years ago in ancient Egypt, women reigned supreme. Regularly, repeatedly, and with impunity, queens like Hatshepsut, Nefertiti, and Cleopatra controlled the totalitarian state as power-brokers and rulers. But throughout human history, women in positions of power were more often used as political pawns in a male-dominated society. What was so special about ancient Egypt that provided women this kind of access to the highest political office? What was it about these women that allowed them to transcend patriarchal obstacles? What did Egypt gain from its liberal reliance on female leadership, and could today&#8217;s world learn from its example?     </p>
<p>                      Celebrated Egyptologist Kara Cooney delivers a fascinating tale of female power, exploring the reasons why it has seldom been allowed through the ages, and why we should care.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-women-ruled-the-world-six-queens-of-egypt-kara-cooney-abridged/">When Women Ruled the World : Six Queens of Egypt &#8211; Kara Cooney (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crafts & Hobbies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge &#8211; over one million copies sold** Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge  &#8211; over one million copies sold**    </p>
<p>                    Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness    </p>
<p>                    Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. In The Little Book of Lykke, he reveals what he has found.    </p>
<p>                    This captivating read features case studies from Bhutan to Australia, South Korea to Canada, France to Denmark, taking the reader on a happiness treasure hunt. Written in the same warm tone as Meik&#8217;s phenomenal bestseller The Little Book of Hygge, this easy-to-understand book will change the way you think about how you relate to your neighbours, the rituals around cooking and eating dinner, and when to book your next holiday &#8211; and is guaranteed to put a smile on your face.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is a happy book about happiness, written with a twinkle and packaged with Danish style&#8217; (John Helliwell, Economist and Editor of the World Happiness Report)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Down Under : Travels in a Sunburned Country &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/down-under-travels-in-a-sunburned-country-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/down-under-travels-in-a-sunburned-country-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It is the driest, flattest, hottest, most desiccated, infertile and climatically aggressive of all the inhabited continents and still Australia teems with life &#8211; a large portion of it quite deadly. In fact, Australia has more things that can kill you in a very nasty way than anywhere else. Ignoring such dangers &#8211; and yet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/down-under-travels-in-a-sunburned-country-bill-bryson-abridged/">Down Under : Travels in a Sunburned Country &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is the driest, flattest, hottest, most desiccated, infertile and climatically aggressive of all the inhabited continents and still Australia teems with life &#8211; a large portion of it quite deadly. In fact, Australia has more things that can kill you in a very nasty way than anywhere else.    </p>
<p>                    Ignoring such dangers &#8211; and yet curiously obsessed by them &#8211; Bill Bryson journeyed to Australia and promptly fell in love with the country. And who can blame him? The people are cheerful, extrovert, quick-witted and unfailingly obliging: their cities are safe and clean and nearly always built on water; the food is excellent; the beer is cold and the sun nearly always shines. Life doesn&#8217;t get much better than this&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/down-under-travels-in-a-sunburned-country-bill-bryson-abridged/">Down Under : Travels in a Sunburned Country &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Blue Zones Kitchen : 100 Recipes to Live to 100 &#8211; DAN BUETTNER (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-blue-zones-kitchen-100-recipes-to-live-to-100-dan-buettner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-blue-zones-kitchen-100-recipes-to-live-to-100-dan-buettner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Best-selling author Dan Buettner debuts his first cookbook, filled with 100 longevity recipes inspired by the Blue Zones locations around the world, where people live the longest. Building on decades of research, longevity guru Dan Buettner has gathered 100 recipes inspired by the Blue Zones, home to the healthiest and happiest communities in the world. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blue-zones-kitchen-100-recipes-to-live-to-100-dan-buettner-abridged/">The Blue Zones Kitchen : 100 Recipes to Live to 100 &#8211; DAN BUETTNER (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Best-selling author Dan Buettner debuts his first cookbook, filled with 100 longevity recipes inspired by the Blue Zones locations around the world, where people live the longest.    </p>
<p>                     Building on decades of research, longevity guru Dan Buettner has gathered 100 recipes inspired by the Blue Zones, home to the healthiest and happiest communities in the world. Each dish&#8211;for example, Sardinian Herbed Lentil Minestrone; Costa Rican Hearts of Palm Ceviche; Cornmeal Waffles from Loma Linda, California; and Okinawan Sweet Potatoes&#8211;uses ingredients and cooking methods proven to increase longevity, wellness, and mental health. Complemented by mouthwatering photography, the recipes also include lifestyle tips (including the best times to eat dinner and proper portion sizes), all gleaned from countries as far away as Japan and as near as Blue Zones project cities in Texas. Innovative, easy to follow, and delicious, these healthy living recipes make the Blue Zones lifestyle even more attainable, thereby improving your health, extending your life, and filling your kitchen with happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blue-zones-kitchen-100-recipes-to-live-to-100-dan-buettner-abridged/">The Blue Zones Kitchen : 100 Recipes to Live to 100 &#8211; DAN BUETTNER (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Sky Full of Birds &#8211; Matt Merritt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-sky-full-of-birds-matt-merritt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Birds & Birdwatching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-sky-full-of-birds-matt-merritt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Prose from a poet and a personal take on the spectacles&#8217; Chris Packham, author of Fingers in the Sparkle Jar Shortlisted for Richard Jefferies Society &#038; White Horse Bookshop Literary Prize 2017 Longlisted for the Wainwright Prize 2017 Britain is a nation of bird-lovers. However, few of us fully appreciate the sheer scale, variety and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-sky-full-of-birds-matt-merritt-abridged/">A Sky Full of Birds &#8211; Matt Merritt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prose from a poet and a personal take on the spectacles&#8217; Chris Packham, author of Fingers in the Sparkle Jar    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for Richard Jefferies Society &#038; White Horse Bookshop Literary Prize 2017<br />
                    Longlisted for the Wainwright Prize 2017    </p>
<p>                    Britain is a nation of bird-lovers. However, few of us fully appreciate the sheer scale, variety and drama of our avian life. From city-centre hunters to vast flocks straight out of the Arctic wilderness, much-loved dawn songsters to the exotic invaders of supermarket car parks, a host of remarkable wildlife spectacles are waiting to be discovered right outside our front doors.    </p>
<p>                    In A Sky Full of Birds, poet and nature writer Matt Merritt shares his passion for birdwatching by taking us to some of the great avian gatherings that occur around the British isles &#8211; from ravens in Anglesey and raptors on the Wirral, to Kent nightingales and Scottish capercaillies. By turns lyrical, informative and entertaining, he shows how natural miracles can be found all around us, if only we know where to look for them.    </p>
<p>                    A Sky Full of Birds is the perfect read for avid birdwatchers and a beautiful gift for lovers of nature and poetic prose.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-sky-full-of-birds-matt-merritt-abridged/">A Sky Full of Birds &#8211; Matt Merritt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Walk in the Woods : Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Outdoor Survival Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Walking, Hiking, Trekking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Appalachian Trail trail stretches from Georgia to Maine and covers some of the most breathtaking terrain in America-majestic mountains, silent forests, sparking lakes. If you&#8217;re going to take a hike, it&#8217;s probably the place to go. And Bill Bryson is surely the most entertaining guide you&#8217;ll find. He introduces us to the history and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/">A Walk in the Woods : Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Appalachian Trail trail stretches from Georgia to Maine and covers some of the most breathtaking terrain in America-majestic mountains, silent forests, sparking lakes. If you&#8217;re going to take a hike, it&#8217;s probably the place to go. And Bill Bryson is surely the most entertaining guide you&#8217;ll find. He introduces us to the history and ecology of the trail and to some of the other hardy (or just foolhardy) folks he meets along the way-and a couple of bears. Already a classic, A Walk in the Woods  will make you long for the great outdoors (or at least a comfortable chair to sit and read in).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-walk-in-the-woods-rediscovering-america-on-the-appalachian-trail-bill-bryson-abridged/">A Walk in the Woods : Rediscovering America on the Appalachian Trail &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes. &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world. Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen. 54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves. Norway is the richest country on earth. 5 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world.    </p>
<p>                    Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen.    </p>
<p>                    54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves.    </p>
<p>                    Norway is the richest country on earth.    </p>
<p>                    5 per cent of Danish men have had sex with an animal.    </p>
<p>                    Michael Booth has lived among the Scandinavians, on and off, for over ten years, perplexed by their many strange paradoxes and character traits and equally bemused by the unquestioning enthusiasm for all things Nordic and hygge that has engulfed the rest of the world.     </p>
<p>                    He leaves his adopted home of Denmark and embarks on a journey through all five of the Nordic countries to discover who these curious tribes are, the secrets of their success and, most intriguing of all, what they think of each other. Along the way a more nuanced, often darker picture emerges of a region plagued by taboos, characterised by suffocating parochialism and populated by extremists of various shades.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The next Bill Bryson.&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Best Narrative Travel Book Award from the British Guild of Travel Writers</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motorcycles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed as one of the most exciting books in the history of American letters, this modern epic became an instant bestseller upon publication in 1974, transforming a generation and continuing to inspire millions. A narration of a summer motorcycle trip undertaken by a father and his son, the book becomes a personal and philosophical odyssey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/">Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed as one of the most exciting books in the history of American letters, this modern epic became an instant bestseller upon publication in 1974, transforming a generation and continuing to inspire millions. A narration of a summer motorcycle trip undertaken by a father and his son, the book becomes a personal and philosophical odyssey into fundamental questions of how to live. Resonant with the confusions of existence, Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance is a touching and transcendent book of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/">Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER &#8216;Honest, funny and dripping with witty aphorisms. Extremely entertaining and enlightening [&#8230;] all the way to journey&#8217;s end&#8217; Herald One of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life, presents a travel guide [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Honest, funny and dripping with witty aphorisms. Extremely entertaining and enlightening [&#8230;] all the way to journey&#8217;s end&#8217; Herald     </p>
<p>                    One of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life, presents a travel guide with a difference &#8211; an exploration of why we travel, and what we learn along the way&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Few activities seem to promise as much happiness as going travelling: taking off for somewhere else, somewhere far from home, a place with more interesting weather, customs and landscapes. But although we are inundated with advice on where to travel to, we seldom ask why we go and how we might become more fulfilled by doing so.    </p>
<p>                    With the help of a selection of writers, artists and thinkers &#8211; including Flaubert, Edward Hopper, Wordsworth and Van Gogh &#8211; Alain de Botton provides invaluable insights into everything from holiday romance to hotel minibars, airports to sightseeing. The perfect antidote to those guides that tell us what to do when we get there, The Art of Travel tries to explain why we really went in the first place &#8211; and helpfully suggest how we might be happier on our journeys.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Delightful, profound, entertaining. I doubt if de Botton has written a dull sentence in his life&#8217; Jan Morris    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An elegant and subtle work, unlike any other. Beguiling&#8217; Colin Thubron, The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
