<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Earth Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/earth-sciences/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/earth-sciences/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Earth Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/earth-sciences/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life. Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211; probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life.     </p>
<p>                    Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of<br />
                    nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211;<br />
                    probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine rock formations and fossil charcoals<br />
                    all tell the same story. High oxygen levels may also explain the global firestorm that contributed to the<br />
                    demise of the dinosaurs after the asteroid impact.    </p>
<p>                    The strange and profound effects that oxygen has had on the evolution of life pose a riddle, which this book<br />
                    sets out to answer. Oxygen is a toxic gas. Divers breathing pure oxygen at depth suffer from convulsions<br />
                    and lung injury. Fruit flies raised at twice normal atmospheric levels of oxygen live half as long as their<br />
                    siblings. Reactive forms of oxygen, known as free radicals, are thought to cause ageing in people. Yet if<br />
                    atmospheric oxygen reached 35 per cent in the Carboniferous, why did it promote exuberant growth,<br />
                    instead of rapid ageing and death?    </p>
<p>                    Oxygen takes the reader on an enthralling journey, as gripping as a thriller, as it unravels the unexpected<br />
                    ways in which oxygen spurred the evolution of life and death. The book explains far more than the size of<br />
                    ancient insects: it shows how oxygen underpins the origin of biological complexity, the birth of photosynthesis, the sudden evolution of animals, the need for two sexes, the accelerated ageing of cloned animals like Dolly the sheep, and the surprisingly long lives of bats and birds.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on this grand evolutionary canvas, Oxygen offers fresh perspectives on our own lives and deaths,<br />
                    explaining modern killer diseases, why we age, and what we can do about it. Advancing revelatory new ideas,<br />
                    following chains of evidence, the book ranges through many disciplines, from environmental sciences to<br />
                    molecular medicine. The result is a captivating vision of contemporary science and a humane synthesis of our<br />
                    place in nature. This remarkable book might just redefine the way we think about the world.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A World Without Ice &#8211; Henry Pollack (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hydrology & The Hydrosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meteorology & Climatology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clear-eyed explanation of the impact of ice on Earth, its climate, and its residents. Much has been written about global warming, but the crucial relationship between people and ice has received little focus, until now &#8211; and there is a fierce urgency as the problem accelerates. With clarity and insight, geophysicist and a co-winner [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/">A World Without Ice &#8211; Henry Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clear-eyed explanation of the impact of ice on Earth, its climate, and its residents.      </p>
<p>                     Much has been written about global warming, but the crucial relationship between people and ice has received little focus, until now &#8211; and there is a fierce urgency as the problem accelerates. With clarity and insight, geophysicist and a co-winner of the 2007 Nobel Peace Prize, Henry Pollack, paints a compelling portrait of the delicate geological balance between Earth and its ice, and shows why the current rapid loss of ice portends serious consequences in our not-so-distant future.     </p>
<p>                     Whether sculpting mountains, regulating temperatures, influencing ocean currents, or defining the limits of human settlement, ice has shaped &#8211; and continues to shape &#8211; the world we live in. This important and increasingly relevant book traces the effect of mountain glaciers on supplies of drinking water and agricultural irrigation, as well as the current results of melting permafrost and shrinking Arctic sea ice &#8211; a situation that has degraded the habitat of numerous animals and sparked an international race for seabed oil and minerals. Catastrophic possibilities loom, including rising sea levels and subsequent flooding of low-lying regions worldwide.     </p>
<p>                     A World Without Ice explains why ice matters, and lays out the urgent actions we can take to restore Earth&#8217;s delicate climate balance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/">A World Without Ice &#8211; Henry Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geographical Discovery & Exploration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geology & The Lithosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Geography & Topography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** Winner of Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books 2015 ** We live in epoch-making times. The changes we humans have made in recent decades have altered our world beyond anything it has experienced in its 4.6 billion-year history. As a result, our planet is said to be crossing into the Anthropocene &#8211; the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/">Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** Winner of Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books 2015 **    </p>
<p>                    We live in epoch-making times. The changes we humans have made in recent decades have altered our world beyond anything it has experienced in its 4.6 billion-year history. As a result, our planet is said to be crossing into the Anthropocene &#8211; the Age of Humans.     </p>
<p>                     Gaia Vince decided to travel the world at the start of this new age to see what life is really like for the people on the frontline of the planet we&#8217;ve made.  From artificial glaciers in the Himalayas to painted mountains in Peru, electrified reefs in the Maldives to garbage islands in the Caribbean, Gaia found people doing the most extraordinary things to solve the problems that we ourselves have created.    </p>
<p>                     These stories show what the Anthropocene means for all of us &#8211; and they illuminate how we might engineer Earth for our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/">Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Knowledge : How To Rebuild Our World After An Apocalypse &#8211; Lewis Dartnell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-knowledge-how-to-rebuild-our-world-after-an-apocalypse-lewis-dartnell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-knowledge-how-to-rebuild-our-world-after-an-apocalypse-lewis-dartnell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If the world as we know it ended tomorrow, how would you survive? A nuclear war, viral pandemic or asteroid strike. The world as we know it has ended. You and the other survivors must start again. What knowledge would you need to start rebuilding civilisation from scratch? How do you grow food, generate power, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-knowledge-how-to-rebuild-our-world-after-an-apocalypse-lewis-dartnell-abridged/">The Knowledge : How To Rebuild Our World After An Apocalypse &#8211; Lewis Dartnell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If the world as we know it ended tomorrow, how would you survive?    </p>
<p>                    A nuclear war, viral pandemic or asteroid strike. The world as we know it has ended. You and the other survivors must start again. What knowledge would you need to start rebuilding civilisation from scratch?<br />
                    How do you grow food, generate power, prepare medicines, or get metal out of rocks? Could you avert another Dark Ages, or take shortcuts to accelerate redevelopment? Living in the modern world, we have become disconnected from the basic processes and key fundamentals of science that sustain our lives.    </p>
<p>                    Ingenious and groundbreaking, The Knowledge explains everything you need to know about everything, revolutionising your understanding of the world.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A glorious compendium of the knowledge we have lost in the living&#8230;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve read in a long time&#8217; Independent     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A terrifically engrossing history of science and technology&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    http://the-knowledge.org/</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-knowledge-how-to-rebuild-our-world-after-an-apocalypse-lewis-dartnell-abridged/">The Knowledge : How To Rebuild Our World After An Apocalypse &#8211; Lewis Dartnell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
