<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Society &amp; Social Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/society-social-sciences/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/society-social-sciences/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Society &amp; Social Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/society-social-sciences/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fear : Trump in the White House &#8211; Bob Woodward</title>
		<link>/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER THE OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR THE INSIDE STORY ON PRESIDENT TRUMP, AS ONLY BOB WOODWARD CAN TELL IT. &#8216;Fear is a meticulously researched account of a White House and a president in financial, legal and personal disorder&#8230;essential reading&#8230;&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;I think you&#8217;ve always been fair.&#8217; &#8211; President [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/">Fear : Trump in the White House &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER<br />
                    THE OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR</p>
<p>                     THE INSIDE STORY ON PRESIDENT TRUMP, AS ONLY BOB WOODWARD CAN TELL IT.</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fear is a meticulously researched account of a White House and a president in financial, legal and personal disorder&#8230;essential reading&#8230;&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I think you&#8217;ve always been fair.&#8217; &#8211; President Donald J. Trump, in a call to Bob Woodward, August 14, 2018</p>
<p>                     &#8216;The sheer weight of anecdotes depicts a man with no empathy and a pathological capacity for lying.&#8217; &#8211; The Financial Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fuelling his narrative is an astonishing cast of rogues, ideologues, self-made millionaires and men in uniform who have spent the past two years in and out of Trump&#8217;s administration.&#8217; &#8211; The Sunday Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Woodward&#8217;s meticulous account of office intrigues, the president&#8217;s men don&#8217;t seem to be trembling with fright.  What they mostly feel is contempt for Trump or pity for his ignorance and the &#8220;teenage logic&#8221; of his obsessively vented grievances.&#8217; &#8211; The Observer</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Horribly fascinating. Strongly recommended. If you can bear it.&#8217; Richard Dawkins</p>
<p>                     &#8216;To me the standout message from the book&#8230;is that the president is a bit clueless, a bit vain, a bit dangerous even; but his people are utterly at sea&#8230;&#8217; &#8211; Justin Webb, The Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;He is the master and I&#8217;d trust him over politicians of either party any day of the week.&#8217; -Peter Baker, New York Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;His work has been factually unassailable . . . In an age of &#8216;alternative facts&#8217; and corrosive tweets about &#8216;fake news,&#8217; Woodward is truth&#8217;s gold standard.&#8217; &#8211; Jill Abramson, The Washington Post</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fear depicts a White House awash in dysfunction, where the Lord of the Flies is the closest thing to an owner&#8217;s manual.&#8217; The Guardian</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I wonder how many journalists have arrived in Washington over the years dreaming of becoming the next Bob Woodward . . . Though his books are often sensational, he is the opposite of sensationalist. He&#8217;s diligent, rigorous, fastidious about the facts, and studiously ethical. There&#8217;s something almost monastic about his method . . . He&#8217;s Washington&#8217;s chronicler in chief.&#8217; &#8211;  Nick Bryant, BBC</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I&#8217;ve been on the receiving end of a Bob Woodward book. There were quotes in it I didn&#8217;t like. But never once-never-did I think Woodward made it up. Anonymous sources have looser lips and may take liberties. But Woodward always plays is straight. Someone told it to him.&#8217; &#8211; Ari Fleisher, White House Press Secretary for George W. Bush</p>
<p>                     With authoritative reporting honed through eight presidencies from Nixon to Obama, author Bob Woodward reveals in unprecedented detail the harrowing life inside President Donald Trump&#8217;s White House and precisely how he makes decisions on major foreign and domestic policies. Woodward draws from hundreds of hours of interviews with firsthand sources, meeting notes, personal diaries, files and documents. The focus is on the explosive debates and the decision-making in the Oval Office, the Situation Room, Air Force One and the White House residence.</p>
<p>                    Fear is the most intimate portrait of a sitting president ever published during the president&#8217;s first years in office.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/">Fear : Trump in the White House &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sex and Lies &#8211; Leila Slimani</title>
		<link>/sex-and-lies-leila-slimani/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Aspects Of Sexuality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sex-and-lies-leila-slimani/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first work of non-fiction in English from the prize-winning and internationally bestselling author of Lullaby and Adele, translated by Sophie Lewis. In these essays, Leila Slimani gives voice to young Moroccan women who are grappling with a conservative Arab culture that at once condemns and commodifies sex. In a country where the law punishes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-and-lies-leila-slimani/">Sex and Lies &#8211; Leila Slimani</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first work of non-fiction in English from the prize-winning and internationally bestselling author of Lullaby and Adele, translated by Sophie Lewis.     </p>
<p>                    In these essays, Leila Slimani gives voice to young Moroccan women who are grappling with a conservative Arab culture that at once condemns and commodifies sex. In a country where the law punishes and outlaws all forms of sex outside marriage, as well as homosexuality and prostitution, women have only two options for their sexual identities: virgin or wife. Sex and Lies is an essential confrontation with Morocco&#8217;s intimate demons and a vibrant appeal for the universal freedom to be, to love and to desire.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-and-lies-leila-slimani/">Sex and Lies &#8211; Leila Slimani</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fifth Risk : Undoing Democracy &#8211; Michael Lewis</title>
		<link>/the-fifth-risk-undoing-democracy-michael-lewis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fifth-risk-undoing-democracy-michael-lewis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Will set your hair on end&#8217; Telegraph, Top 50 Books of the Year &#8216;Life is what happens between Michael Lewis books. I forgot to breathe while reading The Fifth Risk&#8217; Michael Hofmann, TLS, Books of the Year The phenomenal new book from the international bestselling author of The Big Short &#8216;The election happened &#8230; And [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fifth-risk-undoing-democracy-michael-lewis/">The Fifth Risk : Undoing Democracy &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will set your hair on end&#8217; Telegraph, Top 50 Books of the Year</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Life is what happens between Michael Lewis books. I forgot to breathe while reading The Fifth Risk&#8217; Michael Hofmann, TLS, Books of the Year</p>
<p>                    The phenomenal new book from the international bestselling author of The Big Short</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The election happened &#8230; And then there was radio silence.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    The   morning after Trump was elected president, the people who ran the US   Department of Energy &#8211; an agency that deals with some of the most   powerful risks facing humanity &#8211; waited to welcome the incoming   administration&#8217;s transition team. Nobody appeared. Across the US   government, the same thing happened: nothing.</p>
<p>                    People don&#8217;t  notice  when stuff goes right. That is the stuff government does. It  manages  everything that underpins our lives from funding free school  meals, to  policing rogue nuclear activity, to predicting extreme  weather events.  It steps in where private investment fears to tread,  innovates and  creates knowledge, assesses extreme long-term risk. </p>
<p>                    And now, government is under attack. By its own leaders.</p>
<p>                    In The Fifth Risk,   Michael Lewis reveals the combustible cocktail of wilful ignorance and   venality that is fuelling the destruction of a country&#8217;s fabric. All  of  this, Lewis shows, exposes America and the world to the biggest risk  of  all. It is what you never learned that might have saved you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fifth-risk-undoing-democracy-michael-lewis/">The Fifth Risk : Undoing Democracy &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rage &#8211; Bob Woodward</title>
		<link>/rage-bob-woodward/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rage-bob-woodward/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BOB WOODWARD&#8217;S NEW BOOK, RAGE, IS AN UNPRECEDENTED AND INTIMATE TOUR DE FORCE OF NEW REPORTING ON THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY FACING A GLOBAL PANDEMIC, ECONOMIC DISASTER AND RACIAL UNREST. Woodward, the No 1 international bestselling author of Fear: Trump in the White House, has uncovered the precise moment the president was warned that the Covid-19 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rage-bob-woodward/">Rage &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BOB WOODWARD&#8217;S NEW BOOK, RAGE, IS AN UNPRECEDENTED AND INTIMATE TOUR DE FORCE OF NEW REPORTING ON THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY FACING A GLOBAL PANDEMIC, ECONOMIC DISASTER AND RACIAL UNREST.</p>
<p>                     Woodward, the No 1 international bestselling author of Fear: Trump in the White House, has uncovered the precise moment the president was warned that the Covid-19 epidemic would be the biggest national security threat to his presidency. In dramatic detail, Woodward takes readers into the Oval Office as Trump&#8217;s head pops up when he is told in January 2020 that the pandemic could reach the scale of the 1918 Spanish Flu that killed 675,000 Americans.</p>
<p>                     In 17 on-the-record interviews with Woodward over seven volatile months &#8211; an utterly vivid window into Trump&#8217;s mind &#8211; the president provides a self-portrait that is part denial and part combative interchange mixed with surprising moments of doubt as he glimpses the perils in the presidency and what he calls the &#8216;dynamite behind every door&#8217;. At key decision points, Rage shows how Trump&#8217;s responses to the crises of 2020 were rooted in the instincts, habits and style he developed during his first three years as president.</p>
<p>                     Revisiting the earliest days of the Trump presidency, Rage reveals how Secretary of Defense James Mattis, Secretary of State Rex Tillerson and Director of National Intelligence Dan Coats struggled to keep the country safe as the president dismantled any semblance of collegial national security decision making. Rage draws from hundreds of hours of interviews with first-hand witnesses as well as participants&#8217; notes, emails, diaries, calendars and confidential documents.</p>
<p>                     Woodward obtained 25 never-seen personal letters exchanged between Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, who describes the bond between the two leaders as out of a &#8216;fantasy film&#8217;. Trump insists to Woodward he will triumph over Covid-19 and the economic calamity. &#8216;Don&#8217;t worry about it, Bob. Okay?&#8217; Trump told the author in July. &#8216;Don&#8217;t worry about it. We&#8217;ll get to do another book. You&#8217;ll find I was right.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rage-bob-woodward/">Rage &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sapiens : A Brief History of Humankind &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</title>
		<link>/sapiens-a-brief-history-of-humankind-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sapiens-a-brief-history-of-humankind-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**THE MULTI-MILLION COPY BESTSELLER** &#8216;Interesting and provocative&#8230; It gives you a sense of how briefly we&#8217;ve been on this Earth&#8217; Barack Obama What makes us brilliant? What makes us deadly? What makes us Sapiens? Yuval Noah Harari challenges everything we know about being human. Earth is 4.5 billion years old. In just a fraction of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sapiens-a-brief-history-of-humankind-yuval-noah-harari/">Sapiens : A Brief History of Humankind &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**THE MULTI-MILLION COPY BESTSELLER**</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Interesting and provocative&#8230; It gives you a sense of how briefly we&#8217;ve been on this Earth&#8217; Barack Obama</p>
<p>                    What makes us brilliant? What makes us deadly? What makes us Sapiens?</p>
<p>                    Yuval Noah Harari challenges everything we know about being human.</p>
<p>                    Earth is 4.5 billion years old. In just a fraction of that time, one species among countless others has conquered it: us.</p>
<p>                    In this bold and provocative book, Yuval Noah Harari explores who we are, how we got here and where we&#8217;re going. </p>
<p>                    ________________</p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR SAPIENS:</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jaw-dropping from the first word to the last&#8230; It may be the best book I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; Chris Evans</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Sweeps the cobwebs out of your brain&#8230; Radiates power and clarity&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It altered how I view our species and our world&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Startling&#8230; It changes the way you look at the world&#8217; Simon Mayo</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I would recommend Sapiens to anyone who&#8217;s interested in the history and future of our species&#8217; Bill Gates</p>
<p>                    **ONE OF THE GUARDIAN&#8217;S 100 BEST BOOKS OF THE 21st CENTURY**</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sapiens-a-brief-history-of-humankind-yuval-noah-harari/">Sapiens : A Brief History of Humankind &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Winners Take All : The Elite Charade of Changing the World &#8211; Anand Giridharadas</title>
		<link>/winners-take-all-the-elite-charade-of-changing-the-world-anand-giridharadas/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/winners-take-all-the-elite-charade-of-changing-the-world-anand-giridharadas/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*The International Bestseller* &#8216;Superb, hugely enjoyable &#8230; a spirited examination of the hubris and hypocrisy of the super-rich who claim they are helping the world&#8217; Aditya Chakrabortty, Guardian What explains the spreading backlash against the global elite? In this revelatory investigation, Anand Giridharadas takes us into the inner sanctums of a new gilded age, showing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/winners-take-all-the-elite-charade-of-changing-the-world-anand-giridharadas/">Winners Take All : The Elite Charade of Changing the World &#8211; Anand Giridharadas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*The International Bestseller*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Superb, hugely enjoyable &#8230; a spirited examination of the hubris and  hypocrisy of the super-rich who claim they are helping the world&#8217; Aditya  Chakrabortty, Guardian    </p>
<p>                    What explains the spreading backlash against the global elite? In this revelatory investigation, Anand Giridharadas takes us into the inner sanctums of a new gilded age, showing how the elite follow a &#8216;win-win&#8217; logic, fighting for equality and justice any way they can &#8211; except ways that threaten their position at the top.     </p>
<p>                    But why should our gravest problems be solved by consultancies, technology companies and corporate-sponsored charities instead of public institutions and elected officials? Why should we rely on scraps from the winners? Trenchant and gripping, this is an indispensable guide and call to action for elites and citizens alike.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/winners-take-all-the-elite-charade-of-changing-the-world-anand-giridharadas/">Winners Take All : The Elite Charade of Changing the World &#8211; Anand Giridharadas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Virtual Light &#8211; William Gibson</title>
		<link>/virtual-light-william-gibson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/virtual-light-william-gibson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES bestseller * 2005: Welcome to NoCal and SoCal, the uneasy sister-states of what used to be California. The millennium has come and gone, leaving in its wake only stunned survivors. In Los Angeles, Berry Rydell is a former armed-response rentacop now working for a bounty hunter. Chevette Washington is a bicycle messenger [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/virtual-light-william-gibson/">Virtual Light &#8211; William Gibson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES bestseller * 2005: Welcome to NoCal and SoCal, the uneasy sister-states of what used to be California. </p>
<p>                    The millennium has come and gone, leaving in its wake only stunned survivors. In Los Angeles, Berry Rydell is a former armed-response rentacop now working  for a bounty hunter. Chevette Washington is a  bicycle messenger turned pickpocket who impulsively  snatches a pair of innocent-looking sunglasses. But  these are no ordinary shades. What you can see  through these high-tech specs can make you rich-or  get you killed. Now Berry and Chevette are on the  run, zeroing in on the digitalized heart of  DatAmerica, where pure information is the greatest high.  And a mind can be a terrible thing to crash. . . . </p>
<p>                    Praise for Virtual Light</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Both exhilarating and terrifying . . . Although considered the master of &#8216;cyberpunk&#8217; science fiction, William Gibson is also one fine suspense writer.&#8221;-People</p>
<p>                    &#8220;A stunner . . . A terrifically stylish burst of kick-butt imagination.&#8221;-Entertainment Weekly</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Convincing . . . frightening . . . Virtual Light is written with a sense of craft, a sense of humor and a sense of the ultimate seriousness of the problems it explores.&#8221;-Chicago Tribune</p>
<p>                    &#8220;In the emerging pop culture of the information age, Gibson is the brightest star.&#8221;-The San Diego Union-Tribune</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/virtual-light-william-gibson/">Virtual Light &#8211; William Gibson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</title>
		<link>/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER** In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER**</p>
<p>                    In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay</p>
<p>                    How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake news or the threat of terrorism? What should we teach our children? </p>
<p>                    Yuval Noah Harari takes us on a thrilling journey through today&#8217;s most urgent issues. The golden thread running through his exhilarating new book is the challenge of maintaining our collective and individual focus in the face of constant and disorienting change.</p>
<p>                    Are we still capable of understanding the world we have created?</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating&#8230; compelling&#8230; [Harari] has teed up a crucial global conversation about how to take on the problems of the 21st century&#8217; Bill Gates, New York Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Truly mind-expanding&#8230; Ultra-topical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</title>
		<link>/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. </p>
<p>                    The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level official. With almost daily access to the President, John Bolton has produced a precise rendering of his days in and around the Oval Office. What Bolton saw astonished him: a President for whom getting reelected was the only thing that mattered, even if it meant endangering or weakening the nation. &#8220;I am hard-pressed to identify any significant Trump decision during my tenure that wasn&#8217;t driven by reelection calculations,&#8221; he writes. In fact, he argues that the House committed impeachment malpractice by keeping their prosecution focused narrowly on Ukraine when Trump&#8217;s Ukraine-like transgressions existed across the full range of his foreign policy-and Bolton documents exactly what those were, and attempts by him and others in the Administration to raise alarms about them.</p>
<p>                    He shows a President addicted to chaos, who embraced our enemies and spurned our friends, and was deeply suspicious of his own government. In Bolton&#8217;s telling, all this helped put Trump on the bizarre road to impeachment. &#8220;The differences between this presidency and previous ones I had served were stunning,&#8221; writes Bolton, who worked for Reagan, Bush 41, and Bush 43. He discovered a President who thought foreign policy is like closing a real estate deal-about personal relationships, made-for-TV showmanship, and advancing his own interests. As a result, the US lost an opportunity to confront its deepening threats, and in cases like China, Russia, Iran, and North Korea ended up in a more vulnerable place. </p>
<p>                    Bolton&#8217;s account starts with his long march to the West Wing as Trump and others woo him for the National Security job. The minute he lands, he has to deal with Syria&#8217;s chemical attack on the city of Douma, and the crises after that never stop. As he writes in the opening pages, &#8220;If you don&#8217;t like turmoil, uncertainty, and risk-all the while being constantly overwhelmed with information, decisions to be made, and sheer amount of work-and enlivened by international and domestic personality and ego conflicts beyond description, try something else.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    The turmoil, conflicts, and egos are all there-from the upheaval in Venezuela, to the erratic and manipulative moves of North Korea&#8217;s Kim Jong Un, to the showdowns at the G7 summits, the calculated warmongering by Iran, the crazy plan to bring the Taliban to Camp David, and the placating of an authoritarian China that ultimately exposed the world to its lethal lies. But this seasoned public servant also has a great eye for the Washington inside game, and his story is full of wit and wry humor about how he saw it played.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Future Crimes : Inside The Digital Underground and the Battle For Our Connected World &#8211; Marc Goodman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER * * Future-proof yourself and your business by reading this book * Technological advances have benefited our world in immeasurable ways, but there is an ominous flipside. Criminals are often the earliest, and most innovative, adopters of technology and modern times have led to modern crimes. Today&#8217;s criminals are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/">Future Crimes : Inside The Digital Underground and the Battle For Our Connected World &#8211; Marc Goodman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER *    </p>
<p>                    * Future-proof yourself and your business by reading this book *     </p>
<p>                    Technological advances have benefited our world in immeasurable ways, but there is an ominous flipside. Criminals are often the earliest, and most innovative, adopters of technology and modern times have led to modern crimes. Today&#8217;s criminals are stealing identities, draining online bank-accounts and wiping out computer servers.  It&#8217;s disturbingly easy to activate baby cam monitors to spy on families, pacemakers can be hacked to deliver a lethal jolt, and thieves are analyzing your social media in order to determine the best time for a home invasion.    </p>
<p>                    Meanwhile, 3D printers produce AK-47s, terrorists can download the recipe for the Ebola virus, and drug cartels are building drones. This is just the beginning of the tsunami of technological threats coming our way.  In Future Crimes, Marc Goodman rips open his database of hundreds of real cases to give us front-row access to these impending perils. Reading like a sci-fi thriller, but based in startling fact, Goodman raises tough questions about the expanding role of technology in our lives. Future Crimes is a call to action for better security measures worldwide, but most importantly, will empower readers to protect themselves against these looming technological threats &#8211; before it&#8217;s too late.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/">Future Crimes : Inside The Digital Underground and the Battle For Our Connected World &#8211; Marc Goodman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why I&#8217;m No Longer Talking to White People About Race : The #1 Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Reni Eddo-Lodge (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-im-no-longer-talking-to-white-people-about-race-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-reni-eddo-lodge-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-im-no-longer-talking-to-white-people-about-race-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-reni-eddo-lodge-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every voice raised against racism chips away at its power. We can&#8217;t afford to stay silent. This book is an attempt to speak&#8217; The book that sparked a national conversation. Exploring everything from eradicated black history to the inextricable link between class and race, Why I&#8217;m No Longer Talking to White People About Race is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-im-no-longer-talking-to-white-people-about-race-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-reni-eddo-lodge-abridged/">Why I&#8217;m No Longer Talking to White People About Race : The #1 Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Reni Eddo-Lodge (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every voice raised against racism chips away at its power. We can&#8217;t afford to stay silent. This book is an attempt to speak&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    The book that sparked a national conversation. Exploring everything from eradicated black history to the inextricable link between class and race, Why I&#8217;m No Longer Talking to White People About Race is the essential handbook for anyone who wants to understand race relations in Britain today.    </p>
<p>                    THE NO.1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    WINNER OF THE BRITISH BOOK AWARDS NON-FICTION NARRATIVE BOOK OF THE YEAR 2018<br />
                    FOYLES NON-FICTION BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    BLACKWELL&#8217;S NON-FICTION BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    WINNER OF THE JHALAK PRIZE<br />
                    LONGLISTED FOR THE BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION<br />
                    LONGLISTED FOR THE ORWELL PRIZE<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR A BOOKS ARE MY BAG READERS AWARD</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-im-no-longer-talking-to-white-people-about-race-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-reni-eddo-lodge-abridged/">Why I&#8217;m No Longer Talking to White People About Race : The #1 Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Reni Eddo-Lodge (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year! &#8216;Will snare you in its web of deceit &#8230; A brilliant investigative expose&#8217; &#8211; Harlan Coben, bestselling thriller author &#8216;Reads like a fast-paced John le Carre thriller, and never lets up&#8217; &#8211; New York Times book review The Spider Network is the almost-unbelievable and darkly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/">The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year!    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Will snare you in its web of deceit &#8230; A brilliant investigative expose&#8217; &#8211; Harlan Coben, bestselling thriller author     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Reads like a fast-paced John le Carre thriller, and never lets up&#8217; &#8211; New York Times book review     </p>
<p>                    The Spider Network is the almost-unbelievable and darkly entertaining inside account of the Libor scandal &#8211; one of the biggest, farthest-reaching financial scams since the global financial crisis &#8211; written by the only journalist with access to Tom Hayes before he was sentenced to fourteen years in prison.   Full of exclusive details, and with ramifications that stretch right across the British establishment, this is a gripping, real-life story of outlandish characters and reckless greed in the City of London.     </p>
<p>                    By turns a rollicking account of the scandal and also a provocative examination of a financial system that was crooked throughout, The Spider Network is a perfect read for fans of The Wolf of Wall Street and The Big Short.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/">The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Asking : How I learned to stop worrying and let people help &#8211; Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History: From c 1960]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>REDISCOVER THE FORGOTTEN ART OF ASKING IN THIS NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING BOOK &#8216;Amanda Palmer joyfully shows a generation how to change their lives&#8217; Caitlin Moran &#8216;To read Amanda Palmer&#8217;s remarkable memoir about asking and giving is to tumble headlong into her world&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert &#8216;The Art of Asking is a book about cultivating trust [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/">The Art of Asking : How I learned to stop worrying and let people help &#8211; Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>REDISCOVER THE FORGOTTEN ART OF ASKING IN THIS NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING BOOK     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Amanda Palmer joyfully shows a generation how to change their lives&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;To read Amanda Palmer&#8217;s remarkable memoir about asking and giving is to tumble headlong into her world&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The Art of Asking is a book about cultivating trust and getting as close as possible to love, vulnerability, and connection. Uncomfortably close. Dangerously close. Beautifully close&#8217; Brene Brown    </p>
<p>                    Imagine standing on a box in the middle of a busy city, dressed as a white-faced bride, and silently using your eyes to ask people for money. Or touring Europe in a punk cabaret band, and finding a place to sleep each night by reaching out to strangers on Twitter. For Amanda Palmer, actions like these have gone beyond satisfying her basic needs for food and shelter &#8211; they&#8217;ve taught her how to turn strangers into friends, build communities, and discover her own giving impulses. And because she had learned how to ask, she was able to go to the world to ask for the money to make a new album and tour with it, and to raise over a million dollars in a month.    </p>
<p>                    In the New York TImes bestseller The Art of Asking, Palmer expands upon her popular TED talk to reveal how ordinary people, those of us without thousands of Twitter followers and adoring fans, can use these same principles in our own lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/">The Art of Asking : How I learned to stop worrying and let people help &#8211; Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Black Swan : The Impact of the Highly Improbable &#8211; Nassim Nicholas Taleb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-black-swan-the-impact-of-the-highly-improbable-nassim-nicholas-taleb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Risk Assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-black-swan-the-impact-of-the-highly-improbable-nassim-nicholas-taleb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The phenomenal international bestseller that shows us how to stop trying to predict everything &#8211; and take advantage of uncertainty What have the invention of the wheel, Pompeii, the Wall Street Crash, Harry Potter and the internet got in common? Why are all forecasters con-artists? Why should you never run for a train or read [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-black-swan-the-impact-of-the-highly-improbable-nassim-nicholas-taleb-abridged/">The Black Swan : The Impact of the Highly Improbable &#8211; Nassim Nicholas Taleb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The phenomenal international bestseller that shows us how to stop trying to predict everything &#8211; and take advantage of uncertainty    </p>
<p>                    What have the invention of the wheel, Pompeii, the Wall Street Crash, Harry Potter and the internet got in common? Why are all forecasters  con-artists? Why should you never run for a train or read a newspaper?     </p>
<p>                    This book is all about Black Swans: the random events that underlie our lives, from bestsellers to world disasters. Their impact is huge; they&#8217;re impossible to predict; yet after they happen we always try to rationalize them.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Taleb is a bouncy and even exhilarating  guide &#8230; I came to relish what he said, and even develop a sneaking affection for him as a person&#8217; Will Self, Independent on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;He leaps like some superhero of the mind&#8217; Boyd Tonkin, Independent</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-black-swan-the-impact-of-the-highly-improbable-nassim-nicholas-taleb-abridged/">The Black Swan : The Impact of the Highly Improbable &#8211; Nassim Nicholas Taleb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed &#8211; Jon Ronson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Jon Ronson, the Sunday Times top ten bestselling author of The Psychopath Test, this is a captivating and brilliant exploration of one of our world&#8217;s most underappreciated forces: shame. &#8216;It&#8217;s about the terror, isn&#8217;t it?&#8217; &#8216;The terror of what?&#8217; I said. &#8216;The terror of being found out.&#8217; Jon Ronson has travelled the world meeting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/">So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed &#8211; Jon Ronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Jon Ronson, the Sunday Times top ten bestselling author of The Psychopath Test, this is a captivating and brilliant exploration of one of our world&#8217;s most underappreciated forces: shame.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s about the terror, isn&#8217;t it?&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;The terror of what?&#8217; I said.<br />
                    &#8216;The terror of being found out.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Jon Ronson has travelled the world meeting recipients of high-profile public shamings. The shamed are people like us &#8211; people who, say, made a joke on social media that came out badly, or made a mistake at work. Once their transgression is revealed, collective outrage circles with the force of a hurricane and the next thing they know they&#8217;re being torn apart by an angry mob, jeered at, demonized, sometimes even fired from their job.    </p>
<p>                    A great renaissance of public shaming is sweeping our land. Justice has been democratized. The silent majority are getting a voice. But what are we doing with our voice? We are mercilessly finding people&#8217;s faults. We are defining the boundaries of normality by ruining the lives of those outside it. We are using shame as a form of social control.    </p>
<p>                    Simultaneously powerful and hilarious in the way only Jon Ronson can be, So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed is a deeply honest book about modern life, full of eye-opening truths about the escalating war on human flaws &#8211; and the very scary part we all play in it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/">So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed &#8211; Jon Ronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historiography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Liberation & Independence, Post-colonialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton In this highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our  understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton    </p>
<p>                    In this  highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of  Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a  powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for writers, philosophers  and colonial administrators to deal with the &#8216;otherness&#8217; of eastern  culture, customs and beliefs. He traces this view through the writings  of Homer, Nerval and Flaubert, Disraeli and Kipling, whose imaginative  depictions have greatly contributed to the West&#8217;s romantic and exotic  picture of the Orient. Drawing on his own experiences as an Arab  Palestinian living in the West, Said examines how these ideas can be a  reflection of European imperialism and racism.<br />
                    &#8216;Beautifully patterned and passionately argued&#8217;<br />
                    New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Very exciting &#8230; his case is not merely persuasive, but conclusive&#8217;<br />
                    John Leonard, New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Headscarves and Hymens : Why the Middle East Needs a Sexual Revolution &#8211; Mona Eltahawy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shocking, heartfelt and well-researched&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;A ground-shaping book that defines the edge of so many vital contemporary debates. Hers is a voice simultaneously behind and beyond the veil&#8217; Colum McCann &#8216;A fascinating, can&#8217;t-look-away, whistle-stop tour of the Middle East&#8217; Daily Telegraph &#8216;Brave and impassioned . . . A shocking book, and one that will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/">Headscarves and Hymens : Why the Middle East Needs a Sexual Revolution &#8211; Mona Eltahawy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shocking, heartfelt and well-researched&#8217; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A ground-shaping book that defines the edge of so many vital contemporary debates. Hers is a voice simultaneously behind and beyond the veil&#8217; Colum McCann    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fascinating, can&#8217;t-look-away, whistle-stop tour of the Middle East&#8217; Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brave and impassioned . . . A shocking book, and one that will make anyone who has seen veiling as a cultural issue think very hard about what is really going on&#8217; Mail on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    Headscarves and Hymens explodes the myth that we should stand back and watch while women are disempowered and abused in the name of religion.    </p>
<p>                     In this laceratingly honest account, Eltahawy takes aim both at attitudes in the Middle East and at the western liberals who mistake misogyny for cultural difference. Her argument is clear: unless political revolution in the Arab world is accompanied by social and sexual revolution, no progress will be made.    </p>
<p>                    Headscarves and Hymens is the book the world has been crying out for: a powerful, fearless account of what it really means to be a woman in the Muslim world.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A fascinating, can&#8217;t-look-away, whistle-stop tour of the Middle East&#8217; Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brave and impassioned . . . A shocking book, and one that will make anyone who has seen veiling as a cultural issue think very hard about what is really going on&#8217; Mail on Sunday</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/headscarves-and-hymens-why-the-middle-east-needs-a-sexual-revolution-mona-eltahawy-abridged/">Headscarves and Hymens : Why the Middle East Needs a Sexual Revolution &#8211; Mona Eltahawy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN* A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood<br />
                    &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson<br />
                    &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson    </p>
<p>                    *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN*    </p>
<p>                    A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey that helped change the world.    </p>
<p>                    Hollywood was talking as never before. Kantor and Twohey outmanoeuvred Harvey Weinstein, his team of defenders and private investigators, convincing some of the most famous women in the world &#8211; and some unknown ones &#8211; to go on the record. Three years later, it helped lead to his conviction.    </p>
<p>                    This is how they did it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hunger : A Memoir of (My) Body &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hunger-a-memoir-of-my-body-roxane-gay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hunger-a-memoir-of-my-body-roxane-gay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I ate and ate and ate in the hopes that if I made myself big, my body would be safe. I buried the girl I was because she ran into all kinds of trouble. I tried to erase every memory of her, but she is still there, somewhere. . . . I was trapped in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hunger-a-memoir-of-my-body-roxane-gay-abridged/">Hunger : A Memoir of (My) Body &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I ate and ate and ate in the hopes that if I made myself big, my body would be safe. I buried the girl I was because she ran into all kinds of trouble. I tried to erase every memory of her, but she is still there, somewhere. . . . I was trapped in my body, one that I barely recognized or understood, but at least I was safe.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    New York Times bestselling author Roxane Gay has written with intimacy and sensitivity about food and bodies, using her own emotional and psychological struggles as a means of exploring our shared anxieties over pleasure, consumption, appearance, and health. As a woman who describes her own body as &#8220;wildly undisciplined,&#8221; Roxane understands the tension between desire and denial, between self-comfort and self-care. In Hunger, she casts an insightful and critical eye on her childhood, teens, and twenties-including the devastating act of violence that acted as a turning point in her young life-and brings readers into the present and the realities, pains, and joys of her daily life.    </p>
<p>                    With the bracing candor, vulnerability, and authority that have made her one of the most admired voices of her generation, Roxane explores what it means to be overweight in a time when the bigger you are, the less you are seen. Hunger is a deeply personal memoir from one of our finest writers, and tells a story that hasn&#8217;t yet been told but needs to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hunger-a-memoir-of-my-body-roxane-gay-abridged/">Hunger : A Memoir of (My) Body &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soonish : Ten Emerging Technologies That Will Improve and/or Ruin Everything &#8211; Dr. Kelly Weinersmith, Zach Weinersmith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/soonish-ten-emerging-technologies-that-will-improve-and-or-ruin-everything-dr-kelly-weinersmith-zach-weinersmith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cartoons & Comic Strips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Engineering: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/soonish-ten-emerging-technologies-that-will-improve-and-or-ruin-everything-dr-kelly-weinersmith-zach-weinersmith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What will the world of tomorrow be like? How does progress happen? And why don&#8217;t we have a lunar colony already? In this witty and entertaining book, Kelly and Zach Weinersmith give us a snapshot of the transformative technologies that are coming next &#8211; from robot swarms to nuclear fusion powered-toasters &#8211; and explain how [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soonish-ten-emerging-technologies-that-will-improve-and-or-ruin-everything-dr-kelly-weinersmith-zach-weinersmith-abridged/">Soonish : Ten Emerging Technologies That Will Improve and/or Ruin Everything &#8211; Dr. Kelly Weinersmith, Zach Weinersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What will the world of tomorrow be like? How does progress happen? And why don&#8217;t we have a lunar colony already? In this witty and entertaining book, Kelly and Zach Weinersmith give us a snapshot of the transformative technologies that are coming next &#8211; from robot swarms to nuclear fusion powered-toasters &#8211; and explain how they will change our world in astonishing ways. By weaving together their own research, interviews with pioneering scientists and Zach&#8217;s trademark comics, the Weinersmiths investigate why these innovations are needed, how they would work, and what is standing in their way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soonish-ten-emerging-technologies-that-will-improve-and-or-ruin-everything-dr-kelly-weinersmith-zach-weinersmith-abridged/">Soonish : Ten Emerging Technologies That Will Improve and/or Ruin Everything &#8211; Dr. Kelly Weinersmith, Zach Weinersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Political Order and Political Decay : From the Industrial Revolution to the Globalisation of Democracy &#8211; Francis Fukuyama (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Origins of Political Order, Francis Fukuyama took us from the dawn of mankind to the French and American Revolutions. Here, he picks up the thread again in the second instalment of his definitive account of mankind&#8217;s emergence as a political animal. This is the story of how state, law and democracy developed after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/">Political Order and Political Decay : From the Industrial Revolution to the Globalisation of Democracy &#8211; Francis Fukuyama (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Origins of Political Order, Francis Fukuyama took us from the dawn of mankind to the French and American Revolutions.  Here, he picks up the thread again in the second instalment of his definitive account of mankind&#8217;s emergence as a political animal.    </p>
<p>                    This is the story of how state, law and democracy developed after these cataclysmic events, how the modern landscape &#8211; with its uneasy tension between dictatorships and liberal democracies &#8211; evolved and how in the United States and in other developed democracies, unmistakable signs of decay have emerged.     </p>
<p>                    If we want to understand the political systems that dominate and order our lives, we must first address their origins &#8211; in our own recent past as well as in the earliest systems of human government. Fukuyama argues that the key to successful government can be reduced to three key elements: a strong state, the rule of law and institutions of democratic accountability.    </p>
<p>                    This magisterial account is required reading for anyone wishing to know more about mankind&#8217;s greatest achievements.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/">Political Order and Political Decay : From the Industrial Revolution to the Globalisation of Democracy &#8211; Francis Fukuyama (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bad Feminist &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bad-feminist-roxane-gay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bad-feminist-roxane-gay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Roxane Gay is so great at weaving the intimate and personal with what is most bewildering and upsetting at this moment in culture. She is always looking, always thinking, always passionate, always careful, always right there.&#8221; &#8212; Sheila Heti, author of How Should a Person Be? A New York Times Bestseller Best Book of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bad-feminist-roxane-gay-abridged/">Bad Feminist &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Roxane Gay is so great at weaving the intimate and personal with what is most bewildering and upsetting at this moment in culture. She is always looking, always thinking, always passionate, always careful, always right there.&#8221; &#8212; Sheila Heti, author of How Should a Person Be?    </p>
<p>                    A New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Best Book of the Year: NPR &#8211; Boston Globe &#8211; Newsweek &#8211; Time Out New York &#8211; Oprah.com &#8211; Miami Herald &#8211; Book Riot &#8211; Buzz Feed &#8211; Globe and Mail (Toronto) &#8211; The Root &#8211; Shelf Awareness    </p>
<p>                    A collection of essays spanning politics, criticism, and feminism from one of the most-watched cultural observers of her generation    </p>
<p>                    In these funny and insightful essays, Gay takes us through the journey of her evolution as a woman (Sweet Valley High) of color (The Help) while also taking readers on a ride through culture of the last few years (Girls, Django in Chains) and commenting on the state of feminism today (abortion, Chris Brown). The portrait that emerges is not only one of an incredibly insightful woman continually growing to understand herself and our society, but also one of our culture.    </p>
<p>                    Bad Feminist is a sharp, funny, and spot-on look at the ways in which the culture we consume becomes who we are, and an inspiring call-to-arms of all the ways we still need to do better, coming from one of our most interesting and important cultural critics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bad-feminist-roxane-gay-abridged/">Bad Feminist &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime in Progress : The Secret History of the Trump-Russia Investigation &#8211; Glenn Simpson, Peter Fritsch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Campaigning & Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** The never-before-told inside story of the Steele Dossier and the Trump-Russia investigation &#8216;The best procedural yet written about the discovery of Trump&#8217;s Russia ties&#8217; New York Times In the autumn of 2015, the founders of the Washington-based intelligence firm Fusion GPS, Glenn Simpson and Peter Fritsch, were hired by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/">Crime in Progress : The Secret History of the Trump-Russia Investigation &#8211; Glenn Simpson, Peter Fritsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**<br />
                    The never-before-told inside story of the Steele Dossier and the Trump-Russia investigation    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The best procedural yet written about the discovery of Trump&#8217;s Russia ties&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    In the autumn of 2015, the founders of the Washington-based intelligence firm Fusion GPS, Glenn Simpson and Peter Fritsch, were hired by a republican client to look into the records of Donald Trump. What began as a march through a mind-boggling trove of lawsuits and sketchy overseas projects soon took a darker turn, as they became the first to uncover Trump&#8217;s disturbing ties to the Kremlin and the crimes that since have plagued his presidency.     </p>
<p>                     To help them decipher this alarming evidence, they engaged the services of an old acquaintance, the former British MI6 agent and Russia expert Christopher Steele. Steele would produce the notorious dossier which disclosed that the Trump team was deeply compromised by a hostile foreign power bent on disrupting the West and influencing the US presidential election.    </p>
<p>                     In Crime in Progress, the authors break their silence for the first time, chronicling their high-stakes investigation and their desperate efforts to warn both the American and British governments, the FBI and the media, to little avail &#8211; and no matter the costs. Yet when the dossier finally exploded onto the world stage after a leak, a ten-person research firm above a Starbucks in Washington was thrust into the centre of the biggest news story on the planet &#8211; a story that would lead to the Mueller report and disrupt Trump&#8217;s secret planned rapprochement with Putin&#8217;s Russia that could have re-ordered the western alliance. After four years on his trail, the authors&#8217; inescapable conclusion is that Trump is an asset of the Russian government, whether he knows it or not.     </p>
<p>                     A real-life political thriller with the makings of a modern classic, Crime in Progress is the definitive story of the pursuit of the truth about Trump and one of the greatest betrayals in American history.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ve read all the books on this subject &#8211; this is the one you want to read . . . I feel fairly steeped in this matter and I learned something on every page&#8217; Rachel Maddow, MSNBC     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You don&#8217;t need to read John le Carre or Tom Clancy to find espionage thrills in Washington these days, turn over any stone in the Beltway&#8217;s secret world and you&#8217;ll observe the seething mass of conspiracy and subterfuge beneath . . . Take Glenn Simpson and Peter Fritsch, who have become central characters in a quite terrifying international spy thriller&#8217; Josh Glancy, Sunday Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/">Crime in Progress : The Secret History of the Trump-Russia Investigation &#8211; Glenn Simpson, Peter Fritsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A personal and powerful essay from Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie, the bestselling author of Americanah and Half of a Yellow Sun. &#8216;I would like to ask that we begin to dream about and plan for a different world. A fairer world. A world of happier men and happier women who are truer to themselves. And this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A personal and powerful essay from Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie, the bestselling author of Americanah and Half of a Yellow Sun.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;I would like to ask that we begin to dream about and plan for a different world. A fairer world. A world of happier men and happier women who are truer to themselves. And this is how to start: we must raise our daughters differently. We must also raise our sons differently&#8230;&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              What does &#8220;feminism&#8221; mean today?    </p>
<p>                              In this personal, eloquently argued essay &#8211; adapted from her much-admired Tedx talk of the same name &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie offers readers a unique definition of feminism for the twenty-first century, one rooted in inclusion and awareness. Drawing extensively on her own experiences and her deep understanding of the often masked realities of sexual politics, here is one remarkable author&#8217;s exploration of what it means to be a woman now &#8211; an of-the-moment rallying cry for why we should all be feminists.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Creator&#8217;s Code : The Six Essential Skills of Extraordinary Entrepreneurs &#8211; Amy Wilkinson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-creators-code-the-six-essential-skills-of-extraordinary-entrepreneurs-amy-wilkinson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-creators-code-the-six-essential-skills-of-extraordinary-entrepreneurs-amy-wilkinson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Plank was relatively small for an American footballer, and when he weighed the cotton T-shirt he wore under his team uniform, he found it weighed three pounds because it was so drenched in sweat. Knowing he couldn&#8217;t hinder himself in this way, he set about finding a material that wasn&#8217;t so absorbent. Going to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creators-code-the-six-essential-skills-of-extraordinary-entrepreneurs-amy-wilkinson-abridged/">The Creator&#8217;s Code : The Six Essential Skills of Extraordinary Entrepreneurs &#8211; Amy Wilkinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Plank was relatively small for an American footballer, and when he weighed the cotton T-shirt he wore under his team uniform, he found it weighed three pounds because it was so drenched in sweat. Knowing he couldn&#8217;t hinder himself in this way, he set about finding a material that wasn&#8217;t so absorbent. Going to a local fabric shop, he soon learned that synthetic materials would not take in as much sweat, so he had a shirt made and found it added just four ounces over the course of a game. When he gave some team-mates samples to try, they also soon saw the advantages. He began to produce the shirts commercially, and now Under Armour is a $2 billion global brand used by people from every sport.     </p>
<p>                    Packed with fascinating and inspirational tales of success, Amy Wilkinson&#8217;s brilliant book explains the six essential skills required by entrepreneurs to achieve their dreams. Based on in-depth interviews with the founders of numerous global brands, from eBay to Spanx, from LinkedIn to PayPal, she shows just what they did and what set them apart. For the key to being a successful entrepreneur isn&#8217;t necessarily about being &#8216;first&#8217;, it is about being the &#8216;only&#8217; one, and devising a new formula where none previously existed. Above all, these stories show how &#8211; if you follow the right steps &#8211; anyone can become a successful entrepreneur.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creators-code-the-six-essential-skills-of-extraordinary-entrepreneurs-amy-wilkinson-abridged/">The Creator&#8217;s Code : The Six Essential Skills of Extraordinary Entrepreneurs &#8211; Amy Wilkinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Spy Among Friends : Philby and the Great Betrayal &#8211; Ben Macintyre (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-spy-among-friends-philby-and-the-great-betrayal-ben-macintyre-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cold War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-spy-among-friends-philby-and-the-great-betrayal-ben-macintyre-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A SUNDAY TIMES No. 1 BESTSELLER WITH AN AFTERWORD BY JOHN LE CARRE &#8216;Riveting, astounding &#8230; An unputdownable postwar thriller&#8217; Observer &#8216;Irresistibly readable&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Worthy of John le Carre at his best&#8217; John Banville, Guardian &#8216;Hugely engrossing &#8230; Both authoritative and enthralling&#8217; William Boyd ________________ Kim Philby was the most notorious British defector and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-spy-among-friends-philby-and-the-great-betrayal-ben-macintyre-abridged/">A Spy Among Friends : Philby and the Great Betrayal &#8211; Ben Macintyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A SUNDAY TIMES No. 1 BESTSELLER<br />
                    WITH AN AFTERWORD BY JOHN LE CARRE    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Riveting, astounding &#8230; An unputdownable postwar thriller&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Irresistibly readable&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Worthy of John le Carre at his best&#8217; John Banville, Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hugely engrossing &#8230; Both authoritative and enthralling&#8217; William Boyd<br />
                    ________________    </p>
<p>                    Kim Philby was the most notorious British defector and Soviet mole in history. Agent, double agent, charmer and traitor, he betrayed every secret of Allied operations to the Russians in the early years of the Cold War. In the aftermath of the Second World War, Philby, Nicholas Elliott and James Jesus Angleton were rising stars in the intelligence world and shared every secret. Elliott and Angleton thought they knew Philby better than anyone &#8211; and then discovered they had not known him at all.    </p>
<p>                    This is a story of loyalty, trust and treachery, class and conscience, of male friendships forged, and then systematically betrayed. With access to newly released MI5 files and previously unseen papers, A Spy Among Friends unlocks what is perhaps the last great secret of the Cold War.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-spy-among-friends-philby-and-the-great-betrayal-ben-macintyre-abridged/">A Spy Among Friends : Philby and the Great Betrayal &#8211; Ben Macintyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Work Rules! : Insights from Inside Google That Will Transform How You Live and Lead &#8211; Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times and Wall Street Journal Bestseller Daily Telegraph, Huffington Post &#038; Business Insider Top Business Book to Read &#8216;Every year, 2 million people apply for a job at Google &#8211; so what&#8217;s the secret?&#8217; Guardian A compelling manifesto with the potential to change how we work and live, Work Rules! offers both [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/">Work Rules! : Insights from Inside Google That Will Transform How You Live and Lead &#8211; Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times and Wall Street Journal Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Daily Telegraph, Huffington Post &#038; Business Insider Top Business Book to Read     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Every year, 2 million people apply for a job at Google &#8211; so what&#8217;s the secret?&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    A compelling manifesto with the potential to change how we work and live, Work Rules! offers both a philosophy of the new world of work and a blueprint for attracting the most spectacular talent and ensuring the brightest and best prosper. The way we work is changing &#8211; are you?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/">Work Rules! : Insights from Inside Google That Will Transform How You Live and Lead &#8211; Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Information: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT    </p>
<p>                    We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need to be late.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master class &#8230; As a guide for perplexed Westerners, this book is very hard to beat &#8230; an honest, cohesive explanation for why the world is the way it is, without miracle cures or scapegoats&#8217; John Micklethwait, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; admirably honest &#8230; injects a badly needed dose of optimism into the modern debate&#8217; Gillian Tett, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;His main piece of advice for individuals, corporations, and countries is clear: Take a deep breath and adapt. This world isn&#8217;t going to wait for you&#8217; Fortune    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A humane and empathetic book&#8217; David Henkin, The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feminist Fight Club : A Survival Manual For a Sexist Workplace &#8211; Jessica Bennett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/feminist-fight-club-a-survival-manual-for-a-sexist-workplace-jessica-bennett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feminist-fight-club-a-survival-manual-for-a-sexist-workplace-jessica-bennett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Engaging, hilarious and practical &#8211; I will proudly proclaim myself a card-carrying member of the FFC&#8217; &#8211; Sheryl Sandberg, COO of Facebook and bestselling author of Lean In This is a call to arms. Are you aged zero to infinity? Finished with the sexist status quo? Ready to kick ass and take names? Welcome to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feminist-fight-club-a-survival-manual-for-a-sexist-workplace-jessica-bennett-abridged/">Feminist Fight Club : A Survival Manual For a Sexist Workplace &#8211; Jessica Bennett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Engaging, hilarious and practical &#8211; I will proudly proclaim myself a card-carrying member of the FFC&#8217; &#8211; Sheryl Sandberg, COO of Facebook and bestselling author of Lean In    </p>
<p>                    This is a call to arms.    </p>
<p>                    Are you aged zero to infinity? Finished with the sexist status quo? Ready to kick ass and take names?    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the Feminist Fight Club. You have lifetime membership.    </p>
<p>                    Feminist Fight Club provides an arsenal of weapons for surviving in an unequal world. You will learn how to fight micro-aggressions, correct unconscious bias, deal with male colleagues who can&#8217;t stop &#8216;manterrupting&#8217; or &#8216;bro-propriating&#8217; your ideas &#8211; and how to lean in without falling the f*ck over.    </p>
<p>                    Every woman needs this book &#8211; and they needed it yesterday.    </p>
<p>                    This is not a drill.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feminist-fight-club-a-survival-manual-for-a-sexist-workplace-jessica-bennett-abridged/">Feminist Fight Club : A Survival Manual For a Sexist Workplace &#8211; Jessica Bennett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In September 2014, a Chinese company that most Westerners had never heard of held the largest IPO in history &#8211; bigger than Google, Facebook and Twitter combined. Alibaba, now the world&#8217;s largest e-commerce company, mostly escaped Western notice for over ten years, while building a customer base larger than Amazon&#8217;s, and handling the bulk of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/">Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In September 2014, a Chinese company that most Westerners had never heard of held the largest IPO in history &#8211; bigger than Google, Facebook and Twitter combined. Alibaba, now the world&#8217;s largest e-commerce company, mostly escaped Western notice for over ten years, while building a customer base larger than Amazon&#8217;s, and handling the bulk of e-commerce transactions in China. How did it happen? And what was it like to be along for such a revolutionary ride?    </p>
<p>                    In Alibaba&#8217;s World, author Porter Erisman, one of Alibaba&#8217;s first Western employees, who helped spearhead its international expansion, shows how Jack Ma, a Chinese schoolteacher who twice failed his college entrance exams, rose from obscurity to found Alibaba and lead it from struggling startup to the world&#8217;s most dominant e-commerce player.     </p>
<p>                    Now, in the first English language account of Alibaba&#8217;s extraordinary success, Erisman shares stories of weathering the dotcom crash, facing down eBay and Google, negotiating with the unpredictable Chinese government, and enduring the misguided advice of foreign experts, all to build the behemoth that&#8217;s poised to sweep the ecommerce world today. And he analyzes Alibaba&#8217;s role as a harbinger of the new global business landscape &#8211; with its focus on the East rather than the West, emerging markets over developed ones, and the nimble entrepreneur over the industry titan. As we face this near future, the story of Alibaba &#8211; and its inevitable descendants &#8211; is both essential and instructive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/">Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Dark Age : Technology and the End of the Future &#8211; James Bridle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/new-dark-age-technology-and-the-end-of-the-future-james-bridle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban & Municipal Planning]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/new-dark-age-technology-and-the-end-of-the-future-james-bridle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We live in times of increasing inscrutability. Our news feeds are filled with unverified, unverifiable speculation, much of it automatically generated by anonymous software. As a result, we no longer understand what is happening around us. Underlying all of these trends is a single idea: the belief that quantitative data can provide a coherent model [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-dark-age-technology-and-the-end-of-the-future-james-bridle-abridged/">New Dark Age : Technology and the End of the Future &#8211; James Bridle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We live in times of increasing inscrutability. Our news feeds are filled with unverified, unverifiable speculation, much of it automatically generated by anonymous software. As a result, we no longer understand what is happening around us. Underlying all of these trends is a single idea: the belief that quantitative data can provide a coherent model of the world, and the efficacy of computable information to provide us with ways of acting within it. Yet the sheer volume of information available to us today reveals less than we hope. Rather, it heralds a new Dark Age: a world of ever-increasing incomprehension.    </p>
<p>                    In his brilliant new work, leading artist and writer James Bridle offers us a warning against the future in which the contemporary promise of a new technologically assisted Enlightenment may just deliver its opposite: an age of complex uncertainty, predictive algorithms, surveillance, and the hollowing out of empathy. Surveying the history of art, technology and information systems he reveals the dark clouds that gather over discussions of the digital sublime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-dark-age-technology-and-the-end-of-the-future-james-bridle-abridged/">New Dark Age : Technology and the End of the Future &#8211; James Bridle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The One Thing : The Surprisingly Simple Truth Behind Extraordinary Results: Achieve your goals with one of the world&#8217;s bestselling success books &#8211; Gary Keller, WithJay Papasan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-one-thing-the-surprisingly-simple-truth-behind-extraordinary-results-achieve-your-goals-with-one-of-the-worlds-bestselling-success-books-gary-keller-with-jay-papasan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-one-thing-the-surprisingly-simple-truth-behind-extraordinary-results-achieve-your-goals-with-one-of-the-worlds-bestselling-success-books-gary-keller-with-jay-papasan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER THAT WILL HELP YOU FIND THE ONE THING YOU NEED TO DO THAT WILL MAKE EVERYTHING ELSE EASIER &#8211; OR UNNECESSARY YOU WANT LESS You want fewer distractions and less on your plate. The daily barrage of e-mails, texts, tweets, messages, and meetings distract you and stress you out. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-one-thing-the-surprisingly-simple-truth-behind-extraordinary-results-achieve-your-goals-with-one-of-the-worlds-bestselling-success-books-gary-keller-with-jay-papasan-abridged/">The One Thing : The Surprisingly Simple Truth Behind Extraordinary Results: Achieve your goals with one of the world&#8217;s bestselling success books &#8211; Gary Keller, WithJay Papasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER THAT WILL HELP YOU FIND THE ONE THING YOU NEED TO DO THAT WILL MAKE EVERYTHING ELSE EASIER &#8211; OR UNNECESSARY    </p>
<p>                    YOU WANT LESS<br />
                    You want fewer distractions and less on your plate. The daily barrage of e-mails, texts, tweets, messages, and meetings distract you and stress you out. The simultaneous demands of work and family are taking a toll. And what&#8217;s the cost? Second-rate work, missed deadlines, smaller pay cheques, fewer promotions &#8211; and lots of stress.     </p>
<p>                    AND YOU WANT MORE<br />
                    You want more productivity from your work. More income for a better lifestyle. You want more satisfaction from life, and more time for yourself, your family, and your friends.    </p>
<p>                    NOW YOU CAN HAVE BOTH &#8211; LESS AND MORE.    </p>
<p>                    In The ONE Thing, you&#8217;ll learn to    </p>
<p>                    * Cut through the clutter<br />
                    * Achieve better results in less time<br />
                    * Build momentum toward your goal<br />
                    * Dial down the stress<br />
                    * Overcome that overwhelmed feeling<br />
                    * Revive your energy<br />
                    * Stay on track<br />
                    * Master what matters to you    </p>
<p>                    The ONE Thing is the New York Times bestseller that delivers extraordinary results in every area of your life &#8211; work, personal, family, and spiritual.    </p>
<p>                    WHAT&#8217;S YOUR ONE THING?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-one-thing-the-surprisingly-simple-truth-behind-extraordinary-results-achieve-your-goals-with-one-of-the-worlds-bestselling-success-books-gary-keller-with-jay-papasan-abridged/">The One Thing : The Surprisingly Simple Truth Behind Extraordinary Results: Achieve your goals with one of the world&#8217;s bestselling success books &#8211; Gary Keller, WithJay Papasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend. A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend.<br />
                              A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. Dear Ijeawele is Adichie&#8217;s letter of response.    </p>
<p>                              Here are fifteen invaluable suggestions-compelling, direct, wryly funny, and perceptive-for how to empower a daughter to become a strong, independent woman. From encouraging her to choose a helicopter, and not only a doll, as a toy if she so desires; having open conversations with her about clothes, makeup, and sexuality; debunking the myth that women are somehow biologically arranged to be in the kitchen making dinner, and that men can &#8220;allow&#8221; women to have full careers, Dear Ijeawele goes right to the heart of sexual politics in the twenty-first century. It will start a new and urgently needed conversation about what it really means to be a woman today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW* In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement. &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW*    </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New York Magazine    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compellingly motivational read&#8217; The Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book you need in your life&#8217; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                    *Winner of the 2014 Goodreads Choice Award for Best Business Book*    </p>
<p>                    In the space of ten years, Sophia Amoruso has gone from high-school dropout to founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal, one of the fastest-growing retailers in the world.     </p>
<p>                    Sophia&#8217;s never been a typical executive, or a typical anything, and she&#8217;s written #GIRLBOSS for other girls like her: outsiders (and insiders) seeking a unique path to success.    </p>
<p>                    Filled with brazen wake-up calls, cunning and frank observations, and behind-the-scenes stories from Nasty Gal&#8217;s meteoric rise, #GIRLBOSS covers a lot of ground. It proves that success doesn&#8217;t come from where you went to college or how popular you were in school. Success is about trusting your instincts and following your gut, knowing which rules to follow and which to break.    </p>
<p>                    Inspiring, motivating and empowering, #GIRLBOSS will give you the kick up the ass you need to reach your potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unfinished Business : Women Men Work Family &#8211; Anne-Marie Slaughter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Orwell Prize for Books 2016 Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015 When Anne-Marie Slaughter&#8217;s Atlantic article, &#8220;Why Women Still Can&#8217;t Have it All&#8221; first appeared, it immediately went viral, sparking a firestorm of debate across countries and continents. Within four days, it had become [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/">Unfinished Business : Women Men Work Family &#8211; Anne-Marie Slaughter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Orwell Prize for Books 2016    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015    </p>
<p>                    When Anne-Marie Slaughter&#8217;s Atlantic article, &#8220;Why Women Still Can&#8217;t Have it All&#8221; first appeared, it immediately went viral, sparking a firestorm of debate across countries and continents. Within four days, it had become the most-read article in the history of the magazine. In the following months, Slaughter became a leading voice in the discussion on work-life balance and on women&#8217;s changing role in the workplace.    </p>
<p>                    Now, Slaughter is here with her eagerly anticipated take on the problems we still face, and how we can finally get past them. In her pragmatic, down-to-earth style, Slaughter bursts the bubble on all the &#8220;half-truths&#8221; we tell young women about &#8220;having it all&#8221;, and explains what is really necessary to get true gender equality, both in the workplace and at home. Deeply researched, and filled with all the warm, wise and funny anecdotes that first made her the most trusted and admired voice on the issue, Anne-Marie Slaughter&#8217;s book is sure to change minds, ignite debate and be the topic of conversation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/">Unfinished Business : Women Men Work Family &#8211; Anne-Marie Slaughter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Upside of Stress : Why stress is good for you (and how to get good at it) &#8211; Kelly McGonigal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-upside-of-stress-why-stress-is-good-for-you-and-how-to-get-good-at-it-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-upside-of-stress-why-stress-is-good-for-you-and-how-to-get-good-at-it-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if everything you thought you knew about stress was wrong? Over the years we&#8217;ve grown to see stress as Public Enemy No.1, responsible for countless health problems, relationship troubles, unhappiness and anxiety, and to be avoided at all costs. But what if changing your mindset about stress could actually make you healthier, happier and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upside-of-stress-why-stress-is-good-for-you-and-how-to-get-good-at-it-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Upside of Stress : Why stress is good for you (and how to get good at it) &#8211; Kelly McGonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What if everything you thought you knew about stress was wrong?    </p>
<p>                    Over the years we&#8217;ve grown to see stress as Public Enemy No.1, responsible for countless health problems, relationship troubles, unhappiness and anxiety, and to be avoided at all costs. But what if changing your mindset about stress could actually make you healthier, happier and better able to reach your goals?    </p>
<p>                    In this new book, health psychologist Dr Kelly McGonigal reveals the new science of stress, showing that by embracing stress and changing your thinking, your stress response could become your most powerful ally. Drawing on the latest research and practical brain-training techniques, The Upside of Stress shows you how to do stress better, to improve your health and resilience, focus your energy, build relationships and boost courage. Rethink stress, and watch your life change for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upside-of-stress-why-stress-is-good-for-you-and-how-to-get-good-at-it-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Upside of Stress : Why stress is good for you (and how to get good at it) &#8211; Kelly McGonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stuffocation : Living More with Less &#8211; James Wallman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stuffocation-living-more-with-less-james-wallman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumerism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stuffocation-living-more-with-less-james-wallman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re all stuffocated. We have more stuff than we could ever need &#8211; but it&#8217;s bad for the planet and it&#8217;s making us stressed. It might even be killing us. In this groundbreaking book, trend forecaster James Wallman finds that a rising number of people are turning away from all-you-can-get consumption, from the exec who&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stuffocation-living-more-with-less-james-wallman-abridged/">Stuffocation : Living More with Less &#8211; James Wallman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re all stuffocated. We have more stuff than we could ever need &#8211; but it&#8217;s bad for the planet and it&#8217;s making us stressed. It might even be killing us.     </p>
<p>                      In this groundbreaking book, trend forecaster James Wallman finds that a rising number of people are turning away from all-you-can-get consumption, from the exec who&#8217;s sold almost everything he owns, to the well-off family who moved to a remote mountain cabin.    </p>
<p>                      In Stuffocation, Wallman&#8217;s solution is to focus less on possessions and more on experiences. It is a manifesto for a vital change in how you live &#8211; and it&#8217;s the one book you won&#8217;t be able to live without.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stuffocation-living-more-with-less-james-wallman-abridged/">Stuffocation : Living More with Less &#8211; James Wallman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Icarus Deception : How High Will You Fly? &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-icarus-deception-how-high-will-you-fly-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-icarus-deception-how-high-will-you-fly-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Icarus Deception, Seth Godin&#8217;s most inspiring book, he challenges readers to find the courage to treat their work as a form of art Everyone knows that Icarus&#8217;s father made him wings and told him not to fly too close to the sun; he ignored the warning and plunged to his doom. The lesson: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-icarus-deception-how-high-will-you-fly-seth-godin-abridged/">The Icarus Deception : How High Will You Fly? &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Icarus Deception, Seth Godin&#8217;s most inspiring book, he challenges readers to find the courage to treat their work as a form of art    </p>
<p>                    Everyone knows that Icarus&#8217;s father made him wings and told him not to fly too close to the sun; he ignored the warning and plunged to his doom. The lesson: Play it safe. Listen to the experts. It was the perfect propaganda for the industrial economy. What boss wouldn&#8217;t want employees to believe that obedience and conformity are the keys to success?    </p>
<p>                    But we tend to forget that Icarus was also warned not to fly too low, because seawater would ruin the lift in his wings. Flying too low is even more dangerous than flying too high, because it feels deceptively safe.    </p>
<p>                    The safety zone has moved. Conformity no longer leads to comfort. But the good news is that creativity is scarce and more valuable than ever. So is choosing to do something unpredictable and brave: Make art. Being an artist isn&#8217;t a genetic disposition or a specific talent. It&#8217;s an attitude we can all adopt. It&#8217;s a hunger to seize new ground, make connections, and work without a map. If you do those things you&#8217;re an artist, no matter what it says on your business card.    </p>
<p>                    Godin shows us how it&#8217;s possible and convinces us why it&#8217;s essential.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If Seth Godin didn&#8217;t exist, we&#8217;d need to invent him&#8217; Fast Company     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Seth Godin is a demigod on the web, a bestselling author, highly sought-after lecturer, successful entrepreneur, respected pundit and high-profile blogger&#8217; Forbes     </p>
<p>                    Seth Godin is the author of thirteen international bestsellers that have changed the way people think about marketing, the ways ideas spread, leadership and change including Permission Marketing, Purple Cow, All Marketers are Liars, The Dip and Tribes. He is the CEO of Squidoo.com and a very popular lecturer. His blog, www.sethgodin.typepad.com, is the most influential business blog in the world, and consistently one of the 100 most popular blogs on any subject.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-icarus-deception-how-high-will-you-fly-seth-godin-abridged/">The Icarus Deception : How High Will You Fly? &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes. &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world. Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen. 54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves. Norway is the richest country on earth. 5 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world.    </p>
<p>                    Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen.    </p>
<p>                    54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves.    </p>
<p>                    Norway is the richest country on earth.    </p>
<p>                    5 per cent of Danish men have had sex with an animal.    </p>
<p>                    Michael Booth has lived among the Scandinavians, on and off, for over ten years, perplexed by their many strange paradoxes and character traits and equally bemused by the unquestioning enthusiasm for all things Nordic and hygge that has engulfed the rest of the world.     </p>
<p>                    He leaves his adopted home of Denmark and embarks on a journey through all five of the Nordic countries to discover who these curious tribes are, the secrets of their success and, most intriguing of all, what they think of each other. Along the way a more nuanced, often darker picture emerges of a region plagued by taboos, characterised by suffocating parochialism and populated by extremists of various shades.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The next Bill Bryson.&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Best Narrative Travel Book Award from the British Guild of Travel Writers</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Know How She Does It : How Successful Women Make the Most of their Time &#8211; Laura Vanderkam (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-know-how-she-does-it-how-successful-women-make-the-most-of-their-time-laura-vanderkam-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-know-how-she-does-it-how-successful-women-make-the-most-of-their-time-laura-vanderkam-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most positive take on work and family I&#8217;ve read in a long time&#8221; New York Times Do you struggle to balance the demands of a successful career with quality time with family and friends, your hobbies, and even a decent night&#8217;s sleep? In I Know How She Does It, time management expert and bestselling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-know-how-she-does-it-how-successful-women-make-the-most-of-their-time-laura-vanderkam-abridged/">I Know How She Does It : How Successful Women Make the Most of their Time &#8211; Laura Vanderkam (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most positive take on work and family I&#8217;ve read in a long time&#8221;<br />
                     New York Times    </p>
<p>                    Do you struggle to balance the demands of a successful career with quality time with family and friends, your hobbies, and even a decent night&#8217;s sleep?     </p>
<p>                    In I Know How She Does It, time management expert and bestselling author of What the Most Successful People Do Before Breakfast Laura Vanderkam reveals the surprising strategies you can use to spend more time on the things you enjoy. By following her advice, you will be able to work less, sleep more, enjoy date nights, go to the gym and socialise.    </p>
<p>                    Based on hour-by-hour time logs from 1,001 days in the lives of real women, Vanderkam proves that you don&#8217;t have to give up on the things you really want. I Know How She Does It offers specific strategies proven to help you build a life that works, one hour at a time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-know-how-she-does-it-how-successful-women-make-the-most-of-their-time-laura-vanderkam-abridged/">I Know How She Does It : How Successful Women Make the Most of their Time &#8211; Laura Vanderkam (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When They Call You a Terrorist : A Black Lives Matter Memoir &#8211; Patrisse Khan-Cullors, asha bandele, Foreword byAngela Davis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/when-they-call-you-a-terrorist-a-black-lives-matter-memoir-patrisse-khan-cullors-asha-bandele-foreword-by-angela-davis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/when-they-call-you-a-terrorist-a-black-lives-matter-memoir-patrisse-khan-cullors-asha-bandele-foreword-by-angela-davis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the acquittal of George Zimmerman in the fatal shooting of Trayvon Martin, three women &#8211; Alicia Garza, Opal Tometi, and Patrisse Khan-Cullors &#8211; came together to form an active response to the systemic racism causing the deaths of so many African-Americans. They simply said: Black Lives Matter; and for that, they were labelled terrorists. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-they-call-you-a-terrorist-a-black-lives-matter-memoir-patrisse-khan-cullors-asha-bandele-foreword-by-angela-davis-abridged/">When They Call You a Terrorist : A Black Lives Matter Memoir &#8211; Patrisse Khan-Cullors, asha bandele, Foreword byAngela Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following the acquittal of George Zimmerman in the fatal shooting of Trayvon Martin, three women &#8211; Alicia Garza, Opal Tometi, and Patrisse Khan-Cullors &#8211; came together to form an active response to the systemic racism causing the deaths of so many African-Americans. They simply said: Black Lives Matter; and for that, they were labelled terrorists.    </p>
<p>                    In this empowering account of survival, strength and resilience, Patrisse Khan-Cullors and award-winning author and journalist asha bandele recount the personal story that led Patrisse to become a founder of Black Lives Matter, seeking to end the culture that declares Black life expendable. Like the era-defining movement she helped create, this rallying cry demands you do not look away.    </p>
<p>                    With foreword by Angela Davis.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-they-call-you-a-terrorist-a-black-lives-matter-memoir-patrisse-khan-cullors-asha-bandele-foreword-by-angela-davis-abridged/">When They Call You a Terrorist : A Black Lives Matter Memoir &#8211; Patrisse Khan-Cullors, asha bandele, Foreword byAngela Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Is Not Enough : Defeating the New Shock Politics &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-is-not-enough-defeating-the-new-shock-politics-naomi-klein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-is-not-enough-defeating-the-new-shock-politics-naomi-klein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**The New York Times and Sunday Times Bestseller** &#8216;An ordinary person&#8217;s guide to hope. Read this book&#8217; Arundhati Roy &#8216;As accessible as it is brilliant&#8217; Owen Jones &#8216;A genuine page turner&#8217; Michelle Alexander Naomi Klein &#8211; award-winning journalist, bestselling author of No Logo, The Shock Doctrine and This Changes Everything, scourge of brand bullies and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-is-not-enough-defeating-the-new-shock-politics-naomi-klein-abridged/">No Is Not Enough : Defeating the New Shock Politics &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**The New York Times and Sunday Times Bestseller**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An ordinary person&#8217;s guide to hope. Read this book&#8217; Arundhati Roy<br />
                    &#8216;As accessible as it is brilliant&#8217; Owen Jones<br />
                    &#8216;A genuine page turner&#8217; Michelle Alexander    </p>
<p>                    Naomi Klein &#8211; award-winning journalist, bestselling author of No Logo, The Shock Doctrine and This Changes Everything, scourge of brand bullies and corporate liars &#8211; gives us the toolkit we need to survive our surreal, shocking age.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This  is a look at how we arrived at this surreal political moment, how to  keep it from getting a lot worse, and how, if we keep our heads, we can  flip the script.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    Remember when love was supposed to  Trump hate? Remember when the oil companies and bankers seemed to be  running scared? What the hell happened? And what can we do about it?  Naomi Klein shows us how we got here, and how we can make things better.      </p>
<p>                    No Is Not Enough reveals, among other things, that the  disorientation we&#8217;re feeling is deliberate. That around the world, shock  political tactics are being used to generate crisis after crisis,  designed to force through policies that will destroy people, the  environment, the economy and our security. That extremism isn&#8217;t a freak  event &#8211; it&#8217;s a toxic cocktail of our times.     </p>
<p>                    From how to trash  the Trump megabrand to the art of reclaiming the populist argument,  Naomi Klein shows all of us how we can break the spell and win the world  we need. Don&#8217;t let them get away with it.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Who better than Naomi to make sense of this madness, and help us find a way out? A top-of-the-stack must read&#8217; Michael Stipe    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Naomi  Klein&#8217;s new book incites us brilliantly to interweave our No with a  programmatic Yes. A manual for emancipation&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Magnificent &#8230; a courageous coruscating counterspell&#8217; Junot Diaz</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-is-not-enough-defeating-the-new-shock-politics-naomi-klein-abridged/">No Is Not Enough : Defeating the New Shock Politics &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Seven Brief Lessons on Physics &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/seven-brief-lessons-on-physics-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theoretical & Mathematical Astronomy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/seven-brief-lessons-on-physics-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE PHENOMENAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF HELGOLAND AND THE ORDER OF TIME &#8216;The perfect antidote to the fluff and nonsense around right now. Learn how the world is and how you might just fit in&#8217; Simon Mayo &#8216;By God, it&#8217;s beguiling&#8217; New Statesman These seven short lessons guide us, with simplicity and clarity, through [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/seven-brief-lessons-on-physics-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Seven Brief Lessons on Physics &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE PHENOMENAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF HELGOLAND AND THE ORDER OF TIME    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The perfect antidote to the fluff and nonsense around right now. Learn how the world is and how you might just fit in&#8217; Simon Mayo    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;By God, it&#8217;s beguiling&#8217; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    These seven short lessons guide us, with simplicity and clarity, through the scientific revolution that shook physics in the twentieth century and still continues to shake us today. In this mind-bending overview of modern physics, Carlo Rovelli explains Einstein&#8217;s theory of general relativity, quantum mechanics, black holes, the complex architecture of the universe, elementary particles, gravity, and the nature of the mind. Not since Richard Feynman&#8217;s celebrated Six Easy Pieces has physics been so vividly, intelligently and entertainingly revealed.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/seven-brief-lessons-on-physics-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Seven Brief Lessons on Physics &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The People Vs Tech : How the internet is killing democracy (and how we save it) &#8211; Jamie Bartlett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-people-vs-tech-how-the-internet-is-killing-democracy-and-how-we-save-it-jamie-bartlett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-people-vs-tech-how-the-internet-is-killing-democracy-and-how-we-save-it-jamie-bartlett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**Winner of the 2019 Transmission Prize** **Longlisted for the 2019 Orwell Prize for Political Writing** &#8216;A superb book by one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on the digital revolution&#8217; David Patrikarakos, Literary Review &#8216;This book could not have come at a better moment&#8230; The People Vs Tech makes clear that there is still time &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-people-vs-tech-how-the-internet-is-killing-democracy-and-how-we-save-it-jamie-bartlett-abridged/">The People Vs Tech : How the internet is killing democracy (and how we save it) &#8211; Jamie Bartlett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**Winner of the 2019 Transmission Prize**<br />
                    **Longlisted for the 2019 Orwell Prize for Political Writing**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A superb book by one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on the digital revolution&#8217; David Patrikarakos, Literary Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book could not have come at a better moment&#8230; The People Vs Tech makes clear that there is still time &#8211; just &#8211; for us to take back control&#8217; &#8211; Camilla Cavendish, Sunday Times     </p>
<p>                    The internet was meant to set us free.    </p>
<p>                    Tech has radically changed the way we live our lives. But have we unwittingly handed too much away to shadowy powers behind a wall of code, all manipulated by a handful of Silicon Valley utopians, ad men, and venture capitalists? And, in light of recent data breach scandals around companies like Facebook and Cambridge Analytica, what does that mean for democracy, our delicately balanced system of government that was created long before big data, total information and artificial intelligence? In this urgent polemic, Jamie Bartlett argues that through our unquestioning embrace of big tech, the building blocks of democracy are slowly being removed. The middle class is being eroded, sovereign authority and civil society is weakened, and we citizens are losing our critical faculties, maybe even our free will.    </p>
<p>                    The People Vs Tech is an enthralling account of how our fragile political system is being threatened by the digital revolution. Bartlett explains that by upholding six key pillars of democracy, we can save it before it is too late. We need to become active citizens; uphold a shared democratic culture; protect free elections; promote equality; safeguard competitive and civic freedoms; and trust in a sovereign authority. This essential book shows that the stakes couldn&#8217;t be higher and that, unless we radically alter our course, democracy will join feudalism, supreme monarchies and communism as just another political experiment that quietly disappeared.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-people-vs-tech-how-the-internet-is-killing-democracy-and-how-we-save-it-jamie-bartlett-abridged/">The People Vs Tech : How the internet is killing democracy (and how we save it) &#8211; Jamie Bartlett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER* &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran Imagine a world where&#8230; * Your phone is too big for your hand * Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body * [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    Imagine a world where&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    *        Your phone is too big for your hand<br />
                    *        Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body<br />
                    *        In a car accident you are 47% more likely to be injured.    </p>
<p>                    If any of that sounds familiar, chances are you&#8217;re a woman.    </p>
<p>                    From government policy and medical research, to technology, workplaces, and the media. Invisible Women reveals how in a world built for and by men we are systematically ignoring half of the population, often with disastrous consequences. Caroline Criado Perez brings together for the first time an impressive range of case studies, stories and new research from across the world that illustrate the hidden ways in which women are forgotten, and the profound impact this has on us all.    </p>
<p>                    Discover the shocking gender bias that affects our everyday lives.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book that changes the way you see the world&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Revelatory, frightening, hopeful&#8217; Jeanette Winterson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals. In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals.     </p>
<p>                    In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind societies. He explores how the tension between identity and anonymity defines how societies develop, function, and fail. In the vein of Guns, Germs, and Steel and Sapiens, The Human Swarm reveals how mankind created sprawling civilizations of unrivalled complexity &#8211; and what it will take to sustain them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power Paradox : How We Gain and Lose Influence &#8211; Dacher Keltner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-paradox-how-we-gain-and-lose-influence-dacher-keltner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-paradox-how-we-gain-and-lose-influence-dacher-keltner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revolutionary rethinking of everything we know about power It shapes every interaction we have, whether we&#8217;re trying to get a two-year-old to eat green vegetables or ask for a promotion at work. But how do we really gain and maintain power &#8211; through coercion or cooperation? What does it do to our behaviour? And [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-paradox-how-we-gain-and-lose-influence-dacher-keltner-abridged/">The Power Paradox : How We Gain and Lose Influence &#8211; Dacher Keltner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revolutionary rethinking of everything we know about power    </p>
<p>                    It  shapes every interaction we have, whether we&#8217;re trying to get a  two-year-old to eat green vegetables or ask for a promotion at work. But  how do we really gain and maintain power &#8211; through coercion or cooperation?  What does it do to our behaviour? And what makes us lose power? In  twenty revolutionary &#8216;power principles&#8217;, renowned psychologist Dacher  Keltner turns everything we thought we knew about influence and status  upside down, redefining power for our times.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Keltner is the  most interesting psychologist in America. It&#8217;s only a matter of time  before his ideas spread everywhere&#8217; Michael Lewis    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Sheds light  on human power&#8217;s dark side, as well as its redeeming qualities. Everyone  can learn from this wise book&#8217; Susan T. Fiske, author of Social Cognition    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A lively description of how true power is like a return on a social investment in others&#8217; Frans de Waal, author of Are We Smart Enough to Know How Smart Animals Are?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Lively and intriguing &#8230; A much-needed dose of positivity&#8217; Prospect</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-paradox-how-we-gain-and-lose-influence-dacher-keltner-abridged/">The Power Paradox : How We Gain and Lose Influence &#8211; Dacher Keltner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Suicide of the West : How the Rebirth of Tribalism, Nationalism, and Socialism Is Destroying American Democracy &#8211; Jonah Goldberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/suicide-of-the-west-how-the-rebirth-of-tribalism-nationalism-and-socialism-is-destroying-american-democracy-jonah-goldberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/suicide-of-the-west-how-the-rebirth-of-tribalism-nationalism-and-socialism-is-destroying-american-democracy-jonah-goldberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent argument that America and other democracies are in peril because they have lost the will to defend the values and institutions that sustain freedom and prosperity. Now updated with a new preface! &#8220;Epic and debate-shifting.&#8221;&#8211;David Brooks, New York Times Only once in the last 250,000 years have humans [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/suicide-of-the-west-how-the-rebirth-of-tribalism-nationalism-and-socialism-is-destroying-american-democracy-jonah-goldberg-abridged/">Suicide of the West : How the Rebirth of Tribalism, Nationalism, and Socialism Is Destroying American Democracy &#8211; Jonah Goldberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent argument that America and other democracies are in peril because they have lost the will to defend the values and institutions that sustain freedom and prosperity. Now updated with a new preface!    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Epic and debate-shifting.&#8221;&#8211;David Brooks, New York Times  Only once in the last 250,000 years have humans stumbled upon a way to lift ourselves out of the endless cycle of poverty, hunger, and war that defines most of history. If democracy, individualism, and the free market were humankind&#8217;s destiny, they should have appeared and taken hold a bit earlier in the evolutionary record. The emergence of freedom and prosperity was nothing short of a miracle.  As Americans we are doubly blessed, because the radical ideas that made the miracle possible were written not just into the Constitution but in our hearts, laying the groundwork for our uniquely prosperous society. Those ideas are:  &#8211; Our rights come from God, not from the government. <br />
                     &#8211; The government belongs to us; we do not belong to it. <br />
                     &#8211; The individual is sovereign. We are all captains of our own souls, not bound by the circumstances of our birth. <br />
                     &#8211; The fruits of our labors belong to us.  In the last few decades, these political virtues have been turned into vices. As we are increasingly taught to view our traditions as a system of oppression, exploitation, and privilege, the principles of liberty and the rule of law are under attack from left and right. For the West to survive, we must renew our sense of gratitude for what our civilization has given us and rediscover the ideals and habits of the heart that led us out of the bloody muck of the past&#8211;or back to the muck we will go.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/suicide-of-the-west-how-the-rebirth-of-tribalism-nationalism-and-socialism-is-destroying-american-democracy-jonah-goldberg-abridged/">Suicide of the West : How the Rebirth of Tribalism, Nationalism, and Socialism Is Destroying American Democracy &#8211; Jonah Goldberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hardwiring Happiness : How to reshape your brain and your life &#8211; Rick Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hardwiring-happiness-how-to-reshape-your-brain-and-your-life-rick-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hardwiring-happiness-how-to-reshape-your-brain-and-your-life-rick-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A book to savour, to practise, and take to heart&#8217; Professor Mark Williams &#8216;As clear and inspired as it gets&#8217; Ruby Wax Four steps to counterbalance your brain&#8217;s negativity bias and learn to hardwire happiness in only a few minutes each day. Recent scientific breakthroughs have revealed that what we think and feel changes the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hardwiring-happiness-how-to-reshape-your-brain-and-your-life-rick-hanson-abridged/">Hardwiring Happiness : How to reshape your brain and your life &#8211; Rick Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A book to savour, to practise, and take to heart&#8217; Professor Mark Williams    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;As clear and inspired as it gets&#8217; Ruby Wax    </p>
<p>                    Four steps to counterbalance your brain&#8217;s negativity bias and learn to hardwire happiness in only a few minutes each day.     </p>
<p>                    Recent scientific breakthroughs have revealed that what we think and feel changes the brain. Dr Rick Hanson&#8217;s Hardwiring Happiness is the first book to show how to transform the simple positive experiences of daily life into neural structures that promote lasting health, contentment, love and inner peace.     </p>
<p>                     To keep our ancestors alive, our brain evolved a &#8216;negativity bias&#8217;, which lets positive experiences flow through it like water through a sieve. Yet positive experiences are the building blocks needed for health, happiness and fulfilling relationships. Drawing on neuroscience and the contemplative traditions, Hardwiring Happiness shows how to overcome that negativity bias and get those good experiences into the brain where it can use them, providing the tools we need to heal old wounds, develop our inner resources and, ultimately, transform our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hardwiring-happiness-how-to-reshape-your-brain-and-your-life-rick-hanson-abridged/">Hardwiring Happiness : How to reshape your brain and your life &#8211; Rick Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice we receive from public health bodies is muddled, out of date, and frequently contradictory, and in many quarters still promotes the unproven hypothesis that fats are the greatest evil.    </p>
<p>                    With expert science and compelling storytelling, Gary Taubes investigates the history of nutritional science which, shaped by a handful of charismatic and misguided individuals, has for a hundred years denied the impact of sugar on our health. He exposes the powerful influence of the food industry which has lobbied for sugar&#8217;s ubiquity &#8211; the Sugar Association even today promoting &#8216;sugar&#8217;s goodness&#8217; &#8211;  and the extent that the industry has corrupted essential scientific research. He delves into the science of sugar, exposes conventional thinking that sugar is &#8217;empty calories&#8217; as a myth, and finds that its addictive pleasures are resulting in worldwide consumption as never experienced before, to devastating effect.     </p>
<p>                    The Case Against Sugar is a revelatory read, which will fundamentally change the way we eat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Can&#8217;t Read This Book : Censorship in an Age of Freedom &#8211; Nick Cohen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-cant-read-this-book-censorship-in-an-age-of-freedom-nick-cohen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-cant-read-this-book-censorship-in-an-age-of-freedom-nick-cohen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The uncompromising Nick Cohen exposes the reality behind the freedoms we enjoy in the book that won Polemic of the Year at the 2013 Political Book Awards. After the fall of the Berlin Wall, the collapse of Communism, and the advent of the Web which allowed for even the smallest voice to be heard, everywhere [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-cant-read-this-book-censorship-in-an-age-of-freedom-nick-cohen-abridged/">You Can&#8217;t Read This Book : Censorship in an Age of Freedom &#8211; Nick Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The uncompromising Nick Cohen exposes the reality behind the freedoms we enjoy in the book that won Polemic of the Year at the 2013 Political Book Awards.    </p>
<p>                              After the fall of the Berlin Wall, the collapse of Communism, and the advent of the Web which allowed for even the smallest voice to be heard, everywhere you turned you were told that we were living in an age of unparalleled freedom.    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;You Can&#8217;t Read This Book&#8217; argues that this view is dangerously naive. From the revolution in Iran that wasn&#8217;t, to the Great Firewall of China and the imposition of super-injunctions from the filthy rich protecting their privacy, the traditional opponents of freedom of speech &#8211; religious fanaticism, plutocratic power and dictatorial states &#8211; are thriving and in many respects finding the world a more comfortable place in the early 21st century than they did in the late 20th.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-cant-read-this-book-censorship-in-an-age-of-freedom-nick-cohen-abridged/">You Can&#8217;t Read This Book : Censorship in an Age of Freedom &#8211; Nick Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
