<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/medicine/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/medicine/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/medicine/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Just Breathe : My Journey Through Cancer and Back &#8211; Stephen Graham King</title>
		<link>/just-breathe-my-journey-through-cancer-and-back-stephen-graham-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/just-breathe-my-journey-through-cancer-and-back-stephen-graham-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the year 2000, Stephen Graham King was diagnosed with a rare, aggressive cancer known as synovial sarcoma, beginning a four-year ordeal of radiation, chemotherapy, physiotherapy, and multiple recurrences. After having trouble with his left knee for much of his adult life, King finally saw a doctor following a bump to the leg that almost [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-breathe-my-journey-through-cancer-and-back-stephen-graham-king/">Just Breathe : My Journey Through Cancer and Back &#8211; Stephen Graham King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the year 2000, Stephen Graham King was diagnosed with a rare, aggressive cancer known as synovial sarcoma, beginning a four-year ordeal of radiation, chemotherapy, physiotherapy, and multiple recurrences.    </p>
<p>                     After having trouble with his left knee for much of his adult life, King finally saw a doctor following a bump to the leg that almost made him pass out from the excruciating pain. After the diagnosis, he endured five major, invasive surgeries that cost him a large portion of his left leg and half of his left lung, radically changing his body, mind, and self-image forever. And in the end, forcing him to relearn many things: some as basic as re-learning how to walk.    </p>
<p>                     As a gay man who is part of an image-conscious subculture within our image-driven society, he was forced to confront his feelings about his body on the long road back to health.    </p>
<p>                     Now, in Just Breathe, King shares his journey from health to illness and back to health again through prose and journal entries written during the battle. Told with candour and humour, this is the story of his challenging recovery and the love of life, friends, and family that helped him to survive.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-breathe-my-journey-through-cancer-and-back-stephen-graham-king/">Just Breathe : My Journey Through Cancer and Back &#8211; Stephen Graham King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Language]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite 21st-century fears of an &#8216;epidemic&#8217; of loneliness, its history has been sorely neglected. A Biography of Loneliness offers a radically new interpretation of loneliness as an emotional language and experience. Using letters and diaries, philosophical tracts, political discussions, and medical literature from the eighteenth century to the present, historian of the emotions Fay Bound [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/">A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite 21st-century fears of an &#8216;epidemic&#8217; of loneliness, its history has been sorely neglected. A Biography of Loneliness offers a radically new interpretation of loneliness as an emotional language and experience. Using letters and diaries, philosophical tracts, political discussions, and medical literature from the eighteenth century to the present, historian of the emotions Fay Bound Alberti argues that loneliness is not an ahistorical, universal<br />
                    phenomenon. It is, in fact, a modern emotion: before 1800, its language did not exist. And where loneliness is identified, it is not always bad, but a complex emotional state that differs according to class, gender, ethnicity and experience.    </p>
<p>                    Looking at informative case studies such as Sylvia Plath, Queen Victoria, and Virginia Woolf, A Biography of Loneliness charts the emergence of loneliness as a modern and embodied emotional state.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/">A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Equipment & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nursing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Telemedicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy & Therapeutics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they indicate further (and more invasive) tests, most of which will probably prove unnecessary (much like physicals themselves). And your bill will be astronomical.In  The Patient Will See You Now , Eric Topol, one of the nation&#8217;s top physicians, shows why medicine does not have to be that way. Instead, you could use your smartphone to get rapid test results from one drop of blood, monitor your vital signs both day and night, and use an artificially intelligent algorithm to receive a diagnosis without having to see a doctor, all at a small fraction of the cost imposed by our modern healthcare system. The change is powered by what Topol calls medicine&#8217;s &#8220;Gutenberg moment.&#8221; Much as the printing press took learning out of the hands of a priestly class, the mobile internet is doing the same for medicine, giving us unprecedented control over our healthcare. With smartphones in hand, we are no longer beholden to an impersonal and paternalistic system in which &#8220;doctor knows best.&#8221; Medicine has been digitized, Topol argues now it will be democratized. Computers will replace physicians for many diagnostic tasks, citizen science will give rise to citizen medicine, and enormous data sets will give us new means to attack conditions that have long been incurable. Massive, open, online medicine, where diagnostics are done by Facebook-like comparisons of medical profiles, will enable real-time, real-world research on massive populations. There&#8217;s no doubt the path forward will be complicated: the medical establishment will resist these changes, and digitized medicine inevitably raises serious issues surrounding privacy. Nevertheless, the result,better, cheaper, and more human health care,will be worth it.Provocative and engrossing,  The Patient Will See You Now  is essential reading for anyone who thinks they deserve better health care. That is, for all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon : The New Science and Stories of the Brain &#8211; Dr Rahul Jandial (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosurgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rehabilitation: Brain & Spinal Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER *As heard on Chris Evans&#8217; Virgin Radio* &#8216;You&#8217;re amazing I could talk to you (Rahul) all day&#8217; Chris Evans &#8216;This is a gripping new book&#8217; The Times World-leading neuroscientist and neurosurgeon Dr Rahul Jandial draws on his years of work with patients suffering from the most extreme cases of brain damage, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/">Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon : The New Science and Stories of the Brain &#8211; Dr Rahul Jandial (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    *As heard on Chris Evans&#8217; Virgin Radio*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You&#8217;re amazing I could talk to you (Rahul) all day&#8217; Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is a gripping new book&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    World-leading neuroscientist and neurosurgeon Dr Rahul Jandial draws on his years of work with patients suffering from the most extreme cases of brain damage, disorders and illnesses to reveal what they can tell us about the science of the mind.    </p>
<p>                    From a languages teacher who has to choose whether to lose her ability to speak Spanish or English after brain surgery, to a former TV exec, now homeless, who discovers that his life-altering despondency is the result of a tumour, to a fainting teen who learns that deep breathing can mean the difference between life or death, these stories uncover the secret workings of the brain.    </p>
<p>                    Blending cutting-edge research and beautiful storytelling, Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon is a vital resource on the best ways to boost your memory, control stress and emotions, minimize pain, unleash your creativity, raise smart kids and reduce the risk of Alzheimer&#8217;s. This is a deeply practical and readable book, which will take you on an expedition through the anatomy of the most fascinating &#8211; and mysterious &#8211; of organs.    </p>
<p>                    Rahul&#8217;s new book Life on a Knife&#8217;s Edge is out now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/">Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon : The New Science and Stories of the Brain &#8211; Dr Rahul Jandial (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Read with Jenna Book Club Pick as Featured on Today &#8211; As a young mother facing a terminal diagnosis, Julie Yip-Williams began to write her story, a story like no other. What began as the chronicle of an imminent and early death became something much more&#8211;a powerful exhortation to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/">The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Read with Jenna Book Club Pick as Featured on Today &#8211; As a young mother facing a terminal diagnosis, Julie Yip-Williams began to write her story, a story like no other. What began as the chronicle of an imminent and early death became something much more&#8211;a powerful exhortation to the living.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An exquisitely moving portrait of the daily stuff of life.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review (Editors&#8217; Choice) NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY The New York Times Book Review &#8211; Time &#8211; Real Simple &#8211; Good Housekeeping  That Julie Yip-Williams survived infancy was a miracle. Born blind in Vietnam, she narrowly escaped euthanasia at the hands of her grandmother, only to flee with her family the political upheaval of her country in the late 1970s. Loaded into a rickety boat with three hundred other refugees, Julie made it to Hong Kong and, ultimately, America, where a surgeon at UCLA gave her partial sight. She would go on to become a Harvard-educated lawyer, with a husband, a family, and a life she had once assumed would be impossible. Then, at age thirty-seven, with two little girls at home, Julie was diagnosed with terminal metastatic colon cancer, and a different journey began.  The Unwinding of the Miracle is the story of a vigorous life refracted through the prism of imminent death. When she was first diagnosed, Julie Yip-Williams sought clarity and guidance through the experience and, finding none, began to write her way through it&#8211;a chronicle that grew beyond her imagining. Motherhood, marriage, the immigrant experience, ambition, love, wanderlust, tennis, fortune-tellers, grief, reincarnation, jealousy, comfort, pain, the marvel of the body in full rebellion&#8211;this book is as sprawling and majestic as the life it records. It is inspiring and instructive, delightful and shattering. It is a book of indelible moments, seared deep&#8211;an incomparable guide to living vividly by facing hard truths consciously.  With humor, bracing honesty, and the cleansing power of well-deployed anger, Julie Yip-Williams set the stage for her lasting legacy and one final miracle: the story of her life. Praise for The Unwinding of the Miracle  &#8220;Everything worth understanding and holding on to is in this book. . . . A miracle indeed.&#8221;&#8211;Kelly Corrigan, New York Times bestselling author &#8220;A beautifully written, moving, and compassionate chronicle that deserves to be read and absorbed widely.&#8221;&#8211;Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/">The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Planet of Viruses : Second Edition &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The past year has been one of viral panic-panic about viruses, that is. Through headlines, public health warnings, and at least one homemade hazmat suit, we were reminded of the powerful force of viruses. They are the smallest living things known to science, yet they can hold the entire planet in their sway. A Planet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/">A Planet of Viruses : Second Edition &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past year has been one of viral panic-panic about viruses, that is. Through headlines, public health warnings, and at least one homemade hazmat suit, we were reminded of the powerful force of viruses. They are the smallest living things known to science, yet they can hold the entire planet in their sway. A Planet of Viruses is Carl Zimmer&#8217;s eye-opening look at the hidden world of viruses. Zimmer, the popular science writer and author of National Geographic&#8217;s award-winning blog The Loom, has updated this edition to include the stories of new outbreaks, such as Ebola, MERS, and chikungunya virus; new scientific discoveries, such as a hundred-million-year-old virus that infected the common ancestor of armadillos, elephants, and humans; and new findings that show why climate change may lead to even deadlier outbreaks. Zimmer&#8217;s lucid explanations and fascinating stories demonstrate how deeply humans and viruses are intertwined. Viruses helped give rise to the first life-forms, are responsible for many of our most devastating diseases, and will continue to control our fate for centuries.<br />
                    Thoroughly readable, and as reassuring as it is frightening, A Planet of Viruses is a fascinating tour of a formidable hidden world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/">A Planet of Viruses : Second Edition &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Going to Hurt : Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optometry / Opticians]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now A Major BBC Series Starring Ben Whishaw. The multi-million copy bestseller and Book of the Year at The National Book Awards. &#8216;Painfully funny. The pain and the funniness somehow add up to something entirely good, entirely noble and entirely loveable.&#8217; &#8211; Stephen Fry Welcome to the life of a junior doctor: 97-hour weeks, life [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/">This is Going to Hurt : Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now A Major BBC Series Starring Ben Whishaw.    </p>
<p>                    The multi-million copy bestseller and Book of the Year at The National Book Awards.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Painfully funny. The pain and the funniness somehow add up to something entirely good, entirely noble and entirely loveable.&#8217; &#8211; Stephen Fry    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the life of a junior doctor: 97-hour weeks, life and death decisions, a constant tsunami of bodily fluids, and the hospital parking meter earns more than you.    </p>
<p>                    Scribbled in secret after endless days, sleepless nights and missed weekends, Adam Kay&#8217;s This is Going to Hurt provides a no-holds-barred account of his time on the NHS front line. Hilarious, horrifying and heartbreaking, this diary is everything you wanted to know &#8211; and more than a few things you didn&#8217;t &#8211; about life on and off the hospital ward.    </p>
<p>                    Sunday Times Number One Bestseller for over eight months and winner of a record FOUR National Book Awards: Book of the Year, Non-Fiction Book of the Year, New Writer of the Year and Zoe Ball Book Club Book of the Year.    </p>
<p>                    This edition includes extra diary entries and an afterword by the author.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/">This is Going to Hurt : Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health    </p>
<p>                    Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, bacteria and human cells have co-existed in a relationship that has ensured the health and equilibrium of our body. But now, much like the natural world outside of us, our internal environment is being irrevocably destroyed. The culprit: some of our most revered medical advances &#8211; antibiotics &#8211; which appear to be linked to the epidemics of asthma, eczema, obesity, certain forms of cancer, and other diseases plaguing modern society.    </p>
<p>                    In a book that stands as the Silent Spring of its day, Blaser sounds a provocative alarm that we ignore at our peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling work that overturns conventional conceptions of health and illness to offer new methods for increasing vital longevity. CAN WE LIVE ROBUSTLY UNTIL OUR LAST BREATH? Do we have to suffer from debilitating conditions and sickness? Is it possible to add more vibrant years to our lives? In the #1 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/">The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling work that overturns conventional conceptions of health and illness to offer new methods for increasing vital longevity. CAN WE LIVE ROBUSTLY UNTIL OUR LAST BREATH? Do we have to suffer from debilitating conditions and sickness? Is it possible to add more vibrant years to our lives? In the #1 New York Times bestselling The End of Illness, Dr. David Agus tackles these fundamental questions and dismantles misperceptions about what &#8220;health&#8221; really means. Presenting an eye-opening picture of the human body and all the ways it works&#8211;and fails&#8211;Dr. Agus shows us how a new perspective on our individual health will allow us to achieve a long, vigorous life. Offering insights and access to powerful new technologies that promise to transform medicine, Dr. Agus emphasizes his belief that there is no &#8220;right&#8221; answer, no master guide that is &#8220;one size fits all.&#8221; Each one of us must get to know our bodies in uniquely personal ways, and he shows us exactly how to do that. A bold call for all of us to become our own personal health advocates, The End of Illness is a moving departure from orthodox thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/">The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
