<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Public Opinion &amp; Polls Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/public-opinion-polls/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/public-opinion-polls/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Public Opinion &amp; Polls Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/public-opinion-polls/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Opinion & Polls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans. &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate. You have nowhere to go. You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221; &#8211;From the Introduction In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate.<br />
                     You have nowhere to go.<br />
                     You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;From the Introduction     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools: How a Selfish Ruling Class is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution, Tucker Carlson tells the truth about the new American elites, a group whose power and wealth has grown beyond imagination even as the rest of the country has withered. The people who run America now barely interact with it. They fly on their own planes, ski on their own mountains, watch sporting events far from the stands in sky boxes. They have total contempt for you.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;They view America the way a private equity firm sizes up an aging conglomerate,&#8221; Carlson writes, &#8220;as something outdated they can profit from. When it fails, they&#8217;re gone.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools,  Tucker Carlson offers a blistering critique of our new overlords. Traditional liberals are gone, he writes. The patchouli-scented hand-wringers who worried about whales and defended free speech have been replaced by globalists who hide their hard-edged economic agenda behind the smokescreen of identity politics. They&#8217;ll outsource your job while lecturing you about transgender bathrooms. Left and right, Carlson says, are no longer meaningful categories in America. &#8220;The rift is between those who benefit from the status quo, and those who don&#8217;t.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     Our leaders are fools, Carlson concludes, &#8220;unaware that they are captains of a sinking ship.&#8221; But in the signature and witty style that viewers of Tucker Carlson Tonight have come to enjoy, his book answers the all-important question: How do we put the country back on course?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>For the Record &#8211; David Cameron (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Administration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Opinion & Polls]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The political memoir of the decade&#8217; Sunday Times The referendum on Britain&#8217;s membership of the EU is one of the most controversial political events of our times. For the first time, the man who called that vote talks about the decision and its origins, as well as giving a candid account of his time at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/">For the Record &#8211; David Cameron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The political memoir of the decade&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                                The referendum on Britain&#8217;s membership of the EU is one of the most controversial political events of our times. For the first time, the man who called that vote talks about the decision and its origins, as well as giving a candid account of his time at the top of British politics.    </p>
<p>                              David Cameron was Conservative Party leader during the largest financial crash in living memory. The Arab Spring and the Eurozone crisis both started during his first year as prime minister. The backdrop to his time in office included the advent of ISIS, surging migration and a rapidly changing EU.    </p>
<p>                              Here he talks about how he confronted those challenges, from modernising a party that had suffered three successive electoral defeats to forming the first coalition government for seventy years. He sets out how he helped turn around Britain&#8217;s economy, implementing a modern, compassionate agenda that included education and welfare reform, the legalisation of gay marriage, the referendum on Scottish independence and world-leading environmental policies.    </p>
<p>                              David Cameron is searingly honest about the key players from his time in politics. And he is frank about himself &#8211; the things he got right and the things he got wrong. He opens up about family life too, including the tragic loss of his eldest son.    </p>
<p>                              We learn why he kept Britain&#8217;s promise on overseas aid spending and what it was like to commit British troops to conflicts in Libya, Iraq and Syria. He sets out how he won the first outright Conservative majority in nearly a quarter of a century, and describes the events leading up to the EU referendum, the renegotiation, the campaign &#8211; and his thoughts on it all today.    </p>
<p>                              It is the most compelling record yet of what it&#8217;s like to lead in modern times and to live behind the most famous door in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/">For the Record &#8211; David Cameron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
