<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Historical Crime Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/historical-crime/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/historical-crime/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Historical Crime Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/historical-crime/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Corruption of Blood &#8211; Ambrose Parry</title>
		<link>/a-corruption-of-blood-ambrose-parry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-corruption-of-blood-ambrose-parry/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Raven and Fisher Mystery: Book 3 Edinburgh, 1850. This city will bleed you dry. Dr Will Raven is a man seldom shocked by human remains, but even he is disturbed by the contents of a package washed up at the Port of Leith. Stranger still, a man Raven has long detested is pleading for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-corruption-of-blood-ambrose-parry/">A Corruption of Blood &#8211; Ambrose Parry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Raven and Fisher Mystery: Book 3    </p>
<p>                    Edinburgh, 1850. This city will bleed you dry.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Will Raven is a man seldom shocked by human remains, but even he is disturbed by the contents of a package washed up at the Port of Leith. Stranger still, a man Raven has long detested is pleading for his help to escape the hangman.    </p>
<p>                    Back in the townhouse of Dr James Simpson, Sarah Fisher has set her sights on learning to practise medicine. Almost everyone seems intent on dissuading her from this ambition, but when word reaches her that a woman has recently obtained a medical degree despite her gender, Sarah decides to seek her out.    </p>
<p>                    Raven&#8217;s efforts to prove his former adversary&#8217;s innocence are failing and he desperately needs Sarah&#8217;s help. Putting their feelings for one another aside, their investigations take them to both extremes of Edinburgh&#8217;s social divide, where they discover that wealth and status cannot alter a fate written in the blood.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-corruption-of-blood-ambrose-parry/">A Corruption of Blood &#8211; Ambrose Parry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Angel&#8217;s Game : The Cemetery of Forgotten Books 2 &#8211; Carlos Ruiz Zafón</title>
		<link>/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ephemera & Printed Matter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction In Translation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manuscripts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The stunning new novel from the internationally bestselling author of THE SHADOW OF THE WIND. In an abandoned mansion at the heart of Barcelona, a young man &#8211; David Martin &#8211; makes his living by writing sensationalist novels under a pseudonym. The survivor of a troubled childhood, he has taken refuge in the world of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/">The Angel&#8217;s Game : The Cemetery of Forgotten Books 2 &#8211; Carlos Ruiz Zafón</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The stunning new novel from the internationally bestselling author of THE SHADOW OF THE WIND.    </p>
<p>                    In an abandoned mansion at the heart of Barcelona, a young man &#8211; David Martin &#8211; makes his living by writing sensationalist novels under a pseudonym. The survivor of a troubled childhood, he has taken refuge in the world of books, and spends his nights spinning baroque tales about the city&#8217;s underworld. But perhaps his dark imaginings are not as strange as they seem, for in a locked room deep within the house letters hinting at the mysterious death of the previous owner. Like a slow poison, the history of the place seeps into his bones as he struggles with an impossible love.     </p>
<p>                    Then David receives the offer of a lifetime: he is to write a book with the power to change hearts and minds. In return, he will receive a fortune, perhaps more. But as David begins the work, he realises that there is a connection between this haunting book and the shadows that surround his home&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/">The Angel&#8217;s Game : The Cemetery of Forgotten Books 2 &#8211; Carlos Ruiz Zafón</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tournament &#8211; Matthew Reilly</title>
		<link>/the-tournament-matthew-reilly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tournament-matthew-reilly/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A tale of murder, passion and intrigue set in the majestic city of Constantinople. From global superstar Matthew Reilly comes this gripping historical thriller . . . * * * * * A PRINCESS IN DANGER England, 1546. A young Princess Elizabeth is in a dangerous position as her older siblings jostle for the throne. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tournament-matthew-reilly/">The Tournament &#8211; Matthew Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A tale of murder, passion and intrigue set in the majestic city of Constantinople.</p>
<p>                    From global superstar Matthew Reilly comes this gripping historical thriller . . . </p>
<p>                    * * * * *</p>
<p>                    A PRINCESS IN DANGER<br />
                    England, 1546. A young Princess Elizabeth is in a dangerous position as her older siblings jostle for the throne.</p>
<p>                    A TOURNAMENT UNLIKE ANY OTHER<br />
                    Roger Ascham, Elizabeth&#8217;s teacher and mentor, is determined to keep her safe. So when he receives an unusual invitation from the Sultan in Constantinople, asking him to take part in the greatest chess tournament the world has ever seen, he resolves to take the princess with him.</p>
<p>                    A DEVASTATING SECRET<br />
                    But death stalks the streets of the glittering Ottoman capital &#8211; a cardinal has been found mutilated. Ascham is asked to investigate, but as he and Elizabeth delve deeper, they uncover a secret that marks the young Princess for life. And a darkness that defines the queen she will become.</p>
<p>                    * * * * * </p>
<p>                    READERS LOVE THE TOURNAMENT</p>
<p>                    &#8216;So full of intrigue, it kept me reading late into the night&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An amazing book. Thrills, spills, twists and turns&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Action, adventure, history . . . A read that you cannot put down&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Totally unputdownable . . . Magic stuff!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Another blinding read&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tournament-matthew-reilly/">The Tournament &#8211; Matthew Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magpie Murders : the Sunday Times bestseller crime thriller with a fiendish twist &#8211; Anthony Horowitz</title>
		<link>/magpie-murders-the-sunday-times-bestseller-crime-thriller-with-a-fiendish-twist-anthony-horowitz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/magpie-murders-the-sunday-times-bestseller-crime-thriller-with-a-fiendish-twist-anthony-horowitz/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Want to read a great whodunnit? Anthony Horowitz has one for you: MAGPIE MURDERS. It&#8217;s as good as an Agatha Christie. Better, in some ways. Cleverer.&#8217; Stephen King &#8216;The finest crime novel of the year&#8217; Daily Mail ***** Seven for a mystery that needs to be solved . . . Editor Susan Ryland has worked [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magpie-murders-the-sunday-times-bestseller-crime-thriller-with-a-fiendish-twist-anthony-horowitz/">Magpie Murders : the Sunday Times bestseller crime thriller with a fiendish twist &#8211; Anthony Horowitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Want to read a great whodunnit? Anthony Horowitz has one for you: MAGPIE MURDERS. It&#8217;s as good as an Agatha Christie. Better, in some ways. Cleverer.&#8217; Stephen King</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The finest crime novel of the year&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    *****</p>
<p>                     Seven for a mystery that needs to be solved . . .<br />
                    Editor Susan Ryland has worked with bestselling crime writer Alan Conway for years. Readers love his detective, Atticus Pund, a celebrated solver of crimes in the sleepy English villages of the 1950s.<br />
                    But Conway&#8217;s latest tale of murder at Pye Hall is not quite what it seems. Yes, there are dead bodies and a host of intriguing suspects, but hidden in the pages of the manuscript lies another story: a tale written between the very words on the page, telling of real-life jealousy, greed, ruthless ambition and murder.<br />
                    From the creator of Midsomer Murders comes a fiendish mystery perfect for fans of Agatha Christie&#8217;s Miss Marple and Hercule Poirot.</p>
<p>                    *****</p>
<p>                    Praise for Magpie Murders &#8211; the gripping Sunday Times bestselling crime thriller:<br />
                    &#8216;Ingenious&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling and compelling with a stunning twist&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A stylish thriller&#8217; Sunday Mirror</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A cunning reinvention of the thriller&#8217; Mail on Sunday</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magpie-murders-the-sunday-times-bestseller-crime-thriller-with-a-fiendish-twist-anthony-horowitz/">Magpie Murders : the Sunday Times bestseller crime thriller with a fiendish twist &#8211; Anthony Horowitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ordinary Grace : A Novel &#8211; William Kent Krueger</title>
		<link>/ordinary-grace-a-novel-william-kent-krueger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ordinary-grace-a-novel-william-kent-krueger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WINNER OF THE 2014 EDGAR AWARD FOR BEST NOVEL WINNER OF THE 2014 DILYS AWARD A SCHOOL LIBRARY JOURNAL BEST BOOK OF 2013 From New York Times bestselling author William Kent Krueger, a brilliant new novel about a young man, a small town, and murder in the summer of 1961. &#8220;That [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ordinary-grace-a-novel-william-kent-krueger/">Ordinary Grace : A Novel &#8211; William Kent Krueger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                     WINNER OF THE 2014 EDGAR AWARD FOR BEST NOVEL<br />
                     WINNER OF THE 2014 DILYS AWARD<br />
                     A SCHOOL LIBRARY JOURNAL BEST BOOK OF 2013</p>
<p>                    From New York Times bestselling author William Kent Krueger, a brilliant new novel about a young man, a small town, and murder in the summer of 1961.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;That was it. That was all of it. A grace so ordinary there was no reason at all to remember it. Yet I have never across the forty years since it was spoken forgotten a single word.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    New Bremen, Minnesota, 1961. The Twins were playing their debut season, ice-cold root beers were selling out at the soda counter of Halderson&#8217;s Drugstore, and Hot Stuff comic books were a mainstay on every barbershop magazine rack. It was a time of innocence and hope for a country with a new, young president. But for thirteen-year-old Frank Drum it was a grim summer in which death visited frequently and assumed many forms. Accident. Nature. Suicide. Murder. </p>
<p>                    Frank begins the season preoccupied with the concerns of any teenage boy, but when tragedy unexpectedly strikes his family-which includes his Methodist minister father; his passionate, artistic mother; Juilliard-bound older sister; and wise-beyond-his-years kid brother-he finds himself thrust into an adult world full of secrets, lies, adultery, and betrayal, suddenly called upon to demonstrate a maturity and gumption beyond his years. </p>
<p>                    Told from Frank&#8217;s perspective forty years after that fateful summer, Ordinary Grace is a brilliantly moving account of a boy standing at the door of his young manhood, trying to understand a world that seems to be falling apart around him. It is an unforgettable novel about discovering the terrible price of wisdom and the enduring grace of God.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ordinary-grace-a-novel-william-kent-krueger/">Ordinary Grace : A Novel &#8211; William Kent Krueger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Last Mrs. Summers &#8211; Rhys Bowen</title>
		<link>/the-last-mrs-summers-rhys-bowen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-last-mrs-summers-rhys-bowen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lady Georgiana Rannoch is just back from her honeymoon with dashing Darcy O&#8217;Mara when a friend in need pulls her into a twisted Gothic tale of betrayal, deception and, most definitely, murder. . . . I am a bit at loose ends at the moment. My cook, Queenie, is making my new role as mistress [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-last-mrs-summers-rhys-bowen/">The Last Mrs. Summers &#8211; Rhys Bowen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lady Georgiana Rannoch is just back from her honeymoon with dashing Darcy O&#8217;Mara when a friend in need pulls her into a twisted Gothic tale of betrayal, deception and, most definitely, murder. . . .</p>
<p>                    I am a bit at loose ends at the moment. My cook, Queenie, is making my new role as mistress of Eynsleigh something akin to constant torture as Darcy is off on another one of his top secret jaunts. And Grandad is busy helping wayward youths avoid lives of crime. So when my dearest friend, Belinda, inherits an old cottage in Cornwall and begs me to go with her to inspect the property, I jump at the chance. </p>
<p>                    After a heart-stopping journey in Belinda&#8217;s beast of a motorcar, we arrive at the creaky old cottage called White Sails and quickly realize that it is completely uninhabitable. Just when I&#8217;m starting to wonder if I would have been better off trying to get Queenie to cook a roast that hasn&#8217;t been burnt beyond all recognition, we meet Rose Summers, a woman Belinda knew as a child when she spent time in Cornwall. Rose invites us to stay at Trewoma Hall, the lovely estate now owned by her husband, Tony. </p>
<p>                    Belinda confesses that she never liked Rose and had a fling with Tony years ago, so staying with them is far from ideal but beggars can&#8217;t be choosers as they say. Trewoma is not the idyllic house Belinda remembers. There&#8217;s something claustrophobic and foreboding about the place. Matters aren&#8217;t helped by the oppressively efficient housekeeper Mrs. Mannering or by the fact that Tony seems to want to rekindle whatever he and Belinda once had right under his wife&#8217;s nose. </p>
<p>                    Our increasingly awkward visit soon turns deadly when a member of the household is found murdered and all clues point to Belinda as the prime suspect. I soon learn that some long buried secrets have come back to haunt those in residence at Trewoma Hall and I&#8217;ll need to sift through the ruins of their past so Belinda doesn&#8217;t lose her chance at freedom in the present. . . .</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-last-mrs-summers-rhys-bowen/">The Last Mrs. Summers &#8211; Rhys Bowen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Love And Death Among The Cheetahs &#8211; Rhys Bowen</title>
		<link>/love-and-death-among-the-cheetahs-rhys-bowen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/love-and-death-among-the-cheetahs-rhys-bowen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Georgie and Darcy are finally on their honeymoon in Kenya&#8217;s Happy Valley, but murder crashes the party in this all-new installment in the New York Times bestselling series. I was so excited when Darcy announced out of the blue that we were flying to Kenya for our extended honeymoon. Now that we are here, I [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/love-and-death-among-the-cheetahs-rhys-bowen/">Love And Death Among The Cheetahs &#8211; Rhys Bowen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Georgie and Darcy are finally on their honeymoon in Kenya&#8217;s Happy Valley, but murder crashes the party in this all-new installment in the New York Times bestselling series. </p>
<p>                    I was so excited when Darcy announced out of the blue that we were flying to Kenya for our extended honeymoon. Now that we are here, I suspect he has actually been sent to fulfill another secret mission. I am trying very hard not to pick a fight about it, because after all, we are in paradise! Darcy finally confides that there have been robberies in London and Paris. It seems the thief was a member of the aristocracy and may have fled to Kenya. Since we are staying in the Happy Valley&#8211;the center of upper-class English life&#8211;we are well positioned to hunt for clues and ferret out possible suspects. </p>
<p>                     Now that I am a sophisticated married woman, I am doing my best to sound like one. But crikey! These aristocrats are a thoroughly loathsome sort enjoying a completely decadent lifestyle filled with wild parties and rampant infidelity. And one of the leading lights in the community, Lord Cheriton, has the nerve to make a play for me. While I am on my honeymoon! Of course, I put an end to that right off. </p>
<p>                     When he is found bloodied and lifeless along a lonely stretch of road, it appears he fell victim to a lion. But it seems that the Happy Valley community wants to close the case a bit too quickly. Darcy and I soon discover that there is much more than a simple robbery and an animal attack to contend with here in Kenya. Nearly everyone has a motive to want Lord Cheriton dead and some will go to great lengths to silence anyone who asks too many questions. The hunt is on! I just hope I can survive my honeymoon long enough to catch a killer. . . .</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/love-and-death-among-the-cheetahs-rhys-bowen/">Love And Death Among The Cheetahs &#8211; Rhys Bowen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strange Sight : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</title>
		<link>/strange-sight-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Witchcraft & Wicca]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/strange-sight-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The La Fleur restaurant has a slew of unusual phenomena. Bonnet-clad apparitions pass through walls, blood leaks from ceilings and rats besiege the dining room. Experts from the Great Essex Witch Museum are called in to quell these strange sights. But before Rosie Strange and Sam Stone can do their thing events turn darker. For [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strange-sight-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/">Strange Sight : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The La Fleur restaurant has a slew of unusual phenomena. Bonnet-clad apparitions pass through walls, blood leaks from ceilings and rats besiege the dining room. Experts from the Great Essex Witch Museum are called in to quell these strange sights. But before Rosie Strange and Sam Stone can do their thing events turn darker. For La Fleur&#8217;s chef has been strung up and slaughtered like a pig. More oddly, the only witness, the owner&#8217;s daughter Mary, swears blind a ghost did it.       </p>
<p>                    Rosie and Sam must find out what&#8217;s happening before Mary takes the fall. But intuitions and tip-offs lead them stumbling into the dark waters of the past, exposing secrets of a wider conspiracy, as well as secrets all Rosie&#8217;s own. With strange chills Rosie and Sam learn that seeing isn&#8217;t always believing, while thoughts of truth may be just as illusory.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strange-sight-an-essex-witch-museum-mystery-syd-moore/">Strange Sight : An Essex Witch Museum Mystery &#8211; Syd Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Officer and a Spy : The gripping Richard and Judy Book Club favourite &#8211; Robert Harris</title>
		<link>/an-officer-and-a-spy-the-gripping-richard-and-judy-book-club-favourite-robert-harris/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-officer-and-a-spy-the-gripping-richard-and-judy-book-club-favourite-robert-harris/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Book Awards Popular Fiction Book of the Year 2013 They lied to protect their country. He told the truth to save it. A gripping historical thriller from the bestselling author of FATHERLAND. January 1895. On a freezing morning in the heart of Paris, an army officer, Georges Picquart, witnesses a convicted spy, Captain Alfred [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-officer-and-a-spy-the-gripping-richard-and-judy-book-club-favourite-robert-harris/">An Officer and a Spy : The gripping Richard and Judy Book Club favourite &#8211; Robert Harris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Book Awards Popular Fiction Book of the Year 2013</p>
<p>                    They lied to protect their country. He told the truth to save it. A gripping historical thriller from the bestselling author of FATHERLAND.</p>
<p>                    January 1895. On a freezing morning in the heart of Paris, an army officer, Georges Picquart, witnesses a convicted spy, Captain Alfred Dreyfus, being publicly humiliated in front of twenty thousand spectators baying &#8216;Death to the Jew!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    The officer is rewarded with promotion: Picquart is made the French army&#8217;s youngest colonel and put in command of &#8216;the Statistical Section&#8217; &#8211; the shadowy intelligence unit that tracked down Dreyfus.</p>
<p>                    The spy, meanwhile, is given a punishment of medieval cruelty: Dreyfus is shipped off to a lifetime of solitary confinement on Devil&#8217;s Island &#8211; unable to speak to anyone, not even his guards, his case seems closed forever.</p>
<p>                    But gradually Picquart comes to believe there is something rotten at the heart of the Statistical Section. When he discovers another German spy operating on French soil, his superiors are oddly reluctant to pursue it. Despite official warnings, Picquart persists, and soon the officer and the spy are in the same predicament&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Narrated by Picquart, An Officer and a Spy is a compelling recreation of a scandal that became the most famous miscarriage of justice in history. Compelling, too, are the echoes for our modern world: an intelligence agency gone rogue, justice corrupted in the name of national security, a newspaper witch-hunt of a persecuted minority, and the age-old instinct of those in power to cover-up their crimes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-officer-and-a-spy-the-gripping-richard-and-judy-book-club-favourite-robert-harris/">An Officer and a Spy : The gripping Richard and Judy Book Club favourite &#8211; Robert Harris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The House of Silk : The Bestselling Sherlock Holmes Novel &#8211; Anthony Horowitz</title>
		<link>/the-house-of-silk-the-bestselling-sherlock-holmes-novel-anthony-horowitz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-house-of-silk-the-bestselling-sherlock-holmes-novel-anthony-horowitz/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Horowitz has captured Holmes Heaven&#8217; THE TIMES THE HOUSE OF SILK was the first official new Sherlock Holmes mystery and a SUNDAY TIMES bestseller from the author of MAGPIE MURDERS THE GAME&#8217;S AFOOT . . . It is November 1890 and London is gripped by a merciless winter. Sherlock Holmes and Dr Watson are enjoying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-silk-the-bestselling-sherlock-holmes-novel-anthony-horowitz/">The House of Silk : The Bestselling Sherlock Holmes Novel &#8211; Anthony Horowitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Horowitz has captured Holmes Heaven&#8217; THE TIMES     </p>
<p>                    THE HOUSE OF SILK was the first official new Sherlock Holmes mystery and a SUNDAY TIMES bestseller from the author of MAGPIE MURDERS    </p>
<p>                    THE GAME&#8217;S AFOOT . . .    </p>
<p>                    It is November 1890 and London is gripped by a merciless winter. Sherlock Holmes and Dr Watson are enjoying tea by the fire when an agitated gentleman arrives unannounced at 221b Baker Street. He begs Holmes for help, telling the unnerving story of a scar-faced man with piercing eyes who has stalked him in recent weeks.     </p>
<p>                    Intrigued, Holmes and Watson find themselves swiftly drawn into a series of puzzling and sinister events, stretching from the gas-lit streets of London to the teeming criminal underworld of Boston and the mysterious &#8216;House of Silk&#8217; . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-silk-the-bestselling-sherlock-holmes-novel-anthony-horowitz/">The House of Silk : The Bestselling Sherlock Holmes Novel &#8211; Anthony Horowitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scandalous Duke &#8211; Scarlett Scott, Read by Rosalyn Landor</title>
		<link>/scandalous-duke-scarlett-scott-read-by-rosalyn-landor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/scandalous-duke-scarlett-scott-read-by-rosalyn-landor/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Felix Markham, Duke of Winchelsea, has devoted his life to being the perfect statesman and raising his daughter after his beloved wife&#8217;s death. But when devastating bombings on the railway leave London in an uproar, he is determined to bring the mastermind of the attacks to justice. He will lure the fox from his den [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scandalous-duke-scarlett-scott-read-by-rosalyn-landor/">Scandalous Duke &#8211; Scarlett Scott, Read by Rosalyn Landor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Felix Markham, Duke of Winchelsea, has devoted his life to being the perfect statesman and raising his daughter after his beloved wife&#8217;s death. But when devastating bombings on the railway leave London in an uproar, he is determined to bring the mastermind of the attacks to justice. He will lure the fox from his den by any means. In her youth, Johanna McKenna donned a French accent and stage name to escape the clutches of her violent father and became the darling of the New York City stage as Rose Beaumont. Her past comes calling when her brother&#8217;s reappearance in her life leads her into a dangerous web of deceit. She finds herself hopelessly trapped until she receives an offer she cannot refuse from London&#8217;s most famous theater. Felix&#8217;s plan is clear: bring the famed Rose of New York to London, secure her as his mistress, and drive his quarry to English shores. But the more time he spends in Johanna&#8217;s company, the more he realizes nothing is as it seems, least of all the woman who feels as if she were made to be in his arms. When he finally learns the truth, it may be too late to save both his city and the enigmatic lady who has stolen his heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scandalous-duke-scarlett-scott-read-by-rosalyn-landor/">Scandalous Duke &#8211; Scarlett Scott, Read by Rosalyn Landor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Race &#8211; Clive Cussler</title>
		<link>/the-race-clive-cussler/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-race-clive-cussler/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>20th century detective Isaac Bell protects a promising aviator from her jealous husband in this remarkable adventure from #1 New York Times-bestselling author Clive Cussler. It is 1910, the age of flying machines is still in its infancy, and newspaper publisher Preston Whiteway is offering $50,000 for the first daring aviator to cross America in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-race-clive-cussler/">The Race &#8211; Clive Cussler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>20th century detective Isaac Bell protects a promising aviator from her jealous husband in this remarkable adventure from #1 New York Times-bestselling author Clive Cussler.    </p>
<p>                    It is 1910, the age of flying machines is still in its infancy, and newspaper publisher Preston Whiteway is offering $50,000 for the first daring aviator to cross America in less than fifty days. He is even sponsoring one of the prime candidates-an intrepid woman named Josephine Frost-and that&#8217;s where Bell, chief investigator for the Van Dorn Detective Agency, comes in.    </p>
<p>                    Frost&#8217;s violent-tempered husband has just killed her lover and tried to kill her, and he is bound to make another attempt. Bell has tangled with Harry Frost before; he knows that the man has made his millions leading gangs of thieves, murderers, and thugs in every city across the country. He also knows Frost won&#8217;t be after just his wife, but after Whiteway as well. And if Bell takes the case . . . Frost will be after him, too.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-race-clive-cussler/">The Race &#8211; Clive Cussler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Silver Swan &#8211; Benjamin Black</title>
		<link>/the-silver-swan-benjamin-black/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-silver-swan-benjamin-black/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Time has moved on for Quirke, the world-weary pathologist first encountered in Christine Falls. It is the middle of the 1950s, that low, dishonourable decade; a woman he loved has died, a man he once admired is dying, while the daughter he for so long denied is still finding it hard to accept him as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-silver-swan-benjamin-black/">The Silver Swan &#8211; Benjamin Black</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Time has moved on for Quirke, the world-weary pathologist first encountered in Christine Falls. It is the middle of the 1950s, that low, dishonourable decade; a woman he loved has died, a man he once admired is dying, while the daughter he for so long denied is still finding it hard to accept him as her father. When an old acquaintance approaches him about his wife&#8217;s apparent suicide, Quirke recognizes trouble but, as always, trouble is something he cannot resist.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Drug addiction, morbid sexual obsession, blackmail and murder, as well as prose as crisp as a winter&#8217;s morning by the Liffey . . . Quirke is human enough to swell the hardest of hearts&#8217; GQ    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A neat whodunit plot and a delightful command of suspense&#8217;  Independent on Sunday    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The death of Michael Dibdin left a huge hole in crime fiction. Black and Quirke are filling that gap with this wholly gripping account for the shady, priest-ridden and blithely corrupt society of mid-twentieth-century Dublin&#8217; Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A romp of a read, a compelling fix&#8217; Scotsman    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Dublin&#8217;s clammy atmosphere and its oppressive social and religious mores are a convincing backdrop to a moving drama conveyed by a master writer&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-silver-swan-benjamin-black/">The Silver Swan &#8211; Benjamin Black</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
