<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Internet &amp; WWW Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/internet-www-industries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/internet-www-industries/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Internet &amp; WWW Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/internet-www-industries/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award! There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life. In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award!<br />
                    There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life.<br />
                    In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest spam and hacker operations targeting Americans and their bank accounts. Tracing the rise, fall, and alarming resurrection of the digital mafia behind the two largest spam pharmacies-and countless viruses, phishing, and spyware attacks-he delivers the first definitive narrative of the global spam problem and its threat to consumers everywhere.<br />
                    Blending cutting-edge research, investigative reporting, and firsthand interviews, this terrifying true story reveals how we unwittingly invite these digital thieves into our lives every day. From unassuming computer programmers right next door to digital mobsters like &#8220;Cosma&#8221;-who unleashed a massive malware attack that has stolen thousands of Americans&#8217; logins and passwords-Krebs uncovers the shocking lengths to which these people will go to profit from our data and our wallets.<br />
                    Not only are hundreds of thousands of Americans exposing themselves to fraud and dangerously toxic products from rogue online pharmacies, but even those who never open junk messages are at risk. As Krebs notes, spammers can-and do-hack into accounts through these emails, harvest personal information like usernames and passwords, and sell them on the digital black market. The fallout from this global epidemic doesn&#8217;t just cost consumers and companies billions, it costs lives too.<br />
                    Fast-paced and utterly gripping, Spam Nation ultimately proposes concrete solutions for protecting ourselves online and stemming this tidal wave of cybercrime-before it&#8217;s too late.<br />
                    &#8220;Krebs&#8217;s talent for exposing the weaknesses in online security has earned him respect in the IT business and loathing among cybercriminals&#8230; His track record of scoops&#8230;has helped him become the rare blogger who supports himself on the strength of his reputation for hard-nosed reporting.&#8221; -Bloomberg Businessweek</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An indispensable guide.&#8217; Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn &#8216;Tech&#8217;s most valuable teacher.&#8217; Forbes Silicon Valley&#8217;s leading intellectual and the founder of O&#8217;Reilly Media explores the upside and the potential downsides of our future &#8211; what he calls the &#8216;next economy&#8217;. Tim O&#8217;Reilly&#8217;s genius is to identify and explain emerging technologies with world shaking potential &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/">WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An indispensable guide.&#8217; Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tech&#8217;s most valuable teacher.&#8217; Forbes    </p>
<p>                    Silicon Valley&#8217;s leading intellectual and the founder of O&#8217;Reilly Media explores the upside and the potential downsides of our future &#8211; what he calls the &#8216;next economy&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    Tim O&#8217;Reilly&#8217;s genius is to identify and explain emerging technologies with world shaking potential &#8211; the World Wide Web, Open Source Software, Web 2.0, Open Government data, the Maker Movement, Big Data. &#8216;The man who can really can make a whole industry happen,&#8217; according to Executive Chairman of Google Eric Schmidt, O&#8217;Reilly has most recently focused on the future of work &#8211; AI, algorithms, and new approaches to business organisation that will shape our lives. He has brought together an unlikely coalition of technologists, business leaders, labour advocates, and policy makers to wrestle with these issues. In WTF? he shares the evolution of his intellectual development, applying his approach to a number of challenging issues we will face as citizens, employees, business leaders, and a nation.    </p>
<p>                    What is the future when an increasing number of jobs can be performed by intelligent machines instead of people, or only done by people in partnership with those machines? What happens to our consumer based societies &#8211; to workers and to the companies that depend on their purchasing power? Is income inequality and unemployment an inevitable consequence of technological advancement, or are there paths to a better future? What will happen to business when technology-enabled networks and marketplaces are better at deploying talent than traditional companies? What&#8217;s the future of education when on-demand learning outperforms traditional institutions? Will the fundamental social safety nets of the developed world survive the transition, and if not, what will replace them?    </p>
<p>                    The digital revolution has transformed the world of media, upending centuries-old companies and business models. Now, it is restructuring every business, every job, and every sector of society. Yet the biggest changes are still ahead. To survive, every industry and organisation will have to transform itself in multiple ways. O&#8217;Reilly explores what the next economy will mean for the world and every aspect of our lives &#8211; and what we can do to shape it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/">WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A gripping read&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Originals Reddit hails itself as &#8216;the front page of the Internet&#8217;. It&#8217;s the sixth most-visited website in the world &#8211; and yet, millions have no idea what it is. They should be paying attention. This definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit is perfect for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/">We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A gripping read&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    Reddit hails itself as &#8216;the front page of the Internet&#8217;. It&#8217;s the sixth most-visited website in the world &#8211; and yet, millions have no idea what it is. They should be paying attention.    </p>
<p>                    This definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit is perfect for readers of The Everything Store, Googled and The Facebook Effect.    </p>
<p>                    We Are the Nerds takes readers inside this captivating, maddening enterprise, whose army of obsessed users have been credited with everything from solving crimes and spurring millions in charitable donations to seeding alt-right fury and even landing Donald Trump in the White House. Reddit has become a mirror of the Internet itself: It has dark trenches, shiny memes, malicious trolls, and a heart-warming ability to connect people across cultures, oceans, and ideological divides.    </p>
<p>                    This is the gripping story of how Reddit&#8217;s founders, Steve Huffman and Alexis Ohanian, transformed themselves from student video-gamers into Silicon Valley millionaires as they turned their creation into an icon of the digital age. But the journey was often fraught. Reporting on Reddit for more than six years, conducting hundreds of interviews and gaining exclusive access to its founders, Christine Lagorio-Chafkin has written the definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit. Packed with revelatory details about its biggest triumphs and controversies, this inside look at Reddit includes fresh insights on the relationship between Huffman and Ohanian, staff turmoil, the tragic life of Aaron Swartz, and Reddit&#8217;s struggle to become profitable.    </p>
<p>                    In a time when we are increasingly concerned about privacy and manipulation on social platforms, We Are the Nerds reveals Reddit&#8217;s central role in the dissemination of culture and information in history&#8217;s first fully digital century. Rigorously reported and highly entertaining, We Are the Nerds explores how this unique platform has changed the way we all communicate today.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR THE BOOK:    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Incisive, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Emily Chang, bestselling author of Brotopia    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A triumph &#8211; a business book that reads like a page-turning novel&#8217; &#8211; James Ledbetter, author of One Nation Under Gold    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The best, grittiest, most accurate book yet about what it&#8217;s like to build a startup and a community from scratch&#8217; &#8211; John Zeratsky, bestselling author of Sprint and Make Time    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A gripping, entertaining book that is a must-read for every entrepreneur&#8217; &#8211; Daymond John, bestselling author of Rise and Grind    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Too many books on tech feel like they have been Googled together; Lagorio-Chafkin&#8217;s is rich in original reportage&#8217; &#8211; TLS</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/">We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
