<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Accounting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/accounting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/accounting/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Accounting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/accounting/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Accounting Made Simple : Accounting Explained in 100 Pages or Less &#8211; Mike Piper (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/accounting-made-simple-accounting-explained-in-100-pages-or-less-mike-piper-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/accounting-made-simple-accounting-explained-in-100-pages-or-less-mike-piper-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Find all of the following explained in Plain-English with no technical jargon: The Accounting Equation and why it&#8217;s so significant How to read and prepare financial statements How to calculate and interpret several different financial ratios The concepts and assumptions behind Generally Accepted Accounting Principles (GAAP) Preparing journal entries with debits and credits Cash method [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accounting-made-simple-accounting-explained-in-100-pages-or-less-mike-piper-abridged/">Accounting Made Simple : Accounting Explained in 100 Pages or Less &#8211; Mike Piper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Find all of the following explained in Plain-English with no technical jargon: The Accounting Equation and why it&#8217;s so significant How to read and prepare financial statements How to calculate and interpret several different financial ratios The concepts and assumptions behind Generally Accepted Accounting Principles (GAAP) Preparing journal entries with debits and credits Cash method vs. accrual method Inventory and Cost of Goods Sold How to calculate depreciation and amortization expenses</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accounting-made-simple-accounting-explained-in-100-pages-or-less-mike-piper-abridged/">Accounting Made Simple : Accounting Explained in 100 Pages or Less &#8211; Mike Piper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simple Numbers, Straight Talk, Big Profits! &#8211; Greg Crabtree, Beverly Herzog (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/simple-numbers-straight-talk-big-profits-greg-crabtree-beverly-herzog-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/simple-numbers-straight-talk-big-profits-greg-crabtree-beverly-herzog-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Simple Numbers can guide you to increased business profitability Take the mystery out of small business finance with this no-frills guide to understanding the numbers that will guide your business out of any financial black hole. Author Greg Crabtree, a successful accountant, small business advisor, and popular presenter, shows you how to use your firm&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simple-numbers-straight-talk-big-profits-greg-crabtree-beverly-herzog-abridged/">Simple Numbers, Straight Talk, Big Profits! &#8211; Greg Crabtree, Beverly Herzog (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Simple Numbers can guide you to increased business profitability Take the mystery out of small business finance with this no-frills guide to understanding the numbers that will guide your business out of any financial black hole. Author Greg Crabtree, a successful accountant, small business advisor, and popular presenter, shows you how to use your firm&#8217;s key financial indicators as a basis for smart business decisions as you grow your firm from startup to $5 million (and, more ) in annual revenue. Jargon free, and presented in an easy-to-follow, step-by-step format, with plenty of real-world examples, Crabtree&#8217;s down-to-earth discussion highlights the most common financial errors committed by small businesses, and how to avoid them. You&#8217;ll be fascinated to learn: Why your numbers are lying to you (and why you are the cause ) How labor productivity is the key to profitability and simplifying human resource decisions Why the amount of tax you pay is your #1 key performance indicator Take advantage of Crabtree&#8217;s years of experience teaching clients how to build successful businesses by &#8221;seeing beyond numbers&#8221; with this step-by-step guide to increasing your businesses profitability.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simple-numbers-straight-talk-big-profits-greg-crabtree-beverly-herzog-abridged/">Simple Numbers, Straight Talk, Big Profits! &#8211; Greg Crabtree, Beverly Herzog (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD. This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career. An MBA at a top business school is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold     </p>
<p>                    ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD.    </p>
<p>                    This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career.    </p>
<p>                    An MBA at a top business school is an enormous investment in time and cash. And if you don&#8217;t want to work for a consulting firm or an investment bank, the chances are it simply isn&#8217;t worth it.    </p>
<p>                    The Personal MBA gives you simple mental models for every subject that&#8217;s key to commercial success. From the basics of products and marketing to the nuances of teamwork and systems, this book distils everything you need to know to take on the MBA graduates and win.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;File this book under: NO EXCUSES&#8217; Seth Godin    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;No matter what they tell you, an MBA is not essential. If you combine reading this book with actually trying stuff, you&#8217;ll be far ahead in the business game&#8217; Kevin Kelly, founder of Wired</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Business Chemistry : Practical Magic for Crafting Powerful Work Relationships &#8211; Kim Christfort, Suzanne Vickberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/business-chemistry-practical-magic-for-crafting-powerful-work-relationships-kim-christfort-suzanne-vickberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/business-chemistry-practical-magic-for-crafting-powerful-work-relationships-kim-christfort-suzanne-vickberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A guide to putting cognitive diversity to work Ever wonder what it is that makes two people click or clash? Or why some groups excel while others fumble? Or how you, as a leader, can make or break team potential? Business Chemistry holds the answers. Based on extensive research and analytics, plus years of proven [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/business-chemistry-practical-magic-for-crafting-powerful-work-relationships-kim-christfort-suzanne-vickberg-abridged/">Business Chemistry : Practical Magic for Crafting Powerful Work Relationships &#8211; Kim Christfort, Suzanne Vickberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A guide to putting cognitive diversity to work    </p>
<p>                     Ever wonder what it is that makes two people click or clash? Or why some groups excel while others fumble? Or how you, as a leader, can make or break team potential?    </p>
<p>                     Business Chemistry holds the answers. Based on extensive research and analytics, plus years of proven success in the field, the Business Chemistry framework provides a simple yet powerful way to identify meaningful differences between people&#8217;s working styles. Who seeks possibilities and who seeks stability? Who values challenge and who values connection? Business Chemistry will help you grasp where others are coming from, appreciate the value they bring, and determine what they need in order to excel. It offers practical ways to be more effective as an individual and as a leader.    </p>
<p>                     Imagine you had a more in-depth understanding of yourself and why you thrive in some work environments and flounder in others. Suppose you had a clearer view on what to do about it so that you could always perform at your best.    </p>
<p>                     Imagine you had more insight into what makes people tick and what ticks them off, how some interactions unlock potential while others shut people down. Suppose you could gain people&#8217;s trust, influence them, motivate them, and get the very most out of your work relationships.    </p>
<p>                     Imagine you knew how to create a work environment where all types of people excel, even if they have conflicting perspectives, preferences and needs. Suppose you could activate the potential benefits of diversity on your teams and in your organizations, improving collaboration to achieve the group&#8217;s collective potential.    </p>
<p>                     Business Chemistry offers all of this&#8211;you don&#8217;t have to leave it up to chance, and you shouldn&#8217;t. Let this book guide you in creating great chemistry!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/business-chemistry-practical-magic-for-crafting-powerful-work-relationships-kim-christfort-suzanne-vickberg-abridged/">Business Chemistry : Practical Magic for Crafting Powerful Work Relationships &#8211; Kim Christfort, Suzanne Vickberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 1% Windfall : How Successful Companies Use Price to Profit and Grow &#8211; Rafi Mohammed (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Mathematics & Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In &#8220;The Art of Pricing&#8221;, Rafi Mohammed gave readers advice on setting prices. In this essential follow up, he takes them to the next level, teaching them how to use price as a competitive strategy. A study of the Global 1200 found that if companies increased prices by just 1 percent, their average operating profits [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/">The 1% Windfall : How Successful Companies Use Price to Profit and Grow &#8211; Rafi Mohammed (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In &#8220;The Art of Pricing&#8221;, Rafi Mohammed gave readers advice on setting prices. In this essential follow up, he takes them to the next level, teaching them how to use price as a competitive strategy. A study of the Global 1200 found that if companies increased prices by just 1 percent, their average operating profits would increase by 11 percent. Using small incremental changes in price, Fortune 200 companies would see enormous growth in percentage of profit: Amazon, 40 percent; Aramark, 30 percent; Archer Daniels Midland, 19 percent; AMR, 68 percent; Boeing, 19 percent; Ingram Micro, 83 percent; McKesson, 82 percent; Wal Mart, 22 percent. Unfortunately, most companies have no clue how to capitalise on the direct link between pricing and profits. But how do executives and managers set the right price? Underpinned by sound empirical research and real-life anecdotes &#8220;The 1% Windfall&#8221; addresses this fundamental question, offering guidelines any company-whether a multi-national conglomerate, a small business, or even a non-profit can follow to create a comprehensive pricing strategy for any product and service.<br />
                    In addition, these techniques and tools apply equally to offensive and defensive solutions whether a company wants to keep ahead of the competition, avert a slump in a recession, or offset the impact of inflation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/">The 1% Windfall : How Successful Companies Use Price to Profit and Grow &#8211; Rafi Mohammed (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
