<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Media, Information &amp; Communication Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/media-information-communication-industries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/media-information-communication-industries/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Media, Information &amp; Communication Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/media-information-communication-industries/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising. For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising.     </p>
<p>                     For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup founder, a small business owner, or part of a large corporation.     </p>
<p>                     No matter what your product or service, this book will help you reframe how it&#8217;s presented to the world, in order to meaningfully connect with people who want it. Seth employs his signature blend of insight, observation, and memorable examples to teach you:    </p>
<p>                     * How to build trust and permission with your target market.<br />
                     * The art of positioning&#8211;deciding not only who it&#8217;s for, but who it&#8217;s not for.<br />
                     * Why the best way to achieve your goals is to help others become who they want to be.<br />
                     * Why the old approaches to advertising and branding no longer work.<br />
                     * The surprising role of tension in any decision to buy (or not).<br />
                     * How marketing is at its core about the stories we tell ourselves about our social status.    </p>
<p>                     You can do work that matters for people who care. This book shows you the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This Is Marketing is a very accessible way into Godin&#8217;s thinking&#8230;. Godin writes in pacy, jargon-free prose and this book is interesting and useful for anyone who wants an insight into how, and why, we buy things or change our habits in any way.&#8221; &#8211; The Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s Purple Cow, a true business classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trust Me, I&#8217;m Lying : Confessions of a Media Manipulator &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ve seen it all before. A malicious online rumor costs a company millions. A political sideshow derails the national news cycle and destroys a candidate. Some product or celebrity zooms from total obscurity to viral sensation. What you don&#8217;t know is that someone is responsible for all this. Usually, someone like me. I&#8217;m a media [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Trust Me, I&#8217;m Lying : Confessions of a Media Manipulator &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ve seen it all before. A malicious online rumor costs a company millions. A  political sideshow derails the national news cycle and destroys a candidate.  Some product or celebrity zooms from total obscurity to viral sensation. What  you don&#8217;t know is that someone is responsible for all this. Usually, someone  like me.    </p>
<p>                    I&#8217;m a media manipulator. In a world where blogs control and  distort the news, my job is to control blogs-as much as any one person  can.    </p>
<p>                    IN TODAY&#8217;S CULTURE&#8230;  Blogs like Gawker, BuzzFeed, and The Huffington Post drive the media agenda.   Bloggers are slaves to money, technology, and deadlines.  Manipulators wield these levers to shape everything you read, see, and hear-  online and off.Why am I giving away these secrets? Because I&#8217;m tired  of a world where blogs take indirect bribes, marketers help write the news,  reckless journalists spread lies, and no one is accountable for any of it. I&#8217;m  going to explain exactly how the media really works. What you choose to do with  this information is up to you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Trust Me, I&#8217;m Lying : Confessions of a Media Manipulator &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution. For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers. Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution.    For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers.       Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created.       They are using blogs, Twitter, and Facebook to share stories, and selecting their sources to create their own &#8216;front page&#8217;.   In this lively, biting critique, media commentator Tim Dunlop explores the rise of the audience, and how unprepared the mainstream media has been for this changing balance of power.       Drawing on his experiences as prominent political blogger, he argues that the future of meaningful journalism &#8211; the sort we need in order to be informed citizens &#8211; will increasingly rely on journalists and editors taking the audience into their confidence and working with them, rather than against them.   The New Front Page is a passionate plea on behalf of those tired of being talked down to by the fourth estate.       Perceptive and illuminating, it asks audiences and media to work together to hold the powerful to account, and to produce the sort of news and analysis that enriches public debate.   &#8216;A fascinating account of how digital technology has changed Australian media forever.&#8217;       Katharine Viner, editor-in-chief of The Guardian Australia   &#8216;An essential guide to understanding our insurgent new media.&#8217;       Lindsay Tanner, author of Sideshow   &#8216;Dunlop writes with humour, passion, and insight.&#8217;       Gay Alcorn, journalist</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The War on Journalism &#8211; Andrew Fowler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The War on Journalism The War on Journalism is a harrowing story of megalomaniac press barons, conspiracies, sackings, cutbacks, and self censoring journalists, cowed by what legendary investigative reporter Seymour Hersh called ochicken shit editorso. When first Chelsea Manning and then Edward Snowden blew the whistle, they did more than reveal extraordinary secrets, they struck [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/">The War on Journalism &#8211; Andrew Fowler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The War on Journalism    </p>
<p>                    The War on Journalism is a harrowing story of  megalomaniac press barons, conspiracies, sackings, cutbacks, and self censoring journalists, cowed by what legendary investigative reporter Seymour Hersh called ochicken shit editorso.     </p>
<p>                    When first Chelsea Manning and then Edward Snowden blew the whistle, they did more than reveal extraordinary secrets, they struck the first solid blows against centuries old traditions, where journalism was played by agreed rules.  Governments oleakedo secret information to their favorite journalists in return for sympathetic coverage.     </p>
<p>                    Now racked by public distrust, the cash-starved mainstream media  is struggling to survive. Newspapers which flourished for hundreds of years  and TV networks that once ruled the world are in serious decline.   Andrew Fowler gives the inside story on how and why the media helped write its own epitaph. Fowler, an investigate reporter with Australia&#8217;s prestigious Four Corners documentary program for almost 20 years, and author of the international best seller The Most Dangerous Man in the World, the revelatory story of Julian Assange and the rise of WikiLeaks, has pieced together the extraordinary story on the decline of mainstream journalism.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s not just the notorious tabloids like Rupert Murdoch&#8217;s News of the World, infamous for its phone hacking crimes, which have caused the trouble.  The BBC,  Australia&#8217;s ABC, the Washington Post and the New York Times, and the Guardian, are also in the firing line.    </p>
<p>                    Now the establishment is fighting back with draconian laws to silence the new journalism. From the UK to the US to Australia, governments are harassing journalists, threatening to jail both the whistleblowers and those who publish  their leaks     </p>
<p>                    A battle, shrouded in the cloak of national security, pitting the public&#8217;s right to know against the powerful interests of those who want business as usual, it&#8217;s a stark choice- an increasingly democratic world, or one dominated by executive government, often unchallenged and unaccountable, spying on its own citizens and producing fraudulent arguments to fight horrific wars. Just who wins this information battle will not only define the kind of journalism that survives but also the kind of world we will all live in.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/">The War on Journalism &#8211; Andrew Fowler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The indispensable classic on marketing by the bestselling author of Tribes and Purple Cow. Legendary business writer Seth Godin has three essential questions for every marketer: &#8220;What&#8217;s your story?&#8221; &#8220;Will the people who need to hear this story believe it?&#8221; &#8220;Is it true?&#8221; All marketers tell stories. And if they do it right, we believe [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/">All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The indispensable classic on marketing by the bestselling author of Tribes and Purple Cow.    </p>
<p>                     Legendary business writer Seth Godin has three essential questions for every marketer:     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;What&#8217;s your story?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Will the people who need to hear this story believe it?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Is it true?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     All marketers tell stories. And if they do it right, we believe them. We believe that wine tastes better in a $20 glass than a $1 glass. We believe that an $80,000 Porsche is vastly superior to a $36,000 Volkswagen that&#8217;s virtually the same car. We believe that $225 sneakers make our feet feel better&#8211;and look cooler&#8211;than a $25 brand. And believing it makes it true.     </p>
<p>                     As Seth Godin has taught hundreds of thousands of marketers and students around the world, great marketers don&#8217;t talk about features or even benefits. Instead, they tell a story&#8211;a story we want to believe, whether it&#8217;s factual or not. In a world where most people have an infinite number of choices and no time to make them, every organization is a marketer, and all marketing is about telling stories.     </p>
<p>                     Marketers succeed when they tell us a story that fits our worldview, a story that we intuitively embrace and then share with our friends. Think of the Dyson vacuum cleaner, or Fiji water, or the iPod.     </p>
<p>                     But beware: If your stories are inauthentic, you cross the line from fib to fraud. Marketers fail when they are selfish and scurrilous, when they abuse the tools of their trade and make the world worse. That&#8217;s a lesson learned the hard way by telemarketers, cigarette companies, and sleazy politicians.     </p>
<p>                     But for the rest of us, it&#8217;s time to embrace the power of the story. As Godin writes, &#8220;Stories make it easier to understand the world. Stories are the only way we know to spread an idea. Marketers didn&#8217;t invent storytelling. They just perfected it.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/">All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Than Enough : Claiming Space for Who You Are (No Matter What They Say) &#8211; Elaine Welteroth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WINNER OF THE 2020 NAACP IMAGE AWARD FOR OUTSTANDING LITERARY WORK &#8211; BIOGRAPHY/AUTOBIOGRAPHY In this part-manifesto, part-memoir, the revolutionary editor who infused social consciousness into the pages of Teen Vogue explores what it means to come into your own &#8211; on your own terms. Elaine Welteroth has climbed the ranks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/">More Than Enough : Claiming Space for Who You Are (No Matter What They Say) &#8211; Elaine Welteroth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    WINNER OF THE 2020 NAACP IMAGE AWARD FOR OUTSTANDING LITERARY WORK &#8211; BIOGRAPHY/AUTOBIOGRAPHY    </p>
<p>                    In this part-manifesto, part-memoir, the revolutionary editor who infused social consciousness into the pages of Teen Vogue explores what it means to come into your own &#8211; on your own terms.    </p>
<p>                    Elaine Welteroth has climbed the ranks of media and fashion,  shattering ceilings along the way. In this riveting and timely memoir,  the groundbreaking editor unpacks lessons on race, identity, and  success through her own journey, from navigating her way as the  unstoppable child of a unlikely interracial marriage in small-town  California to finding herself on the frontlines of a modern movement for  the next generation of change makers.     </p>
<p>                    Welteroth moves beyond  the headlines and highlight reels to share the profound lessons and  struggles of being a barrier-breaker across so many intersections. As a  young boss and the only black woman in the room, she&#8217;s had enough of the  world telling her &#8211; and all women &#8211; they&#8217;re not enough. As she learns to  rely on herself by looking both inward and upward, we&#8217;re ultimately  reminded that we&#8217;re more than enough.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-than-enough-claiming-space-for-who-you-are-no-matter-what-they-say-elaine-welteroth-abridged/">More Than Enough : Claiming Space for Who You Are (No Matter What They Say) &#8211; Elaine Welteroth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Age of Propaganda &#8211; Anthony Pratkanis, Elliot Aronson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dance & Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Americans create 57% of the world&#8217;s advertising while representing only 6% of its population; half of our waking hours are spent immersed in the mass media. Persuasion has always been integral to the democratic process, but increasingly, thoughtful discussion is being replaced with simplistic soundbites and manipulative messages. Drawing on the history of propaganda as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/">Age of Propaganda &#8211; Anthony Pratkanis, Elliot Aronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Americans create 57% of the world&#8217;s advertising while representing only 6% of its population; half of our waking hours are spent immersed in the mass media. Persuasion has always been integral to the democratic process, but increasingly, thoughtful discussion is being replaced with simplistic soundbites and manipulative messages.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the history of propaganda as well as on contemporary research in social psychology, Age of Propaganda shows how the tactics used by political campaigners, sales agents, advertisers, televangelists, demagogues, and others often take advantage of our emotions by appealing to our deepest fears and most irrational hopes, creating a distorted vision of the world we live in.     </p>
<p>                    This revised and updated edition includes coverage of the Clinton/Lewinsky scandal, recent election campaigns, talk radio, teen suicide, U.F.O. abductions, the Columbine shootings, and novel propaganda tactics based on hypocrisy and false allegations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/">Age of Propaganda &#8211; Anthony Pratkanis, Elliot Aronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>50th Anniversary Edition &#8211; With an introduction by Caity Weaver, acclaimed New York Times journalist This cult classic of gonzo journalism is the best chronicle of drug-soaked, addle-brained, rollicking good times ever committed to the printed page. It is also the tale of a long weekend road trip that has gone down in the annals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/">Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>50th Anniversary Edition &#8211; With an introduction by Caity Weaver, acclaimed New York Times journalist     </p>
<p>                    This cult classic of gonzo journalism is the best chronicle of drug-soaked, addle-brained, rollicking good times ever committed to the printed page. It is also the tale of a long weekend road trip that has gone down in the annals of American pop culture as one of the strangest journeys ever undertaken.     </p>
<p>                    Also a major motion picture directed by Terry Gilliam, starring Johnny Depp and Benicio del Toro.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/">Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semiotics / Semiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They reveal how issues are framed and topics chosen, and contrast the double standards underlying accounts of free elections, a free press, and governmental repression between Nicaragua and El Salvador; between the Russian invasion of Afghanistan and the American invasion of Vietnam; between the genocide in Cambodia under a pro-American government and genocide under Pol Pot. What emerges from this groundbreaking work is an account of just how propagandistic our mass media are, and how we can learn to read them and see their function in a radically new way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217; Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene amounts of money &#8212; as well as how to dress, talk, date, drink, and schmooze like real financiers. Young Money is the exclusive, inside story of this well-guarded world.<br />
                    Investigative reporter Kevin Roose shadows eight rookies as they are exposed to the exhausting workloads, huge bonuses, and recreational drugs that have always characterized Wall Street life. But they experience something new, too: an industry forever changed by the massive financial collapse of 2008. And as they get their Wall Street educations, they face hard questions about morality, prestige, and the value of their work.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A great new read that doubles as a post-crash update to Michael Lewis&#8217; Liar&#8217;s Poker &#8211; Mother Jones    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fun fast read that will make you laugh out loud&#8217; Fortune Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marissa Mayer and the Fight to Save Yahoo! &#8211; Nicholas Carlson, Read by Kiff Vandenheuvel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/marissa-mayer-and-the-fight-to-save-yahoo-nicholas-carlson-read-by-kiff-vandenheuvel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/marissa-mayer-and-the-fight-to-save-yahoo-nicholas-carlson-read-by-kiff-vandenheuvel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A page-turning warts-and-all narrative about Marissa Mayer&#8217;s efforts to remake Yahoo as well as her own rise from Stanford University undergrad to CEO of a $30 billion corporation by the age of thirty-eight. When Yahoo hired star Google executive Marissa Mayer to be its CEO in 2012, employees rejoiced. They put posters on the walls [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/marissa-mayer-and-the-fight-to-save-yahoo-nicholas-carlson-read-by-kiff-vandenheuvel-abridged/">Marissa Mayer and the Fight to Save Yahoo! &#8211; Nicholas Carlson, Read by Kiff Vandenheuvel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A page-turning warts-and-all narrative about Marissa Mayer&#8217;s efforts to remake Yahoo as well as her own rise from Stanford University undergrad to CEO of a $30 billion corporation by the age of thirty-eight.    </p>
<p>                    When Yahoo hired star Google executive Marissa Mayer to be its CEO in 2012, employees rejoiced. They put posters on the walls throughout Yahoo&#8217;s California headquarters. On them was Mayer&#8217;s face and one word: hope.    </p>
<p>                    Just over a year later-on November 4, 2013-Mayer sat in front of those same employees in a huge cafeteria on Yahoo&#8217;s campus and took the beating of her life. Her hair wet and her tone defensive, Mayer read and answered a series of employee-posed questions challenging the basic elements of her plan. There was anger in the room; and behind it, a question: Was Mayer actually going to be able to do this thing?    </p>
<p>                    Nicholas Carlson&#8217;s fast-paced narrative is the inside story of Mayer&#8217;s controversial rise at Google, her desperate fight to save an Internet icon, and how Yahoo got into such awful shape in the first place.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/marissa-mayer-and-the-fight-to-save-yahoo-nicholas-carlson-read-by-kiff-vandenheuvel-abridged/">Marissa Mayer and the Fight to Save Yahoo! &#8211; Nicholas Carlson, Read by Kiff Vandenheuvel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media. Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media.     </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography    </p>
<p>                    In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers and Watergate, tells her story&#8211;one that is extraordinary both for the events it encompasses and for the courage, candor, and dignity of its telling.     </p>
<p>                     Here is the awkward child who grew up amid material wealth and emotional isolation; the young bride who watched her brilliant, charismatic husband&#8211;a confidant to John F. Kennedy and Lyndon Johnson&#8211;plunge into the mental illness that would culminate in his suicide. And here is the widow who shook off her grief and insecurity to take on a president and a pressman&#8217;s union as she entered the profane boys&#8217; club of the newspaper business.     </p>
<p>                     As timely now as ever, Personal History is an exemplary record of our history and of the woman who played such a shaping role within them, discovering her own strength and sense of self as she confronted&#8211;and mastered&#8211;the personal and professional crises of her fascinating life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FULLY REVISED &#038; UPDATED, WITH A NEW EPILOGUE &#8220;Delightful.&#8221;-The Economist There&#8217;s Santa Claus, Shakespeare, Mickey Mouse, the Bible, and then there&#8217;s Star Wars. Nothing quite compares to sitting down with a young child and hearing the sound of John Williams&#8217;s score as those beloved golden letters fill the screen. In this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/">The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    FULLY REVISED &#038; UPDATED, WITH A NEW EPILOGUE    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Delightful.&#8221;-The Economist    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s Santa Claus, Shakespeare, Mickey Mouse, the Bible, and then there&#8217;s Star Wars. Nothing quite compares to sitting down with a young child and hearing the sound of John Williams&#8217;s score as those beloved golden letters fill the screen. In this fun, erudite, and often moving book, Cass R. Sunstein explores the lessons of Star Wars as they relate to childhood, fathers, the Dark Side, rebellion, and redemption. As it turns out, Star Wars also has a lot to teach us about constitutional law, economics, and political uprisings.    </p>
<p>                              In rich detail, Sunstein tells the story of the films&#8217; wildly unanticipated success and explores why some things succeed while others fail. Ultimately, Sunstein argues, Star Wars is about freedom of choice and our never-ending ability to make the right decision when the chips are down. Written with buoyant prose and considerable heart, The World According to Star Wars shines a bright new light on the most beloved story of our time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/">The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019 _____________________________ The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES<br />
                    THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                    _____________________________    </p>
<p>                    The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in the world and inspire the people who bring the magic to life.     </p>
<p>                    Robert Iger became CEO of The Walt Disney Company in 2005, during a difficult time. Morale had deteriorated, competition was intense, and technology was changing faster than at any time in the company&#8217;s history. His vision came down to three clear ideas: Recommit to the concept that quality matters, embrace technology instead of fighting it, and think bigger-think global-and turn Disney into a stronger brand in international markets.     </p>
<p>                    Fourteen years later, Disney is the largest, most respected media company in the world, counting Pixar, Marvel, Lucasfilm and 21st Century Fox among its properties. Its value is nearly five times what it was when Iger took over, and he is recognized as one of the most innovative and successful CEOs of our era.    </p>
<p>                    In The Ride of a Lifetime, Robert Iger shares the lessons he&#8217;s learned while running Disney and leading its 200,000 employees, and he explores the principles that are necessary for true leadership, including:    </p>
<p>                     Optimism. Even in the face of difficulty, an optimistic leader will find the path toward the best possible outcome and focus on that, rather than give in to pessimism and blaming.<br />
                     Courage. Leaders have to be willing to take risks and place big bets. Fear of failure destroys creativity.<br />
                     Decisiveness. All decisions, no matter how difficult, can be made on a timely basis. Indecisiveness is both wasteful and destructive to morale.<br />
                     Fairness. Treat people decently, with empathy, and be accessible to them.     </p>
<p>                    This book is about the relentless curiosity that has driven Iger for forty-five years, since the day he started as the lowliest studio grunt at ABC. It&#8217;s also about thoughtfulness and respect, and a decency-over-dollars approach that has become the bedrock of every project and partnership Iger pursues, from a deep friendship with Steve Jobs in his final years to an abiding love of the Star Wars mythology.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The ideas in this book strike me as universal&#8221; Iger writes. &#8220;Not just to the aspiring CEOs of the world, but to anyone wanting to feel less fearful, more confidently themselves, as they navigate their professional and even personal lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING * &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING *     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly written haymaker&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly three years of reporting, hundreds of hours of interviews and more than two hundred sources, including some of the most senior members of the administration, friends and first-hand witnesses who have never spoken before, Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig take us inside some of the most controversial moments of Trump&#8217;s presidency. They peer deeply into Trump&#8217;s White House &#8211; at the aides pressured to lie to the public, the lawyers scrambling to clear up norm-breaking disasters, and the staffers whose careers have been reduced to ashes &#8211; to paint an unparalleled group portrait of an administration driven by self-preservation and paranoia.     </p>
<p>                    Rucker and Leonnig reveal Trump at his most unvarnished, showing the unhinged decision-making and incompetence that has floored officials and stunned foreign leaders. They portray unscripted calls with Vladimir Putin, steak dinners with Kim Jong-un, and calls with Theresa May so hostile that they left her aides shaken. They also take a hard look at Robert Mueller, Trump&#8217;s greatest antagonist to date, and how his investigation slowly unravelled an administration whose universal value is loyalty &#8211; not to country, but to the president himself.    </p>
<p>                    Grippingly told, A Very Stable Genius is a behind-the-scenes account of Trump&#8217;s vainglorious pursuit of power in his first term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Truth : 13 Reasons To Question Everything You Are Told &#8211; Hector Macdonald (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>_________________ &#8216;Macdonald zeros in on the slipperiness of factuality, offering an array of case studies from the worlds of history, commerce and &#8211; of course &#8211; politics.&#8217; New York Times True or false? It&#8217;s rarely that simple. There is always more than one truth in every story. Eating meat is nutritious but it&#8217;s also damaging [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/">Truth : 13 Reasons To Question Everything You Are Told &#8211; Hector Macdonald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>_________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Macdonald zeros in on the slipperiness of factuality, offering an array of case studies from the worlds of history, commerce and &#8211; of course &#8211; politics.&#8217; New York Times     </p>
<p>                    True or false?  It&#8217;s rarely that simple.    </p>
<p>                    There is always more than one truth in every story.  Eating meat is nutritious but it&#8217;s also damaging to the environment.  The Internet disseminates knowledge but it also spreads hatred.  As communicators, we select the truths that are most useful to our agenda.    </p>
<p>                    We can select truths constructively to inspire nations, encourage children, and drive progressive change.  Or we can select truths that give a false impression of reality, misleading people without actually lying.  Others can do the same, motivating or deceiving us with the truth.      </p>
<p>                    In Truth, communications strategy expert Hector Macdonald explores how truth is used and abused in politics, business, the media and everyday life.   Combining great storytelling with practical takeaways and a litany of fascinating, funny and insightful case studies, Truth is a chilling and engaging read about how profoundly our mindsets and actions are influenced by the truths that those around us choose to tell.    </p>
<p>                    For fans of Factfulness, A Field Guide to Lies and Statistics and The Art of Thinking Clearly, a fascinating dive into the many ways in which &#8216;competing truths&#8217; shape our opinions, behaviours and beliefs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/">Truth : 13 Reasons To Question Everything You Are Told &#8211; Hector Macdonald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Enhance your copywriting skills with psychology-driven techniques to create stand out copy that taps into consumer decision making and sells, using this second edition of the ultimate copywriting survival guide for the 21st century &#8211; essential to every marketing or creative professional&#8217;s bookshelf. With many professionals now developing their skills on the job, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/">Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Enhance your copywriting skills with psychology-driven techniques to create stand out copy that taps into consumer decision making and sells, using this second edition of the ultimate copywriting survival guide for the 21st century &#8211; essential to every marketing or creative professional&#8217;s bookshelf.    </p>
<p>                    With many professionals now developing their skills on the job, it is notoriously difficult to benchmark successful copy. This book provides a step up for those who already know the basics of writing copy, and are seeking more advanced, psychology-driven techniques to gain the competitive edge. With practical insight into human decision making and consumer engagement, it will inspire the clear-cut confidence needed to create, quantify, and sell stand out copy in a cluttered marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    Complementing the &#8216;how to&#8217; perspective of copywriting, with impressive interviews from leading ad agencies and copywriters across the globe, this second edition addresses the everyday issues faced in a multitude of roles, including:    </p>
<p>                    -Practical advice to measure and benchmark effective copy<br />
                    -Guidance on creating and critiquing briefs<br />
                    -New chapters on how to weave copywriting skills into the wider industry<br />
                    -Storytelling and content marketing<br />
                    -The impact of evolving channels like mobile and social media    </p>
<p>                    Practical, inspiring and extremely digestible, Persuasive Copywriting is the only vibrant, all-encompassing guide to copywriting that you need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/persuasive-copywriting-cut-through-the-noise-and-communicate-with-impact-andy-maslen-abridged/">Persuasive Copywriting : Cut Through the Noise and Communicate With Impact &#8211; Andy Maslen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dance & Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital TV & Media Centres: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Radio & Television Industry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How big data is transforming the creative industries, and how those industries can use lessons from Netflix, Amazon, and Apple to fight back. &#8220;[The authors explain] gently yet firmly exactly how the internet threatens established ways and what can and cannot be done about it. Their book should be required for anyone who wishes to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/">Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How big data is transforming the creative industries, and how those industries can use lessons from Netflix, Amazon, and Apple to fight back.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;[The authors explain] gently yet firmly exactly how the internet threatens established ways and what can and cannot be done about it. Their book should be required for anyone who wishes to believe that nothing much has changed.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;The Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Packed with examples, from the nimble-footed who reacted quickly to adapt their businesses, to laggards who lost empires.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    Traditional network television programming has always followed the same script: executives approve a pilot, order a trial number of episodes, and broadcast them, expecting viewers to watch a given show on their television sets at the same time every week. But then came Netflix&#8217;s House of Cards. Netflix gauged the show&#8217;s potential from data it had gathered about subscribers&#8217; preferences, ordered two seasons without seeing a pilot, and uploaded the first thirteen episodes all at once for viewers to watch whenever they wanted on the devices of their choice.     </p>
<p>                    In this book, Michael Smith and Rahul Telang, experts on entertainment analytics, show how the success of House of Cards upended the film and TV industries&#8211;and how companies like Amazon and Apple are changing the rules in other entertainment industries, notably publishing and music. We&#8217;re living through a period of unprecedented technological disruption in the entertainment industries. Just about everything is affected: pricing, production, distribution, piracy. Smith and Telang discuss niche products and the long tail, product differentiation, price discrimination, and incentives for users not to steal content. To survive and succeed, businesses have to adapt rapidly and creatively. Smith and Telang explain how.    </p>
<p>                    How can companies discover who their customers are, what they want, and how much they are willing to pay for it? Data. The entertainment industries, must learn to play a little &#8220;moneyball.&#8221; The bottom line: follow the data.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/">Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
