<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cybernetics &amp; Systems Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/cybernetics-systems-theory/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/cybernetics-systems-theory/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Cybernetics &amp; Systems Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/cybernetics-systems-theory/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Thinking in Systems : a Primer &#8211; Donella Meadows, Edited by Diana Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thinking-in-systems-a-primer-donella-meadows-edited-by-diana-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybernetics & Systems Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thinking-in-systems-a-primer-donella-meadows-edited-by-diana-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the years following her role as the lead author of the international bestseller, Limits to Growth&#8211;the first book to show the consequences of unchecked growth on a finite planet&#8211; Donella Meadows remained a pioneer of environmental and social analysis until her untimely death in 2001. Meadows&#8217; newly released manuscript, Thinking in Systems, is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-in-systems-a-primer-donella-meadows-edited-by-diana-wright-abridged/">Thinking in Systems : a Primer &#8211; Donella Meadows, Edited by Diana Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the years following her role as the lead author of the international bestseller, Limits to Growth&#8211;the first book to show the consequences of unchecked growth on a finite planet&#8211; Donella Meadows remained a pioneer of environmental and social analysis until her untimely death in 2001. Meadows&#8217; newly released manuscript, Thinking in Systems, is a concise and crucial book offering insight for problem solving on scales ranging from the personal to the global. Edited by the Sustainability Institute&#8217;s Diana Wright, this essential primer brings systems thinking out of the realm of computers and equations and into the tangible world, showing readers how to develop the systems-thinking skills that thought leaders across the globe consider critical for 21st-century life. Some of the biggest problems facing the world&#8211;war, hunger, poverty, and environmental degradation&#8211;are essentially system failures. They cannot be solved by fixing one piece in isolation from the others, because even seemingly minor details have enormous power to undermine the best efforts of too-narrow thinking. While readers will learn the conceptual tools and methods of systems thinking, the heart of the book is grander than methodology. Donella Meadows was known as much for nurturing positive outcomes as she was for delving into the science behind global dilemmas. She reminds readers to pay attention to what is important, not just what is quantifiable, to stay humble, and to stay a learner. In a world growing ever more complicated, crowded, and interdependent, Thinking in Systems helps readers avoid confusion and helplessness, the first step toward finding proactive and effective solutions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-in-systems-a-primer-donella-meadows-edited-by-diana-wright-abridged/">Thinking in Systems : a Primer &#8211; Donella Meadows, Edited by Diana Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simply Complexity : A Clear Guide to Complexity Theory &#8211; Neil Johnson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/simply-complexity-a-clear-guide-to-complexity-theory-neil-johnson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chaos Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybernetics & Systems Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/simply-complexity-a-clear-guide-to-complexity-theory-neil-johnson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What do traffic jams, stock market crashes, and wars have in common? They are all explained using complexity, an unsolved puzzle that many researchers believe is the key to predicting &#8211; and ultimately solving-everything from terrorist attacks and pandemic viruses right down to rush hour traffic congestion. Complexity is considered by many to be the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simply-complexity-a-clear-guide-to-complexity-theory-neil-johnson-abridged/">Simply Complexity : A Clear Guide to Complexity Theory &#8211; Neil Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What do traffic jams, stock market crashes, and wars have in common? They are all explained using complexity, an unsolved puzzle that many researchers believe is the key to predicting &#8211; and ultimately solving-everything from terrorist attacks and pandemic viruses right down to rush hour traffic congestion.    </p>
<p>                    Complexity is considered by many to be the single most important scientific development since general relativity and it promises to make sense of no less than the very heart of the Universe. Using it, scientists can find order emerging from seemingly random interactions of all kinds, from something as simple as flipping coins through to more challenging problems such as the patterns in modern jazz, the growth of cancer tumours, and predicting shopping habits.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simply-complexity-a-clear-guide-to-complexity-theory-neil-johnson-abridged/">Simply Complexity : A Clear Guide to Complexity Theory &#8211; Neil Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions by Mig Greengard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybernetics & Systems Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In May 1997, the world watched as Garry Kasparov, the greatest chess player in the world, was defeated for the first time by the IBM supercomputer Deep Blue. It was a watershed moment in the history of technology: machine intelligence had arrived at the point where it could best human intellect. It wasn&#8217;t a coincidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/">Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions by Mig Greengard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In May 1997, the world watched as Garry Kasparov, the greatest chess player in the world, was defeated for the first time by the IBM supercomputer Deep Blue. It was a watershed moment in the history of technology: machine intelligence had arrived at the point where it could best human intellect.    </p>
<p>                    It wasn&#8217;t a coincidence that Kasparov became the symbol of man&#8217;s fight against the machines. Chess has long been the fulcrum in development of machine intelligence; the hoax automaton &#8216;The Turk&#8217; in the 18th century and Alan Turing&#8217;s first chess program in 1952 were two early examples of the quest for machines to think like humans &#8212; a talent we measured by their ability to beat their creators at chess. As the pre-eminent chessmaster of the 80s and 90s, it was Kasparov&#8217;s blessing and his curse to play against each generation&#8217;s strongest computer champions, contributing to their development and advancing the field.     </p>
<p>                    Like all passionate competitors, Kasparov has taken his defeat and learned from it. He has devoted much energy to devising ways in which humans can partner with machines in order to produce results better than either can achieve alone. During the twenty years since playing Deep Blue, he&#8217;s played both with and against machines, learning a great deal about our vital relationship with our most remarkable creations. Ultimately, he&#8217;s become convinced that by embracing the competition between human and machine intelligence, we can spend less time worrying about being replaced and more thinking of new challenges to conquer.    </p>
<p>                    In this breakthrough book, Kasparov tells his side of the story of Deep Blue for the first time &#8212; what it was like to strategize against an implacable, untiring opponent &#8212; the mistakes he made and the reasons the odds were against him. But more than that, he tells his story of AI more generally, and how he&#8217;s evolved to embrace it, taking part in an urgent debate with philosophers worried about human values, programmers creating self-learning neural networks, and engineers of cutting edge robotics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/">Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions by Mig Greengard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
