<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Environmental Science, Engineering &amp; Technology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/environmental-science-engineering-technology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/environmental-science-engineering-technology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Environmental Science, Engineering &amp; Technology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/environmental-science-engineering-technology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electricity, Electromagnetism & Magnetism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Power Generation & Distribution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory look at our national power grid&#8211;how it developed, its current flaws, and how it must be completely reimagined for our fast-approaching energy future. America&#8217;s electrical grid, an engineering triumph of the twentieth century, is turning out to be a poor fit for the present. It&#8217;s not just that the grid has grown old [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/">The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory look at our national power grid&#8211;how it developed, its current flaws, and how it must be completely reimagined for our fast-approaching energy future.     </p>
<p>                    America&#8217;s electrical grid, an engineering triumph of the twentieth century, is turning out to be a poor fit for the present. It&#8217;s not just that the grid has grown old and is now in dire need of basic repair. Today, as we invest great hope in new energy sources&#8211;solar, wind, and other alternatives&#8211;the grid is what stands most firmly in the way of a brighter energy future. If we hope to realize this future, we need to reimagine the grid according to twenty-first-century values. It&#8217;s a project which forces visionaries to work with bureaucrats, legislators with storm-flattened communities, moneymen with hippies, and the left with the right. And though it might not yet be obvious, this revolution is already well under way.     </p>
<p>                     Cultural anthropologist Gretchen Bakke unveils the many facets of America&#8217;s energy infrastructure, its most dynamic moments and its most stable ones, and its essential role in personal and national life. The grid, she argues, is an essentially American artifact, one which developed with us: a product of bold expansion, the occasional foolhardy vision, some genius technologies, and constant improvisation. Most of all, her focus is on how Americans are changing the grid right now, sometimes with gumption and big dreams and sometimes with legislation or the brandishing of guns.     </p>
<p>                    The Grid tells&#8211;entertainingly, perceptively&#8211;the story of what has been called the largest machine in the world: its fascinating history, its problematic present, and its potential role in a brighter, cleaner future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/">The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A World Without Ice &#8211; Henry Pollack (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hydrology & The Hydrosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meteorology & Climatology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clear-eyed explanation of the impact of ice on Earth, its climate, and its residents. Much has been written about global warming, but the crucial relationship between people and ice has received little focus, until now &#8211; and there is a fierce urgency as the problem accelerates. With clarity and insight, geophysicist and a co-winner [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/">A World Without Ice &#8211; Henry Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clear-eyed explanation of the impact of ice on Earth, its climate, and its residents.      </p>
<p>                     Much has been written about global warming, but the crucial relationship between people and ice has received little focus, until now &#8211; and there is a fierce urgency as the problem accelerates. With clarity and insight, geophysicist and a co-winner of the 2007 Nobel Peace Prize, Henry Pollack, paints a compelling portrait of the delicate geological balance between Earth and its ice, and shows why the current rapid loss of ice portends serious consequences in our not-so-distant future.     </p>
<p>                     Whether sculpting mountains, regulating temperatures, influencing ocean currents, or defining the limits of human settlement, ice has shaped &#8211; and continues to shape &#8211; the world we live in. This important and increasingly relevant book traces the effect of mountain glaciers on supplies of drinking water and agricultural irrigation, as well as the current results of melting permafrost and shrinking Arctic sea ice &#8211; a situation that has degraded the habitat of numerous animals and sparked an international race for seabed oil and minerals. Catastrophic possibilities loom, including rising sea levels and subsequent flooding of low-lying regions worldwide.     </p>
<p>                     A World Without Ice explains why ice matters, and lays out the urgent actions we can take to restore Earth&#8217;s delicate climate balance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/">A World Without Ice &#8211; Henry Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Green Illusions : The Dirty Secrets of Clean Energy and the Future of Environmentalism &#8211; Ozzie Zehner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/green-illusions-the-dirty-secrets-of-clean-energy-and-the-future-of-environmentalism-ozzie-zehner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alternative & Renewable Energy Sources & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/green-illusions-the-dirty-secrets-of-clean-energy-and-the-future-of-environmentalism-ozzie-zehner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We don&#8217;t have an energy crisis. We have a consumption crisis. And this book, which takes aim at cherished assumptions regarding energy, offers refreshingly straight talk about what&#8217;s wrong with the way we think and talk about the problem. Though we generally believe we can solve environmental problems with more energy-more solar cells, wind turbines, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/green-illusions-the-dirty-secrets-of-clean-energy-and-the-future-of-environmentalism-ozzie-zehner-abridged/">Green Illusions : The Dirty Secrets of Clean Energy and the Future of Environmentalism &#8211; Ozzie Zehner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We don&#8217;t have an energy crisis. We have a consumption crisis. And this book, which takes aim at cherished assumptions regarding energy, offers refreshingly straight talk about what&#8217;s wrong with the way we think and talk about the problem. Though we generally believe we can solve environmental problems with more energy-more solar cells, wind turbines, and biofuels-alternative technologies come with their own side effects and limitations. How, for instance, do solar cells cause harm? Why can&#8217;t engineers solve wind power&#8217;s biggest obstacle? Why won&#8217;t contraception solve the problem of overpopulation lying at the heart of our concerns about energy, and what will?<br />
                    This practical, environmentally informed, and lucid book persuasively argues for a change of perspective. If consumption is the problem, as Ozzie Zehner suggests, then we need to shift our focus from suspect alternative energies to improving social and political fundamentals: walkable communities, improved consumption, enlightened governance, and, most notably, women&#8217;s rights. The dozens of first steps he offers are surprisingly straightforward. For instance, he introduces a simple sticker that promises a greater impact than all of the nation&#8217;s solar cells. He uncovers why carbon taxes won&#8217;t solve our energy challenges (and presents two taxes that could). Finally, he explores how future environmentalists will focus on similarly fresh alternatives that are affordable, clean, and can actually improve our well-being.<br />
                    Watch a book trailer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/green-illusions-the-dirty-secrets-of-clean-energy-and-the-future-of-environmentalism-ozzie-zehner-abridged/">Green Illusions : The Dirty Secrets of Clean Energy and the Future of Environmentalism &#8211; Ozzie Zehner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Technologies & Applied Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).     </p>
<p>                    Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot be closed. But it is closing-fast.     </p>
<p>                    InAbundance, space entrepreneur turned innovation pioneer Peter H. Diamandis and award-winning science writer Steven Kotler document how progress in artificial intelligence, robotics, digital manufacturing synthetic biology, and other exponentially growing technologies will enable us to make greater gains in the next two decades than we have in the previous 200 years. We will soon have the ability to meet and exceed the basic needs of every person on the planet. Abundance for all is within our grasp.     </p>
<p>                    Breaking down human needs by category-water, food, energy, healthcare, education, freedom-Diamandis and Kotler introduce us to innovators and industry captains making tremendous strides in each area. &#8220;Not only isAbundancea riveting page-turner&#8230;but it&#8217;s a book that gives us a future worth fighting for. And even more than that, it shows us our place in that fight&#8221; (The Christian Science Monitor).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Plant Ecology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Comfortably Unaware, Dr. Richard Oppenlander tackles the crucial issue of global depletion as it relates to food choice. We should all be committed, he tells us, to understanding the reality and consequences of our diet, the footprint it makes on our environment, and seek food products that are in the best interest of all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/">Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Comfortably Unaware, Dr. Richard Oppenlander tackles the crucial issue of global depletion as it relates to food choice. We should all be committed, he tells us, to understanding the reality and consequences of our diet, the footprint it makes on our environment, and seek food products that are in the best interest of all living things. His forthright information and stark mental images are often disturbing-and that&#8217;s how it should be. As the guardians of Planet Earth, we need to be shaken out of our complacency, to stop being comfortably unaware, and to understand the measures we must take to ensure the health and well-being of our planet-and of ourselves. Oppenlander</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/">Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geographical Discovery & Exploration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geology & The Lithosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Geography & Topography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** Winner of Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books 2015 ** We live in epoch-making times. The changes we humans have made in recent decades have altered our world beyond anything it has experienced in its 4.6 billion-year history. As a result, our planet is said to be crossing into the Anthropocene &#8211; the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/">Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** Winner of Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books 2015 **    </p>
<p>                    We live in epoch-making times. The changes we humans have made in recent decades have altered our world beyond anything it has experienced in its 4.6 billion-year history. As a result, our planet is said to be crossing into the Anthropocene &#8211; the Age of Humans.     </p>
<p>                     Gaia Vince decided to travel the world at the start of this new age to see what life is really like for the people on the frontline of the planet we&#8217;ve made.  From artificial glaciers in the Himalayas to painted mountains in Peru, electrified reefs in the Maldives to garbage islands in the Caribbean, Gaia found people doing the most extraordinary things to solve the problems that we ourselves have created.    </p>
<p>                     These stories show what the Anthropocene means for all of us &#8211; and they illuminate how we might engineer Earth for our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-the-anthropocene-a-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-planet-we-made-gaia-vince-abridged/">Adventures in the Anthropocene : A Journey to the Heart of the Planet we Made &#8211; Gaia Vince (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Bad Are Bananas? : The carbon footprint of everything &#8211; Mike Berners-Lee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-bad-are-bananas-the-carbon-footprint-of-everything-mike-berners-lee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self-sufficiency]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-bad-are-bananas-the-carbon-footprint-of-everything-mike-berners-lee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How Bad Are Bananas? was a groundbreaking book when first published in 2009, when most of us were hearing the phrase &#8216;carbon footprint&#8217; for the first time. Mike Berners-Lee set out to inform us what was important (aviation, heating, swimming pools) and what made very little difference (bananas, naturally packaged, are good!). This new edition [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-bad-are-bananas-the-carbon-footprint-of-everything-mike-berners-lee-abridged/">How Bad Are Bananas? : The carbon footprint of everything &#8211; Mike Berners-Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How Bad Are Bananas? was a groundbreaking book when first published in 2009, when most of us were hearing the phrase &#8216;carbon footprint&#8217; for the first time. Mike Berners-Lee set out to inform us what was important (aviation, heating, swimming pools) and what made very little difference (bananas, naturally packaged, are good!).     </p>
<p>                    This new edition updates all the figures (from data centres to hosting a World Cup) and introduces many areas that have become a regular part of modern life &#8211; Twitter, the Cloud, Bitcoin, electric bikes and cars, even space tourism. Berners-Lee runs a considered eye over each area and gives us the figures to manage and reduce our own carbon footprint, as well as to lobby our companies, businesses and government. His findings, presented in clear and even entertaining prose, are often surprising. And they are essential if we are to address climate change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-bad-are-bananas-the-carbon-footprint-of-everything-mike-berners-lee-abridged/">How Bad Are Bananas? : The carbon footprint of everything &#8211; Mike Berners-Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making the Modern World : Materials and Dematerialization &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Materials Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mechanical Engineering & Materials]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How much further should the affluent world push its material consumption? Does relative dematerialization lead to absolute decline in demand for materials? These and many other questions are discussed and answered in Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization. Over the course of time, the modern world has become dependent on unprecedented flows of materials. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Making the Modern World : Materials and Dematerialization &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How much further should the affluent world push its material consumption? Does relative dematerialization lead to absolute decline in demand for materials?  These and many other questions are discussed and answered in Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization. Over the course of time, the modern world has become dependent on unprecedented flows of materials. Now even the most efficient production processes and the highest practical rates of recycling may not be enough to result in dematerialization rates that would be high enough to negate the rising demand for materials generated by continuing population growth and rising standards of living. This book explores the costs of this dependence and the potential for substantial dematerialization of modern economies. Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization considers the principal materials used throughout history, from wood and stone, through to metals, alloys, plastics and silicon, describing their extraction and production as well as their dominant applications.<br />
                    The evolving productivities of material extraction, processing, synthesis, finishing and distribution, and the energy costs and environmental impact of rising material consumption are examined in detail. The book concludes with an outlook for the future, discussing the prospects for dematerialization and potential constrains on materials. This interdisciplinary text provides useful perspectives for readers with backgrounds including resource economics, environmental studies, energy analysis, mineral geology, industrial organization, manufacturing and material science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Making the Modern World : Materials and Dematerialization &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agricultural Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainable Agriculture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever? At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world. She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever?    </p>
<p>                    At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world.    </p>
<p>                    She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, robot weedkillers, lab-grown meat, 3D-printed meals, water networks run by supercomputers, cloud seeding and sensors that monitor the microclimate of individual plants. She meets the creative and controversial minds changing the face of modern food production, and tackles fears over genetic modification with hard facts.    </p>
<p>                    The Fate of Food is a fascinating look at the threats and opportunities that lie ahead as we struggle for food security.    </p>
<p>                    Faced with a perilous future, it gives us reason to hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rachel Carson: Silent Spring &#038; Other Environmental Writings &#8211; Rachel Carson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rachel-carson-silent-spring-other-environmental-writings-rachel-carson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rachel-carson-silent-spring-other-environmental-writings-rachel-carson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The book that sparked the modern environmental movement, with an unprecedented collection of letters, speeches, and other writings that reveal the extraordinary courage and vision of its author Library of America launches its Rachel Carson edition with this deluxe illustrated volume presenting one of the landmark books of the twentieth century together with rare letters, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rachel-carson-silent-spring-other-environmental-writings-rachel-carson-abridged/">Rachel Carson: Silent Spring &#038; Other Environmental Writings &#8211; Rachel Carson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The book that sparked the modern environmental movement, with an unprecedented collection of letters, speeches, and other writings that reveal the extraordinary courage and vision of its author     </p>
<p>                    Library of America launches its Rachel Carson edition with this deluxe illustrated volume presenting one of the landmark books of the twentieth century together with rare letters, speeches, and other writings that reveal the personal courage and passionate commitment of its author. A huge bestseller when published in September 1962, Silent Spring led not only to many of the laws and government agencies that protect our air, land, and water, but prompted a revolution in environmental consciousness. Now for the first time, in previously unpublished and newly collected letters to biochemists, ecologists, cancer specialists, ornithologists, and other experts, Carson&#8217;s groundbreaking expose of the unintended consequences of pesticide use comes together piece-by-piece, like a puzzle or detective story. She makes common cause with conservationists and other allies to build public awareness, hiding her private battle with cancer for fear it might distract from her message. And in the wake of her book&#8217;s astonishing impact, as she becomes the target of an organized campaign of disinformation by the chemical industry, Carson speaks out in defense of her findings while remaining a model of grace under pressure. Throughout the collection, Carson&#8217;s lifelong love of nature shines through. In writings both lyrical and intensely moving, she conveys her sense of wonder to her young nephew, dreams of conserving old-growth forest in Maine for posterity, and recounts her adventures and epiphanies as birdwatcher and beachcomber. A future companion volume will gather Carson&#8217;s sea trilogy: Under the Sea-Wind (1941), The Sea Around Us (1951), and The Edge of the Sea (1955).     </p>
<p>                    LIBRARY OF AMERICA is an independent nonprofit cultural organization founded in 1979 to preserve our nation&#8217;s literary heritage by publishing, and keeping permanently in print, America&#8217;s best and most significant writing. The Library of America series includes more than 300 volumes to date, authoritative editions that average 1,000 pages in length, feature cloth covers, sewn bindings, and ribbon markers, and are printed on premium acid-free paper that will last for centuries.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rachel-carson-silent-spring-other-environmental-writings-rachel-carson-abridged/">Rachel Carson: Silent Spring &#038; Other Environmental Writings &#8211; Rachel Carson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A new age &#8211; the novacene &#8211; has already begun.    </p>
<p>                    New beings will emerge from existing artificial intelligence systems. They will think 10,000 times faster than we do and will regard us as we now regard plants. The cruel, violent machine takeover imagined by sci-fi writers will not happen: these hyper-intelligent beings will be as dependent on the health of the planet as we are. They will need the planetary cooling system of Gaia to defend from the increasing heat of the sun. Gaia depends on organic life. We will be partners in this project. It is crucial, Lovelock argues, that the intelligence of Earth survives and prospers. We are at present the only beings capable of understanding the cosmos, but he speculates that the novacene could be the beginning of a process that will see intelligence suffusing the entire cosmos. At the age 100, Lovelock has produced the most compelling work of his life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Energy Myths and Realities : Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/energy-myths-and-realities-bringing-science-to-the-energy-policy-debate-vaclav-smil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/energy-myths-and-realities-bringing-science-to-the-energy-policy-debate-vaclav-smil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are many misconceptions about the future of global energy often presented as fact by the media, politicians, business leaders, activists, and even scientists-wasting time and money and hampering the development of progressive energy policies. Energy Myths and Realities: Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate debunks the most common fallacies to make way for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/energy-myths-and-realities-bringing-science-to-the-energy-policy-debate-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Energy Myths and Realities : Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many misconceptions about the future of global energy often presented as fact by the media, politicians, business leaders, activists, and even scientists-wasting time and money and hampering the development of progressive energy policies. Energy Myths and Realities: Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate debunks the most common fallacies to make way for a constructive, scientific approach to the global energy challenge.  When will the world run out of oil? Should nuclear energy be adopted on a larger scale? Are ethanol and wind power viable sources of energy for the future? Vaclav Smil advises the public to be wary of exaggerated claims and impossible promises. The global energy transition will be prolonged and expensive-and hinges on the development of an extensive new infrastructure. Established technologies and traditional energy sources are persistent and adaptable enough to see the world through that transition.  Energy Myths and Realities brings a scientific perspective to an issue often dominated by groundless assertions, unfounded claims, and uncritical thinking. Before we can create sound energy policies for the future, we must renounce the popular myths that cloud our judgment and impede true progress.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/energy-myths-and-realities-bringing-science-to-the-energy-policy-debate-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Energy Myths and Realities : Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Drawdown : The Most Comprehensive Plan Ever Proposed to Roll Back Global Warming &#8211; Paul Hawken (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8211; New York Times bestseller &#8211; The 100 most substantive solutions to reverse global warming, based on meticulous research by leading scientists and policymakers around the world &#8220;At this point in time, the Drawdown book is exactly what is needed; a credible, conservative solution-by-solution narrative that we can do it. Reading it is an effective [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/">Drawdown : The Most Comprehensive Plan Ever Proposed to Roll Back Global Warming &#8211; Paul Hawken (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8211; New York Times bestseller &#8211;     </p>
<p>                    The 100 most substantive solutions to reverse global warming, based on meticulous research by leading scientists and policymakers around the world     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;At this point in time, the Drawdown book is exactly what is needed; a credible, conservative solution-by-solution narrative that we can do it. Reading it is an effective inoculation against the widespread perception of doom that humanity cannot and will not solve the climate crisis. Reported by-effects include increased determination and a sense of grounded hope.&#8221; &#8211;Per Espen Stoknes, Author, What We Think About When We Try Not To Think About Global Warming     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There&#8217;s been no real way for ordinary people to get an understanding of what they can do and what impact it can have. There remains no single, comprehensive, reliable compendium of carbon-reduction solutions across sectors. At least until now. . . . The public is hungry for this kind of practical wisdom.&#8221; &#8211;David Roberts, Vox    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is the ideal environmental sciences textbook&#8211;only it is too interesting and inspiring to be called a textbook.&#8221; &#8211;Peter Kareiva, Director of the Institute of the Environment and Sustainability, UCLA     </p>
<p>                    In the face of widespread fear and apathy, an international coalition of researchers, professionals, and scientists have come together to offer a set of realistic and bold solutions to climate change. One hundred techniques and practices are described here&#8211;some are well known; some you may have never heard of. They range from clean energy to educating girls in lower-income countries to land use practices that pull carbon out of the air. The solutions exist, are economically viable, and communities throughout the world are currently enacting them with skill and determination. If deployed collectively on a global scale over the next thirty years, they represent a credible path forward, not just to slow the earth&#8217;s warming but to reach drawdown, that point in time when greenhouse gases in the atmosphere peak and begin to decline. These measures promise cascading benefits to human health, security, prosperity, and well-being&#8211;giving us every reason to see this planetary crisis as an opportunity to create a just and livable world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/">Drawdown : The Most Comprehensive Plan Ever Proposed to Roll Back Global Warming &#8211; Paul Hawken (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
