<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Local History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/local-history/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/local-history/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Local History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/local-history/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The true tale of the 1893 World&#8217;s Fair in Chicago and the cunning serial killer who used the magic and majesty of the fair to lure his victims to their death. &#8220;Relentlessly fuses history and entertainment to give this nonfiction book the dramatic effect of a novel &#8230;. It doesn&#8217;t [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/">The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The true tale of the 1893 World&#8217;s Fair in Chicago and the cunning serial killer who used the magic and majesty of the fair to lure his victims to their death.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Relentlessly fuses history and entertainment to give this nonfiction book the dramatic effect of a novel &#8230;. It doesn&#8217;t hurt that this truth is stranger than fiction.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                    Combining meticulous research with nail-biting storytelling, Erik Larson has crafted a narrative with all the wonder of newly discovered history and the thrills of the best fiction.    </p>
<p>                    Two men, each handsome and unusually adept at his chosen work, embodied an element of the great dynamic that characterized America&#8217;s rush toward the twentieth century. The architect was Daniel Hudson Burnham, the fair&#8217;s brilliant director of works and the builder of many of the country&#8217;s most important structures, including the Flatiron Building in New York and Union Station in Washington, D.C. The murderer was Henry H. Holmes, a young doctor who, in a malign parody of the White City, built his &#8220;World&#8217;s Fair Hotel&#8221; just west of the fairgrounds&#8211;a torture palace complete with dissection table, gas chamber, and 3,000-degree crematorium.     </p>
<p>                    Burnham overcame tremendous obstacles and tragedies as he organized the talents of Frederick Law Olmsted, Charles McKim, Louis Sullivan, and others to transform swampy Jackson Park into the White City, while Holmes used the attraction of the great fair and his own satanic charms to lure scores of young women to their deaths. What makes the story all the more chilling is that Holmes really lived, walking the grounds of that dream city by the lake.     </p>
<p>                    The Devil in the White City draws the reader into the enchantment of the Guilded Age, made all the more appealing by a supporting cast of real-life characters, including Buffalo Bill, Theodore Dreiser, Susan B. Anthony, Thomas Edison, Archduke Francis Ferdinand, and others. Erik Larson&#8217;s gifts as a storyteller are magnificently displayed in this rich narrative of the master builder, the killer, and the great fair that obsessed them both.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/">The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land *A New York Post Must-Read Book* *A Newsweek Best New Book* *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017* *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017* *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks* The Wall Street Journal: A devastating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land     </p>
<p>                    *A New York Post Must-Read Book*<br />
                    *A Newsweek Best New Book*<br />
                    *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017*<br />
                    *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017*<br />
                    *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks*     </p>
<p>                    The Wall Street Journal: A devastating portrait&#8230;For anyone wondering why swing-state America voted against the establishment in 2016, Mr. Alexander supplies plenty of answers.      </p>
<p>                    Laura Miller, Slate: This book hunts bigger game. Reads like an odd&#8211;and oddly satisfying&#8211;fusion of George Packer&#8217;s The Unwinding and one of Michael Lewis&#8217; real-life financial thrillers.     </p>
<p>                    The New Yorker: Does a remarkable job.     </p>
<p>                    Beth Macy, author of Factory Man: This book should be required reading for people trying to understand Trumpism, inequality, and the sad state of a needlessly wrecked rural America. I wish I had written it.      </p>
<p>                    In 1947, Forbes magazine declared Lancaster, Ohio the epitome of the all-American town. Today it is damaged, discouraged, and fighting for its future. In Glass House, journalist Brian Alexander uses the story of one town to show how seeds sown 35 years ago have sprouted to give us Trumpism, inequality, and an eroding national cohesion.     </p>
<p>                    The Anchor Hocking Glass Company, once the world&#8217;s largest maker of glass tableware, was the base on which Lancaster&#8217;s society was built. As Glass House unfolds, bankruptcy looms. With access to the company and its leaders, and Lancaster&#8217;s citizens, Alexander shows how financial engineering took hold in the 1980s, accelerated in the 21st Century, and wrecked the company. We follow CEO Sam Solomon, an African-American leading the nearly all-white town&#8217;s biggest private employer, as he tries to rescue the company from the New York private equity firm that hired him. Meanwhile, Alexander goes behind the scenes, entwined with the lives of residents as they wrestle with heroin, politics, high-interest lenders, low wage jobs, technology, and the new demands of American life: people like Brian Gossett, the fourth generation to work at Anchor Hocking; Joe Piccolo, first-time director of the annual music festival who discovers the town relies on him, and it, for salvation; Jason Roach, who police believed may have been Lancaster&#8217;s biggest drug dealer; and Eric Brown, a local football hero-turned-cop who comes to realize that he can never arrest Lancaster&#8217;s real problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
