<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Autobiography: Business &amp; Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/autobiography-business-industry/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/autobiography-business-industry/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Autobiography: Business &amp; Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/autobiography-business-industry/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</title>
		<link>/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Golf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>President Donald J. Trump lays out his professional and personal worldview in this classic work&#8211;a firsthand account of the rise of America&#8217;s foremost deal-maker. &#8220;I like thinking big. I always have. To me it&#8217;s very simple: If you&#8217;re going to be thinking anyway, you might as well think big.&#8221;&#8211;Donald J. Trump Here is Trump in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/">Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>President Donald J. Trump lays out his professional and personal worldview in this classic work&#8211;a firsthand account of the rise of America&#8217;s foremost deal-maker. </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I like thinking big. I always have. To me it&#8217;s very simple: If you&#8217;re going to be thinking anyway, you might as well think big.&#8221;&#8211;Donald J. Trump </p>
<p>                    Here is Trump in action&#8211;how he runs his organization and how he runs his life&#8211;as he meets the people he needs to meet, chats with family and friends, clashes with enemies, and challenges conventional thinking. But even a maverick plays by rules, and Trump has formulated time-tested guidelines for success. He isolates the common elements in his greatest accomplishments; he shatters myths; he names names, spells out the zeros, and fully reveals the deal-maker&#8217;s art. And throughout, Trump talks&#8211;really talks&#8211;about how he does it. Trump: The Art of the Deal is an unguarded look at the mind of a brilliant entrepreneur&#8211;the ultimate read for anyone interested in the man behind the spotlight. </p>
<p>                     Praise for Trump: The Art of the Deal </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Trump makes one believe for a moment in the American dream again.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times  </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Donald Trump is a deal maker. He is a deal maker the way lions are carnivores and water is wet.&#8221;&#8211;Chicago Tribune</p>
<p>                     &#8220;Fascinating . . . wholly absorbing . . . conveys Trump&#8217;s larger-than-life demeanor so vibrantly that the reader&#8217;s attention is instantly and fully claimed.&#8221;&#8211;Boston Herald</p>
<p>                     &#8220;A chatty, generous, chutzpa-filled autobiography.&#8221;&#8211;New York Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/">Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger</title>
		<link>/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019 _____________________________ The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES<br />
                    THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                    _____________________________</p>
<p>                    The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in the world and inspire the people who bring the magic to life. </p>
<p>                    Robert Iger became CEO of The Walt Disney Company in 2005, during a difficult time. Morale had deteriorated, competition was intense, and technology was changing faster than at any time in the company&#8217;s history. His vision came down to three clear ideas: Recommit to the concept that quality matters, embrace technology instead of fighting it, and think bigger-think global-and turn Disney into a stronger brand in international markets. </p>
<p>                    Fourteen years later, Disney is the largest, most respected media company in the world, counting Pixar, Marvel, Lucasfilm and 21st Century Fox among its properties. Its value is nearly five times what it was when Iger took over, and he is recognized as one of the most innovative and successful CEOs of our era.</p>
<p>                    In The Ride of a Lifetime, Robert Iger shares the lessons he&#8217;s learned while running Disney and leading its 200,000 employees, and he explores the principles that are necessary for true leadership, including:</p>
<p>                     Optimism. Even in the face of difficulty, an optimistic leader will find the path toward the best possible outcome and focus on that, rather than give in to pessimism and blaming.<br />
                     Courage. Leaders have to be willing to take risks and place big bets. Fear of failure destroys creativity.<br />
                     Decisiveness. All decisions, no matter how difficult, can be made on a timely basis. Indecisiveness is both wasteful and destructive to morale.<br />
                     Fairness. Treat people decently, with empathy, and be accessible to them. </p>
<p>                    This book is about the relentless curiosity that has driven Iger for forty-five years, since the day he started as the lowliest studio grunt at ABC. It&#8217;s also about thoughtfulness and respect, and a decency-over-dollars approach that has become the bedrock of every project and partnership Iger pursues, from a deep friendship with Steve Jobs in his final years to an abiding love of the Star Wars mythology.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;The ideas in this book strike me as universal&#8221; Iger writes. &#8220;Not just to the aspiring CEOs of the world, but to anyone wanting to feel less fearful, more confidently themselves, as they navigate their professional and even personal lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution. For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers. Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution.    For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers.       Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created.       They are using blogs, Twitter, and Facebook to share stories, and selecting their sources to create their own &#8216;front page&#8217;.   In this lively, biting critique, media commentator Tim Dunlop explores the rise of the audience, and how unprepared the mainstream media has been for this changing balance of power.       Drawing on his experiences as prominent political blogger, he argues that the future of meaningful journalism &#8211; the sort we need in order to be informed citizens &#8211; will increasingly rely on journalists and editors taking the audience into their confidence and working with them, rather than against them.   The New Front Page is a passionate plea on behalf of those tired of being talked down to by the fourth estate.       Perceptive and illuminating, it asks audiences and media to work together to hold the powerful to account, and to produce the sort of news and analysis that enriches public debate.   &#8216;A fascinating account of how digital technology has changed Australian media forever.&#8217;       Katharine Viner, editor-in-chief of The Guardian Australia   &#8216;An essential guide to understanding our insurgent new media.&#8217;       Lindsay Tanner, author of Sideshow   &#8216;Dunlop writes with humour, passion, and insight.&#8217;       Gay Alcorn, journalist</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Invisible Thread : The True Story of an 11-Year-Old Panhandler, a Busy Sales Executive, and an Unlikely Meeting with Destiny &#8211; Laura Schroff, Alex Tresniowski (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This inspirational New York Times bestseller chronicles the lifelong friendship between a busy sales executive and a disadvantaged young boy, and how both of their lives were changed by what began as one small gesture of kindness. Stopping was never part of the plan&#8230; She was a successful ad sales rep in Manhattan. He was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/">An Invisible Thread : The True Story of an 11-Year-Old Panhandler, a Busy Sales Executive, and an Unlikely Meeting with Destiny &#8211; Laura Schroff, Alex Tresniowski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This inspirational New York Times bestseller chronicles the lifelong friendship between a busy sales executive and a disadvantaged young boy, and how both of their lives were changed by what began as one small gesture of kindness.     </p>
<p>                    Stopping was never part of the plan&#8230;     </p>
<p>                     She was a successful ad sales rep in Manhattan. He was a homeless, eleven-year-old panhandler on the street. He asked for spare change; she kept walking. But then something stopped her in her tracks, and she went back. And she continued to go back, again and again. They met up nearly every week for years and built an unexpected, life-changing friendship that has today spanned almost three decades.     </p>
<p>                     Whatever made me notice him on that street corner so many years ago is clearly something that cannot be extinguished, no matter how relentless the forces aligned against it. Some may call it spirit. Some may call it heart. It drew me to him, as if we were bound by some invisible, unbreakable thread. And whatever it is, it binds us still.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/">An Invisible Thread : The True Story of an 11-Year-Old Panhandler, a Busy Sales Executive, and an Unlikely Meeting with Destiny &#8211; Laura Schroff, Alex Tresniowski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uncanny Valley : Seduction and Disillusionment in San Francisco&#8217;s Startup Scene &#8211; Anna Wiener (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Joan Didion at a startup&#8217; Rebecca Solnit &#8216;Impossibly pleasurable&#8217; Jia Tolentino &#8216;This is essential reading&#8217; Stylist At twenty-five years old, Anna Wiener was beginning to tire of her assistant job in New York publishing. There was no room to grow, and the voyeuristic thrill of answering someone else&#8217;s phone had worn thin. Within a year [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/">Uncanny Valley : Seduction and Disillusionment in San Francisco&#8217;s Startup Scene &#8211; Anna Wiener (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joan Didion at a startup&#8217; Rebecca Solnit    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Impossibly pleasurable&#8217; Jia Tolentino    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;This is essential reading&#8217; Stylist    </p>
<p>                              At twenty-five years old, Anna Wiener was beginning to tire of her assistant job in New York publishing. There was no room to grow, and the voyeuristic thrill of answering someone else&#8217;s phone had worn thin.    </p>
<p>                              Within a year she had moved to Silicon Valley to take up a job at a data analytics startup in San Francisco. Leaving her business casual skirts and shirts in the wardrobe, she began working in company-branded T-shirts. She had a healthy income for the first time in her life. She felt like part of the future.    </p>
<p>                              But a tide was beginning to turn. People were speaking of tech startups as surveillance companies. Out of sixty employees, only eight of her colleagues were women. Casual sexism was rife. Sexual harassment cases were proliferating. And soon, like everyone else, she was addicted to the internet, refreshing the news, refreshing social media, scrolling and scrolling and scrolling. Slowly, she began to realise that her blind faith in ambitious, arrogant young men from America&#8217;s soft suburbs wasn&#8217;t just her own personal pathology. It had become a global affliction.    </p>
<p>                              Uncanny Valley is a coming of age story set against the backdrop of our generation&#8217;s very own gold rush. It&#8217;s a story about the tension between old and new, between art and tech, between the quest for money and the quest for meaning &#8211; about how our world is changing forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/">Uncanny Valley : Seduction and Disillusionment in San Francisco&#8217;s Startup Scene &#8211; Anna Wiener (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big : Kind of the Story of My Life &#8211; Scott Adams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blasting clichéd career advice, the contrarian pundit and creator of Dilbert recounts the humorous ups and downs of his career, revealing the outsized role of luck in our lives and how best to play the system. Scott Adams has likely failed at more things than anyone you&#8217;ve ever met or anyone you&#8217;ve even heard of. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/">How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big : Kind of the Story of My Life &#8211; Scott Adams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blasting clichéd career advice, the contrarian pundit and creator of Dilbert recounts the humorous ups and downs of his career, revealing the outsized role of luck in our lives and how best to play the system.      </p>
<p>                     Scott Adams has likely failed at more things than anyone you&#8217;ve ever met or anyone you&#8217;ve even heard of. So how did he go from hapless office worker and serial failure to the creator of Dilbert, one of the world&#8217;s most famous syndicated comic strips, in just a few years? In How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big, Adams shares the game plan he&#8217;s followed since he was a teen: invite failure in, embrace it, then pick its pocket.     </p>
<p>                     No career guide can offer advice that works for everyone. As Adams explains, your best bet is to study the ways of others who made it big and try to glean some tricks and strategies that make sense for you. Adams pulls back the covers on his own unusual life and shares how he turned one failure after another&#8211;including his corporate career, his inventions, his investments, and his two restaurants&#8211;into something good and lasting. There&#8217;s a lot to learn from his personal story, and a lot of entertainment along the way. Adams discovered some unlikely truths that helped to propel him forward. For instance:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Goals are for losers. Systems are for winners.<br />
                     &#8211; &#8220;Passion&#8221; is bull. What you need is personal energy.<br />
                     &#8211; A combination of mediocre skills can make you surprisingly valuable.<br />
                     &#8211; You can manage your odds in a way that makes you look lucky to others.     </p>
<p>                     Adams hopes you can laugh at his failures while discovering some unique and helpful ideas on your own path to personal victory. As he writes: &#8220;This is a story of one person&#8217;s unlikely success within the context of scores of embarrassing failures. Was my eventual success primarily a result of talent, luck, hard work, or an accidental just-right balance of each? All I know for sure is that I pursued a conscious strategy of managing my opportunities in a way that would make it easier for luck to find me.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/">How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big : Kind of the Story of My Life &#8211; Scott Adams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Virgin Way : How to Listen, Learn, Laugh and Lead &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-virgin-way-how-to-listen-learn-laugh-and-lead-sir-richard-branson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-virgin-way-how-to-listen-learn-laugh-and-lead-sir-richard-branson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In September 2012, a YOUGOV poll conducted in Britain found that the person British workers would most like as their manager was Sir Richard Branson. With over 40 years in business, Richard Branson is an inspiring pioneer of humanitarian projects and an iconic business leader. In The Virgin Way: How to Listen, Learn, Laugh and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-virgin-way-how-to-listen-learn-laugh-and-lead-sir-richard-branson-abridged/">The Virgin Way : How to Listen, Learn, Laugh and Lead &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In September 2012, a YOUGOV poll conducted in Britain found that the person British workers would most like as their manager was Sir Richard Branson.    </p>
<p>                    With over 40 years in business, Richard Branson is an inspiring pioneer of humanitarian projects and an iconic business leader. In The Virgin Way: How to Listen, Learn, Laugh and Lead, Richard shares and distils his secrets of leadership and success. Featuring anecdotes from his own business dealings, as well as his observations of many others who have inspired him &#8211; from politicians, business leaders, explorers, scientists and philanthropists &#8211; Richard reflects on the qualities he feels are essential for success in today&#8217;s world.    </p>
<p>                    This is not a conventional book on leadership. There are no rules &#8211; but rather the secrets of leadership that he has learned along the way from his days at Virgin Records, to his recent work with The Elders. Whether you&#8217;re at the beginning of your career, or head of a Fortune 500 company &#8211; this is your guide to being your own CEO (Chief Enabling Officer) and becoming a true leader &#8211; not just a boss.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-virgin-way-how-to-listen-learn-laugh-and-lead-sir-richard-branson-abridged/">The Virgin Way : How to Listen, Learn, Laugh and Lead &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let My People Go Surfing : The Education of a Reluctant Businessman &#8211; Including 10 More Years of Business as Usual &#8211; Yvon Chouinard, Introduction by Naomi Klein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/let-my-people-go-surfing-the-education-of-a-reluctant-businessman-including-10-more-years-of-business-as-usual-yvon-chouinard-introduction-by-naomi-klein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-my-people-go-surfing-the-education-of-a-reluctant-businessman-including-10-more-years-of-business-as-usual-yvon-chouinard-introduction-by-naomi-klein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wonderful . . . a moving autobiography, the story of a unique business, and a detailed blueprint for hope. &#8211;Jared Diamond, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Guns, Germs, and Steel In this newly revised 10th anniversary edition, Yvon Chouinard&#8211;legendary climber, businessman, environmentalist, and founder of Patagonia, Inc.&#8211;shares the persistence and courage that have gone into being [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-my-people-go-surfing-the-education-of-a-reluctant-businessman-including-10-more-years-of-business-as-usual-yvon-chouinard-introduction-by-naomi-klein-abridged/">Let My People Go Surfing : The Education of a Reluctant Businessman &#8211; Including 10 More Years of Business as Usual &#8211; Yvon Chouinard, Introduction by Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wonderful . . . a moving autobiography, the story of a unique business, and a detailed blueprint for hope. &#8211;Jared Diamond, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Guns, Germs, and Steel     </p>
<p>                    In this newly revised 10th anniversary edition, Yvon Chouinard&#8211;legendary climber, businessman, environmentalist, and founder of Patagonia, Inc.&#8211;shares the persistence and courage that have gone into being head of one of the most respected and environmentally responsible companies on earth.     </p>
<p>                     From his youth as the son of a French Canadian handyman to the thrilling, ambitious climbing expeditions that inspired his innovative designs for the sport&#8217;s equipment, Let My People Go Surfing is the story of a man who brought doing good and having grand adventures into the heart of his business life-a book that will deeply affect entrepreneurs and outdoor enthusiasts alike.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-my-people-go-surfing-the-education-of-a-reluctant-businessman-including-10-more-years-of-business-as-usual-yvon-chouinard-introduction-by-naomi-klein-abridged/">Let My People Go Surfing : The Education of a Reluctant Businessman &#8211; Including 10 More Years of Business as Usual &#8211; Yvon Chouinard, Introduction by Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding My Virginity : The New Autobiography &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>PAPERBACK EDITION FULLY UPDATED WITH TWO NEW CHAPTERS After creating 12 different billion-dollar businesses and breaking dozens of world records, wouldn&#8217;t you think you&#8217;d done it all? Not Sir Richard Branson. Having brought the Virgin brand to all corners of the globe, he&#8217;s now reaching out to the stars as he prepares to launch commercial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/">Finding My Virginity : The New Autobiography &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PAPERBACK EDITION FULLY UPDATED WITH TWO NEW CHAPTERS    </p>
<p>                    After creating 12 different billion-dollar businesses and breaking dozens of world records, wouldn&#8217;t you think you&#8217;d done it all?    </p>
<p>                    Not Sir Richard Branson. Having brought the Virgin brand to all corners of the globe, he&#8217;s now reaching out to the stars as he prepares to launch commercial space travel with Virgin Galactic.    </p>
<p>                    In this non-stop memoir, Richard takes you inside his whirlwind life: from reinventing his companies in the midst of the financial crisis and devastating personal losses, to tackling the planet&#8217;s biggest challenges, to the joys of becoming a &#8216;grand-dude&#8217; at 64.Discover the irrepressible spirit, ingenious vision and relentless drive that has made Richard the ultimate entrepreneur.    </p>
<p>                    The iconoclastic Virgin founder is still changing the world. Next comes outer space.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/">Finding My Virginity : The New Autobiography &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW* In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement. &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW*    </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New York Magazine    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compellingly motivational read&#8217; The Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book you need in your life&#8217; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                    *Winner of the 2014 Goodreads Choice Award for Best Business Book*    </p>
<p>                    In the space of ten years, Sophia Amoruso has gone from high-school dropout to founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal, one of the fastest-growing retailers in the world.     </p>
<p>                    Sophia&#8217;s never been a typical executive, or a typical anything, and she&#8217;s written #GIRLBOSS for other girls like her: outsiders (and insiders) seeking a unique path to success.    </p>
<p>                    Filled with brazen wake-up calls, cunning and frank observations, and behind-the-scenes stories from Nasty Gal&#8217;s meteoric rise, #GIRLBOSS covers a lot of ground. It proves that success doesn&#8217;t come from where you went to college or how popular you were in school. Success is about trusting your instincts and following your gut, knowing which rules to follow and which to break.    </p>
<p>                    Inspiring, motivating and empowering, #GIRLBOSS will give you the kick up the ass you need to reach your potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave, Not Perfect : Fear Less, Fail More and Live Bolder &#8211; Reshma Saujani (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brave-not-perfect-fear-less-fail-more-and-live-bolder-reshma-saujani-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-not-perfect-fear-less-fail-more-and-live-bolder-reshma-saujani-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The new Lean In, from the multi-award-winning Founder and CEO of national non-profit Girls Who Code and New York Times bestselling author Reshma Saujani. &#8216;We are raising our boys to be brave, but our girls to be perfect. And this is holding us back.&#8217; Imagine if you lived without the fear of failure, without the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-not-perfect-fear-less-fail-more-and-live-bolder-reshma-saujani-abridged/">Brave, Not Perfect : Fear Less, Fail More and Live Bolder &#8211; Reshma Saujani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The new Lean In, from the multi-award-winning Founder and CEO of national non-profit Girls Who Code and New York Times bestselling author Reshma Saujani.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;We are raising our boys to be brave, but our girls to be perfect. And this is holding us back.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              Imagine if you lived without the fear of failure, without the fear of not measuring up. If you no longer felt the need to stifle your thoughts and swallow what you really want to say in order to please and appease others. If you could stop berating yourself mercilessly for human mistakes, let go of the guilt and the strangling pressure to be perfect, and just breathe. What if, in every decision you faced, you made the brave choice or took the bolder path. Would you be happier? Would you impact the world in the ways you dream you can?    </p>
<p>                                I believe the answer to both is yes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-not-perfect-fear-less-fail-more-and-live-bolder-reshma-saujani-abridged/">Brave, Not Perfect : Fear Less, Fail More and Live Bolder &#8211; Reshma Saujani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Entreleadership : 20 Years of Practical Business Wisdom from the Trenches &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/entreleadership-20-years-of-practical-business-wisdom-from-the-trenches-dave-ramsey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/entreleadership-20-years-of-practical-business-wisdom-from-the-trenches-dave-ramsey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of The Total Money Makeover and radio and podcast host Dave Ramsey comes an informative guide based on how he grew a successful, multimillion dollar company from a card table in his living room. Your company is only as strong as your leaders. These are the men and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/entreleadership-20-years-of-practical-business-wisdom-from-the-trenches-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Entreleadership : 20 Years of Practical Business Wisdom from the Trenches &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of The Total Money Makeover and radio and podcast host Dave Ramsey comes an informative guide based on how he grew a successful, multimillion dollar company from a card table in his living room.     </p>
<p>                    Your company is only as strong as your leaders. These are the men and women doing battle daily beneath the banner that is your brand. Are they courageous or indecisive? Are they serving a motivated team or managing employees? Are they valued?     </p>
<p>                    Your team will never grow beyond you, so here&#8217;s another question to consider&#8211;are you growing? Whether you&#8217;re sitting at the CEO&#8217;s desk, the middle manager&#8217;s cubicle, or a card table in your living-room-based start-up, EntreLeadership provides the practical, step-by-step guidance to grow your business where you want it to go. Dave Ramsey opens up his championship playbook for business to show you how to:     </p>
<p>                    -Inspire your team to take ownership and love what they do<br />
                     -Unify your team and get rid of all gossip<br />
                     -Handle money to set your business up for success<br />
                     -Reach every goal you set<br />
                     -And much, much more!     </p>
<p>                    EntreLeadership is a one-stop guide filled with accessible advice for businesses and leaders to ensure success even through the toughest of times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/entreleadership-20-years-of-practical-business-wisdom-from-the-trenches-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Entreleadership : 20 Years of Practical Business Wisdom from the Trenches &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019 _____________________________ The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES<br />
                    THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                    _____________________________    </p>
<p>                    The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in the world and inspire the people who bring the magic to life.     </p>
<p>                    Robert Iger became CEO of The Walt Disney Company in 2005, during a difficult time. Morale had deteriorated, competition was intense, and technology was changing faster than at any time in the company&#8217;s history. His vision came down to three clear ideas: Recommit to the concept that quality matters, embrace technology instead of fighting it, and think bigger-think global-and turn Disney into a stronger brand in international markets.     </p>
<p>                    Fourteen years later, Disney is the largest, most respected media company in the world, counting Pixar, Marvel, Lucasfilm and 21st Century Fox among its properties. Its value is nearly five times what it was when Iger took over, and he is recognized as one of the most innovative and successful CEOs of our era.    </p>
<p>                    In The Ride of a Lifetime, Robert Iger shares the lessons he&#8217;s learned while running Disney and leading its 200,000 employees, and he explores the principles that are necessary for true leadership, including:    </p>
<p>                     Optimism. Even in the face of difficulty, an optimistic leader will find the path toward the best possible outcome and focus on that, rather than give in to pessimism and blaming.<br />
                     Courage. Leaders have to be willing to take risks and place big bets. Fear of failure destroys creativity.<br />
                     Decisiveness. All decisions, no matter how difficult, can be made on a timely basis. Indecisiveness is both wasteful and destructive to morale.<br />
                     Fairness. Treat people decently, with empathy, and be accessible to them.     </p>
<p>                    This book is about the relentless curiosity that has driven Iger for forty-five years, since the day he started as the lowliest studio grunt at ABC. It&#8217;s also about thoughtfulness and respect, and a decency-over-dollars approach that has become the bedrock of every project and partnership Iger pursues, from a deep friendship with Steve Jobs in his final years to an abiding love of the Star Wars mythology.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The ideas in this book strike me as universal&#8221; Iger writes. &#8220;Not just to the aspiring CEOs of the world, but to anyone wanting to feel less fearful, more confidently themselves, as they navigate their professional and even personal lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
