<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ethical Issues &amp; Debates Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/ethical-issues-debates/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/ethical-issues-debates/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:56:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Ethical Issues &amp; Debates Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/ethical-issues-debates/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Why Are We Yelling? : The Art of Productive Disagreement &#8211; Buster Benson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-are-we-yelling-the-art-of-productive-disagreement-buster-benson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues & Debates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-are-we-yelling-the-art-of-productive-disagreement-buster-benson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is a life-changing book. Read it three times and then give a copy to anyone you care about. It will make things better&#8217; &#8211; Seth Godin, author of This is Marketing &#8216;All you need is Buster Benson. His methods are instantly actionable, [and] his writing is funny and relatable&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, author of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-are-we-yelling-the-art-of-productive-disagreement-buster-benson-abridged/">Why Are We Yelling? : The Art of Productive Disagreement &#8211; Buster Benson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a life-changing book. Read it three times and then give a copy to anyone you care about. It will make things better&#8217; &#8211; Seth Godin, author of This is Marketing    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;All you need is Buster Benson. His methods are instantly actionable, [and] his writing is funny and relatable&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    Why Are We Yelling is Buster Benson&#8217;s essential guide to having more honest and constructive arguments.    </p>
<p>                    The way we argue is broken. Whether it&#8217;s about Brexit, the existence of ghosts, the best burger in the city or who&#8217;s allowed to sit in your favourite chair, we end up digging our heels in and yelling at one another or choosing to avoid heated topics entirely. There has to be a better way.    </p>
<p>                    Buster Benson, a Silicon Valley entrepreneur with two decades of experience facilitating hard conversations at some of the biggest tech companies in the world, recommends eight things to try in order to make disagreements more productive. By applying these eight new habits, we can flip frustrating, unproductive disagreements into ones that bear fruit and bring people closer together.    </p>
<p>                    In this book you&#8217;ll master practical skills to make your disagreements more productive by:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Understanding four ways of disagreeing that are more valuable than simply &#8216;winning&#8217; the argument<br />
                    &#8211; Identifying the kind of argument you&#8217;re having so you know how best to negotiate it<br />
                    &#8211; Articulating the best possible version of your opponent&#8217;s argument before attacking it    </p>
<p>                    With this toolkit we can explore more possibilities and perspectives in the world, simply because we&#8217;ll no longer be afraid to wade into scary topics of conversation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-are-we-yelling-the-art-of-productive-disagreement-buster-benson-abridged/">Why Are We Yelling? : The Art of Productive Disagreement &#8211; Buster Benson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger : Heretics, Activists, and One Scholar&#8217;s Search for Justice &#8211; Alice Dreger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues & Debates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Smart, delightful . . . a splendidly entertaining education in ethics, activism, and science.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review (Editor&#8217;s Choice) An impassioned defense of intellectual freedom and a clarion call to intellectual responsibility, Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger is one American&#8217;s eye-opening story of life in the trenches of scientific controversy. For two decades, historian [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/">Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger : Heretics, Activists, and One Scholar&#8217;s Search for Justice &#8211; Alice Dreger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Smart, delightful . . . a splendidly entertaining education in ethics, activism, and science.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review (Editor&#8217;s Choice)    </p>
<p>                     An impassioned defense of intellectual freedom and a clarion call to intellectual responsibility, Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger is one American&#8217;s eye-opening story of life in the trenches of scientific controversy. For two decades, historian Alice Dreger has led a life of extraordinary engagement, combining activist service to victims of unethical medical research with defense of scientists whose work has outraged identity politics activists. With spirit and wit, Dreger offers in Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger an unforgettable vision of the importance of rigorous truth seeking in today&#8217;s America, where both the free press and free scholarly inquiry struggle under dire economic and political threats.    </p>
<p>                     This illuminating chronicle begins with Dreger&#8217;s own research into the treatment of people born intersex (once called hermaphrodites). Realization of the shocking surgical and ethical abuses conducted in the name of &#8220;normalizing&#8221; intersex children&#8217;s gender identities moved Dreger to become an internationally recognized patient rights activist. But even as the intersex rights movement succeeded, Dreger began to realize how some fellow progressive activists were employing lies and personal attacks to silence scientists whose data revealed uncomfortable truths about humans. In researching one such case, Dreger suddenly became the target of just these kinds of attacks.    </p>
<p>                     Troubled, she decided to try to understand more-to travel the country to ferret out the truth behind various controversies, to obtain a global view of the nature and costs of these battles. Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger describes Dreger&#8217;s long and harrowing journeys between the two camps for which she felt equal empathy: social justice activists determined to win and researchers determined to put hard truths before comfort. Ultimately what emerges is a lesson about the intertwining of justice and of truth-and a lesson of the importance of responsible scholars and journalists to our fragile democracy.    </p>
<p>                     Praise for Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger:<br />
                     &#8220;An engrossing volume that is sure to undo any lingering notions that academic debate is the province of empiricists who pledge allegiance to the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth . . . Dreger&#8217;s clear and well-paced prose makes for compelling . . . reading.&#8221; -The Chicago Tribune</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/">Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger : Heretics, Activists, and One Scholar&#8217;s Search for Justice &#8211; Alice Dreger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
