<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Self, Ego, Identity, Personality Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/self-ego-identity-personality/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/self-ego-identity-personality/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Self, Ego, Identity, Personality Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/self-ego-identity-personality/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</title>
		<link>/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neuro Linguistic Programming (NLP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dark Psychology Series Complete 3 Book Compilation This book includes: How to Analyze People: Dark Psychology &#8211; Dark Secrets to Analyze and Influence Anyone Using Body Language, Human Psychology, Subliminal Persuasion and NLP Persuasion: Dark Psychology &#8211; How People are Influencing You to Do What They Want Using Manipulation, NLP, and Subliminal Persuasion Dark Psychology: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/">How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dark Psychology Series Complete 3 Book Compilation    </p>
<p>                    This book includes: How to Analyze People: Dark Psychology &#8211; Dark Secrets to Analyze and Influence Anyone Using Body Language, Human Psychology, Subliminal Persuasion and NLP<br />
                    Persuasion: Dark Psychology &#8211; How People are Influencing You to Do What They Want Using Manipulation, NLP, and Subliminal Persuasion<br />
                    Dark Psychology: The Practical Uses and Best Defenses of Psychological Warfare in Everyday Life &#8211; How to Detect and Defend Against Manipulation, Deception, Dark Persuasion, and Covert NLP    </p>
<p>                    If you&#8217;re tired of being manipulated, whether you&#8217;re being tricked into doing things you don&#8217;t want, or others are taking advantage of you, there are ways to stop manipulation and persuasion in its tracks.    </p>
<p>                    In this book, you will get a groundwork for what different types of persuasion and manipulation might be. You will learn the process of how people use these tactics to their advantage.    </p>
<p>                    The first half of the book will discuss what makes up an individual. The way you use your body, the words that you choose to speak, and the way that they were raised all play important roles in what makes an individual. You will also have to look at your own self and pick out all of these unique things that make them different from everyone else as well.    </p>
<p>                    There are psychological studies that back up the idea of certain methods of persuasion, such as NLP tactics, that prove that anyone has the power to persuade others.    </p>
<p>                    Inside this book, you will discover: WhatDark Psychologyis and how it&#8217;s used to control people.How to plant different emotional seeds that will grow in people&#8217;s mindsHow to use words to steer people however you likeHow to identify and work with different types of people like contrarians and control freaks.The jobs/roles in society that you are most likely to be manipulated inThe language of the subconsciousThedirty trickslovers and family members use to control their victims.How to analyze different personality typesMind-blowing tricks for manipulationMagic words for influencing othersA step-by-step guide on influencing others with NLPForbidden secrets of dark psychologyCase studies showcasing how much damage a master manipulator can do.And much more&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Although there are many differences among people, there are also many things that make us the same. In order to better analyze and understand those around you, it&#8217;s crucial to find those things that we do connect on, and the things that bring us together rather than the things that tear us apart.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s important when reading this book to remember that not all manipulation is bad. In the first book of this boxset, it is emphasized that those who might be manipulating you might also be taking advantage of you.    </p>
<p>                    When reading this book, you should remember that manipulation is a tool, much like a hammer. You can either use that hammer to destroy everything around you, or you could alternatively use that hammer to create something organic, something new.    </p>
<p>                    This book will take you first through the discovery and analyzation of those around you, and then it will provide different ways that you can persuade them.    </p>
<p>                    The only thing you need before starting this book is the willingness to change. You might have to confront some of your darkest issues, and you might have to put yourself through future scenarios that elicit a feeling of discomfort. In the end, however, you&#8217;ll find yourself to be much more self-aware and independent.Click &#8220;Add to Cart&#8221; nowand learn how to defend against dark psychology and keep your mind and life in control.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/">How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adaptability : The Art of Winning in an Age of Uncertainty &#8211; Mike Grady, Max McKeown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adaptability-the-art-of-winning-in-an-age-of-uncertainty-mike-grady-max-mckeown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adaptability-the-art-of-winning-in-an-age-of-uncertainty-mike-grady-max-mckeown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Adaptability is the key human trait. The ability to adapt faster and smarter than the situation is what makes the powerful difference between adapting to cope and adapting to win. Our history is a story of adaptation and change; and in the times of brutal competition and economic uncertainty, it has never been more important [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptability-the-art-of-winning-in-an-age-of-uncertainty-mike-grady-max-mckeown-abridged/">Adaptability : The Art of Winning in an Age of Uncertainty &#8211; Mike Grady, Max McKeown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Adaptability is the key human trait. The ability to adapt faster and smarter than the situation is what makes the powerful difference between adapting to cope and adapting to win. Our history is a story of adaptation and change; and in the times of brutal competition and economic uncertainty, it has never been more important to understand how to adapt successfully. Using a series of powerful rules, Max Mckeown explores how to increase the adaptability of you and your organization to create winning positions. Fascinating real-world examples from business, government, military and sport bring the rules of Adaptability to life&#8211;from the world&#8217;s most innovative corporations, to street-level creativity emerging from the slums. Adaptability is a powerful, practical and inspirational guide to success in uncertain times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptability-the-art-of-winning-in-an-age-of-uncertainty-mike-grady-max-mckeown-abridged/">Adaptability : The Art of Winning in an Age of Uncertainty &#8211; Mike Grady, Max McKeown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do What You Are (Revised) : Discover the Perfect Career for You Through the Secrets of Personality Type &#8211; Barbara Barron-Tieger, Kelly Tieger, Paul D. Tieger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-what-you-are-revised-discover-the-perfect-career-for-you-through-the-secrets-of-personality-type-barbara-barron-tieger-kelly-tieger-paul-d-tieger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-what-you-are-revised-discover-the-perfect-career-for-you-through-the-secrets-of-personality-type-barbara-barron-tieger-kelly-tieger-paul-d-tieger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do What You Are &#8212; the bestselling classic that has helped more than a million people find truly satisfying work &#8212; is now updated for the modern workforce. With the global economy&#8217;s ups and downs, the advent of astonishing new technology, the migration to online work and study, and the ascendancy of mobile communication, so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-what-you-are-revised-discover-the-perfect-career-for-you-through-the-secrets-of-personality-type-barbara-barron-tieger-kelly-tieger-paul-d-tieger-abridged/">Do What You Are (Revised) : Discover the Perfect Career for You Through the Secrets of Personality Type &#8211; Barbara Barron-Tieger, Kelly Tieger, Paul D. Tieger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do What You Are &#8212; the bestselling classic that has helped more than a million people find truly satisfying work &#8212; is now updated for the modern workforce. With the global economy&#8217;s ups and downs, the advent of astonishing new technology, the migration to online work and study, and the ascendancy of mobile communication, so much has changed in the American workplace since this book&#8217;s fifth edition was published in 2014.    </p>
<p>                    What hasn&#8217;t changed is the power of Personality Type to help people achieve job satisfaction. This updated edition, featuring 30% new material, is especially useful for millennials and for baby boomers experiencing midlife career switches, and even those looking for fulfillment in retirement. The book leads readers step-by-step through the process of determining and verifying Personality Type. Then it identifies occupations that are popular with each Type, provides helpful case studies, and offers a rundown of each Type&#8217;s work-related strengths and weaknesses.    </p>
<p>                    Focusing on each Type&#8217;s strengths, Do What You Are uses workbook exercises to help you customize your job search, get the most out of your current career, obtain leadership positions, and ensure that you achieve the best results in the shortest period of time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-what-you-are-revised-discover-the-perfect-career-for-you-through-the-secrets-of-personality-type-barbara-barron-tieger-kelly-tieger-paul-d-tieger-abridged/">Do What You Are (Revised) : Discover the Perfect Career for You Through the Secrets of Personality Type &#8211; Barbara Barron-Tieger, Kelly Tieger, Paul D. Tieger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Road Back to You : An Enneagram Journey to Self-Discovery &#8211; Ian Morgan Cron, Suzanne Stabile (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over 750,000 Copies Sold Worldwide! Foreword INDIES Book of the Year Awards Finalist Missio Alliance Essential Reading List Ignorance is bliss-except in self-awareness. What you don&#8217;t know about yourself can hurt you and your relationships-and even keep you in the shallows with God. Do you want help figuring out who you are and why you&#8217;re [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/">The Road Back to You : An Enneagram Journey to Self-Discovery &#8211; Ian Morgan Cron, Suzanne Stabile (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over 750,000 Copies Sold Worldwide!    </p>
<p>                                Foreword INDIES Book of the Year Awards Finalist    </p>
<p>                    Missio Alliance Essential Reading List<br />
                             Ignorance is bliss-except in self-awareness.<br />
                    What you don&#8217;t know about yourself can hurt you and your relationships-and even keep you in the shallows with God. Do you want help figuring out who you are and why you&#8217;re stuck in the same ruts?<br />
                    The Enneagram is an ancient personality typing system with an uncanny accuracy in describing how human beings are wired, both positively and negatively. In The Road Back to You Ian Morgan Cron and Suzanne Stabile forge a unique approach-a practical, comprehensive way of accessing Enneagram wisdom and exploring its connections with Christian spirituality for a deeper knowledge of ourselves, compassion for others, and love for God.<br />
                    Witty and filled with stories, this book allows you to peek inside each of the nine Enneagram types, keeping you turning the pages long after you have read the chapter about your own number. Not only will you learn more about yourself, but you will also start to see the world through other people&#8217;s eyes, understanding how and why people think, feel, and act the way they do.<br />
                    Beginning with changes you can start making today, the wisdom of the Enneagram can help take you further along into who you really are-leading you into places of spiritual discovery you would never have found on your own, and paving the way to the wiser, more compassionate person you want to become.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-back-to-you-an-enneagram-journey-to-self-discovery-ian-morgan-cron-suzanne-stabile-abridged/">The Road Back to You : An Enneagram Journey to Self-Discovery &#8211; Ian Morgan Cron, Suzanne Stabile (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Outer Order Inner Calm : declutter and organize to make more room for happiness &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/outer-order-inner-calm-declutter-and-organize-to-make-more-room-for-happiness-gretchen-rubin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/outer-order-inner-calm-declutter-and-organize-to-make-more-room-for-happiness-gretchen-rubin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;MOVE OVER, MARIE KONDO&#8217; Washington Post &#8216;EXCELLENT&#8217; Telegraph &#8216;WISHING I HAD A RUBIN TO HELP ME MAKE SENSE OF MY BELONGINGS&#8217; Red &#8216;DECLUTTER YOUR WAY TO HAPPINESS&#8217; Good Housekeeping In the context of a happy life, a messy desk or a crowded wardrobe is a trivial problem &#8211; yet Gretchen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outer-order-inner-calm-declutter-and-organize-to-make-more-room-for-happiness-gretchen-rubin-abridged/">Outer Order Inner Calm : declutter and organize to make more room for happiness &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;MOVE OVER, MARIE KONDO&#8217; Washington Post<br />
                    &#8216;EXCELLENT&#8217; Telegraph<br />
                    &#8216;WISHING I HAD A RUBIN TO HELP ME MAKE SENSE OF MY BELONGINGS&#8217; Red<br />
                    &#8216;DECLUTTER YOUR WAY TO HAPPINESS&#8217; Good Housekeeping    </p>
<p>                    In the context of a happy life, a messy desk or a crowded wardrobe is a trivial problem &#8211; yet Gretchen Rubin found that getting control of our stuff makes us feel more in control of our lives.    </p>
<p>                    Ask yourself: DO I NEED IT? DO I LOVE IT? DO I USE IT?    </p>
<p>                    With 150 concrete clutter-clearing ideas, insights, strategies, and sometimes surprising tips, Gretchen tackles the key challenges of creating outer order by explaining how to &#8216;make choices&#8217;, &#8216;create order&#8217;, &#8216;know yourself&#8217;, &#8216;cultivate useful habits&#8217; and, of course, how to &#8216;add beauty&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    At home, at work, and in life, when we get our possessions under control, we can create a more serene environment. With a sense of fun, and a clear idea of what&#8217;s realistic for most people, Gretchen suggests dozens of manageable steps to help us achieve the lives we yearn for.    </p>
<p>                    ALSO BY GRETCHEN RUBIN    </p>
<p>                    The Four Tendencies: the indispensable personality profiles that reveal how to make your life better    </p>
<p>                    AND    </p>
<p>                    Better Than Before: learn how to make good habits and break bad ones, for good    </p>
<p>                    AND    </p>
<p>                    Happier At Home: a year-long experiment in making the everyday extraordinary</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outer-order-inner-calm-declutter-and-organize-to-make-more-room-for-happiness-gretchen-rubin-abridged/">Outer Order Inner Calm : declutter and organize to make more room for happiness &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I&#8217;m Ok, You&#8217;re Ok : A practical guide to Transactional Analysis &#8211; Thomas A. Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/im-ok-youre-ok-a-practical-guide-to-transactional-analysis-thomas-a-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychoanalytical Theory (Freudian Psychology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/im-ok-youre-ok-a-practical-guide-to-transactional-analysis-thomas-a-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This practical guide to Transactional Analysis is a unique approach to your problems. Hundreds of thousands of people have found this phenomenal breakthrough in psychotherapy a turning point in their lives. In sensible, non-technical language Thomas A Harris explains how to gain control of yourself, your relationships and your future &#8211; no matter what happened [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/im-ok-youre-ok-a-practical-guide-to-transactional-analysis-thomas-a-harris-abridged/">I&#8217;m Ok, You&#8217;re Ok : A practical guide to Transactional Analysis &#8211; Thomas A. Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This practical guide to Transactional Analysis is a unique approach to your problems.     </p>
<p>                    Hundreds of thousands of people have found this phenomenal breakthrough in psychotherapy a turning point in their lives.     </p>
<p>                    In sensible, non-technical language Thomas A Harris explains how to gain control of yourself, your relationships and your future &#8211; no matter what happened in the past.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/im-ok-youre-ok-a-practical-guide-to-transactional-analysis-thomas-a-harris-abridged/">I&#8217;m Ok, You&#8217;re Ok : A practical guide to Transactional Analysis &#8211; Thomas A. Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Separation & Divorce]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>_____________________________ Is having &#8216;somebody to love&#8217; the most important thing in your life? Do you constantly believe in Mr Right, and that being with him would guarantee you would no longer feel depressed or lonely? Are you bored with &#8216;nice guys&#8217; who are open, honest and dependable? If being in love means being in pain, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/">Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>_____________________________<br />
                    Is having &#8216;somebody to love&#8217; the most important thing in your life?<br />
                    Do you constantly believe in Mr Right, and that being with him would guarantee you would no longer feel depressed or lonely?<br />
                    Are you bored with &#8216;nice guys&#8217; who are open, honest and dependable?     </p>
<p>                    If being in love means being in pain, this book was written for you. Leading relationship and marriage therapist Robin Norwood describes loving too much as a pattern of thoughts and behaviour, which certain women develop as a response to problems from childhood.     </p>
<p>                    Many women find themselves repeatedly drawn into unhappy and destructive relationships with men. They then struggle to make these doomed relationships work. This bestselling relationship self-help book investigates and reveals how powerfully addictive these unhealthy relationships are &#8211; but also gives a very specific programme for recovery from the disease of loving too much, a problem that plagues women everywhere.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/">Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Ideals : The Real Story of Moral Choice &#8211; William Damon, Anne Colby (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-ideals-the-real-story-of-moral-choice-william-damon-anne-colby-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-ideals-the-real-story-of-moral-choice-william-damon-anne-colby-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cynicism often seems a smarter choice than idealism, and there are seemingly good reasons for this. Politicians have disappointed us time and again, trusted institutions have proven silf-serving and corrupt, and social inequities persist and increase, unabated by even the grandest of charitable efforts. Moreover, trends in contemporrary moral psychology support this bleak view of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-ideals-the-real-story-of-moral-choice-william-damon-anne-colby-abridged/">The Power of Ideals : The Real Story of Moral Choice &#8211; William Damon, Anne Colby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cynicism often seems a smarter choice than idealism, and there are seemingly good reasons for this. Politicians have disappointed us time and again, trusted institutions have proven silf-serving and corrupt, and social inequities persist and increase, unabated by even the grandest of charitable efforts. Moreover, trends in contemporrary moral psychology support this bleak view of the human condition. Famous studies have shown that we have an almost unlimited<br />
                    potential for cruelty when placed in the wrong situations. Other studies imply that our moral responses are dictated by inborn biological intuitions, or that people do little more than act out conventional cultural scripts when confronted with moral chices.    </p>
<p>                    The Power of Ideals presents a different vision, supported by a different kind of evidence. It examines the lives and work of six 20th century moral leaders who pursued moral causes ranging from world peace to social justice and human rights. Using these six cases to illustrate how people can make choices guided by their moral convictions, rather than by base emotion or social pressures, authors William Damon and Anne Colby explore the workings of three virtues: inner truthfulness,<br />
                    humility, and faith. Through their portrayal of the noble lives of moral leaders, the authors argue that everyone -including those of us   with ordinary lives &#8211; can exercise control over important life decisions and pursue ideals that inspire us. The Power of Ideals offers a hopeful and much-needed vision for<br />
                    moral progress in the worl.    </p>
<p>                    This message flies in the face of contemporary thought in moral psychology, much of which has drawn  mainstream media coverage in recent years. But the more accurate, constructive, and inspiring view in The Power of Ideals provides a sound basis for helping all people achieve their moral potentials. The Power of Ideals offers a needed and hopeful vision for personal well-being, for rebuilding trust among disillusioned citizens, for the flourishing of democracy, and for moral<br />
                    progress in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-ideals-the-real-story-of-moral-choice-william-damon-anne-colby-abridged/">The Power of Ideals : The Real Story of Moral Choice &#8211; William Damon, Anne Colby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Suspicious Minds : Why We Believe Conspiracy Theories &#8211; Rob Brotherton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/suspicious-minds-why-we-believe-conspiracy-theories-rob-brotherton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conspiracy Theories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/suspicious-minds-why-we-believe-conspiracy-theories-rob-brotherton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A first class book&#8217; Sunday Times We&#8217;re all conspiracy theorists. Some of us just hide it better than others. Conspiracy theorists do not wear tin-foil hats (for the most part). They are not just a few kooks lurking on the paranoid fringes of society with bizarre ideas about shape-shifting reptilian aliens running society in secret. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/suspicious-minds-why-we-believe-conspiracy-theories-rob-brotherton-abridged/">Suspicious Minds : Why We Believe Conspiracy Theories &#8211; Rob Brotherton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A first class book&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;re all conspiracy theorists. Some of us just hide it better than others.    </p>
<p>                    Conspiracy theorists do not wear tin-foil hats (for the most part). They are not just a few kooks lurking on the paranoid fringes of society with bizarre ideas about shape-shifting reptilian aliens running society in secret. They walk among us. They are us.    </p>
<p>                    Everyone loves a good conspiracy. Yet conspiracy theories are not a recent invention. And they are not always a harmless curiosity. In Suspicious Minds, Rob Brotherton explores the history and consequences of conspiracism, and delves into the research that offers insights into why so many of us are drawn to implausible, unproven and unproveable conspiracy theories. They resonate with some of our brain&#8217;s built-in quirks and foibles, and tap into some of our deepest desires, fears, and assumptions about the world.     </p>
<p>                    The fascinating and often surprising psychology of conspiracy theories tells us a lot &#8211; not just why we are drawn to theories about sinister schemes, but about how our minds are wired and, indeed, why we believe anything at all. Conspiracy theories are not some psychological aberration &#8211; they&#8217;re a predictable product of how brains work. This book will tell you why, and what it means.    </p>
<p>                    Of course, just because your brain&#8217;s biased doesn&#8217;t always mean you&#8217;re wrong. Sometimes conspiracies are real. Sometimes, paranoia is prudent.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/suspicious-minds-why-we-believe-conspiracy-theories-rob-brotherton-abridged/">Suspicious Minds : Why We Believe Conspiracy Theories &#8211; Rob Brotherton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Usage & Grammar Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities. In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A surprising and entertaining explanation of how the words we use (even the ones we don&#8217;t notice) reveal our personalities, emotions, and identities.     </p>
<p>                    In The Secret Life of Pronouns, social psychologist and language expert James W. Pennebaker uses his groundbreaking research in computational linguistics-in essence, counting the frequency of words we use-to show that our language carries secrets about our feelings, our self-concept, and our social intelligence. Our most forgettable words, such as pronouns and prepositions, can be the most revealing: their patterns are as distinctive as fingerprints.     </p>
<p>                    Using innovative analytic techniques, Pennebaker X-rays everything from John McCain&#8217;s tweets to the Federalist Papers. Who would have predicted that the high school student who uses too many verbs in her college admissions essay is likely to make lower grades in college? Or that a world leader&#8217;s use of pronouns could reliably presage whether he will lead his country into war? You&#8217;ll learn what Lady Gaga and William Butler Yeats have in common, and how Ebenezer Scrooge&#8217;s syntax hints at his self-deception and repressed emotion in this sprightly, surprising tour of what our words are saying-whether we mean them to or not.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-pronouns-what-our-words-say-about-us-james-w-pennebaker-abridged/">The Secret Life of Pronouns : What Our Words Say About Us &#8211; James W. Pennebaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dangerous Personalities : An FBI Profiler Shows You How to Identify and Protect Yourself from Harmful People &#8211; Joe Navarro, Toni Sciarra Poynter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dangerous-personalities-an-fbi-profiler-shows-you-how-to-identify-and-protect-yourself-from-harmful-people-joe-navarro-toni-sciarra-poynter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Safety In The Home]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dangerous-personalities-an-fbi-profiler-shows-you-how-to-identify-and-protect-yourself-from-harmful-people-joe-navarro-toni-sciarra-poynter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What makes a narcissist go from self-involved to terrifying? In this national bestseller, Joe Navarro, a leading FBI profiler, unlocks the secrets to the personality disorders that put us all at risk. &#8220;I should have known.&#8221; &#8220;How could we have missed the warning signs?&#8221; &#8220;I always thought there was something off about him.&#8221; When we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerous-personalities-an-fbi-profiler-shows-you-how-to-identify-and-protect-yourself-from-harmful-people-joe-navarro-toni-sciarra-poynter-abridged/">Dangerous Personalities : An FBI Profiler Shows You How to Identify and Protect Yourself from Harmful People &#8211; Joe Navarro, Toni Sciarra Poynter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What makes a narcissist go from self-involved to terrifying? In this national bestseller, Joe Navarro, a leading FBI profiler, unlocks the secrets to the personality disorders that put us all at risk.      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I should have known.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8220;How could we have missed the warning signs?&#8221;<br />
                    &#8220;I always thought there was something off about him.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    When we wake up to new tragedies in the news every day&#8211;shootings, rampages, acts of domestic terrorism&#8211;we often blame ourselves for missing the mania lurking inside unsuspecting individuals. But how could we have known that the charismatic leader had the characteristics of a tyrant? And how can ordinary people identify threats from those who are poised to devastate their lives on a daily basis&#8211;the crazy coworkers, out-of-control family members, or relentless neighbors?     </p>
<p>                    In Dangerous Personalities, former FBI profiler Joe Navarro has the answers. He shows us how to identify the four most common dangerous personalities&#8211;the Narcissist, the Predator, the Paranoid, and the Unstable Personality&#8211; and how to analyze the potential threat level. Along the way, he provides essential tips and tricks to protect ourselves both immediately and in the long-term, as well as how to heal the trauma of being exposed to the destructive egos in our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerous-personalities-an-fbi-profiler-shows-you-how-to-identify-and-protect-yourself-from-harmful-people-joe-navarro-toni-sciarra-poynter-abridged/">Dangerous Personalities : An FBI Profiler Shows You How to Identify and Protect Yourself from Harmful People &#8211; Joe Navarro, Toni Sciarra Poynter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Experiments With People : Revelations From Social Psychology, 2nd Edition &#8211; Kurt P. Frey, Aiden P. Gregg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/experiments-with-people-revelations-from-social-psychology-2nd-edition-kurt-p-frey-aiden-p-gregg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Experimental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Methodology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/experiments-with-people-revelations-from-social-psychology-2nd-edition-kurt-p-frey-aiden-p-gregg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book showcases 28 intriguing social psychological experiments that have significantly advanced our understanding of human social thinking and behavior. Each chapter focuses on the details and implications of a single study, while citing related research and real-life examples along the way. All the chapters are fully self-contained, allowing them to be read in any [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/experiments-with-people-revelations-from-social-psychology-2nd-edition-kurt-p-frey-aiden-p-gregg-abridged/">Experiments With People : Revelations From Social Psychology, 2nd Edition &#8211; Kurt P. Frey, Aiden P. Gregg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book showcases 28 intriguing social psychological experiments that have significantly advanced our understanding of human social thinking and behavior. Each chapter focuses on the details and implications of a single study, while citing related research and real-life examples along the way. All the chapters are fully self-contained, allowing them to be read in any order without loss of coherence. This 2nd Edition contains a number of new studies and, together with its lively, conversational tone, it makes an ideal text for courses in social psychology, introductory psychology, or research design.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/experiments-with-people-revelations-from-social-psychology-2nd-edition-kurt-p-frey-aiden-p-gregg-abridged/">Experiments With People : Revelations From Social Psychology, 2nd Edition &#8211; Kurt P. Frey, Aiden P. Gregg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Language]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite 21st-century fears of an &#8216;epidemic&#8217; of loneliness, its history has been sorely neglected. A Biography of Loneliness offers a radically new interpretation of loneliness as an emotional language and experience. Using letters and diaries, philosophical tracts, political discussions, and medical literature from the eighteenth century to the present, historian of the emotions Fay Bound [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/">A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite 21st-century fears of an &#8216;epidemic&#8217; of loneliness, its history has been sorely neglected. A Biography of Loneliness offers a radically new interpretation of loneliness as an emotional language and experience. Using letters and diaries, philosophical tracts, political discussions, and medical literature from the eighteenth century to the present, historian of the emotions Fay Bound Alberti argues that loneliness is not an ahistorical, universal<br />
                    phenomenon. It is, in fact, a modern emotion: before 1800, its language did not exist. And where loneliness is identified, it is not always bad, but a complex emotional state that differs according to class, gender, ethnicity and experience.    </p>
<p>                    Looking at informative case studies such as Sylvia Plath, Queen Victoria, and Virginia Woolf, A Biography of Loneliness charts the emergence of loneliness as a modern and embodied emotional state.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/">A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can You Learn to be Lucky? : Why Some People Seem to Win More Often Than Others &#8211; Karla Starr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/can-you-learn-to-be-lucky-why-some-people-seem-to-win-more-often-than-others-karla-starr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/can-you-learn-to-be-lucky-why-some-people-seem-to-win-more-often-than-others-karla-starr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t know when I&#8217;ve been so wowed by a new author&#8221; -Chip Health, co-author of The Power of Moments and Switch A talented journalist reveals the hidden patterns behind what we call &#8220;luck&#8221; &#8212; and shows us how we can all improve outcomes despite life&#8217;s inevitable randomness. &#8220;Do you believe in luck?&#8221; is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/can-you-learn-to-be-lucky-why-some-people-seem-to-win-more-often-than-others-karla-starr-abridged/">Can You Learn to be Lucky? : Why Some People Seem to Win More Often Than Others &#8211; Karla Starr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;I don&#8217;t know when I&#8217;ve been so wowed by a new author&#8221;<br />
                    -Chip Health, co-author of The Power of Moments and Switch A talented journalist reveals the hidden patterns behind what we call &#8220;luck&#8221; &#8212; and shows us how we can all improve outcomes despite life&#8217;s inevitable randomness. &#8220;Do you believe in luck?&#8221; is a polarizing question, one you might ask on a first date. Some of us believe that we make our own luck. Others see inequality everywhere and think that everyone&#8217;s fate is at the whim of the cosmos. Karla Starr has a third answer: unlucky, &#8220;random&#8221; outcomes have predictable effects on our behavior that often make us act in self-defeating ways without even realizing it.  In this groundbreaking book, Starr traces wealth, health, and happiness back to subconscious neurological processes, blind cultural assumptions, and tiny details you&#8217;re in the habit of overlooking. Each chapter reveals how we can cultivate personal strengths to overcome life&#8217;s unlucky patterns. For instance: &#8211; Everyone has free access to that magic productivity app&#8211;motivation. The problem? It isn&#8217;t evenly distributed. What lucky accidents of history explain patterns behind why certain groups of people are more motivated in some situations than others? &#8211; If you look like an underperforming employee, your resume can&#8217;t override the gut-level assumptions that a potential boss will make from your LinkedIn photo. How can we make sure that someone&#8217;s first impression is favorable? &#8211; Just as people use irrelevant traits to make assumptions about your intelligence, kindness, and trustworthiness, we also make inaccurate snap judgments. How do these judgments affect our interactions, and what should we assume about others to maximize our odds of having lucky encounters?  We don&#8217;t always realize when the world&#8217;s invisible biases work to our advantage or recognize how much of a role we play in our own lack of luck. By ending the guessing game about how luck works, Starr allows you to improve your fortunes while expending minimal effort.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/can-you-learn-to-be-lucky-why-some-people-seem-to-win-more-often-than-others-karla-starr-abridged/">Can You Learn to be Lucky? : Why Some People Seem to Win More Often Than Others &#8211; Karla Starr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Everyone (Else) Is a Hypocrite : Evolution and the Modular Mind &#8211; Robert Kurzban (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-everyone-else-is-a-hypocrite-evolution-and-the-modular-mind-robert-kurzban-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-everyone-else-is-a-hypocrite-evolution-and-the-modular-mind-robert-kurzban-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re all hypocrites. Why? Hypocrisy is the natural state of the human mind. Robert Kurzban shows us that the key to understanding our behavioral inconsistencies lies in understanding the mind&#8217;s design. The human mind consists of many specialized units designed by the process of evolution by natural selection. While these modules sometimes work together seamlessly, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-everyone-else-is-a-hypocrite-evolution-and-the-modular-mind-robert-kurzban-abridged/">Why Everyone (Else) Is a Hypocrite : Evolution and the Modular Mind &#8211; Robert Kurzban (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re all hypocrites. Why? Hypocrisy is the natural state of the human mind. Robert Kurzban shows us that the key to understanding our behavioral inconsistencies lies in understanding the mind&#8217;s design. The human mind consists of many specialized units designed by the process of evolution by natural selection. While these modules sometimes work together seamlessly, they don&#8217;t always, resulting in impossibly contradictory beliefs, vacillations between patience and impulsiveness, violations of our supposed moral principles, and overinflated views of ourselves. This modular, evolutionary psychological view of the mind undermines deeply held intuitions about ourselves, as well as a range of scientific theories that require a &#8220;self&#8221; with consistent beliefs and preferences. Modularity suggests that there is no &#8220;I&#8221;. Instead, each of us is a contentious &#8220;we&#8221; &#8211; a collection of discrete but interacting systems whose constant conflicts shape our interactions with one another and our experience of the world.<br />
                    In clear language, full of wit and rich in examples, Kurzban explains the roots and implications of our inconsistent minds, and why it is perfectly natural to believe that everyone else is a hypocrite.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-everyone-else-is-a-hypocrite-evolution-and-the-modular-mind-robert-kurzban-abridged/">Why Everyone (Else) Is a Hypocrite : Evolution and the Modular Mind &#8211; Robert Kurzban (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Eating Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she). When a personal crisis causes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she).    </p>
<p>                    When a personal crisis causes her world to come crashing down, Lori Gottlieb &#8211; an experienced therapist with a thriving practice in Los Angeles &#8211; is suddenly adrift. Enter Wendell, himself a veteran therapist with an unconventional style, whose sessions with Gottlieb will prove transformative for her.    </p>
<p>                    As Gottlieb explores the inner chambers of her own patients&#8217; lives &#8211; a self-absorbed Hollywood producer, a young newlywed diagnosed with a terminal illness, a senior citizen who feels she has nothing to live for, and a self-destructive twenty-something who can&#8217;t stop hooking up with the wrong guys &#8211; she finds that the questions they are struggling with are the very questions she is bringing to Wendell.    </p>
<p>                    Taking place over one year, and beginning with the devastating event that lands her in Wendell&#8217;s office, Maybe You Should Talk to Someone offers a rare and candid insight into a profession that is conventionally bound with rules and secrecy. Told with charm and compassion, vulnerability and humour, it&#8217;s also the story of an incredible relationship between two therapists, and a disarmingly funny and illuminating account of our own mysterious inner lives, as well as our power to transform them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out of Character : Surprising Truths About the Liar, Cheat, Sinner (and Saint) Lurking in All of Us &#8211; David Desteno, Piercarlo Valdesolo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-character-surprising-truths-about-the-liar-cheat-sinner-and-saint-lurking-in-all-of-us-david-desteno-piercarlo-valdesolo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-character-surprising-truths-about-the-liar-cheat-sinner-and-saint-lurking-in-all-of-us-david-desteno-piercarlo-valdesolo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever wondered why a trumpeter of family values would suddenly turn around and cheat on his wife? Why jealousy would send an otherwise level-headed person into a violent rage? What could drive a person to blow a family fortune at the blackjack tables? Or have you ever pondered what might make Mr. Right [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-character-surprising-truths-about-the-liar-cheat-sinner-and-saint-lurking-in-all-of-us-david-desteno-piercarlo-valdesolo-abridged/">Out of Character : Surprising Truths About the Liar, Cheat, Sinner (and Saint) Lurking in All of Us &#8211; David Desteno, Piercarlo Valdesolo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever wondered why a trumpeter of family values would suddenly turn around and cheat on his wife? Why jealousy would send an otherwise level-headed person into a violent rage? What could drive a person to blow a family fortune at the blackjack tables?     </p>
<p>                    Or have you ever pondered what might make Mr. Right leave his beloved at the altar, why hypocrisy seems to be rampant, or even why, every once in awhile, even you are secretly tempted, to lie, cheat, or steal (or, conversely, help someone you never even met)?     </p>
<p>                    This book answers these questions and more, and in doing so, turns the prevailing wisdom about who we are upside down. Our character, argue psychologists DeSteno and Valdesolo, isn&#8217;t a stable set of traits, but rather a shifting state that is subject to the constant push and pull of hidden mechanisms in our mind. And it&#8217;s the battle between these dueling psychological forces that determine how we act at any given point in time.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the surprising results of the clever experiments concocted in their own laboratory, DeSteno and Valdesolo shed new scientific light on so many of the puzzling behaviors that regularly grace the headlines. For example, you&#8217;ll learn:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Why Tiger Woods just couldn&#8217;t resist the allure of his mistresses even though he had a picture-perfect family at home. And why no one, including those who knew him best, ever saw it coming.     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Why even the shrewdest of investors can be tempted to gamble their fortunes away (and why risky financial behavior is driven by the same mechanisms that compel us to root for the underdog in sports).     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Why Eliot Spitzer, who made a career of crusading against prostitution, turned out to be one of the most famous johns of all time.     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Why Mel Gibson, a noted philanthropist and devout Catholic, has been repeatedly caught spewing racist rants, even though close friends say he doesn&#8217;t have a racist bone in his body.     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; And why any of us is capable of doing the same, whether we believe it or not!    </p>
<p>                    A surprising look at the hidden forces driving the saint and sinner lurking in us all, Out of Character reveals why human behavior is so much more unpredictable than we ever realized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-character-surprising-truths-about-the-liar-cheat-sinner-and-saint-lurking-in-all-of-us-david-desteno-piercarlo-valdesolo-abridged/">Out of Character : Surprising Truths About the Liar, Cheat, Sinner (and Saint) Lurking in All of Us &#8211; David Desteno, Piercarlo Valdesolo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Introvert&#8217;s Complete Career Guide : From Landing a Job, to Surviving, Thriving and Moving on Up &#8211; Jane Finkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-introverts-complete-career-guide-from-landing-a-job-to-surviving-thriving-and-moving-on-up-jane-finkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-introverts-complete-career-guide-from-landing-a-job-to-surviving-thriving-and-moving-on-up-jane-finkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What do Elon Musk, Warren Buffet, Marissa Mayer, and Bill Gates all have in common outside of being wildly successful? They are all introverts. In today&#8217;s fast-paced, unstable workplace achieving success requires speaking up, promoting oneself and one&#8217;s ideas, and taking initiative. Extroverts, fearless in tooting their own horns, naturally thrive in this environment, but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-introverts-complete-career-guide-from-landing-a-job-to-surviving-thriving-and-moving-on-up-jane-finkle-abridged/">The Introvert&#8217;s Complete Career Guide : From Landing a Job, to Surviving, Thriving and Moving on Up &#8211; Jane Finkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What do Elon Musk, Warren Buffet, Marissa Mayer, and Bill Gates all have in common outside of being wildly successful? They are all introverts.    </p>
<p>                    In today&#8217;s fast-paced, unstable workplace achieving success requires speaking up, promoting oneself and one&#8217;s ideas, and taking initiative. Extroverts, fearless in tooting their own horns, naturally thrive in this environment, but introverts often stumble. If you question your ability to perform and succeed in this extroverted work culture, The Introvert&#8217;s Complete Career Guide is custom fit for you.    </p>
<p>                    In this supportive, all-inclusive handbook, Jane Finkle demonstrates how to use your introverted qualities to their best advantage, then add a sprinkling of extroverted skills to round out a forceful combination for ultimate career success. Finkle shares the keys to navigating each stage of professional development&#8211;from self-assessment and job searching, to survival in a new position and career advancement.    </p>
<p>                    In The Introvert&#8217;s Complete Career Guide you will learn to:     </p>
<p>                    Build confidence by evaluating your values, personality style, interests, and achievementsWrite the story of your career in resume and LinkedIn formatsUse social media at your own comfort level to promote your career and expand your networkExpress yourself clearly and confidently in network meetings, interviews, and workplace situationsBuild strong professional relationships with colleagues and senior leadersOvercome fears that prevent you from embracing new challenges    </p>
<p>                    Equally applicable to the real or virtual workplace, The Introvert&#8217;s Complete Career Guide provides strategies, tools, and success stories that win you the professional respect and recognition you deserve.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-introverts-complete-career-guide-from-landing-a-job-to-surviving-thriving-and-moving-on-up-jane-finkle-abridged/">The Introvert&#8217;s Complete Career Guide : From Landing a Job, to Surviving, Thriving and Moving on Up &#8211; Jane Finkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Be Fearless : 5 Principles for a Life of Breakthroughs and Purpose &#8211; Jean Case (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/be-fearless-5-principles-for-a-life-of-breakthroughs-and-purpose-jean-case-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-profitmaking Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/be-fearless-5-principles-for-a-life-of-breakthroughs-and-purpose-jean-case-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Be Fearless is researched-based call to action for those seeking to live extraordinary lives and bring about transformational change. LOS ANGELES TIMES BESTSELLER * NATIONAL BESTSELLER Weaving together storytelling, practical tips and inspiration, the book will teach you how to put the five fearless principles to work so that you too can spark the sorts [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/be-fearless-5-principles-for-a-life-of-breakthroughs-and-purpose-jean-case-abridged/">Be Fearless : 5 Principles for a Life of Breakthroughs and Purpose &#8211; Jean Case (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Be Fearless is researched-based call to action for those seeking to live extraordinary lives and bring about transformational change.    </p>
<p>                    LOS ANGELES TIMES BESTSELLER * NATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    Weaving together storytelling, practical tips and inspiration, the book will teach you how to put the five fearless principles to work so that you too can spark the sorts of remarkable breakthroughs that can impact the world. Philanthropist, investor, and technology pioneer Jean Case brings to life the five Be Fearless principles common to the people and organizations that bring about transformational change.    </p>
<p>                    When National Geographic Chairman Jean Case set out to investigate the core qualities of great change makers, past and present, from inventors to revolutionaries, she found five surprising traits they all had in common. These weren&#8217;t wealth, privilege, or even genius. What all of these exceptional men and women shared was that they had chosen to make a &#8220;big bet,&#8221; take bold risks, learn from their failures, reach beyond their bubbles, and let urgency conquer fear.    </p>
<p>                    Throughout Be Fearless, Jean vividly illustrates these principles through storytelling-from her own transformational life experiences, to Jane Goodall&#8217;s remarkable breakthroughs in understanding and protecting chimpanzees, to celebrity chef Jose Andres&#8217; decision to be a &#8220;first responder&#8221; and take his kitchen to the sites of devastating hurricanes to feed the hungry, to Madame C.J. Walker&#8217;s vision to build a hair care empire that would employ thousands across the country, and more. She shares new insights to stories you might think you know-like Airbnb&#8217;s tale of starting from scratch to transform the hospitality industry, to John F. Kennedy&#8217;s history-making moonshot-and gems from changemakers you&#8217;ve never heard of. Be Fearless features a compelling foreword from Jane Goodall saying &#8220;there is no time in history when it has been more important to Be Fearless&#8221; and a new afterword with stories of people inspired to take action after reading the book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/be-fearless-5-principles-for-a-life-of-breakthroughs-and-purpose-jean-case-abridged/">Be Fearless : 5 Principles for a Life of Breakthroughs and Purpose &#8211; Jean Case (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Four Tendencies : The Indispensable Personality Profiles That Reveal How to Make Your Life Better (and Other People&#8217;s Lives Better, Too) &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-four-tendencies-the-indispensable-personality-profiles-that-reveal-how-to-make-your-life-better-and-other-peoples-lives-better-too-gretchen-rubin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-four-tendencies-the-indispensable-personality-profiles-that-reveal-how-to-make-your-life-better-and-other-peoples-lives-better-too-gretchen-rubin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this groundbreaking analysis of personality type, bestselling author of Better Than Before and The Happiness Project Gretchen Rubin reveals the one simple question that will transform what you do at home, at work, and in life.  During her multibook investigation into understanding human nature, Gretchen Rubin realized that by asking the seemingly dry [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-four-tendencies-the-indispensable-personality-profiles-that-reveal-how-to-make-your-life-better-and-other-peoples-lives-better-too-gretchen-rubin-abridged/">The Four Tendencies : The Indispensable Personality Profiles That Reveal How to Make Your Life Better (and Other People&#8217;s Lives Better, Too) &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this groundbreaking analysis of personality type, bestselling author of Better Than Before and The Happiness Project Gretchen Rubin reveals the one simple question that will transform what you do at home, at work, and in life.<br />
                     <br />
                     During her multibook investigation into understanding human nature, Gretchen Rubin realized that by asking the seemingly dry question &#8220;How do I respond to expectations?&#8221; we gain explosive self-knowledge. She discovered that based on their answer, people fit into Four Tendencies: Upholders, Questioners, Obligers, and Rebels. Our Tendency shapes every aspect of our behavior, so using this framework allows us to make better decisions, meet deadlines, suffer less stress, and engage more effectively.     </p>
<p>                     More than 600,000 people have taken her online quiz, and managers, doctors, teachers, spouses, and parents already use the framework to help people make significant, lasting change.<br />
                     The Four Tendencies hold practical answers if you&#8217;ve ever thought:    </p>
<p>                      People can rely on me, but I can&#8217;t rely on myself.<br />
                    How can I help someone to follow good advice?<br />
                    People say I ask too many questions.<br />
                    How do I work with someone who refuses to do what I askor who keeps telling me what to do?    </p>
<p>                     With sharp insight, compelling research, and hilarious examples, The Four Tendencies will help you get happier, healthier, more productive, and more creative. It&#8217;s far easier to succeed when you know what works for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-four-tendencies-the-indispensable-personality-profiles-that-reveal-how-to-make-your-life-better-and-other-peoples-lives-better-too-gretchen-rubin-abridged/">The Four Tendencies : The Indispensable Personality Profiles That Reveal How to Make Your Life Better (and Other People&#8217;s Lives Better, Too) &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Perfect for lovers of Quiet and The Power of Now, Emotional Agility shares a new way of relating to yourself and the world around you Every day we speak around 16,000 words &#8211; but inside minds we create tens of thousands more. Thoughts such as &#8216;I&#8217;m not spending enough time with my children&#8217; or &#8216;I&#8217;m [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/">Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Perfect for lovers of Quiet and The Power of Now, Emotional Agility shares a new way of relating to yourself and the world around you    </p>
<p>                     Every day we speak around 16,000 words &#8211; but inside minds we create tens of thousands more.     </p>
<p>                    Thoughts such as &#8216;I&#8217;m not spending enough time with my children&#8217; or &#8216;I&#8217;m not good enough to present my work&#8217; can seem to be unshakeable facts. In reality, they&#8217;re the judgemental opinions of our inner voice.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on more than twenty years of academic research and her own experiences, Susan David PhD, a psychologist and faculty member at Harvard Medical School, has pioneered a new way to make peace with our inner self, achieve our most valued goals and live life to the fullest.    </p>
<p>                     Become aware of your true nature, learn to face your emotions with acceptance and generosity, act according to your deepest values, and flourish.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Essential reading&#8217; Susan Cain, author of Quiet    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A practical, science-backed guide to looking inward and living intentionally&#8217; Arianna Huffington, author of The Sleep Revolution    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An accessible, reader-friendly voyage. Emotional Agility can be helpful to anyone.&#8217; Daniel Goleman, author of Emotional Intelligence</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/">Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Insight : How to succeed by seeing yourself clearly &#8211; Tasha Eurich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/insight-how-to-succeed-by-seeing-yourself-clearly-tasha-eurich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/insight-how-to-succeed-by-seeing-yourself-clearly-tasha-eurich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nominated as one of the 2019 Thinkers50 Radar group Research shows that self-awareness is the meta-skill of the 21st century &#8211; the foundation for high performance, smart choices, and lasting relationships. Unfortunately, we are remarkably poor judges of ourselves and how we come across, and it&#8217;s rare to get candid, objective feedback from colleagues, employees, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/insight-how-to-succeed-by-seeing-yourself-clearly-tasha-eurich-abridged/">Insight : How to succeed by seeing yourself clearly &#8211; Tasha Eurich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nominated as one of the 2019 Thinkers50 Radar group    </p>
<p>                    Research shows that self-awareness is the meta-skill of the 21st century &#8211; the foundation for high performance, smart choices, and lasting relationships. Unfortunately, we are remarkably poor judges of ourselves and how we come across, and it&#8217;s rare to get candid, objective feedback from colleagues, employees, and even friends and family. We can ALL learn to be more self-aware.    </p>
<p>                    Integrating hundreds of studies with her own research and work in the Fortune 500 world, organizational psychologist Dr Tasha Eurich shatters conventional assumptions about what it takes to truly know ourselves &#8211; like why introspection isn&#8217;t a bullet train to insight, how experience is the enemy of self-knowledge, and just how far others will go to avoid telling us the truth about ourselves. Through stories of people who&#8217;ve made dramatic self-awareness gains, she offers surprising secrets, techniques and strategies to help readers do the same &#8211; and therefore improve their work performance, career satisfaction, leadership potential, relationships, and more.    </p>
<p>                    At a time when self-awareness matters more than ever, Insight is the essential playbook for surviving and thriving in an unaware world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/insight-how-to-succeed-by-seeing-yourself-clearly-tasha-eurich-abridged/">Insight : How to succeed by seeing yourself clearly &#8211; Tasha Eurich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flow : The Psychology of Optimal Experience &#8211; Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Csikszentmihalyi arrives at an insight that many of us can intuitively grasp, despite our insistent (and culturally supported) denial of this truth. That is, it is not what happens to us that determines our happiness, but the manner in which we make sense of that reality. . . . The manner in which Csikszentmihalyi integrates [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/">Flow : The Psychology of Optimal Experience &#8211; Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Csikszentmihalyi arrives at an insight that many of us can intuitively grasp, despite our insistent (and culturally supported) denial of this truth. That is, it is not what happens to us that determines our happiness, but the manner in which we make sense of that reality. . . . The manner in which Csikszentmihalyi integrates research on consciousness, personal psychology and spirituality is illuminating.&#8221; &#8211;Los Angeles Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    The bestselling classic that holds the key to unlocking meaning, creativity, peak performance, and true happiness.     </p>
<p>                    Legendary psychologist Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi&#8217;s famous investigations of optimal experience have revealed that what makes an experience genuinely satisfying is a state of consciousness called flow. During flow, people typically experience deep enjoyment, creativity, and a total involvement with life. In this new edition of his groundbreaking classic work, Csikszentmihalyi (the leading researcher into &#8216;flow states&#8217; &#8211;Newsweek) demonstrates the ways this positive state can be controlled, not just left to chance. Flow: The Psychology of Optimal Experience teaches how, by ordering the information that enters our consciousness, we can discover true happiness, unlock our potential, and greatly improve the quality of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/">Flow : The Psychology of Optimal Experience &#8211; Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>59 Seconds : Think a Little, Change a Lot &#8211; Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/59-seconds-think-a-little-change-a-lot-richard-wiseman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/59-seconds-think-a-little-change-a-lot-richard-wiseman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Whether you&#8217;re looking to be more decisive in your life, find a new job or simply be happier, 59 Seconds has the &#8216;magic bullet&#8217; you need. Most people would like to be more creative, more persuasive and more attractive. For years, gurus and &#8216;life coaches&#8217; have urged people to improve their lives by changing the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/59-seconds-think-a-little-change-a-lot-richard-wiseman-abridged/">59 Seconds : Think a Little, Change a Lot &#8211; Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Whether you&#8217;re looking to be more decisive in your life, find a new job or simply be happier, 59 Seconds has the &#8216;magic bullet&#8217; you need.    </p>
<p>                    Most people would like to be more creative, more persuasive and more attractive. For years, gurus and &#8216;life coaches&#8217; have urged people to improve their lives by changing the way they think and behave, but scientific research has revealed that many of their techniques, from group brainstorming to visualization, are ineffective.     </p>
<p>                    Fortunately, in 59 Seconds: Think a Little, Change a Lot psychologist Richard Wiseman is on hand to provide fast-acting, myth-busting scientific answers to a huge range of everyday problems. From job-hunting to relationships, and from parenting to self-esteem, personal and professional success may be less than a minute away . . .     </p>
<p>                     * Find out why putting a pencil between your teeth instantly makes you feel happier.    </p>
<p>                    * Discover why even thinking about going to the gym can help you keep in shape.    </p>
<p>                    * Learn how putting just one thing in your wallet will improve the chance of it being returned if lost.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/59-seconds-think-a-little-change-a-lot-richard-wiseman-abridged/">59 Seconds : Think a Little, Change a Lot &#8211; Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selfie : How the West Became Self-Obsessed &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Electrifying&#8217; Financial Times &#8216;So interesting I literally couldn&#8217;t put it down&#8217; Sunday Times We are living in an age of heightened individualism. Success is a personal responsibility. Our culture tells us that to succeed is to be slim, rich, happy, extroverted, popular &#8211; flawless. The pressure to conform to this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/">Selfie : How the West Became Self-Obsessed &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Evening Standard<br />
                    &#8216;Electrifying&#8217; Financial Times<br />
                    &#8216;So interesting I literally couldn&#8217;t put it down&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    We are living in an age of heightened individualism. Success is a personal responsibility. Our culture tells us that to succeed is to be slim, rich, happy, extroverted, popular &#8211; flawless.    </p>
<p>                    The pressure to conform to this ideal has changed who we are. We have become self-obsessed. And our expectation of perfection comes at a cost. Millions are suffering under the torture of this impossible fantasy.    </p>
<p>                    It was not always like this. To explain how we got here, Will Storr takes us on a journey across continents and centuries. Full of thrilling and unexpected connections between history, psychology, economics, neuroscience and more, Selfie is an unforgettable book that makes sense of who we have become.    </p>
<p>                    As featured on Russell Brand&#8217;s Under The Skin podcast.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selfie-how-the-west-became-self-obsessed-will-storr-abridged/">Selfie : How the West Became Self-Obsessed &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Thought it Was Just Me (but it Isn&#8217;T) : Telling the Truth About Perfectionism, Inadequacy and Power &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-thought-it-was-just-me-but-it-isnt-telling-the-truth-about-perfectionism-inadequacy-and-power-brene-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-thought-it-was-just-me-but-it-isnt-telling-the-truth-about-perfectionism-inadequacy-and-power-brene-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Researcher, thought leader, and New York Times bestselling author Bren Brown offers a liberating study on the importance of our imperfections&#8211;both to our relationships and to our own sense of self The quest for perfection is exhausting and unrelenting. There is a constant barrage of social expectations that teach us that being imperfect is synonymous [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-thought-it-was-just-me-but-it-isnt-telling-the-truth-about-perfectionism-inadequacy-and-power-brene-brown-abridged/">I Thought it Was Just Me (but it Isn&#8217;T) : Telling the Truth About Perfectionism, Inadequacy and Power &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Researcher, thought leader, and New York Times bestselling author Bren Brown offers a liberating study on the importance of our imperfections&#8211;both to our relationships and to our own sense of self     </p>
<p>                    The quest for perfection is exhausting and unrelenting. There is a constant barrage of social expectations that teach us that being imperfect is synonymous with being inadequate. Everywhere we turn, there are messages that tell us who, what and how we&#8217;re supposed to be. So, we learn to hide our struggles and protect ourselves from shame, judgment, criticism and blame by seeking safety in pretending and perfection.     </p>
<p>                    Bren Brown, PhD, LMSW, is the leading authority on the power of vulnerability, and has inspired thousands through her top-selling books Daring Greatly, Rising Strong, and The Gifts of Imperfection, her wildly popular TEDx talks, and a PBS special. Based on seven years of her ground-breaking research and hundreds of interviews, I Thought It Was Just Me shines a long-overdue light on an important truth: Our imperfections are what connect us to each other and to our humanity. Our vulnerabilities are not weaknesses; they are powerful reminders to keep our hearts and minds open to the reality that we&#8217;re all in this together.     </p>
<p>                    Brown writes, &#8220;We need our lives back. It&#8217;s time to reclaim the gifts of imperfection&#8211;the courage to be real, the compassion we need to love ourselves and others, and the connection that gives true purpose and meaning to life. These are the gifts that bring love, laughter, gratitude, empathy and joy into our lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-thought-it-was-just-me-but-it-isnt-telling-the-truth-about-perfectionism-inadequacy-and-power-brene-brown-abridged/">I Thought it Was Just Me (but it Isn&#8217;T) : Telling the Truth About Perfectionism, Inadequacy and Power &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 11 Laws of Likability: Relationship Networking Because People Do Business with People They Like &#8211; Michelle Tillis Lederman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secretarial, Clerical & Office Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We all know that networking is important, and that forming relationships with others is a vital part of success. But sometimes it seems like networking removes all emotions from the equation and focuses only on immediate goals&#8230;whereas the kind of relationships that have true staying power, give us joy, and support us in the long [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/">The 11 Laws of Likability: Relationship Networking Because People Do Business with People They Like &#8211; Michelle Tillis Lederman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We all know that networking is important, and that forming relationships with others is a vital part of success. But sometimes it seems like networking removes all emotions from the equation and focuses only on immediate goals&#8230;whereas the kind of relationships that have true staying power, give us joy, and support us in the long run are founded on simply liking each other.     </p>
<p>                      This book, featuring activities, self-assessment quizzes, and real-life anecdotes from professional and social settings, shows readers how to identify what&#8217;s likable in themselves and create honest, authentic interactions that become &#8220;wins&#8221; for all parties involved. Readers will discover how to:     </p>
<p>                      * Start conversations and keep them going with ease     </p>
<p>                      * Convert acquaintances into friends     </p>
<p>                      * Uncover people&#8217;s preferences and tweak their own personal style to enable engaging, reciprocal interactions     </p>
<p>                      * Create follow-up and stay in others&#8217; minds long after the initial meeting     </p>
<p>                      The worst thing we can do when trying to establish a personal bond with someone is to come across as manipulative or self-serving. Authentic connections go much deeper-and feel much easier-than trying to hit self-imposed business card collection quotas. This book presents a new paradigm that shows how even the most networking-averse can network&#8230;and like it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/">The 11 Laws of Likability: Relationship Networking Because People Do Business with People They Like &#8211; Michelle Tillis Lederman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presence : Bringing Your Boldest Self to Your Biggest Challenges &#8211; Amy Cuddy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/presence-bringing-your-boldest-self-to-your-biggest-challenges-amy-cuddy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/presence-bringing-your-boldest-self-to-your-biggest-challenges-amy-cuddy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Cuddy shows how your body language influences others and even changes the way you see yourself. Social scientists have shown that we make sweeping inferences and judgements based on body language, judgements that can predict meaningful life outcomes like who we hire, who we promote, who we ask out on a date, who we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presence-bringing-your-boldest-self-to-your-biggest-challenges-amy-cuddy-abridged/">Presence : Bringing Your Boldest Self to Your Biggest Challenges &#8211; Amy Cuddy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amy Cuddy shows how your body language influences others and even changes the way you see yourself. Social scientists have shown that we make sweeping inferences and judgements based on body language, judgements that can predict meaningful life outcomes like who we hire, who we promote, who we ask out on a date, who we invest in and who we trust. In PRESENCE, Amy Cuddy reveals that we have the power not only to affect how others see us but also to change how we see ourselves and even the ability to alter our own chemistry, simply by changing body positions. Cuddy&#8217;s research shows how faking body postures that convey competence and power (power posing) even for as little as two minutes changes our cortisone and testosterone levels, increases our appetite for risk, helps us perform better in job interviews and configures our brains to cope in stressful situations. If you act powerfully, you will begin to think powerfully.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presence-bringing-your-boldest-self-to-your-biggest-challenges-amy-cuddy-abridged/">Presence : Bringing Your Boldest Self to Your Biggest Challenges &#8211; Amy Cuddy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Me, Myself, and Us : The Science of Personality and the Art of Well-Being &#8211; Brian R Little (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/me-myself-and-us-the-science-of-personality-and-the-art-of-well-being-brian-r-little-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/me-myself-and-us-the-science-of-personality-and-the-art-of-well-being-brian-r-little-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How does your personality shape your life , and what, if anything, can you do about it?Are you hardwired for happiness, or born to brood? Do you think you&#8217;re in charge of your future, or do you surf the waves of unknowable fate? Would you be happier, or just less socially adept, if you were [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-myself-and-us-the-science-of-personality-and-the-art-of-well-being-brian-r-little-abridged/">Me, Myself, and Us : The Science of Personality and the Art of Well-Being &#8211; Brian R Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How does your personality shape your life ,  and what, if anything, can you do about it?Are you hardwired for happiness, or born to brood? Do you think you&#8217;re in charge of your future, or do you surf the waves of unknowable fate? Would you be happier, or just less socially adept, if you were less concerned about what other people thought of you? And what about your  Type A&#8221; spouse: is he or she destined to have a heart attack, or just drive you to drink?In the past few decades, new scientific research has transformed old ideas about the nature of human personality. Neuroscientists, biologists, and psychological scientists have reexamined the theories of Freud and Jung as well as the humanistic psychologies of the 1960s, upending the simplistic categorizations of personality  types,&#8221; and developing new tools and methods for exploring who we are. Renowned professor and pioneering research psychologist Brian R. Little has been at the leading edge of this new science. In this wise and witty book he shares a wealth of new data and provocative insights about who we are, why we act the way we do, what we can,and can&#8217;t,change, and how we can best thrive in light of our  nature.&#8221; Me, Myself, and Us  explores questions that are rooted in the origins of human consciousness but are as commonplace as yesterday&#8217;s breakfast conversation, such as whether our personality traits are  set&#8221; by age thirty or whether our brains and selves are more plastic. He considers what our personalities portend for our health and success, and the extent to which our well-being depends on the personal projects we pursue.Through stories, studies, personal experiences, and entertaining interactive assessments,  Me, Myself, and Us  provides a lively, thought-provoking, and ultimately optimistic look at the possibilities and perils of being uniquely ourselves, while illuminating the selves of the familiar strangers we encounter, work with, and love.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-myself-and-us-the-science-of-personality-and-the-art-of-well-being-brian-r-little-abridged/">Me, Myself, and Us : The Science of Personality and the Art of Well-Being &#8211; Brian R Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Narcissist You Know : Defending Yourself Against Extreme Narcissists in an All-About-Me Age &#8211; Joseph Burgo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-narcissist-you-know-defending-yourself-against-extreme-narcissists-in-an-all-about-me-age-joseph-burgo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-narcissist-you-know-defending-yourself-against-extreme-narcissists-in-an-all-about-me-age-joseph-burgo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of The Sociopath Next Door, clinical psychologist Joseph Burgo&#8217;s The Narcissist You Know is a &#8220;clear, easily digestible&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews) guide to help you identify, disarm, and coexist with extreme narcissists. In today&#8217;s social media and selfie-obsessed culture, we are living in an age of narcissism&#8211;and a society that often celebrates this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-narcissist-you-know-defending-yourself-against-extreme-narcissists-in-an-all-about-me-age-joseph-burgo-abridged/">The Narcissist You Know : Defending Yourself Against Extreme Narcissists in an All-About-Me Age &#8211; Joseph Burgo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of The Sociopath Next Door, clinical psychologist Joseph Burgo&#8217;s The Narcissist You Know is a &#8220;clear, easily digestible&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews) guide to help you identify, disarm, and coexist with extreme narcissists.     </p>
<p>                    In today&#8217;s social media and selfie-obsessed culture, we are living in an age of narcissism&#8211;and a society that often celebrates this potentially harmful trait rather than understanding it as a psychological disorder. Scientists are beginning to learn that narcissism exists on a spectrum&#8211;much like autism&#8211;and most of us exhibit some mild narcissistic tendencies. But one in twenty people fall into a category the author refers to as Extreme Narcissism, in which these self-absorbed characteristics result in destructive behavior that harms not only the individual but everyone around them, including friends, family, and coworkers.     </p>
<p>                    With more than thirty years of experience studying personality disorders and treating extreme narcissists, Dr. Joseph Burgo has developed a useful guidebook to help you &#8220;spot narcissists out there in the wild&#8221; (Glamour) and then understand and manage the narcissistic personalities in your own life. Relying on detailed profiles, vignettes from the author&#8217;s practice, and celebrity biographies, The Narcissist You Know offers easy-to-understand tools and solutions you can use to defuse hostile situations and survive assaults on your self-esteem should you ever find yourself in an extreme narcissist&#8217;s orbit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-narcissist-you-know-defending-yourself-against-extreme-narcissists-in-an-all-about-me-age-joseph-burgo-abridged/">The Narcissist You Know : Defending Yourself Against Extreme Narcissists in an All-About-Me Age &#8211; Joseph Burgo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Wear the Black Hat : Grappling with Villains (Real and Imagined) &#8211; Chuck Klosterman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-wear-the-black-hat-grappling-with-villains-real-and-imagined-chuck-klosterman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-wear-the-black-hat-grappling-with-villains-real-and-imagined-chuck-klosterman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One-of-a-kind cultural critic and New York Times bestselling author Chuck Klosterman &#8220;offers up great facts, interesting cultural insights, and thought-provoking moral calculations in this look at our love affair with the anti-hero&#8221; (New York magazine). Chuck Klosterman, &#8220;The Ethicist&#8221; for The New York Times Magazine, has walked into the darkness. In I Wear the Black [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-wear-the-black-hat-grappling-with-villains-real-and-imagined-chuck-klosterman-abridged/">I Wear the Black Hat : Grappling with Villains (Real and Imagined) &#8211; Chuck Klosterman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One-of-a-kind cultural critic and New York Times bestselling author Chuck Klosterman &#8220;offers up great facts, interesting cultural insights, and thought-provoking moral calculations in this look at our love affair with the anti-hero&#8221; (New York magazine).     </p>
<p>                    Chuck Klosterman, &#8220;The Ethicist&#8221; for The New York Times Magazine, has walked into the darkness. In I Wear the Black Hat, he questions the modern understanding of villainy. When we classify someone as a bad person, what are we really saying, and why are we so obsessed with saying it? How does the culture of malevolence operate? What was so Machiavellian about Machiavelli? Why don&#8217;t we see Bernhard Goetz the same way we see Batman? Who is more worthy of our vitriol&#8211;Bill Clinton or Don Henley? What was O.J. Simpson&#8217;s second-worst decision? And why is Klosterman still haunted by some kid he knew for one week in 1985?     </p>
<p>                    Masterfully blending cultural analysis with self-interrogation and imaginative hypotheticals, I Wear the Black Hat delivers perceptive observations on the complexity of the antihero (seemingly the only kind of hero America still creates). As the Los Angeles Times notes: &#8220;By underscoring the contradictory, often knee-jerk ways we encounter the heroes and villains of our culture, Klosterman illustrates the passionate but incomplete computations that have come to define American culture&#8211;and maybe even American morality.&#8221; I Wear the Black Hat is a rare example of serious criticism that&#8217;s instantly accessible and really, really funny.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-wear-the-black-hat-grappling-with-villains-real-and-imagined-chuck-klosterman-abridged/">I Wear the Black Hat : Grappling with Villains (Real and Imagined) &#8211; Chuck Klosterman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Personality Brokers : The Strange History of Myers-Briggs and the Birth of Personality Testing &#8211; Merve Emre (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-personality-brokers-the-strange-history-of-myers-briggs-and-the-birth-of-personality-testing-merve-emre-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-personality-brokers-the-strange-history-of-myers-briggs-and-the-birth-of-personality-testing-merve-emre-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unprecedented history of the personality test conceived a century ago by a mother and her daughter&#8211;fiction writers with no formal training in psychology&#8211;and how it insinuated itself into our boardrooms, classrooms, and beyond. The basis for the HBO Max documentary, Persona The Myers-Briggs Type Indicator is the most popular personality test in the world. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personality-brokers-the-strange-history-of-myers-briggs-and-the-birth-of-personality-testing-merve-emre-abridged/">The Personality Brokers : The Strange History of Myers-Briggs and the Birth of Personality Testing &#8211; Merve Emre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unprecedented history of the personality test conceived a century ago by a mother and her daughter&#8211;fiction writers with no formal training in psychology&#8211;and how it insinuated itself into our boardrooms, classrooms, and beyond. The basis for the HBO Max documentary, Persona    </p>
<p>                    The Myers-Briggs Type Indicator is the most popular personality test in the world. It is used regularly by Fortune 500 companies, universities, hospitals, churches, and the military. Its language of personality types&#8211;extraversion and introversion, sensing and intuiting, thinking and feeling, judging and perceiving&#8211;has inspired television shows, online dating platforms, and Buzzfeed quizzes. Yet despite the test&#8217;s widespread adoption, experts in the field of psychometric testing, a $2 billion industry, have struggled to validate its results&#8211;no less account for its success. How did Myers-Briggs, a homegrown multiple choice questionnaire, infiltrate our workplaces, our relationships, our Internet, our lives?     </p>
<p>                    First conceived in the 1920s by the mother-daughter team of Katherine Briggs and Isabel Briggs Myers, a pair of devoted homemakers, novelists, and amateur psychoanalysts, Myers-Briggs was designed to bring the gospel of Carl Jung to the masses. But it would take on a life entirely its own, reaching from the smoke-filled boardrooms of mid-century New York to Berkeley, California, where it was administered to some of the twentieth century&#8217;s greatest creative minds. It would travel across the world to London, Zurich, Cape Town, Melbourne, and Tokyo, until it could be found just as easily in elementary schools, nunneries, and wellness retreats as in shadowy political consultancies and on social networks.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing from original reporting and never-before-published documents, The Personality Brokers takes a critical look at the personality indicator that became a cultural icon. Along the way it examines nothing less than the definition of the self&#8211;our attempts to grasp, categorize, and quantify our personalities. Surprising and absorbing, the book, like the test at its heart, considers the timeless question: What makes you, you?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personality-brokers-the-strange-history-of-myers-briggs-and-the-birth-of-personality-testing-merve-emre-abridged/">The Personality Brokers : The Strange History of Myers-Briggs and the Birth of Personality Testing &#8211; Merve Emre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>To Sell is Human : The Surprising Truth About Persuading, Convincing, and Influencing Others &#8211; Daniel H. Pink (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/to-sell-is-human-the-surprising-truth-about-persuading-convincing-and-influencing-others-daniel-h-pink-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/to-sell-is-human-the-surprising-truth-about-persuading-convincing-and-influencing-others-daniel-h-pink-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re all in Sales now Parents sell their kids on going to bed. Spouses sell their partners on mowing the lawn. We sell our bosses on giving us more money and more time off. And in astonishing numbers we go online to sell ourselves on Facebook, Twitter and online dating profiles. Relying on science, analysis [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-sell-is-human-the-surprising-truth-about-persuading-convincing-and-influencing-others-daniel-h-pink-abridged/">To Sell is Human : The Surprising Truth About Persuading, Convincing, and Influencing Others &#8211; Daniel H. Pink (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We&#8217;re all in Sales now    </p>
<p>                    Parents sell their kids on going to bed. Spouses sell their partners on mowing the lawn. We sell our bosses on giving us more money and more time off. And in astonishing numbers we go online to sell ourselves on Facebook, Twitter and online dating profiles.     </p>
<p>                    Relying on science, analysis and his trademark clarity of thought, Daniel Pink shows that sales isn&#8217;t what it used to be. Then he provides a set of tools, tips, and exercises for succeeding on each new terrain: six new ways to pitch your idea, three ways to understand another&#8217;s perspective, five frames that can make your message clearer, and much more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-sell-is-human-the-surprising-truth-about-persuading-convincing-and-influencing-others-daniel-h-pink-abridged/">To Sell is Human : The Surprising Truth About Persuading, Convincing, and Influencing Others &#8211; Daniel H. Pink (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Resilience : Hard-Won Wisdom for Living a Better Life &#8211; Eric Greitens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/resilience-hard-won-wisdom-for-living-a-better-life-eric-greitens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmetics, Hair & Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/resilience-hard-won-wisdom-for-living-a-better-life-eric-greitens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two years ago, Eric Greitens unexpectedly heard from a former SEAL comrade, a brother-in-arms he hadn&#8217;t seen in a decade. Zach Walker had been one of the toughest of the tough. But ever since he returned home from war to his young family in a small logging town, he&#8217;d been struggling. Without a sense of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/resilience-hard-won-wisdom-for-living-a-better-life-eric-greitens-abridged/">Resilience : Hard-Won Wisdom for Living a Better Life &#8211; Eric Greitens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two years ago, Eric Greitens unexpectedly heard from a former SEAL comrade, a brother-in-arms he hadn&#8217;t seen in a decade. Zach Walker had been one of the toughest of the tough. But ever since he returned home from war to his young family in a small logging town, he&#8217;d been struggling. Without a sense of purpose, plagued by PTSD, and masking his pain with heavy drinking, he needed help. Zach and Eric started writing and talking nearly every day, and Eric set down his thoughts on what it takes to build resilience in our lives. Eric&#8217;s letters drawing on both his own experience and wisdom from ancient and modern thinkers are now gathered and edited into a timeless handbook. They explain how we can build purpose, confront the pain in our lives, practice compassion, develop our vocations, find a mentor, create happiness, follow a role model, think about the story of our lives, and much more. Resilience grapples with real hardship. The lessons are deep, yet practical, and the advice leads to clear solutions. This is a profoundly hopeful book: We all face pain, difficulty, and doubt. But with resilience, we can lead vital, flourishing lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/resilience-hard-won-wisdom-for-living-a-better-life-eric-greitens-abridged/">Resilience : Hard-Won Wisdom for Living a Better Life &#8211; Eric Greitens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Blank Slate : The Modern Denial of Human Nature &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-blank-slate-the-modern-denial-of-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-blank-slate-the-modern-denial-of-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A passionate defence of the enduring power of human nature &#8230; both life-affirming and deeply satisfying&#8217; Daily Telegraph Recently many people have assumed that we are blank slates shaped by our environment. But this denies the heart of our being: human nature. Violence is not just a product of society; male and female minds are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blank-slate-the-modern-denial-of-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Blank Slate : The Modern Denial of Human Nature &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A passionate defence of the enduring power of human nature &#8230; both life-affirming and deeply satisfying&#8217; Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    Recently many people have assumed that we are blank slates shaped by our  environment. But this denies the heart of our being: human nature.  Violence is not just a product of society; male and female minds are  different; the genes we give our children shape them more than our  parenting practices. To acknowledge our innate abilities, Pinker shows,  is not to condone inequality, but to understand the very foundations of  humanity.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brilliant &#8230; enjoyable, informative, clear, humane&#8217;  New Scientist    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you think the nature-nurture debate has been resolved, you are wrong &#8230; this book is required reading&#8217;  Literary Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An original and vital contribution to science and also a rattling good read&#8217;  Matt Ridley, Sunday Telegraph     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Startling &#8230; This is a breath of air for a topic that has been politicized for too long&#8217;  Economist</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blank-slate-the-modern-denial-of-human-nature-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Blank Slate : The Modern Denial of Human Nature &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Introverted Leader : Building on Your Quiet Strength &#8211; Jennifer Kahnweiler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/introverted-leader-building-on-your-quiet-strength-jennifer-kahnweiler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/introverted-leader-building-on-your-quiet-strength-jennifer-kahnweiler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Succeeding in an Extroverted Workplace You don&#8217;t have be an extrovert&#8211;or pretend to be one&#8211;to get to the top! Jennifer Kahnweiler points to Mark Zuckerberg, Arianna Huffington, and Warren Buffett as prime examples of self-identified introverts who have done quite well for themselves. In this new, expanded edition of her pioneering book, she lays out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/introverted-leader-building-on-your-quiet-strength-jennifer-kahnweiler-abridged/">Introverted Leader : Building on Your Quiet Strength &#8211; Jennifer Kahnweiler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Succeeding in an Extroverted Workplace You don&#8217;t have be an extrovert&#8211;or pretend to be one&#8211;to get to the top! Jennifer Kahnweiler points to Mark Zuckerberg, Arianna Huffington, and Warren Buffett as prime examples of self-identified introverts who have done quite well for themselves. In this new, expanded edition of her pioneering book, she lays out a well-tested four-step strategy introverts can use to build on their quiet strength and make it a source of great power. The book includes fresh information on the unique challenges faced by introverted women, how leaders can shape a more introvert-friendly workplace, customized hiring and coaching strategies for introverts, and the positive correlation between introverted leadership and company performance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/introverted-leader-building-on-your-quiet-strength-jennifer-kahnweiler-abridged/">Introverted Leader : Building on Your Quiet Strength &#8211; Jennifer Kahnweiler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shoot for the Moon : How the Moon Landings Taught us the 8 Secrets of Success &#8211; Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/shoot-for-the-moon-how-the-moon-landings-taught-us-the-8-secrets-of-success-richard-wiseman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Astronomy & Space]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shoot-for-the-moon-how-the-moon-landings-taught-us-the-8-secrets-of-success-richard-wiseman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating new book examines the history of Nasa&#8217;s Apollo space missions&#8217; Daily Mail _______ Eight key lessons to revolutionise your life with the mindset that got man to the moon. 20th July 1969: Neil Armstrong becomes the first person to walk on the Moon. We all recognize this to be one of mankind&#8217;s greatest achievements. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shoot-for-the-moon-how-the-moon-landings-taught-us-the-8-secrets-of-success-richard-wiseman-abridged/">Shoot for the Moon : How the Moon Landings Taught us the 8 Secrets of Success &#8211; Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating new book examines the history of Nasa&#8217;s Apollo space missions&#8217; Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    _______    </p>
<p>                    Eight key lessons to revolutionise your life with the mindset that got man to the moon.    </p>
<p>                    20th  July 1969: Neil Armstrong becomes the first person to walk on the Moon.  We all recognize this to be one of mankind&#8217;s greatest achievements. Yet  what did it take to make John F. Kennedy&#8217;s dream a reality?    </p>
<p>                    In  this remarkable book, Professor Richard Wiseman presents a pioneering  study of the mindset that took humanity to the Moon, and shows how you  can harness and use it to achieve the extraordinary in your everyday  life.    </p>
<p>                    Combining personal interviews, mission archives and  cutting-edge psychology, Wiseman embarks on the ultimate voyage through  inner space. Along the way he identifies eight key principles that make  up the Apollo Mindset, including how pessimism is crucial to success,  and how fear and tragedy can be transformed into hope and optimism.     </p>
<p>                    You  will discover a series of practical techniques that you can use to  incorporate these winning principles into both your professional and  personal life.  Whether you want to start a business venture, change  careers, find your perfect partner, raise a loving family, get promoted,  gain a new qualification, escape the rat race, or pursue a lifelong  passion, these techniques will help you to reach your own Moon.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shoot-for-the-moon-how-the-moon-landings-taught-us-the-8-secrets-of-success-richard-wiseman-abridged/">Shoot for the Moon : How the Moon Landings Taught us the 8 Secrets of Success &#8211; Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
