<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Animal Husbandry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/animal-husbandry/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/animal-husbandry/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Animal Husbandry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/animal-husbandry/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agronomy & Crop Production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Husbandry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animals & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made the most courageous decision of her life: a commitment to change things.    </p>
<p>                     Driven by impulsive will and searing passion, Sonia left behind everything she knew and loved to search the planet for solutions to benefit animals, human health, and the environment. Over the course of living with farmers, hitchhiking with strangers, and risking her life, she developed surprising insights and solutions-both about the food industry and herself.    </p>
<p>                     Lively and heartfelt, Sonia takes readers on an unforgettable adventure from top-secret egg warehouses in Canada to dairy feedlots in the United States, from farm offices in Mexico to lush pastures in Belize, from flocks of village chickens in Indonesia to factory farms in Malaysia.    </p>
<p>                     Revelatory in scope, Project Animal Farm illuminates a hidden world that plays a part in all of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lesser Beasts : A Snout-to-Tail History of the Humble Pig &#8211; Mark Essig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Husbandry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Mammals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlike other barnyard animals, which pull plows, give eggs or milk, or grow wool, a pig produces only one thing: meat. Incredibly efficient at converting almost any organic matter into nourishing, delectable protein, swine are nothing short of a gastronomic godsend,yet their flesh is banned in many cultures, and the animals themselves are maligned as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/">Lesser Beasts : A Snout-to-Tail History of the Humble Pig &#8211; Mark Essig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlike other barnyard animals, which pull plows, give eggs or milk, or grow wool, a pig produces only one thing: meat. Incredibly efficient at converting almost any organic matter into nourishing, delectable protein, swine are nothing short of a gastronomic godsend,yet their flesh is banned in many cultures, and the animals themselves are maligned as filthy, lazy brutes.As historian Mark Essig reveals in  Lesser Beasts , swine have such a bad reputation for precisely the same reasons they are so valuable as a source of food: they are intelligent, self-sufficient, and omnivorous. What&#8217;s more, he argues, we ignore our historic partnership with these astonishing animals at our peril. Tracing the interplay of pig biology and human culture from Neolithic villages 10,000 years ago to modern industrial farms, Essig blends culinary and natural history to demonstrate the vast importance of the pig and the tragedy of its modern treatment at the hands of humans. Pork, Essig explains, has long been a staple of the human diet, prized in societies from Ancient Rome to dynastic China to the contemporary American South. Yet pigs&#8217; ability to track down and eat a wide range of substances (some of them distinctly unpalatable to humans) and convert them into edible meat has also led people throughout history to demonize the entire species as craven and unclean. Today&#8217;s unconscionable system of factory farming, Essig explains, is only the latest instance of humans taking pigs for granted, and the most recent evidence of how both pigs and people suffer when our symbiotic relationship falls out of balance.An expansive, illuminating history of one of our most vital yet unsung food animals,  Lesser Beasts  turns a spotlight on the humble creature that, perhaps more than any other, has been a mainstay of civilization since its very beginnings,whether we like it or not.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/">Lesser Beasts : A Snout-to-Tail History of the Humble Pig &#8211; Mark Essig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
