<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Children&#039;s Foreign Language Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/childrens-foreign-language-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/childrens-foreign-language-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Children&#039;s Foreign Language Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/childrens-foreign-language-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>the princess saves herself in this one &#8211; Amanda Lovelace, ladybookmad</title>
		<link>/the-princess-saves-herself-in-this-one-amanda-lovelace-ladybookmad/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Poetry & Poets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry By Individual Poets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-princess-saves-herself-in-this-one-amanda-lovelace-ladybookmad/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2016 Goodreads Choice Award, the princess saves herself in this one is a collection of poetry about resilience. It is about writing your own ending. From Amanda Lovelace, a poetry collection in four parts: the princess, the damsel, the queen, and you. The first three sections piece together the life of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-saves-herself-in-this-one-amanda-lovelace-ladybookmad/">the princess saves herself in this one &#8211; Amanda Lovelace, ladybookmad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2016 Goodreads Choice Award, the princess saves herself in this one is a collection of poetry about resilience. It is about writing your own ending.    </p>
<p>                     From Amanda Lovelace, a poetry collection in four parts: the princess, the damsel, the queen, and you. The first three sections piece together the life of the author while the final section serves as a note to the reader. This moving book explores love, loss, grief, healing, empowerment, and inspiration.    </p>
<p>                    the princess saves herself in this one is the first book in the &#8220;women are some kind of magic&#8221; series.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-saves-herself-in-this-one-amanda-lovelace-ladybookmad/">the princess saves herself in this one &#8211; Amanda Lovelace, ladybookmad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The President is Missing &#8211; President Bill Clinton</title>
		<link>/the-president-is-missing-president-bill-clinton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-president-is-missing-president-bill-clinton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>`The dream team delivers big time &#8230; Clinton&#8217;s insider secrets and Patterson&#8217;s storytelling genius make this the political thriller of the decade.&#8217; &#8211; Lee Child ________________________________ The President is Missing. The world is in shock. But the reason he&#8217;s missing is much worse than anyone can imagine. With details only a President could know, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-president-is-missing-president-bill-clinton/">The President is Missing &#8211; President Bill Clinton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>`The dream team delivers big time &#8230; Clinton&#8217;s insider secrets and Patterson&#8217;s storytelling genius make this the political thriller of the decade.&#8217; &#8211; Lee Child<br />
                    ________________________________</p>
<p>                    The President is Missing. The world is in shock.</p>
<p>                    But the reason he&#8217;s missing is much worse than anyone can imagine. </p>
<p>                    With details only a President could know, and the kind of suspense only James Patterson can deliver.<br />
                    ________________________________</p>
<p>                    `A bullet train of a thriller. The Day of the Jackal for the twenty-first century.&#8217; &#8211; A.J. Finn, author of The Woman in the Window</p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book moves like Air Force One. Big and fast.&#8217; &#8211; Michael Connelly, author of the Harry Bosch series</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The President Is Missing is a big, splashy juggernaut of a novel, combining thrills with a truly authentic look at the inner happenings in Washington. I read it in one gulp. You will too.&#8217; &#8211; Harlan Coben, #1 bestselling author of Don&#8217;t Let Go</p>
<p>                    `Yes, The President is Missing is fiction &#8211; it&#8217;s a thriller &#8211; but James Patterson and I have come up with three of the most frightening days in the history of the presidency. And it could really happen&#8230; These days, the seemingly impossible can happen. And it happens so fast. I believe that readers will not soon forget President Jonathan Duncan and his story.&#8217; &#8211; Bill Clinton</p>
<p>                    `Needless to say, we had some great conversations about the presidency, what life in Washington is really like, and about the state of America and the rest of the world.&#8217; &#8211; James Patterson</p>
<p>                    `I felt like I was right along with the characters for the shocking twists and turns you&#8217;ll never guess are coming. Patterson and Clinton have created a truly unique character in their `missing&#8217; President. The President is Missing puts the listener inside the White House and inside the mind of a President grappling with extraordinary circumstances.&#8217; &#8211; Dennis Quaid on the audiobook of The President is Missing</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Relentless in its plotting and honest in its examination of issues that strike close to our hearts.&#8217; &#8211; Jeffery Deaver</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A first-rate collaboration from a couple of real pros! Engrossing from page one.&#8217; &#8211; David Baldacci</p>
<p>                    &#8216;vivid, engrossing &#8211; and authentically frightening.&#8217; &#8211; Carl Hiaasen, author of Razor Girl</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The President is Missing is more than a thriller &#8211; it&#8217;s a skeleton key that lets you inside the head of a U.S. president.&#8217; &#8211; Brad Meltzer, author of The Escape Artist</p>
<p>                    &#8216;From the pens of two American icons comes a political thriller that rocks&#8230; a helluva story.&#8217; &#8211; Nelson DeMille, author of The Cuban Affair</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The President Is Missing is heart-pounding, gripping, terrifying&#8230; a genuinely masterful thriller. My knuckles are still white!&#8217; &#8211; Louise Penny, #1 bestselling author of Glass Houses</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Marry the political savvy of Bill Clinton with the craftsmanship of James Patterson and you get a fabulously entertaining thriller that is meticulous in its portrayal of Washington politics, gripping in its pacing, and harrowing in its depiction of the perils of cyberwarfare.&#8217; &#8211; Ron Chernow, #1 bestselling and Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Alexander Hamilton and Grant</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Compelling from page one. A fantastic read!&#8217; &#8211; Mary Higgins Clark, #1 bestselling author of I&#8217;ve Got My Eyes on You</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-president-is-missing-president-bill-clinton/">The President is Missing &#8211; President Bill Clinton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mother Tongue : The Story of the English Language &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: History & General Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lexicography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than 300 million people in the world speak English and the rest, it sometimes seems, try to&#8230;&#8217; Only Bill Bryson could make a book about the English language so entertaining. With his boundless enthusiasm and restless eye for the absurd, this is his astonishing tour of English. From its mongrel origins to its status [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/">Mother Tongue : The Story of the English Language &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than 300 million people in the world speak English and the rest, it sometimes seems, try to&#8230;&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Only Bill Bryson could make a book about the English language so entertaining. With his boundless enthusiasm and restless eye for the absurd, this is his astonishing tour of English. From its mongrel origins to its status as the world&#8217;s most-spoken tongue; its apparent simplicity to its deceptive complexity; its vibrant swearing to its uncertain spelling and pronunciation, Bryson covers all this as well as the many curious eccentricities that make it as maddening to learn as it is flexible to use.     </p>
<p>                    Bill Bryson&#8217;s classic Mother Tongue is a highly readable and hilarious tale of how English came to be the world&#8217;s language.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mother-tongue-the-story-of-the-english-language-bill-bryson-abridged/">Mother Tongue : The Story of the English Language &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language Teaching & Learning (other Than ELT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language Teaching & Learning Material & Coursework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; For anyone who wants to learn a foreign language, this is the method that will finally make the words stick. &#8220;A brilliant and thoroughly modern guide to learning new languages.&#8221;&#8211;Gary Marcus, cognitive psychologist and author of the New York Times bestseller Guitar Zero At thirty years old, Gabriel Wyner speaks six languages [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/">Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; For anyone who wants to learn a foreign language, this is the method that will finally make the words stick.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A brilliant and thoroughly modern guide to learning new languages.&#8221;&#8211;Gary Marcus, cognitive psychologist and author of the New York Times bestseller Guitar Zero     </p>
<p>                    At thirty years old, Gabriel Wyner speaks six languages fluently. He didn&#8217;t learn them in school&#8211;who does? Rather, he learned them in the past few years, working on his own and practicing on the subway, using simple techniques and free online resources&#8211;and here he wants to show others what he&#8217;s discovered.     </p>
<p>                    Starting with pronunciation, you&#8217;ll learn how to rewire your ears and turn foreign sounds into familiar sounds. You&#8217;ll retrain your tongue to produce those sounds accurately, using tricks from opera singers and actors. Next, you&#8217;ll begin to tackle words, and connect sounds and spellings to imagery rather than translations, which will enable you to think in a foreign language. And with the help of sophisticated spaced-repetition techniques, you&#8217;ll be able to memorize hundreds of words a month in minutes every day.     </p>
<p>                    This is brain hacking at its most exciting, taking what we know about neuroscience and linguistics and using it to create the most efficient and enjoyable way to learn a foreign language in the spare minutes of your day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/">Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
