<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Central Government Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/central-government/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/central-government/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Central Government Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/central-government/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fear : Trump in the White House &#8211; Bob Woodward</title>
		<link>/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER THE OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR THE INSIDE STORY ON PRESIDENT TRUMP, AS ONLY BOB WOODWARD CAN TELL IT. &#8216;Fear is a meticulously researched account of a White House and a president in financial, legal and personal disorder&#8230;essential reading&#8230;&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;I think you&#8217;ve always been fair.&#8217; &#8211; President [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/">Fear : Trump in the White House &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER<br />
                    THE OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR</p>
<p>                     THE INSIDE STORY ON PRESIDENT TRUMP, AS ONLY BOB WOODWARD CAN TELL IT.</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fear is a meticulously researched account of a White House and a president in financial, legal and personal disorder&#8230;essential reading&#8230;&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I think you&#8217;ve always been fair.&#8217; &#8211; President Donald J. Trump, in a call to Bob Woodward, August 14, 2018</p>
<p>                     &#8216;The sheer weight of anecdotes depicts a man with no empathy and a pathological capacity for lying.&#8217; &#8211; The Financial Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fuelling his narrative is an astonishing cast of rogues, ideologues, self-made millionaires and men in uniform who have spent the past two years in and out of Trump&#8217;s administration.&#8217; &#8211; The Sunday Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Woodward&#8217;s meticulous account of office intrigues, the president&#8217;s men don&#8217;t seem to be trembling with fright.  What they mostly feel is contempt for Trump or pity for his ignorance and the &#8220;teenage logic&#8221; of his obsessively vented grievances.&#8217; &#8211; The Observer</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Horribly fascinating. Strongly recommended. If you can bear it.&#8217; Richard Dawkins</p>
<p>                     &#8216;To me the standout message from the book&#8230;is that the president is a bit clueless, a bit vain, a bit dangerous even; but his people are utterly at sea&#8230;&#8217; &#8211; Justin Webb, The Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;He is the master and I&#8217;d trust him over politicians of either party any day of the week.&#8217; -Peter Baker, New York Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;His work has been factually unassailable . . . In an age of &#8216;alternative facts&#8217; and corrosive tweets about &#8216;fake news,&#8217; Woodward is truth&#8217;s gold standard.&#8217; &#8211; Jill Abramson, The Washington Post</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fear depicts a White House awash in dysfunction, where the Lord of the Flies is the closest thing to an owner&#8217;s manual.&#8217; The Guardian</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I wonder how many journalists have arrived in Washington over the years dreaming of becoming the next Bob Woodward . . . Though his books are often sensational, he is the opposite of sensationalist. He&#8217;s diligent, rigorous, fastidious about the facts, and studiously ethical. There&#8217;s something almost monastic about his method . . . He&#8217;s Washington&#8217;s chronicler in chief.&#8217; &#8211;  Nick Bryant, BBC</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I&#8217;ve been on the receiving end of a Bob Woodward book. There were quotes in it I didn&#8217;t like. But never once-never-did I think Woodward made it up. Anonymous sources have looser lips and may take liberties. But Woodward always plays is straight. Someone told it to him.&#8217; &#8211; Ari Fleisher, White House Press Secretary for George W. Bush</p>
<p>                     With authoritative reporting honed through eight presidencies from Nixon to Obama, author Bob Woodward reveals in unprecedented detail the harrowing life inside President Donald Trump&#8217;s White House and precisely how he makes decisions on major foreign and domestic policies. Woodward draws from hundreds of hours of interviews with firsthand sources, meeting notes, personal diaries, files and documents. The focus is on the explosive debates and the decision-making in the Oval Office, the Situation Room, Air Force One and the White House residence.</p>
<p>                    Fear is the most intimate portrait of a sitting president ever published during the president&#8217;s first years in office.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/">Fear : Trump in the White House &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It Was All a Lie : How the Republican Party Became Donald Trump &#8211; Stuart Stevens</title>
		<link>/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER In his bare-knuckles account, Stevens confesses to the reader that the entire apparatus of his Republican Party is built on a pack of lies&#8230; This reckoning inspired Stevens to publish this blistering, tell-all history&#8230; Although this book will be a hard read for any committed conservatives, they would do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/">It Was All a Lie : How the Republican Party Became Donald Trump &#8211; Stuart Stevens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER </p>
<p>                    In his bare-knuckles account, Stevens confesses to the reader that the entire apparatus of his Republican Party is built on a pack of lies&#8230; This reckoning inspired Stevens to publish this blistering, tell-all history&#8230; Although this book will be a hard read for any committed conservatives, they would do well to ponder it.<br />
                    &#8211;Julian E. Zelizer, The New York Times </p>
<p>                    From the most successful Republican political operative of his generation, a searing, unflinching, and deeply personal exposé of how his party became what it is today </p>
<p>                    Stuart Stevens spent decades electing Republicans at every level, from presidents to senators to local officials. He knows the GOP as intimately as anyone in America, and in this new book he offers a devastating portrait of a party that has lost its moral and political compass. </p>
<p>                    This is not a book about how Donald J. Trump hijacked the Republican Party and changed it into something else. Stevens shows how Trump is in fact the natural outcome of five decades of hypocrisy and self-delusion, dating all the way back to the civil rights legislation of the early 1960s. Stevens shows how racism has always lurked in the modern GOP&#8217;s DNA, from Goldwater&#8217;s opposition to desegregation to Ronald Reagan&#8217;s welfare queens and states&#8217; rights rhetoric. He gives an insider&#8217;s account of the rank hypocrisy of the party&#8217;s claims to embody family values, and shows how the party&#8217;s vaunted commitment to fiscal responsibility has been a charade since the 1980s. When a party stands for nothing, he argues, it is only natural that it will be taken over by the loudest and angriest voices in the room. </p>
<p>                    It Was All a Lie is not just an indictment of the Republican Party, but a candid and often lacerating mea culpa. Stevens is not asking for pity or forgiveness; he is simply telling us what he has seen firsthand. He helped to create the modern party that kneels before a morally bankrupt con man and now he wants nothing more than to see what it has become burned to the ground.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/">It Was All a Lie : How the Republican Party Became Donald Trump &#8211; Stuart Stevens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rage &#8211; Bob Woodward</title>
		<link>/rage-bob-woodward/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rage-bob-woodward/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BOB WOODWARD&#8217;S NEW BOOK, RAGE, IS AN UNPRECEDENTED AND INTIMATE TOUR DE FORCE OF NEW REPORTING ON THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY FACING A GLOBAL PANDEMIC, ECONOMIC DISASTER AND RACIAL UNREST. Woodward, the No 1 international bestselling author of Fear: Trump in the White House, has uncovered the precise moment the president was warned that the Covid-19 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rage-bob-woodward/">Rage &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BOB WOODWARD&#8217;S NEW BOOK, RAGE, IS AN UNPRECEDENTED AND INTIMATE TOUR DE FORCE OF NEW REPORTING ON THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY FACING A GLOBAL PANDEMIC, ECONOMIC DISASTER AND RACIAL UNREST.</p>
<p>                     Woodward, the No 1 international bestselling author of Fear: Trump in the White House, has uncovered the precise moment the president was warned that the Covid-19 epidemic would be the biggest national security threat to his presidency. In dramatic detail, Woodward takes readers into the Oval Office as Trump&#8217;s head pops up when he is told in January 2020 that the pandemic could reach the scale of the 1918 Spanish Flu that killed 675,000 Americans.</p>
<p>                     In 17 on-the-record interviews with Woodward over seven volatile months &#8211; an utterly vivid window into Trump&#8217;s mind &#8211; the president provides a self-portrait that is part denial and part combative interchange mixed with surprising moments of doubt as he glimpses the perils in the presidency and what he calls the &#8216;dynamite behind every door&#8217;. At key decision points, Rage shows how Trump&#8217;s responses to the crises of 2020 were rooted in the instincts, habits and style he developed during his first three years as president.</p>
<p>                     Revisiting the earliest days of the Trump presidency, Rage reveals how Secretary of Defense James Mattis, Secretary of State Rex Tillerson and Director of National Intelligence Dan Coats struggled to keep the country safe as the president dismantled any semblance of collegial national security decision making. Rage draws from hundreds of hours of interviews with first-hand witnesses as well as participants&#8217; notes, emails, diaries, calendars and confidential documents.</p>
<p>                     Woodward obtained 25 never-seen personal letters exchanged between Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, who describes the bond between the two leaders as out of a &#8216;fantasy film&#8217;. Trump insists to Woodward he will triumph over Covid-19 and the economic calamity. &#8216;Don&#8217;t worry about it, Bob. Okay?&#8217; Trump told the author in July. &#8216;Don&#8217;t worry about it. We&#8217;ll get to do another book. You&#8217;ll find I was right.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rage-bob-woodward/">Rage &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Revolt : Inside the Populist Coalition Reshaping American Politics &#8211; Salena Zito</title>
		<link>/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A CNN political analyst and a Republican strategist reframe the discussion of the &#8220;Trump voter&#8221; to answer the question, What&#8217;s next? NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY FOREIGN AFFAIRS &#8211; &#8220;Unlike most retellings of the 2016 election, The Great Revolt provides a cohesive, non-wild-eyed argument about where the Republican Party could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/">The Great Revolt : Inside the Populist Coalition Reshaping American Politics &#8211; Salena Zito</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A CNN political analyst and a Republican strategist reframe the discussion of the &#8220;Trump voter&#8221; to answer the question, What&#8217;s next?</p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY FOREIGN AFFAIRS &#8211; &#8220;Unlike most retellings of the 2016 election, The Great Revolt provides a cohesive, non-wild-eyed argument about where the Republican Party could be headed.&#8221;&#8211;The Atlantic </p>
<p>                    Political experts were wrong about the 2016 election and they continue to blow it, predicting the coming demise of the president without pausing to consider the durability of the winds that swept him into office. </p>
<p>                    Salena Zito and Brad Todd have traveled over 27,000 miles of country roads to interview more than three hundred Trump voters in ten swing counties. What emerges is a portrait of a group of citizens who span job descriptions, income brackets, education levels, and party allegiances, united by their desire to be part of a movement larger than themselves. They want to put pragmatism before ideology and localism before globalism, and demand the respect they deserve from Washington. </p>
<p>                    The 2016 election signaled a realignment in American politics that will outlast any one president. Zito and Todd reframe the discussion of the &#8220;Trump voter&#8221; to answer the question, What&#8217;s next?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/">The Great Revolt : Inside the Populist Coalition Reshaping American Politics &#8211; Salena Zito</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</title>
		<link>/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. </p>
<p>                    The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level official. With almost daily access to the President, John Bolton has produced a precise rendering of his days in and around the Oval Office. What Bolton saw astonished him: a President for whom getting reelected was the only thing that mattered, even if it meant endangering or weakening the nation. &#8220;I am hard-pressed to identify any significant Trump decision during my tenure that wasn&#8217;t driven by reelection calculations,&#8221; he writes. In fact, he argues that the House committed impeachment malpractice by keeping their prosecution focused narrowly on Ukraine when Trump&#8217;s Ukraine-like transgressions existed across the full range of his foreign policy-and Bolton documents exactly what those were, and attempts by him and others in the Administration to raise alarms about them.</p>
<p>                    He shows a President addicted to chaos, who embraced our enemies and spurned our friends, and was deeply suspicious of his own government. In Bolton&#8217;s telling, all this helped put Trump on the bizarre road to impeachment. &#8220;The differences between this presidency and previous ones I had served were stunning,&#8221; writes Bolton, who worked for Reagan, Bush 41, and Bush 43. He discovered a President who thought foreign policy is like closing a real estate deal-about personal relationships, made-for-TV showmanship, and advancing his own interests. As a result, the US lost an opportunity to confront its deepening threats, and in cases like China, Russia, Iran, and North Korea ended up in a more vulnerable place. </p>
<p>                    Bolton&#8217;s account starts with his long march to the West Wing as Trump and others woo him for the National Security job. The minute he lands, he has to deal with Syria&#8217;s chemical attack on the city of Douma, and the crises after that never stop. As he writes in the opening pages, &#8220;If you don&#8217;t like turmoil, uncertainty, and risk-all the while being constantly overwhelmed with information, decisions to be made, and sheer amount of work-and enlivened by international and domestic personality and ego conflicts beyond description, try something else.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    The turmoil, conflicts, and egos are all there-from the upheaval in Venezuela, to the erratic and manipulative moves of North Korea&#8217;s Kim Jong Un, to the showdowns at the G7 summits, the calculated warmongering by Iran, the crazy plan to bring the Taliban to Camp David, and the placating of an authoritarian China that ultimately exposed the world to its lethal lies. But this seasoned public servant also has a great eye for the Washington inside game, and his story is full of wit and wry humor about how he saw it played.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Liars, Leakers, and Liberals : The Case Against the Anti-Trump Conspiracy &#8211; Judge Jeanine Pirro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/liars-leakers-and-liberals-the-case-against-the-anti-trump-conspiracy-judge-jeanine-pirro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/liars-leakers-and-liberals-the-case-against-the-anti-trump-conspiracy-judge-jeanine-pirro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At this point in American history, we are the victims of a liberal sabotage of the presidency unlike anything we&#8217;ve ever witnessed. Nevertheless President Trump continues to fight every day to keep his promise to Make America Great Again. Today that bold idea has already led to a conservative judge on the Supreme Court, tax [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/liars-leakers-and-liberals-the-case-against-the-anti-trump-conspiracy-judge-jeanine-pirro-abridged/">Liars, Leakers, and Liberals : The Case Against the Anti-Trump Conspiracy &#8211; Judge Jeanine Pirro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At this point in American history, we are the victims of a liberal sabotage of the presidency unlike anything we&#8217;ve ever witnessed.  Nevertheless President Trump continues to fight every day to keep his promise to Make America Great Again. Today that bold idea has already led to a conservative judge on the Supreme Court, tax reform, and deregulation that has unleashed an economy stronger than anyone could have imagined.    </p>
<p>                    But there are dark forces that seek to obstruct and undermine the president and reverse the results of the 2016 presidential election.  They are part of a wide-ranging conspiracy that would seem incredible if it weren&#8217;t being perpetrated openly.  Driven by ambition, blinded by greed, and bound by a common goal &#8212; to unseat the 45th President of the United States &#8212; this cabal is determined to maintain its wrongful hold on national political power.    </p>
<p>                    Fox News host Jeanine Pirro uncovers the elements of this conspiracy, including:<br />
                    &#8220;Fake news&#8221; propaganda,Law enforcement corruption at the highest levels,National security leaks by the intelligence community,Bureaucratic resistance to lawful and constitutional executive orders issued by the duly elected president,Crooked deals with foreign governments by U.S. officials sworn to defend our Constitution.<br />
                    It&#8217;s about time the American public knows the truth about the plot to bring down the Trump presidency. By the time you&#8217;ve finished this book, you&#8217;ll agree with Judge Pirro that the only way to stop these hoodlums is to Take Them Out in Cuffs!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/liars-leakers-and-liberals-the-case-against-the-anti-trump-conspiracy-judge-jeanine-pirro-abridged/">Liars, Leakers, and Liberals : The Case Against the Anti-Trump Conspiracy &#8211; Judge Jeanine Pirro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From a preeminent presidential historian comes a &#8220;superb and important&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) saga of America&#8217;s wartime chief executives &#8220;Fascinating and heartbreaking . . . timely . . . Beschloss&#8217;s broad scope lets you draw important crosscutting lessons about presidential leadership.&#8221;&#8211;Bill Gates Widely acclaimed and ten years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/">Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From a preeminent presidential historian comes a &#8220;superb and important&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) saga of America&#8217;s wartime chief executives    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Fascinating and heartbreaking . . . timely . . . Beschloss&#8217;s broad scope lets you draw important crosscutting lessons about presidential leadership.&#8221;&#8211;Bill Gates     </p>
<p>                    Widely acclaimed and ten years in the making, Michael Beschloss&#8217;s Presidents of War is an intimate and irresistibly readable chronicle of the Chief Executives who took the United States into conflict and mobilized it for victory. From the War of 1812 to Vietnam, we see these leaders considering the difficult decision to send hundreds of thousands of Americans to their deaths; struggling with Congress, the courts, the press, and antiwar protesters; seeking comfort from their spouses and friends; and dropping to their knees in prayer. Through Beschloss&#8217;s interviews with surviving participants and findings in original letters and once-classified national security documents, we come to understand how these Presidents were able to withstand the pressures of war&#8211;or were broken by them.     </p>
<p>                    Presidents of War combines this sense of immediacy with the overarching context of two centuries of American history, traveling from the time of our Founders, who tried to constrain presidential power, to our modern day, when a single leader has the potential to launch nuclear weapons that can destroy much of the human race.    </p>
<p>                    Praise for Presidents of War     </p>
<p>                    A marvelous narrative. . . . As Beschloss explains, the greatest wartime presidents successfully leaven military action with moral concerns. . . . Beschloss&#8217;s writing is clean and concise, and he admirably draws upon new documents. Some of the more titillating tidbits in the book are in the footnotes. . . . There are fascinating nuggets on virtually every page of Presidents of War. It is a superb and important book, superbly rendered.&#8221;&#8211;Jay Winik, The New York Times Book Review     </p>
<p>                    Sparkle and bite. . . . Valuable and engrossing study of how our chief executives have discharged the most significant of all their duties. . . . Excellent. . . . A fluent narrative that covers two centuries of national conflict.&#8221; &#8211;Richard Snow,  The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/">Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH     </p>
<p>                    The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, and Obama&#8217;s America.      </p>
<p>                     What is the big lie of the Democratic Party? That conservatives&#8211;and President Donald Trump in particular&#8211;are fascists. Nazis, even. In a typical comment, MSNBC host Rachel Maddow says the Trump era is reminiscent of what it was like when Hitler first became chancellor.     </p>
<p>                     But in fact, this audacious lie is a complete inversion of the truth. Yes, there is a fascist threat in America&#8211;but that threat is from the Left and the Democratic Party. The Democratic left has an ideology virtually identical with fascism and routinely borrows tactics of intimidation and political terror from the Nazi Brownshirts.     </p>
<p>                     To cover up their insidious fascist agenda, Democrats loudly accuse President Trump and other Republicans of being Nazis&#8211;an obvious lie, considering the GOP has been fighting the Democrats over slavery, genocide, racism and fascism from the beginning.     </p>
<p>                     Now, finally, Dinesh D&#8217;Souza explodes the Left&#8217;s big lie. He expertly exonerates President Trump and his supporters, then uncovers the Democratic Left&#8217;s long, cozy relationship with Nazism: how the racist and genocidal acts of early Democrats inspired Adolf Hitler&#8217;s campaign of death; how fascist philosophers influenced the great 20th century lions of the American Left; and how today&#8217;s anti-free speech, anti-capitalist, anti-religious liberty, pro-violence Democratic Party is a frightening simulacrum of the Nazi Party.     </p>
<p>                     Hitler coined the term the big lie to describe a lie that the great masses of the people will fall for precisely because of how bold and monstrous the lie is. In The Big Lie, D&#8217;Souza shows that the Democratic Left&#8217;s orchestrated campaign to paint President Trump and conservatives as Nazis to cover up its own fascism is, in fact, the biggest lie of all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gatekeepers : How the White House Chiefs of Staff Define Every Presidency &#8211; Chris Whipple (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gatekeepers-how-the-white-house-chiefs-of-staff-define-every-presidency-chris-whipple-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gatekeepers-how-the-white-house-chiefs-of-staff-define-every-presidency-chris-whipple-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now with a chapter on the chaos in the Trump administration, the New York Times bestselling, behind-the-scenes look at the White House Chiefs of Staff, whose actions&#8211;and inactions&#8211;have defined the course of our country. What do Dick Cheney and Rahm Emanuel have in common? Aside from polarizing personalities, both served as chief of staff to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gatekeepers-how-the-white-house-chiefs-of-staff-define-every-presidency-chris-whipple-abridged/">The Gatekeepers : How the White House Chiefs of Staff Define Every Presidency &#8211; Chris Whipple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now with a chapter on the chaos in the Trump administration, the New York Times bestselling, behind-the-scenes look at the White House Chiefs of Staff, whose actions&#8211;and inactions&#8211;have defined the course of our country.     </p>
<p>                     What do Dick Cheney and Rahm Emanuel have in common? Aside from polarizing personalities, both served as chief of staff to the president of the United States&#8211;as did Donald Rumsfeld, Leon Panetta, and a relative handful of others. The chiefs of staff, often referred to as the gatekeepers, wield tremendous power in Washington and beyond; they decide who is allowed to see the president, negotiate with Congress to push POTUS&#8217;s agenda, and&#8211;most crucially&#8211;enjoy unparalleled access to the leader of the free world. Each chief can make or break an administration, and each president reveals himself by the chief he picks.     </p>
<p>                     Through extensive, intimate interviews with eighteen living chiefs (including Reince Priebus) and two former presidents, award-winning journalist and producer Chris Whipple pulls back the curtain on this unique fraternity. In doing so, he revises our understanding of presidential history, showing us how James Baker&#8217;s expert managing of the White House, the press, and Capitol Hill paved the way for the Reagan Revolution&#8211;and, conversely, how Watergate, the Iraq War, and even the bungled Obamacare rollout might have been prevented by a more effective chief.     </p>
<p>                     Filled with shrewd analysis and never-before-reported details, The Gatekeepers offers an essential portrait of the toughest job in Washington.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gatekeepers-how-the-white-house-chiefs-of-staff-define-every-presidency-chris-whipple-abridged/">The Gatekeepers : How the White House Chiefs of Staff Define Every Presidency &#8211; Chris Whipple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and Wikileaks to disseminate information that could affect the 2016 election.     </p>
<p>                    The Russians were wildly successful and the great break-in of 2016 was no &#8220;third rate burglary.&#8221; It was far more sophisticated and sinister &#8212; a brazen act of political espionage designed to interfere with American democracy, and at the end of the day, Trump, the candidate with business ties to Russia, won. And millions of Americans were left wondering, what the hell happened?    </p>
<p>                    This story of high-tech spying and multiple political feuds will be told against the backdrop of Donald Trump and his strange relationship with Putin, and his inner circle of advisers with profitable ties to Russia, most notably Michael Flynn and Paul Manafort.    </p>
<p>                    The Russian Connection will chronicle and examine all these bizarre events and relationships, explain the stakes, and seek to answer one of the biggest questions in American politics: How and why did a foreign government infiltrate the country&#8217;s political process and implant its tentacles in Washington?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Triggered : How the Left Thrives on Hate and Wants to Silence Us &#8211; Donald Trump, Jr. (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/triggered-how-the-left-thrives-on-hate-and-wants-to-silence-us-donald-trump-jr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Censorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/triggered-how-the-left-thrives-on-hate-and-wants-to-silence-us-donald-trump-jr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Triggered, Donald Trump, Jr. will expose all the tricks that the left uses to smear conservatives and push them out of the public square, from online &#8220;shadow banning&#8221; to fake accusations of &#8220;hate speech.&#8221; No topic is spared from political correctness. This is the book that the leftist elites don&#8217;t want you to read! [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/triggered-how-the-left-thrives-on-hate-and-wants-to-silence-us-donald-trump-jr-abridged/">Triggered : How the Left Thrives on Hate and Wants to Silence Us &#8211; Donald Trump, Jr. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Triggered, Donald Trump, Jr. will expose all the tricks that the left uses to smear conservatives and push them out of the public square, from online &#8220;shadow banning&#8221; to fake accusations of &#8220;hate speech.&#8221; No topic is spared from political correctness. This is the book that the leftist elites don&#8217;t want you to read!     </p>
<p>                    Trump, Jr. will write about the importance of fighting back and standing up for what you believe in. From his childhood summers in Communist Czechoslovakia that began his political thought process, to working on construction sites with his father, to the major achievements of President Trump&#8217;s administration, Donald Trump, Jr. spares no details and delivers a book that focuses on success and perseverance, and proves offense is the best defense.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/triggered-how-the-left-thrives-on-hate-and-wants-to-silence-us-donald-trump-jr-abridged/">Triggered : How the Left Thrives on Hate and Wants to Silence Us &#8211; Donald Trump, Jr. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years and now the longest-serving independent in U.S. political history. An extensive afterword by The Nation&#8217;s National Affairs correspondent John Nichols continues the story with Sanders&#8217;s entrance into the Senate, the drama of the 2016 Democratic Primary, his ongoing resistance to Trump, and the thrilling launch of his 2020 bid for the White House. A new foreword by Nina Turner, former president of Our Revolution and co-chair of the Sanders for President campaign, provides a rare glimpse of Bernie as a person. Outsider in the White House tells the story of a passionate and principled political life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestselling &#8220;deep dive into the terms of eight former presidents is chock-full of political hijinks-and deja vu&#8221; (Vanity Fair) and provides a fascinating look at the men who came to the office without being elected to it, showing how each affected the nation and world. The strength and prestige of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/">Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestselling &#8220;deep dive into the terms of eight former presidents is chock-full of political hijinks-and deja vu&#8221; (Vanity Fair) and provides a fascinating look at the men who came to the office without being elected to it, showing how each affected the nation and world.    </p>
<p>                    The strength and prestige of the American presidency has waxed and waned since George Washington. Eight men have succeeded to the presidency when the incumbent died in office. In one way or another they vastly changed our history. Only Theodore Roosevelt would have been elected in his own right. Only TR, Truman, Coolidge, and LBJ were re-elected.    </p>
<p>                    John Tyler succeeded William Henry Harrison who died 30 days into his term. He was kicked out of his party and became the first president threatened with impeachment. Millard Fillmore succeeded esteemed General Zachary Taylor. He immediately sacked the entire cabinet and delayed an inevitable Civil War by standing with Henry Clay&#8217;s compromise of 1850. Andrew Johnson, who succeeded our greatest president, sided with remnants of the Confederacy in Reconstruction. Chester Arthur, the embodiment of the spoils system, was so reviled as James Garfield&#8217;s successor that he had to defend himself against plotting Garfield&#8217;s assassination; but he reformed the civil service. Theodore Roosevelt broke up the trusts. Calvin Coolidge silently cooled down the Harding scandals and preserved the White House for the Republican Herbert Hoover and the Great Depression. Harry Truman surprised everybody when he succeeded the great FDR and proved an able and accomplished president. Lyndon B. Johnson was named to deliver Texas electorally. He led the nation forward on Civil Rights but failed on Vietnam.    </p>
<p>                    Accidental Presidents shows that &#8220;history unfolds in death as well as in life&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal) and adds immeasurably to our understanding of the power and limits of the American presidency in critical times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/">Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The WikiLeaks Files : The World According to US Empire &#8211; Wikileaks, Introduction by Julian Assange (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wikileaks-files-the-world-according-to-us-empire-wikileaks-introduction-by-julian-assange-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wikileaks-files-the-world-according-to-us-empire-wikileaks-introduction-by-julian-assange-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When WikiLeaks first came to prominence in 2010, releasing millions of top secret State Department cables, the world saw for the first time what the US really thought about national leaders, friendly dictators, and supposed allies. It also discovered the dark truths of national policies, human rights violations, covert operations, and cover-ups done in your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wikileaks-files-the-world-according-to-us-empire-wikileaks-introduction-by-julian-assange-abridged/">The WikiLeaks Files : The World According to US Empire &#8211; Wikileaks, Introduction by Julian Assange (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When WikiLeaks first came to prominence in 2010, releasing millions of top secret State Department cables, the world saw for the first time what the US really thought about national leaders, friendly dictators, and supposed allies. It also discovered the dark truths of national policies, human rights violations, covert operations, and cover-ups done in your name. The WikiLeaks Files is the first volume that uses experts to collate and analyze the most important cables and show their historic importance. An essential book for anyone who is interested in America&#8217;s role in the world and the history of the twenty-first century. Regional expert contributors include Tim Shorrock, Richard Heydarian, Russ Wellen, Conn Hallinan, Michael Busch, Robert Prince, Stephen Zunes, Peter Certo, Francis Nesbitt, Phyllis Bennis, and Gareth Porter.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wikileaks-files-the-world-according-to-us-empire-wikileaks-introduction-by-julian-assange-abridged/">The WikiLeaks Files : The World According to US Empire &#8211; Wikileaks, Introduction by Julian Assange (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States. &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times    </p>
<p>                    The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about social justice. As she rose to prominence as a political leader, her experiences would become her guiding light as she grappled with an array of complex issues and learned to bring a voice to the voiceless.    </p>
<p>                    Now, in The Truths We Hold, Harris reckons with the big challenges we face together. Drawing on the hard-won wisdom and insight from her own career and the work of those who have most inspired her, she communicates a vision of shared struggle, shared purpose, and shared values as we confront the great work of our day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Personal integrity shines through every page&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A World In Disarray : American Foreign Policy and the Crisis of the Old Order &#8211; Richard Haass (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A valuable primer on foreign policy: a primer that concerned citizens of all political persuasions&#8211;not to mention the president and his advisers&#8211;could benefit from reading.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times An examination of a world increasingly defined by disorder and a United States unable to shape the world in its image, from the president of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/">A World In Disarray : American Foreign Policy and the Crisis of the Old Order &#8211; Richard Haass (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A valuable primer on foreign policy: a primer that concerned citizens of all political persuasions&#8211;not to mention the president and his advisers&#8211;could benefit from reading.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times An examination of a world increasingly defined by disorder and a United States unable to shape the world in its image, from the president of the Council on Foreign Relations Things fall apart; the center cannot hold. The rules, policies, and institutions that have guided the world since World War II have largely run their course. Respect for sovereignty alone cannot uphold order in an age defined by global challenges from terrorism and the spread of nuclear weapons to climate change and cyberspace. Meanwhile, great power rivalry is returning. Weak states pose problems just as confounding as strong ones. The United States remains the world&#8217;s strongest country, but American foreign policy has at times made matters worse, both by what the U.S. has done and by what it has failed to do. The Middle East is in chaos, Asia is threatened by China&#8217;s rise and a reckless North Korea, and Europe, for decades the world&#8217;s most stable region, is now anything but. As Richard Haass explains, the election of Donald Trump and the unexpected vote for &#8220;Brexit&#8221; signals that many in modern democracies reject important aspects of globalization, including borders open to trade and immigrants.  In A World in Disarray, Haass argues for an updated global operating system&#8211;call it world order 2.0&#8211;that reflects the reality that power is widely distributed and that borders count for less. One critical element of this adjustment will be adopting a new approach to sovereignty, one that embraces its obligations and responsibilities as well as its rights and protections. Haass also details how the U.S. should act towards China and Russia, as well as in Asia, Europe, and the Middle East. He suggests, too, what the country should do to address its dysfunctional politics, mounting debt, and the lack of agreement on the nature of its relationship with the world.  A World in Disarray is a wise examination, one rich in history, of the current world, along with how we got here and what needs doing. Haass shows that the world cannot have stability or prosperity without the United States, but that the United States cannot be a force for global stability and prosperity without its politicians and citizens reaching a new understanding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/">A World In Disarray : American Foreign Policy and the Crisis of the Old Order &#8211; Richard Haass (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public. Unfreedom of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public.     </p>
<p>                    Unfreedom of the Press is not just another book about the press. In &#8220;Levin&#8217;s finest work&#8221; (Breitbart), he shows how those entrusted with news reporting today are destroying freedom of the press from within-not through actions of government officials, but with its own abandonment of reportorial integrity and objective journalism.    </p>
<p>                    With the depth of historical background for which his books are renowned, Levin takes you on a journey through the early American patriot press, which proudly promoted the principles set forth in the Declaration of Independence and the Constitution. This is followed by the early decades of the Republic during which newspapers around the young country were open and transparent about their fierce allegiance to one political party or another.    </p>
<p>                    It was only at the start of the Progressive Era and the 20th century that the supposed &#8220;objectivity of the press&#8221; first surfaced, leaving us where we are today: with a partisan party-press overwhelmingly aligned with a political ideology but hypocritically engaged in a massive untruth as to its real nature.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal: to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221; major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal:  to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221;  major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair way.     </p>
<p>                    Breitbart burst on to the national media scene thanks to his coverage of  the ACORN controversy, where a local ACORN community group leader was videotaped giving business advice to a &#8220;gentleman&#8221; who ran a prostitution ring. When the major news media at first tried to bury the story, Breitbart used his extraordinary marketing savvy to make sure the story got full national attention.     </p>
<p>                    More recently, Congressman Anthony Weiner took on Breitbart, claiming that scurrilous photos of Weiner were being sent on the internet by the conservative right. In a new chapter in RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart details how &#8220;Weinergate&#8221; was entirely the personal fault of Congressman Weiner, and how Weiner derailed his own promising career by trying to implicate Breitbart and conservative journalists.    </p>
<p>                    In short, RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart talks about the key issues that Americans face, how he has aligned himself with the Tea Party, and how one needs to deal with the liberal news world head on. Along the way, he details his early years, working with Matt Drudge, the Huffington Post, and so on, and how Breitbart developed his unique style of launching key websites to help get the word out to conservatives all over.     </p>
<p>                    A rollicking and controversial read, Breitbart will certainly raise your blood pressure, one way or another.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Threat : How the FBI Protects America in the Age of Terror and Trump &#8211; Andrew G. McCabe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-threat-how-the-fbi-protects-america-in-the-age-of-terror-and-trump-andrew-g-mccabe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Police & Security Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-threat-how-the-fbi-protects-america-in-the-age-of-terror-and-trump-andrew-g-mccabe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller #1 Washington Post Bestseller #1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller On March 16, 2018, just twenty-six hours before his scheduled retirement from the organization he had served with distinction for more than two decades, Andrew G. McCabe was fired from his position as deputy director of the FBI. President Donald Trump [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-threat-how-the-fbi-protects-america-in-the-age-of-terror-and-trump-andrew-g-mccabe-abridged/">The Threat : How the FBI Protects America in the Age of Terror and Trump &#8211; Andrew G. McCabe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller<br />
                    #1 Washington Post Bestseller<br />
                    #1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    On March 16, 2018, just twenty-six hours before his scheduled retirement from the organization he had served with distinction for more than two decades, Andrew G. McCabe was fired from his position as deputy director of the FBI. President Donald Trump celebrated on Twitter: &#8220;Andrew McCabe FIRED, a great day for the hard working men and women of the FBI &#8211; A great day for Democracy.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    In The Threat: How the FBI Protects America in the Age of Terror and Trump, Andrew G. McCabe offers a dramatic and candid account of his career, and an impassioned defense of the FBI&#8217;s agents, and of the institution&#8217;s integrity and independence in protecting America and upholding our Constitution.    </p>
<p>                    McCabe started as a street agent in the FBI&#8217;s New York field office, serving under director Louis Freeh. He became an expert in two kinds of investigations that are critical to American national security: Russian organized crime&#8211;which is inextricably linked to the Russian state&#8211;and terrorism. Under Director Robert Mueller, McCabe led the investigations of major attacks on American soil, including the Boston Marathon bombing, a plot to bomb the New York subways, and several narrowly averted bombings of aircraft. And under James Comey, McCabe was deeply involved in the controversial investigations of the Benghazi attack, the Clinton Foundation&#8217;s activities, and Hillary Clinton&#8217;s use of a private email server when she was secretary of state.    </p>
<p>                    The Threat recounts in compelling detail the time between Donald Trump&#8217;s November 2016 election and McCabe&#8217;s firing, set against a page-turning narrative spanning two decades when the FBI&#8217;s mission shifted to a new goal: preventing terrorist attacks on Americans. But as McCabe shows, right now the greatest threat to the United States comes from within, as President Trump and his administration ignore the law, attack democratic institutions, degrade human rights, and undermine the U.S. Constitution that protects every citizen.     </p>
<p>                    Important, revealing, and powerfully argued, The Threat tells the true story of what the FBI is, how it works, and why it will endure as an institution of integrity that protects America.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-threat-how-the-fbi-protects-america-in-the-age-of-terror-and-trump-andrew-g-mccabe-abridged/">The Threat : How the FBI Protects America in the Age of Terror and Trump &#8211; Andrew G. McCabe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Were Eight Years in Power : An American Tragedy &#8211; Ta-Nehisi Coates (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-were-eight-years-in-power-an-american-tragedy-ta-nehisi-coates-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Administration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-were-eight-years-in-power-an-american-tragedy-ta-nehisi-coates-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this &#8220;urgently relevant&#8221;* collection featuring the landmark essay &#8220;The Case for Reparations,&#8221; the National Book Award-winning author of Between the World and Me &#8220;reflects on race, Barack Obama&#8217;s presidency and its jarring aftermath&#8221;*&#8211;including the election of Donald Trump. New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Finalist for the PEN/Jean Stein Book Award, the Los Angeles Times [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-were-eight-years-in-power-an-american-tragedy-ta-nehisi-coates-abridged/">We Were Eight Years in Power : An American Tragedy &#8211; Ta-Nehisi Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this &#8220;urgently relevant&#8221;* collection featuring the landmark essay &#8220;The Case for Reparations,&#8221; the National Book Award-winning author of Between the World and Me &#8220;reflects on race, Barack Obama&#8217;s presidency and its jarring aftermath&#8221;*&#8211;including the election of Donald Trump.      </p>
<p>                    New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Finalist for the PEN/Jean Stein Book Award, the Los Angeles Times Book Prize, and the Dayton Literary Peace Prize     </p>
<p>                     Named One of the Best Books of the Year by The New York Times &#8211; USA Today &#8211; Time &#8211; Los Angeles Times &#8211; San Francisco Chronicle &#8211; Essence &#8211; O: The Oprah Magazine &#8211; The Week &#8211; Kirkus Reviews     </p>
<p>                     *Kirkus Reviews (starred review)    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;We were eight years in power&#8221; was the lament of Reconstruction-era black politicians as the American experiment in multiracial democracy ended with the return of white supremacist rule in the South. In this sweeping collection of new and selected essays, Ta-Nehisi Coates explores the tragic echoes of that history in our own time: the unprecedented election of a black president followed by a vicious backlash that fueled the election of the man Coates argues is America&#8217;s &#8220;first white president.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     But the story of these present-day eight years is not just about presidential politics. This book also examines the new voices, ideas, and movements for justice that emerged over this period&#8211;and the effects of the persistent, haunting shadow of our nation&#8217;s old and unreconciled history. Coates powerfully examines the events of the Obama era from his intimate and revealing perspective&#8211;the point of view of a young writer who begins the journey in an unemployment office in Harlem and ends it in the Oval Office, interviewing a president.     </p>
<p>                     We Were Eight Years in Power features Coates&#8217;s iconic essays first published in The Atlantic,  including &#8220;Fear of a Black President,&#8221; &#8220;The Case for Reparations,&#8221; and &#8220;The Black Family in the Age of Mass Incarceration,&#8221; along with eight fresh essays that revisit each year of the Obama administration through Coates&#8217;s own experiences, observations, and intellectual development, capped by a bracingly original assessment of the election that fully illuminated the tragedy of the Obama era. We Were Eight Years in Power is a vital account of modern America, from one of the definitive voices of this historic moment.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-were-eight-years-in-power-an-american-tragedy-ta-nehisi-coates-abridged/">We Were Eight Years in Power : An American Tragedy &#8211; Ta-Nehisi Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Impeachment : An American History &#8211; Jon Meacham, Timothy Naftali, Peter Baker, Jeffrey A. Engel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/impeachment-an-american-history-jon-meacham-timothy-naftali-peter-baker-jeffrey-a-engel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitutional & Administrative Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/impeachment-an-american-history-jon-meacham-timothy-naftali-peter-baker-jeffrey-a-engel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Four experts on the American presidency examine the three times impeachment has been invoked&#8211;against Andrew Johnson, Richard Nixon, and Bill Clinton&#8211;and explain what it means today. Impeachment is a double-edged sword. Though it was designed to check tyrants, Thomas Jefferson also called impeachment &#8220;the most formidable weapon for the purpose of a dominant faction that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/impeachment-an-american-history-jon-meacham-timothy-naftali-peter-baker-jeffrey-a-engel-abridged/">Impeachment : An American History &#8211; Jon Meacham, Timothy Naftali, Peter Baker, Jeffrey A. Engel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Four experts on the American presidency examine the three times impeachment has been invoked&#8211;against Andrew Johnson, Richard Nixon, and Bill Clinton&#8211;and explain what it means today. Impeachment is a double-edged sword. Though it was designed to check tyrants, Thomas Jefferson also called impeachment &#8220;the most formidable weapon for the purpose of a dominant faction that was ever contrived.&#8221; On the one hand, it nullifies the will of voters, the basic foundation of all representative democracies. On the other, its absence from the Constitution would leave the country vulnerable to despotic leadership. It is rarely used, and with good reason.  Only three times has a president&#8217;s conduct led to such political disarray as to warrant his potential removal from office, transforming a political crisis into a constitutional one. None has yet succeeded. Andrew Johnson was impeached in 1868 for failing to kowtow to congressional leaders&#8211;and, in a large sense, for failing to be Abraham Lincoln&#8211;yet survived his Senate trial. Richard Nixon resigned in August 1974 after the House Judiciary Committee approved three articles of impeachment against him for lying, obstructing justice, and employing his executive power for personal and political gain. Bill Clinton had an affair with a White House intern, but in 1999 he faced trial in the Senate less for that prurient act than for lying under oath about it.  In the first book to consider these three presidents alone&#8211;and the one thing they have in common&#8211;Jeffrey A. Engel, Jon Meacham, Timothy Naftali, and Peter Baker explain that the basis and process of impeachment is more political than legal. The Constitution states that the president &#8220;shall be removed from Office on Impeachment for, and Conviction of, Treason, Bribery, or other high Crimes and Misdemeanors,&#8221; leaving room for historical precedent and the temperament of the time to weigh heavily on each case. This book reveals the complicated motives behind each impeachment&#8211;never entirely limited to the question of a president&#8217;s guilt&#8211;and the risks to all sides. Each case depended on factors beyond the president&#8217;s behavior: his relationship with Congress, the polarization of the moment, and the power and resilience of the office itself. This is a realist view of impeachment that looks to history for clues about its potential use in the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/impeachment-an-american-history-jon-meacham-timothy-naftali-peter-baker-jeffrey-a-engel-abridged/">Impeachment : An American History &#8211; Jon Meacham, Timothy Naftali, Peter Baker, Jeffrey A. Engel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! Washington insiders operate by a proven credo: When a Peter Schweizer book drops, duck and brace for impact. For over a decade, the work of six-time New York Times bestselling investigative reporter Peter Schweizer has sent shockwaves through the political universe. Clinton Cash revealed the Clintons&#8217; international money flow, exposed global [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/">Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!    </p>
<p>                    Washington insiders operate by a proven credo: When a Peter Schweizer book drops, duck and brace for impact.    </p>
<p>                    For over a decade, the work of six-time New York Times bestselling investigative reporter Peter Schweizer has sent shockwaves through the political universe.    </p>
<p>                    Clinton Cash revealed the Clintons&#8217; international money flow, exposed global corruption, and sparked an FBI investigation. Secret Empires exposed bipartisan corruption and launched congressional investigations. And Throw Them All Out and Extortion prompted passage of the STOCK Act. Indeed, Schweizer&#8217;s &#8220;follow the money&#8221; bombshell revelations have been featured on the front pages of the New York Times and the Wall Street Journal, and regularly appear on national news programs, including 60 Minutes.    </p>
<p>                    Now Schweizer and his team of seasoned investigators turn their focus to the nation&#8217;s top progressives-politicians who strive to acquire more government power to achieve their political ends.    </p>
<p>                    Can they be trusted with more power?    </p>
<p>                    In Profiles in Corruption, Schweizer offers a deep-dive investigation into the private finances, and secrets deals of some of America&#8217;s top political leaders. And, as usual, he doesn&#8217;t disappoint, with never-before-reported revelations that uncover corruption and abuse of power-all backed up by a mountain of corporate documents and legal filings from around the globe. Learn about how they are making sweetheart deals, generating side income, bending the law to their own benefits, using legislation to advance their own interests, and much more.    </p>
<p>                    Profiles in Corruption contains tomorrow&#8217;s headlines.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/">Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this highly anticipated follow-up to his blockbuster New York Times bestseller The Amateur, former New York Times Magazine editor-in-chief Edward Klein delves into the rocky relationship between the Obamas and the Clintons. An old-school reporter with incredible insider contacts, Klein reveals just how deep the rivalry between the Obamas and the Clintons runs, with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/">Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this highly anticipated follow-up to his blockbuster New York Times bestseller The Amateur, former New York Times Magazine editor-in-chief Edward Klein delves into the rocky relationship between the Obamas and the Clintons. An old-school reporter with incredible insider contacts, Klein reveals just how deep the rivalry between the Obamas and the Clintons runs, with details on closed-door meetings buttressed by hundreds of interviews. Blood Feud is a stunning expose of the animosity, jealousy, and competition between America&#8217;s two most powerful political couples.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/">Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Opinion & Polls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans. &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate. You have nowhere to go. You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221; &#8211;From the Introduction In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate.<br />
                     You have nowhere to go.<br />
                     You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;From the Introduction     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools: How a Selfish Ruling Class is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution, Tucker Carlson tells the truth about the new American elites, a group whose power and wealth has grown beyond imagination even as the rest of the country has withered. The people who run America now barely interact with it. They fly on their own planes, ski on their own mountains, watch sporting events far from the stands in sky boxes. They have total contempt for you.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;They view America the way a private equity firm sizes up an aging conglomerate,&#8221; Carlson writes, &#8220;as something outdated they can profit from. When it fails, they&#8217;re gone.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools,  Tucker Carlson offers a blistering critique of our new overlords. Traditional liberals are gone, he writes. The patchouli-scented hand-wringers who worried about whales and defended free speech have been replaced by globalists who hide their hard-edged economic agenda behind the smokescreen of identity politics. They&#8217;ll outsource your job while lecturing you about transgender bathrooms. Left and right, Carlson says, are no longer meaningful categories in America. &#8220;The rift is between those who benefit from the status quo, and those who don&#8217;t.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     Our leaders are fools, Carlson concludes, &#8220;unaware that they are captains of a sinking ship.&#8221; But in the signature and witty style that viewers of Tucker Carlson Tonight have come to enjoy, his book answers the all-important question: How do we put the country back on course?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Trial of Henry Kissinger &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-trial-of-henry-kissinger-christopher-hitchens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Postwar 20th Century History, From C 1945 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[War Crimes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-trial-of-henry-kissinger-christopher-hitchens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Hitchens goes straight for the jugular in The Trial of Henry Kissinger. Under his fearsome gaze, the former Secretary of State and National Security Advisor is accused of being a war criminal whose reckless actions and heinous disregard for international law have led to torture, kidnapping, and murder. This book is a polemical masterpiece [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-trial-of-henry-kissinger-christopher-hitchens-abridged/">The Trial of Henry Kissinger &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Hitchens goes straight for the jugular in The Trial of Henry Kissinger. Under his fearsome gaze, the former Secretary of State and National Security Advisor is accused of being a war criminal whose reckless actions and heinous disregard for international law have led to torture, kidnapping, and murder.    </p>
<p>                    This book is a polemical masterpiece by a man who, for forty years, was the Angloshpere&#8217;s preeminent man of letters. In The Trial of Henry Kissinger, Hitchens&#8217; verve, style and firebrand wit are on show at the height of their potency.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A good liar must have a good memory: Kissinger is a stupendous liar with a remarkable memory.&#8217; Christopher Hitchens</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-trial-of-henry-kissinger-christopher-hitchens-abridged/">The Trial of Henry Kissinger &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nationalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism. Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections. In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism.    </p>
<p>                    Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections.    </p>
<p>                    In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist and commentator Rick Wilson delivers &#8220;a searingly honest, bitingly funny, comprehensive answer to the question we find ourselves asking most mornings: &#8216;What the hell is going on?&#8217; (Chicago Tribune). The Guardian hails Everything Trump Touches Dies, saying it gives, &#8220;more unvarnished truths about Donald Trump than anyone else in the American political establishment has offered. Wilson never holds back.&#8221; Rick mercilessly exposes the damage Trump has done to the country, to the Republican Party, and to the conservative movement that has abandoned its principles for the worst President in American history.    </p>
<p>                    Wilson unblinkingly dismantles Trump&#8217;s deceptions and the illusions to which his supporters cling, shedding light on the guilty parties who empower and enable Trump in Washington and in the media. He calls out the race-war dead-enders who hitched a ride with Trump, the alt-right basement dwellers who worship him, and the social conservatives who looked the other way. Publishers Weekly calls it, &#8220;a scathing, profane, unflinching, and laugh-out-loud funny rebuke of Donald Trump and his presidency.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    No left-winger, Wilson is a lifelong conservative who delivers his withering critique of Trump from the right. A leader of the Never Trump movement, he warned from the start that Trump would destroy the lives and reputations of everyone in his orbit, and Everything Trump Touches Dies is a deft chronicle the tragicomic political story of our time. From the early campaign days through the shock of election night, to the inconceivable train-wreck of Trump&#8217;s first year. Rick Wilson provides not only an insightful analysis of the Trump administration, but also an optimistic path forward for the GOP, the conservative movement, and the country.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hilarious, smartly written, and usually spot-on&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews), Everything Trump Touches Dies is perfect for those on either side of the aisle who need a dose of unvarnished reality, a good laugh, a strong cocktail, and a return to sanity in American politics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING * &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING *     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly written haymaker&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly three years of reporting, hundreds of hours of interviews and more than two hundred sources, including some of the most senior members of the administration, friends and first-hand witnesses who have never spoken before, Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig take us inside some of the most controversial moments of Trump&#8217;s presidency. They peer deeply into Trump&#8217;s White House &#8211; at the aides pressured to lie to the public, the lawyers scrambling to clear up norm-breaking disasters, and the staffers whose careers have been reduced to ashes &#8211; to paint an unparalleled group portrait of an administration driven by self-preservation and paranoia.     </p>
<p>                    Rucker and Leonnig reveal Trump at his most unvarnished, showing the unhinged decision-making and incompetence that has floored officials and stunned foreign leaders. They portray unscripted calls with Vladimir Putin, steak dinners with Kim Jong-un, and calls with Theresa May so hostile that they left her aides shaken. They also take a hard look at Robert Mueller, Trump&#8217;s greatest antagonist to date, and how his investigation slowly unravelled an administration whose universal value is loyalty &#8211; not to country, but to the president himself.    </p>
<p>                    Grippingly told, A Very Stable Genius is a behind-the-scenes account of Trump&#8217;s vainglorious pursuit of power in his first term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hard Choices : A Memoir &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>HILLARY RODHAM CLINTON&#8217;S INSIDE ACCOUNT OF THE CRISES, CHOICES AND CHALLENGES SHE FACED DURING HER FOUR YEARS AS AMERICA&#8217;S 67THSECRETARY OF STATE, AND HOW THOSE EXPERIENCES DRIVE HER VIEW OF THE FUTURE, INCLUDING A NEW EPILOGUE. &#8216;All of us face hard choices in our lives,&#8217; Hillary Rodham Clinton writes at the start of this personal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">Hard Choices : A Memoir &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HILLARY RODHAM CLINTON&#8217;S INSIDE ACCOUNT OF THE CRISES, CHOICES AND CHALLENGES SHE FACED DURING HER FOUR YEARS AS AMERICA&#8217;S 67THSECRETARY OF STATE, AND HOW THOSE EXPERIENCES DRIVE HER VIEW OF THE FUTURE, INCLUDING A NEW EPILOGUE.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;All of us face hard choices in our lives,&#8217; Hillary Rodham Clinton writes at the start of this personal chronicle of years at the centre of world events. &#8216;Life is about making such choices. Our choices and how we handle them shape the people we become.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                     In the aftermath of her 2008 presidential run, she expected to return to representing New York in the Unites States Senate. To her surprise, her formal rival for the Democratic Party nomination, newly elected President Barack Obama, asked her to serve in his administration as Secretary of State. This memoir is the story of the four extraordinary and historic years that followed, and the hard choices that she and her colleagues confronted.     </p>
<p>                     Secretary Clinton and President Obama had to decide how to repair fractured alliances, wind down two wars and address a global financial crisis. They faced a rising competitor in China, growing threats from Iran and North Korea, and revolutions across the Middle East. Along the way, they grappled with some of the toughest dilemmas of US foreign policy, especially the decision to send Americans into harm&#8217;s way, from Afghanistan to Libya to the hunt for Osama bin Laden.     </p>
<p>                    By the end of her tenure, Secretary Clinton had visited 112 countries, travelled nearly one million miles and gained a truly global perspective on many of the major trends reshaping the landscape of the twenty-first century, from economic inequality to climate change to revolutions in energy, communications and health. Drawing on conversations with numerous leaders and experts, Secretary Clinton offers her views on what it will take for the United States to compete and thrive in an interdependent world. She makes a passionate case for human rights and the full participation in society of girls, youth and LGBT people. An astute eyewitness to decades of social change, she distinguishes the trendlines from the headlines and describes the progress occurring throughout the world, day after day.     </p>
<p>                     Secretary Clinton&#8217;s descriptions of diplomatic conversations at the highest levels offer readers a masterclass in international relations, as does her analysis of how we can best use &#8216;smart power&#8217; to deliver security and prosperity in a rapidly changing world &#8211; one in which America remains the indispensable nation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">Hard Choices : A Memoir &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
