<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Interdisciplinary Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/interdisciplinary-studies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/interdisciplinary-studies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Interdisciplinary Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/interdisciplinary-studies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Rebel Ideas : The Power of Thinking Differently &#8211; Matthew Syed, Matthew Syed Consulting Ltd (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rebel-ideas-the-power-of-thinking-differently-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rebel-ideas-the-power-of-thinking-differently-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I like listening to people who know things that I don&#8217;t,&#8217; Gareth Southgate told me. &#8216;That&#8217;s how you learn.&#8217; Former Olympian and best-selling author Matthew Syed is one of the advisors Gareth Southgate engaged from outside football in order to find new ways of working as a team. In Rebel Ideas, discover how Southgate &#8216;the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rebel-ideas-the-power-of-thinking-differently-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/">Rebel Ideas : The Power of Thinking Differently &#8211; Matthew Syed, Matthew Syed Consulting Ltd (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I like listening to people who know things that I don&#8217;t,&#8217; Gareth Southgate told me. &#8216;That&#8217;s how you learn.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    Former Olympian and best-selling author Matthew Syed is one of the advisors Gareth Southgate engaged from outside football in order to find new ways of working as a team. In Rebel Ideas, discover how Southgate &#8216;the man with the plan&#8217; replaced 50 years of hurt with two major tournament semi-finals in three years.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    Matthew Syed&#8217;s phenomenal bestseller will change the way you think about success &#8211; for ever.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Syed is a superb storyteller. I couldn&#8217;t put the book down, and I learned so much. A stunning achievement&#8217; Tim Harford, author of The Undercover Economist    </p>
<p>                    Rebel Ideas examines the power of &#8216;cognitive diversity&#8217; &#8211; the ability to think differently about the world around us.    </p>
<p>                    It explains how to harness our unique perspectives, pool our collective intelligence and tackle the greatest challenges of our age &#8211; from climate change to terrorism. It draws on a dazzling range of case studies, including the catastrophic failings of the CIA before 9/11, a fatal communication breakdown on top of Mount Everest and a moving tale of deradicalisation in America&#8217;s Deep South.    </p>
<p>                    Rebel Ideas will strengthen any team or organisation, but has dozens of individual applications, too: from the art of reinvention to the remarkable benefits of personalised nutrition. It shows us how to become more creative, how to collaborate in a world becoming more interconnected, and how to break free of echo chambers that surround us all.    </p>
<p>                    Now updated with a new chapter on the Covid-19 crisis    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A gripping read, full of intelligence and perspective&#8217; James Dyson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Will change the way you think about success and even about life&#8217; Judy Murray    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master of the genre&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rebel-ideas-the-power-of-thinking-differently-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/">Rebel Ideas : The Power of Thinking Differently &#8211; Matthew Syed, Matthew Syed Consulting Ltd (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Distracted Mind : Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World &#8211; Adam Gazzaley, Larry D. Rosen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why our brains aren&#8217;t built for media multitasking, and how we can learn to live with technology in a more balanced way. Brilliant and practical, just what we need in these techno-human times.&#8211;Jack Kornfield, author of The Wise Heart Most of us will freely admit that we are obsessed with our devices. We pride ourselves [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/">The Distracted Mind : Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World &#8211; Adam Gazzaley, Larry D. Rosen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why our brains aren&#8217;t built for media multitasking, and how we can learn to live with technology in a more balanced way.    </p>
<p>                    Brilliant and practical, just what we need in these techno-human times.&#8211;Jack Kornfield, author of The Wise Heart    </p>
<p>                    Most of us will freely admit that we are obsessed with our devices. We pride ourselves on our ability to multitask&#8211;read work email, reply to a text, check Facebook, watch a video clip. Talk on the phone, send a text, drive a car. Enjoy family dinner with a glowing smartphone next to our plates. We can do it all, 24/7! Never mind the errors in the email, the near-miss on the road, and the unheard conversation at the table. In The Distracted Mind, Adam Gazzaley and Larry Rosen&#8211;a neuroscientist and a psychologist&#8211;explain why our brains aren&#8217;t built for multitasking, and suggest better ways to live in a high-tech world without giving up our modern technology.    </p>
<p>                    The authors explain that our brains are limited in their ability to pay attention. We don&#8217;t really multitask but rather switch rapidly between tasks. Distractions and interruptions, often technology-related&#8211;referred to by the authors as &#8220;interference&#8221;&#8211;collide with our goal-setting abilities. We want to finish this paper/spreadsheet/sentence, but our phone signals an incoming message and we drop everything. Even without an alert, we decide that we &#8220;must&#8221; check in on social media immediately.    </p>
<p>                    Gazzaley and Rosen offer practical strategies, backed by science, to fight distraction. We can change our brains with meditation, video games, and physical exercise; we can change our behavior by planning our accessibility and recognizing our anxiety about being out of touch even briefly. They don&#8217;t suggest that we give up our devices, but that we use them in a more balanced way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/">The Distracted Mind : Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World &#8211; Adam Gazzaley, Larry D. Rosen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is Wall Street bad for Main Street America? A well-told exploration of why our current economy is leaving too many behind. &#8211;The New York Times In looking at the forces that shaped the 2016 presidential election, one thing is clear: much of the population believes that our economic system is rigged to enrich the privileged [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/">Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is Wall Street bad for Main Street America?     </p>
<p>                    A well-told exploration of why our current economy is leaving too many behind. &#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                     In looking at the forces that shaped the 2016 presidential election, one thing is clear: much of the population believes that our economic system is rigged to enrich the privileged elites at the expense of hard-working Americans. This is a belief held equally on both sides of political spectrum, and it seems only to be gaining momentum.     </p>
<p>                    A key reason, says Financial Times columnist Rana Foroohar, is the fact that Wall Street is no longer supporting Main Street businesses that create the jobs for the middle and working class. She draws on in-depth reporting and interviews at the highest rungs of business and government to show how the &#8220;financialization of America&#8221;&#8211;the phenomenon by which finance and its way of thinking have come to dominate every corner of business&#8211;is threatening the American Dream.     </p>
<p>                     Now updated with new material explaining how our corrupted financial sys­tem propelled Donald Trump to power, Makers and Takers explores the confluence of forces that has led American businesses to favor balance-sheet engineering over the actual kind, greed over growth, and short-term profits over putting people to work. From the cozy relationship between Wall Street and Washington, to a tax code designed to benefit wealthy individuals and corporations, to forty years of bad policy decisions, she shows why so many Americans have lost trust in the sys­tem, and why it matters urgently to us all.     </p>
<p>                     Through colorful stories of both &#8220;Takers,&#8221; those stifling job creation while lining their own pockets, and &#8220;Makers,&#8221; businesses serving the real economy, Foroohar shows how we can reverse these trends for a better path forward.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/">Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Addiction & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life    </p>
<p>                    We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can we kick bad habits &#8211; and stick with it?    </p>
<p>                    According to psychologist and behaviour researcher Dr Sean Young, the answer is to stop trying to change the person, and instead change the process. In Stick With It, Dr Young draws on his own research and that of other leading experts to explain how the mind often interferes with breaking bad habits, and how we can outsmart it, increasing the likelihood of lasting change by 200%.     </p>
<p>                    Packed with practical exercises and real-life case studies, Stick With It shows that it is possible to control spending, stick to a diet, exercise regularly and overcome problem behaviours &#8211; forever.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Scientifically grounded and personally implementable. It&#8217;s a winner&#8217; &#8211; Robert Cialdini, author of Influence and Pre-Suasion    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A must-read for anyone who&#8217;s been unable to keep a New Year&#8217;s resolution or failed at making a lasting change in any other area of their life or work. &#8211; Jonah Berger, author of Contagious    </p>
<p>                    Dr Sean Young is one of the world&#8217;s leading experts in the field of habit-forming. He is an acclaiedpsychologist and the founder and Executive Director of the UCLA Center for Digital Behavior. His research involves the study of cutting-edge ways of using social media and mobile technologies to change and predict human behaviour.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
