<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Global Warming Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/global-warming/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/global-warming/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Global Warming Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/global-warming/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Falter : Has the Human Game Begun to Play Itself Out? &#8211; Bill McKibben (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/falter-has-the-human-game-begun-to-play-itself-out-bill-mckibben-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist, Conservationist & Green Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/falter-has-the-human-game-begun-to-play-itself-out-bill-mckibben-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is Bill McKibben at his glorious best. Wise and warning, with everything on the line. Do not miss it&#8217; Naomi Klein, author of This Changes Everything and The Shock Doctrine Thirty years ago, Bill McKibben wrote The End of Nature, the first book that alerted us to the dangers of climate change. Falter is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/falter-has-the-human-game-begun-to-play-itself-out-bill-mckibben-abridged/">Falter : Has the Human Game Begun to Play Itself Out? &#8211; Bill McKibben (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is Bill McKibben at his glorious best. Wise and warning, with everything on the line. Do not miss it&#8217; Naomi Klein, author of This Changes Everything and The Shock Doctrine    </p>
<p>                    Thirty years ago, Bill McKibben wrote The End of Nature, the first book that alerted us to the dangers of climate change. Falter is a new call to arms, to save not only our planet but our very souls as well.    </p>
<p>                    Over tens of thousands of years, through the harnessing of nature, the development of civilization, and the application of new technologies, human beings have created the world we live in. But as McKibben points out in this provocative and sobering look at the world today, we are fast approaching a tipping point, putting into question the viability of humanity itself.    </p>
<p>                    McKibben argues that we have failed to recognize how individual actions often operated against our collective interest, and as a result we now face three daunting challenges &#8211; to adjust to a new life on a broken planet, to fight the hyper-individualism that now animates government and business; and to reverse the ways that technology is bleaching out the variety of human existence. He asks if we still retain the tools and social capital to fight these larger forces &#8211; and if we are willing to make the effort.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/falter-has-the-human-game-begun-to-play-itself-out-bill-mckibben-abridged/">Falter : Has the Human Game Begun to Play Itself Out? &#8211; Bill McKibben (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Plant Ecology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Comfortably Unaware, Dr. Richard Oppenlander tackles the crucial issue of global depletion as it relates to food choice. We should all be committed, he tells us, to understanding the reality and consequences of our diet, the footprint it makes on our environment, and seek food products that are in the best interest of all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/">Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Comfortably Unaware, Dr. Richard Oppenlander tackles the crucial issue of global depletion as it relates to food choice. We should all be committed, he tells us, to understanding the reality and consequences of our diet, the footprint it makes on our environment, and seek food products that are in the best interest of all living things. His forthright information and stark mental images are often disturbing-and that&#8217;s how it should be. As the guardians of Planet Earth, we need to be shaken out of our complacency, to stop being comfortably unaware, and to understand the measures we must take to ensure the health and well-being of our planet-and of ourselves. Oppenlander</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/">Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No Logo &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-logo-naomi-klein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumerism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-logo-naomi-klein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No Logo&#8217; was a book that defined a generation when it was first published in 1999. For its 10th anniversay Naomi Klein has updated this iconic book. By the time you&#8217;re twenty-one, you&#8217;ll have seen or heard a million advertisements. But you won&#8217;t be happier for it. This is a book about that much-maligned, much-misunderstood [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-logo-naomi-klein-abridged/">No Logo &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No Logo&#8217; was a book that defined a generation when it was first published in 1999. For its 10th anniversay Naomi Klein has updated this iconic book.    </p>
<p>                              By the time you&#8217;re twenty-one, you&#8217;ll have seen or heard a million advertisements. But you won&#8217;t be happier for it.    </p>
<p>                              This is a book about that much-maligned, much-misunderstood generation coming up behind the slackers, who are being intelligent and active about the world in which they find themselves. It is a world in which all that is &#8216;alternative&#8217; is sold, where any innovation or subversion is immediately adopted by un-radical, faceless corporations. But, gradually, tentatively, a new generation is beginning to fight consumerism with its own best weapons; and it is the first skirmishes in this war that this abrasively intelligent book documents brilliantly.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-logo-naomi-klein-abridged/">No Logo &#8211; Naomi Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A new age &#8211; the novacene &#8211; has already begun.    </p>
<p>                    New beings will emerge from existing artificial intelligence systems. They will think 10,000 times faster than we do and will regard us as we now regard plants. The cruel, violent machine takeover imagined by sci-fi writers will not happen: these hyper-intelligent beings will be as dependent on the health of the planet as we are. They will need the planetary cooling system of Gaia to defend from the increasing heat of the sun. Gaia depends on organic life. We will be partners in this project. It is crucial, Lovelock argues, that the intelligence of Earth survives and prospers. We are at present the only beings capable of understanding the cosmos, but he speculates that the novacene could be the beginning of a process that will see intelligence suffusing the entire cosmos. At the age 100, Lovelock has produced the most compelling work of his life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Drawdown : The Most Comprehensive Plan Ever Proposed to Roll Back Global Warming &#8211; Paul Hawken (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8211; New York Times bestseller &#8211; The 100 most substantive solutions to reverse global warming, based on meticulous research by leading scientists and policymakers around the world &#8220;At this point in time, the Drawdown book is exactly what is needed; a credible, conservative solution-by-solution narrative that we can do it. Reading it is an effective [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/">Drawdown : The Most Comprehensive Plan Ever Proposed to Roll Back Global Warming &#8211; Paul Hawken (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8211; New York Times bestseller &#8211;     </p>
<p>                    The 100 most substantive solutions to reverse global warming, based on meticulous research by leading scientists and policymakers around the world     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;At this point in time, the Drawdown book is exactly what is needed; a credible, conservative solution-by-solution narrative that we can do it. Reading it is an effective inoculation against the widespread perception of doom that humanity cannot and will not solve the climate crisis. Reported by-effects include increased determination and a sense of grounded hope.&#8221; &#8211;Per Espen Stoknes, Author, What We Think About When We Try Not To Think About Global Warming     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There&#8217;s been no real way for ordinary people to get an understanding of what they can do and what impact it can have. There remains no single, comprehensive, reliable compendium of carbon-reduction solutions across sectors. At least until now. . . . The public is hungry for this kind of practical wisdom.&#8221; &#8211;David Roberts, Vox    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is the ideal environmental sciences textbook&#8211;only it is too interesting and inspiring to be called a textbook.&#8221; &#8211;Peter Kareiva, Director of the Institute of the Environment and Sustainability, UCLA     </p>
<p>                    In the face of widespread fear and apathy, an international coalition of researchers, professionals, and scientists have come together to offer a set of realistic and bold solutions to climate change. One hundred techniques and practices are described here&#8211;some are well known; some you may have never heard of. They range from clean energy to educating girls in lower-income countries to land use practices that pull carbon out of the air. The solutions exist, are economically viable, and communities throughout the world are currently enacting them with skill and determination. If deployed collectively on a global scale over the next thirty years, they represent a credible path forward, not just to slow the earth&#8217;s warming but to reach drawdown, that point in time when greenhouse gases in the atmosphere peak and begin to decline. These measures promise cascading benefits to human health, security, prosperity, and well-being&#8211;giving us every reason to see this planetary crisis as an opportunity to create a just and livable world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drawdown-the-most-comprehensive-plan-ever-proposed-to-roll-back-global-warming-paul-hawken-abridged/">Drawdown : The Most Comprehensive Plan Ever Proposed to Roll Back Global Warming &#8211; Paul Hawken (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
