<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Business Mathematics &amp; Systems Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/business-mathematics-systems/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/business-mathematics-systems/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Business Mathematics &amp; Systems Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/business-mathematics-systems/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Economist Numbers Guide : The Essentials of Business Numeracy &#8211; The Economist (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-economist-numbers-guide-the-essentials-of-business-numeracy-the-economist-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Mathematics & Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Numerical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-economist-numbers-guide-the-essentials-of-business-numeracy-the-economist-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Economist: Numbers Guide is invaluable for everyone who has to work with numbers, which in today&#8217;s commercially focused world means most managers. In addition to general advice on basic numeracy, the guide points out common errors and explains the recognized techniques for solving financial problems, analyzing information of any kind, forecasting and effective decision [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economist-numbers-guide-the-essentials-of-business-numeracy-the-economist-abridged/">The Economist Numbers Guide : The Essentials of Business Numeracy &#8211; The Economist (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Economist: Numbers Guide is invaluable for everyone who has to work with numbers, which in today&#8217;s commercially focused world means most managers. In addition to general advice on basic numeracy, the guide points out common errors and explains the recognized techniques for solving financial problems, analyzing information of any kind, forecasting and effective decision making. Over 100 charts, graphs, tables and feature boxes highlight key points, and great emphasis is put on the all-important aspect of how you present and communicate numerical information effectively and honestly. At the back of the book is an extensive A-Z dictionary of terms covering everything from amortization to zero-sum game. Whatever your business, whatever your management role, for anyone who needs a good head for figures The Economist Numbers Guide will help you achieve your goals.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economist-numbers-guide-the-essentials-of-business-numeracy-the-economist-abridged/">The Economist Numbers Guide : The Essentials of Business Numeracy &#8211; The Economist (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Mathematics & Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Engineering: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How do today&#8217;s most successful tech companies-Amazon, Google, Facebook, Netflix, Tesla-design, develop, and deploy the products that have earned the love of literally billions of people around the world? Perhaps surprisingly, they do it very differently than most tech companies. In INSPIRED, technology product management thought leader Marty Cagan provides readers with a master class [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/">Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do today&#8217;s most successful tech companies-Amazon, Google, Facebook, Netflix, Tesla-design, develop, and deploy the products that have earned the love of literally billions of people around the world?    </p>
<p>                     Perhaps surprisingly, they do it very differently than most tech companies.    </p>
<p>                     In INSPIRED, technology product management thought leader Marty Cagan provides readers with a master class in how to structure and staff a vibrant and successful product organization, and how to discover and deliver technology products that your customers will love-and that will work for your business.    </p>
<p>                     With sections on assembling the right people and skillsets, discovering the right product, embracing an effective yet lightweight process, and creating a strong product culture, readers can take the information they learn and immediately leverage it within their own organizations-dramatically improving their own product efforts.    </p>
<p>                     Whether you&#8217;re an early stage startup working to get to product/market fit, or a growth-stage company working to scale your product organization, or a large, long-established company trying to regain your ability to consistently deliver new value for your customers, INSPIRED will take you and your product organization to a new level of customer engagement, consistent innovation, and business success.    </p>
<p>                     Filled with the author&#8217;s own personal stories-and profiles of some of today&#8217;s most-successful product managers and technology-powered product companies, including Adobe, Apple, BBC, Google, Microsoft, and Netflix-INSPIRED will show you how to turn up the dial of your own product efforts, creating technology products your customers love.    </p>
<p>                     The first edition of INSPIRED, published ten years ago, established itself as the primary reference for technology product managers, and can be found on the shelves of nearly every successful technology product company worldwide. This thoroughly updated second edition shares the same objective of being the most valuable resource for technology product managers, yet it is completely new-sharing the latest practices and techniques of today&#8217;s most-successful tech product companies, and the men and women behind every great product.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/">Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 1% Windfall : How Successful Companies Use Price to Profit and Grow &#8211; Rafi Mohammed (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Mathematics & Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In &#8220;The Art of Pricing&#8221;, Rafi Mohammed gave readers advice on setting prices. In this essential follow up, he takes them to the next level, teaching them how to use price as a competitive strategy. A study of the Global 1200 found that if companies increased prices by just 1 percent, their average operating profits [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/">The 1% Windfall : How Successful Companies Use Price to Profit and Grow &#8211; Rafi Mohammed (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In &#8220;The Art of Pricing&#8221;, Rafi Mohammed gave readers advice on setting prices. In this essential follow up, he takes them to the next level, teaching them how to use price as a competitive strategy. A study of the Global 1200 found that if companies increased prices by just 1 percent, their average operating profits would increase by 11 percent. Using small incremental changes in price, Fortune 200 companies would see enormous growth in percentage of profit: Amazon, 40 percent; Aramark, 30 percent; Archer Daniels Midland, 19 percent; AMR, 68 percent; Boeing, 19 percent; Ingram Micro, 83 percent; McKesson, 82 percent; Wal Mart, 22 percent. Unfortunately, most companies have no clue how to capitalise on the direct link between pricing and profits. But how do executives and managers set the right price? Underpinned by sound empirical research and real-life anecdotes &#8220;The 1% Windfall&#8221; addresses this fundamental question, offering guidelines any company-whether a multi-national conglomerate, a small business, or even a non-profit can follow to create a comprehensive pricing strategy for any product and service.<br />
                    In addition, these techniques and tools apply equally to offensive and defensive solutions whether a company wants to keep ahead of the competition, avert a slump in a recession, or offset the impact of inflation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-1-windfall-how-successful-companies-use-price-to-profit-and-grow-rafi-mohammed-abridged/">The 1% Windfall : How Successful Companies Use Price to Profit and Grow &#8211; Rafi Mohammed (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
