<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Comparative Religion Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/comparative-religion/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/comparative-religion/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Comparative Religion Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/comparative-religion/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</title>
		<link>/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Worship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Koran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Slavery & Abolition Of Slavery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when authorities you venerate condone something you know is wrong? Every major religion and philosophy once condoned or approved of slavery, but in modern times nothing is seen as more evil. Americans confront this crisis of authority when they erect statues of Founding Fathers who slept with their slaves. And Muslims faced it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/">Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when authorities you venerate condone something you know is wrong?</p>
<p>                    Every major religion and philosophy once condoned or approved of slavery, but in modern times nothing is seen as more evil. Americans confront this crisis of authority when they erect statues of Founding Fathers who slept with their slaves. And Muslims faced it when ISIS revived sex slavery, justifying it with verses from the Quran and the practice of Muhammad.</p>
<p>                    Exploring the moral and ultimately theological problem of slavery, Jonathan A.C. Brown traces how the Christian, Jewish and Islamic traditions have tried to reconcile modern moral certainties with the infallibility of God&#8217;s message. He lays out how Islam viewed slavery in theory, and the reality of how it was practiced across Islamic civilization. Finally, Brown carefully examines arguments put forward by Muslims for the abolition of slavery.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/">Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Become What You Are : Expanded Edition &#8211; Alan W. Watts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/become-what-you-are-expanded-edition-alan-w-watts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Non-Christian Religions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taoism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/become-what-you-are-expanded-edition-alan-w-watts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The prominent Zen Buddhist scholar and author of The Wisdom of Insecurity draws on Taoism, Christianity, and other world religions to explore the dilemma of seeking your true self In this collection of writings, including nine new chapters never before available in book form, Alan Watts displays the intelligence, playfulness of thought, and simplicity of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/become-what-you-are-expanded-edition-alan-w-watts-abridged/">Become What You Are : Expanded Edition &#8211; Alan W. Watts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The prominent Zen Buddhist scholar and author of The Wisdom of Insecurity draws on Taoism, Christianity, and other world religions to explore the dilemma of seeking your true self     </p>
<p>                    In this collection of writings, including nine new chapters never before available in book form, Alan Watts displays the intelligence, playfulness of thought, and simplicity of language that has made him so perennially popular as an interpreter of Eastern thought for Westerners. He draws on a variety of religious traditions, and covers topics such as the challenge of seeing one&#8217;s life &#8220;just as it is,&#8221; the Taoist approach to harmonious living, the limits of language in the face of ineffable spiritual truth, and the psychological symbolism of Christian thought.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/become-what-you-are-expanded-edition-alan-w-watts-abridged/">Become What You Are : Expanded Edition &#8211; Alan W. Watts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Myth &#8211; Joseph Campbell, Bill Moyers (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-myth-joseph-campbell-bill-moyers-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Folklore, Myths & Legends]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-myth-joseph-campbell-bill-moyers-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The national bestseller, now available in a non-illustrated, standard format paperback edition The Power of Myth launched an extraordinary resurgence of interest in Joseph Campbell and his work. A preeminent scholar, writer, and teacher, he has had a profound influence on millions of people&#8211;including Star Wars creator George Lucas. To Campbell, mythology was the &#8220;song [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-myth-joseph-campbell-bill-moyers-abridged/">The Power of Myth &#8211; Joseph Campbell, Bill Moyers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The national bestseller, now available in a non-illustrated, standard format paperback edition    </p>
<p>                    The Power of Myth launched an extraordinary resurgence of interest in Joseph Campbell and his work. A preeminent scholar, writer, and teacher, he has had a profound influence on millions of people&#8211;including Star Wars creator George Lucas. To Campbell, mythology was the &#8220;song of the universe, the music of the spheres.&#8221; With Bill Moyers, one of America&#8217;s most prominent journalists, as his thoughtful and engaging interviewer, The Power of Myth touches on subjects from modern marriage to virgin births, from Jesus to John Lennon, offering a brilliant combination of intelligence and wit.     </p>
<p>                    This extraordinary book reveals how the themes and symbols of ancient narratives continue to bring meaning to birth, death, love, and war. From stories of the gods and goddesses of ancient Greece and Rome to traditions of Buddhism, Hinduism and Christianity, a broad array of themes are considered that together identify the universality of human experience across time and culture. An impeccable match of interviewer and subject, a timeless distillation of Campbell&#8217;s work, The Power of Myth continues to exert a profound influence on our culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-myth-joseph-campbell-bill-moyers-abridged/">The Power of Myth &#8211; Joseph Campbell, Bill Moyers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
