<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Society &amp; Culture: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/society-culture-general/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/society-culture-general/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Society &amp; Culture: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/society-culture-general/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Empire of Illusion : The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle &#8211; Chris Hedges</title>
		<link>/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We now live in two Americas. One,now the minority,functions in a print-based, literate world that can cope with complexity and can separate illusion from truth. The other,the majority,is retreating from a reality-based world into one of false certainty and magic. To this majority,which crosses social class lines, though the poor are overwhelmingly affected,presidential debate and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/">Empire of Illusion : The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle &#8211; Chris Hedges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We now live in two Americas. One,now the minority,functions in a print-based, literate world that can cope with complexity and can separate illusion from truth. The other,the majority,is retreating from a reality-based world into one of false certainty and magic. To this majority,which crosses social class lines, though the poor are overwhelmingly affected,presidential debate and political rhetoric is pitched at a sixth-grade reading level. In this  other America,&#8221; serious film and theatre, as well as newspapers and books, are being pushed to the margins of society. In the tradition of Christopher Lasch&#8217;s  The Culture of Narcissism  and Neil Postman&#8217;s  Amusing Ourselves to Death , Pulitzer Prize-winner Chris Hedges navigates this culture,attending WWF contests, the Adult Video News Awards in Las Vegas, and Ivy League graduation ceremonies,to expose an age of terrifying decline and heightened self-delusion.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/">Empire of Illusion : The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle &#8211; Chris Hedges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism &#8211; Max Weber</title>
		<link>/the-protestant-ethic-and-the-spirit-of-capitalism-max-weber/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-protestant-ethic-and-the-spirit-of-capitalism-max-weber/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Max Weber&#8217;s best-known and most controversial work, The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism, first published in 1904, remains to this day a powerful and fascinating read. Weber&#8217;s highly accessible style is just one of many reasons for his continuing popularity. The book contends that the Protestant ethic made possible and encouraged the development [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-protestant-ethic-and-the-spirit-of-capitalism-max-weber/">The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism &#8211; Max Weber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Max Weber&#8217;s best-known and most controversial work, The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism, first published in 1904, remains to this day a powerful and fascinating read. Weber&#8217;s highly accessible style is just one of many reasons for his continuing popularity. The book contends that the Protestant ethic made possible and encouraged the development of capitalism in the West. Widely considered as the most informed work ever written on the social effects of advanced capitalism, The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism holds its own as one of the most significant books of the twentieth century. The book is one of those rare works of scholarship which no informed citizen can afford to ignore.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-protestant-ethic-and-the-spirit-of-capitalism-max-weber/">The Protestant Ethic and the Spirit of Capitalism &#8211; Max Weber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revival: Economics for the Twenty-first Century (2001) : The Economics of the Economist-fox &#8211; Andrew M. Kamarck</title>
		<link>/revival-economics-for-the-twenty-first-century-2001-the-economics-of-the-economist-fox-andrew-m-kamarck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/revival-economics-for-the-twenty-first-century-2001-the-economics-of-the-economist-fox-andrew-m-kamarck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This title was first published in 2001. To be effective, economics must take into consideration the complex nature of human beings and the contextual, institutional, social and historical factors at play. This text is designed to help economists to be economic foxes by increasing the range of economists&#8217; tools, drawing on the knowledge and experience [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revival-economics-for-the-twenty-first-century-2001-the-economics-of-the-economist-fox-andrew-m-kamarck/">Revival: Economics for the Twenty-first Century (2001) : The Economics of the Economist-fox &#8211; Andrew M. Kamarck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This title was first published in 2001. To be effective, economics must take into consideration the complex nature of human beings and the contextual, institutional, social and historical factors at play. This text is designed to help economists to be economic foxes by increasing the range of economists&#8217; tools, drawing on the knowledge and experience of other disciplines, to cope better with the extraordinary complexity of the modern economy. The objective is to provide the same kind of revelation in understanding an economy that an artist possesses in the visual arts. A beginner looking at a still life sees a green bottle, a red apple and a yellow cloth on a table top. An artist, however, can point out to him all the nuances of colour. Following a rapid dissection of the canonical hypotheses of contemporary economic theory, different sectors of the real economy are explored: the corporation; corporate governance; services; the public sector; civil society; professions; social capital; national cultures; and the tropics.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revival-economics-for-the-twenty-first-century-2001-the-economics-of-the-economist-fox-andrew-m-kamarck/">Revival: Economics for the Twenty-first Century (2001) : The Economics of the Economist-fox &#8211; Andrew M. Kamarck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Major : Notes on Diana Ross, Dark Girls, and Being Dope &#8211; Read by Shayla Lawson</title>
		<link>/this-is-major-notes-on-diana-ross-dark-girls-and-being-dope-read-by-shayla-lawson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-major-notes-on-diana-ross-dark-girls-and-being-dope-read-by-shayla-lawson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a fierce and humorous new voice comes a relevant, insightful, and riveting collection of personal essays on the richness and resilience of black girl culture&#8211;for readers of Samantha Irby, Roxane Gay, Morgan Jerkins, and Lindy West. Shayla Lawson is major. You don&#8217;t know who she is. Yet. But that&#8217;s okay. She is on a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-major-notes-on-diana-ross-dark-girls-and-being-dope-read-by-shayla-lawson/">This Is Major : Notes on Diana Ross, Dark Girls, and Being Dope &#8211; Read by Shayla Lawson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a fierce and humorous new voice comes a relevant, insightful, and riveting collection of personal essays on the richness and resilience of black girl culture&#8211;for readers of Samantha Irby, Roxane Gay, Morgan Jerkins, and Lindy West.     </p>
<p>                    Shayla Lawson is major. You don&#8217;t know who she is. Yet. But that&#8217;s okay. She is on a mission to move black girls like herself from best supporting actress to a starring role in the major narrative. Whether she&#8217;s taking on workplace microaggressions or upending racist stereotypes about her home state of Kentucky, she looks for the side of the story that isn&#8217;t always told, the places where the voices of black girls haven&#8217;t been heard.     </p>
<p>                    The essays in This is Major ask questions like: Why are black women invisible to AI? What is &#8220;black girl magic&#8221;? Or: Am I one viral tweet away from becoming Twitter famous? And: How much magic does it take to land a Tinder date?    </p>
<p>                    With a unique mix of personal stories, pop culture observations, and insights into politics and history, Lawson sheds light on these questions, as well as the many ways black women and girls have influenced mainstream culture&#8211;from their style, to their language, and even their art&#8211;and how &#8220;major&#8221; they really are.    </p>
<p>                    Timely, enlightening, and wickedly sharp, This Is Major places black women at the center&#8211;no longer silenced, no longer the minority.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-major-notes-on-diana-ross-dark-girls-and-being-dope-read-by-shayla-lawson/">This Is Major : Notes on Diana Ross, Dark Girls, and Being Dope &#8211; Read by Shayla Lawson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Inevitable : Understanding the 12 Technological Forces That Will Shape Our Future &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A quintessential work of technological futurism.&#8221; &#8211; James Surowiecki, strategy + business, &#8220;Best Business Books 2017 &#8211; Innovation&#8221; From one of our leading technology thinkers and writers, a guide through the twelve technological imperatives that will shape the next thirty years and transform our lives Much of what will happen in the next thirty years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/">The Inevitable : Understanding the 12 Technological Forces That Will Shape Our Future &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A quintessential work of technological futurism.&#8221; &#8211; James Surowiecki, strategy + business, &#8220;Best Business Books 2017 &#8211; Innovation&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    From one of our leading technology thinkers and writers, a guide through the twelve technological imperatives that will shape the next thirty years and transform our lives     </p>
<p>                    Much of what will happen in the next thirty years is inevitable, driven by technological trends that are already in motion. In this fascinating, provocative new book, Kevin Kelly provides an optimistic road map for the future, showing how the coming changes in our lives&#8211;from virtual reality in the home to an on-demand economy to artificial intelligence embedded in everything we manufacture&#8211;can be understood as the result of a few long-term, accelerating forces. Kelly both describes these deep trends&#8211;interacting, cognifying, flowing, screening, accessing, sharing, filtering, remixing, tracking, and questioning&#8211;and demonstrates how they overlap and are codependent on one another. These larger forces will completely revolutionize the way we buy, work, learn, and communicate with each other. By understanding and embracing them, says Kelly, it will be easier for us to remain on top of the coming wave of changes and to arrange our day-to-day relationships with technology in ways that bring forth maximum benefits. Kelly&#8217;s bright, hopeful book will be indispensable to anyone who seeks guidance on where their business, industry, or life is heading&#8211;what to invent, where to work, in what to invest, how to better reach customers, and what to begin to put into place&#8211;as this new world emerges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/">The Inevitable : Understanding the 12 Technological Forces That Will Shape Our Future &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In a time in which the ways we communicate and connect are constantly changing, and not always for the better, Sherry Turkle provides a much needed voice of caution and reason to help explain what the f*** is going on.&#8221; &#8211;Aziz Ansari, author of Modern Romance Renowned media scholar Sherry Turkle investigates how a flight [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In a time in which the ways we communicate and connect are constantly changing, and not always for the better, Sherry Turkle provides a much needed voice of caution and reason to help explain what the f*** is going on.&#8221; &#8211;Aziz Ansari,  author of Modern Romance     </p>
<p>                    Renowned media scholar Sherry Turkle investigates how a flight from conversation undermines our relationships, creativity, and productivity&#8211;and why reclaiming face-to-face conversation can help us regain lost ground.    </p>
<p>                    We live in a technological universe in which we are always communicating. And yet we have sacrificed conversation for mere connection.     </p>
<p>                     Preeminent author and researcher Sherry Turkle has been studying digital culture for over thirty years. Long an enthusiast for its possibilities, here she investigates a troubling consequence: at work, at home, in politics, and in love, we find ways around conversation, tempted by the possibilities of a text or an email in which we don&#8217;t have to look, listen, or reveal ourselves.     </p>
<p>                     We develop a taste for what mere connection offers. The dinner table falls silent as children compete with phones for their parents&#8217; attention. Friends learn strategies to keep conversations going when only a few people are looking up from their phones. At work, we retreat to our screens although it is conversation at the water cooler that increases not only productivity but commitment to work. Online, we only want to share opinions that our followers will agree with &#8211; a politics that shies away from the real conflicts and solutions of the public square.     </p>
<p>                     The case for conversation begins with the necessary conversations of solitude and self-reflection. They are endangered: these days, always connected, we see loneliness as a problem that technology should solve. Afraid of being alone, we rely on other people to give us a sense of ourselves, and our capacity for empathy and relationship suffers. We see the costs of the flight from conversation everywhere: conversation is the cornerstone for democracy and in business it is good for the bottom line. In the private sphere, it builds empathy, friendship, love, learning, and productivity.     </p>
<p>                     But there is good news: we are resilient. Conversation cures.     </p>
<p>                     Based on five years of research and interviews in homes, schools, and the workplace, Turkle argues that we have come to a better understanding of where our technology can and cannot take us and that the time is right to reclaim conversation. The most human&#8211;and humanizing&#8211;thing that we do.     </p>
<p>                     The virtues of person-to-person conversation are timeless, and our most basic technology, talk, responds to our modern challenges. We have everything we need to start, we have each other.     </p>
<p>                    Turkle&#8217;s latest book, The Empathy Diaries (3/2/21) is available now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel With Children / Family Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* NOW WITH A NEW CHAPTER * &#8216;A hugely enjoyable romp through the pleasures and pitfalls of setting up home in a foreign land.&#8217;- Guardian Given the opportunity of a new life in rural Jutland, Helen Russell discovered a startling statistic: Denmark, land of long dark winters, cured herring, Lego and pastries, was the happiest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/">The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* NOW WITH A NEW CHAPTER *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A hugely enjoyable romp through the pleasures and pitfalls of setting up home in a foreign land.&#8217;- Guardian    </p>
<p>                    Given the opportunity of a new life in rural Jutland, Helen Russell discovered a startling statistic: Denmark, land of long dark winters, cured herring, Lego and pastries, was the happiest place on earth.    </p>
<p>                    Keen to know their secrets, Helen gave herself a year to uncover the formula for Danish happiness.    </p>
<p>                    From childcare, education, food and interior design to SAD and taxes, The Year of Living Danishly records a funny, poignant journey, showing us what the Danes get right, what they get wrong, and how we might all live a little more Danishly ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    In this new edition, six years on Helen reveals how her life and family have changed, and explores how Denmark, too &#8211; or. her understanding of it &#8211; has shifted. It&#8217;s a messy and flawed place, she concludes &#8211; but can still be a model for a better way of living.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/">The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Tyranny : Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century &#8211; Timothy Snyder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** &#8216;A sort of survival book, a sort of symptom-diagnosis manual in terms of losing your democracy and what tyranny and authoritarianism look like up close&#8217; Rachel Maddow &#8216;These 128 pages are a brief primer in every important thing we might have learned from the history of the last century, and all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/">On Tyranny : Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century &#8211; Timothy Snyder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A sort of survival book, a sort of symptom-diagnosis manual in terms of losing your democracy and what tyranny and authoritarianism look like up close&#8217; Rachel Maddow    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;These 128 pages are a brief primer in every important thing we might have learned from the history of the last century, and all that we appear to have forgotten&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                     History does not repeat, but it does instruct.    </p>
<p>                     In the twentieth century, European democracies collapsed into fascism, Nazism and communism. These were movements in which a leader or a party claimed to give voice to the people, promised to protect them from global existential threats, and rejected reason in favour of myth. European history shows us that societies can break, democracies can fall, ethics can collapse, and ordinary people can find themselves in unimaginable circumstances.    </p>
<p>                     History can familiarise, and it can warn. Today, we are no wiser than the Europeans who saw democracy yield to totalitarianism in the twentieth century. But when the political order seems imperilled, our advantage is that we can learn from their experience to resist the advance of tyranny.    </p>
<p>                     Now is a good time to do so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/">On Tyranny : Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century &#8211; Timothy Snyder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year A Guardian book of the year &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year<br />
                              A Guardian book of the year<br />
                              &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times<br />
                              &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman<br />
                              &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith<br />
                              What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation?    </p>
<p>                              Offering nuanced and witty reflections on feminism, reality TV, the internet, drugs, identity and more, Trick Mirror is a multifaceted, thought-provoking and entertaining response to our zeitgeist &#8211; a must-read for anyone interested in the way we live and think today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Clash Of Civilizations : And The Remaking Of World Order &#8211; Samuel P. Huntington (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 1993 the esteemed journal FOREIGN AFFAIRS published an article entitled &#8220;The Clash of Civilizations?&#8221; by Samuel P. Huntington. According to the journal&#8217;s editors it went on to generate more discussion than anything they had published since the Second World War. In the article, Huntington posed the question whether conflicts between civilizations would dominate the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/">The Clash Of Civilizations : And The Remaking Of World Order &#8211; Samuel P. Huntington (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 1993 the esteemed journal FOREIGN AFFAIRS published an article entitled &#8220;The Clash of Civilizations?&#8221; by Samuel P. Huntington. According to the journal&#8217;s editors it went on to generate more discussion than anything they had published since the Second World War. In the article, Huntington posed the question whether conflicts between civilizations would dominate the future of world politics. In the book, he gives the answer, showing not only how clashes between civilizations are the greatest threat to world peace but also how an international order based on civilizations is the best safeguard against war. Since September 11, his thesis has seemed even more prescient and acute. THE CLASH OF CIVILIZATIONS AND THE REMAKING OF WORLD ORDER is now recognised as a classic study of international relations in an increasingly uncertain world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/">The Clash Of Civilizations : And The Remaking Of World Order &#8211; Samuel P. Huntington (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enchanted Objects : Innovation, Design, and the Future of Technology &#8211; David Rose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of Who Owns the Future, an MIT Media Lab scientist imagines how everyday objects can intuit our needs, improve our lives, and form &#8220;an ethereal interconnection of gadgets and human desires that&#8230;will pervade our lives in the very near future&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). We are now standing at the precipice of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/">Enchanted Objects : Innovation, Design, and the Future of Technology &#8211; David Rose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of Who Owns the Future, an MIT Media Lab scientist imagines how everyday objects can intuit our needs, improve our lives, and form &#8220;an ethereal interconnection of gadgets and human desires that&#8230;will pervade our lives in the very near future&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).     </p>
<p>                    We are now standing at the precipice of the next transformative development, a world in which technology becomes more human. Soon, connected technology will be embedded in hundreds of everyday objects we already use: our cars, wallets, watches, umbrellas, even our trash cans. These objects will respond to our needs, come to know us, and even learn to think ahead on our behalf. David Rose calls these devices&#8211;which are just beginning to creep into the marketplace&#8211;Enchanted Objects.     </p>
<p>                     In Rose&#8217;s vision of the future, technology atomizes, combining itself with the objects that make up the very fabric of daily living. Such innovations will be woven into the background of our environment, enhancing human relationships, channeling desires for omniscience, long life, and creative expression. The enchanted objects of fairy tales and science fiction will enter real life.     </p>
<p>                     Groundbreaking, timely, and provocative, Enchanted Objects is a &#8220;delightful&#8221; (The New York Times) blueprint for a better future, where efficient solutions come hand in hand with technology that delights our senses. It is essential reading for designers, technologists, entrepreneurs, business leaders, and anyone who wishes to take a glimpse into the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/">Enchanted Objects : Innovation, Design, and the Future of Technology &#8211; David Rose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Asking : How I learned to stop worrying and let people help &#8211; Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History: From c 1960]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>REDISCOVER THE FORGOTTEN ART OF ASKING IN THIS NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING BOOK &#8216;Amanda Palmer joyfully shows a generation how to change their lives&#8217; Caitlin Moran &#8216;To read Amanda Palmer&#8217;s remarkable memoir about asking and giving is to tumble headlong into her world&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert &#8216;The Art of Asking is a book about cultivating trust [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/">The Art of Asking : How I learned to stop worrying and let people help &#8211; Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>REDISCOVER THE FORGOTTEN ART OF ASKING IN THIS NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING BOOK     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Amanda Palmer joyfully shows a generation how to change their lives&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;To read Amanda Palmer&#8217;s remarkable memoir about asking and giving is to tumble headlong into her world&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The Art of Asking is a book about cultivating trust and getting as close as possible to love, vulnerability, and connection. Uncomfortably close. Dangerously close. Beautifully close&#8217; Brene Brown    </p>
<p>                    Imagine standing on a box in the middle of a busy city, dressed as a white-faced bride, and silently using your eyes to ask people for money. Or touring Europe in a punk cabaret band, and finding a place to sleep each night by reaching out to strangers on Twitter. For Amanda Palmer, actions like these have gone beyond satisfying her basic needs for food and shelter &#8211; they&#8217;ve taught her how to turn strangers into friends, build communities, and discover her own giving impulses. And because she had learned how to ask, she was able to go to the world to ask for the money to make a new album and tour with it, and to raise over a million dollars in a month.    </p>
<p>                    In the New York TImes bestseller The Art of Asking, Palmer expands upon her popular TED talk to reveal how ordinary people, those of us without thousands of Twitter followers and adoring fans, can use these same principles in our own lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/">The Art of Asking : How I learned to stop worrying and let people help &#8211; Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness. As the focus of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness.    </p>
<p>                    As the focus of the family has turned to the glow of the screen&#8211;children constantly texting their friends or going online to do homework; parents working online around the clock&#8211;everyday life is undergoing a massive transformation. Easy access to the Internet and social media has erased the boundaries that protect children from damaging exposure to excessive marketing and the unsavory aspects of adult culture. Parents often feel they are losing a meaningful connection with their children. Children are feeling lonely and alienated. The digital world is here to stay, but what are families losing with technology&#8217;s gain?    </p>
<p>                    As renowned clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair explains, families are in crisis as they face this issue, and even more so than they realize. Not only do chronic tech distractions have deep and lasting effects but children also desperately need parents to provide what tech cannot: close, significant interactions with the adults in their lives. Drawing on real-life stories from her clinical work with children and parents and her consulting work with educators and experts across the country, Steiner-Adair offers insights and advice that can help parents achieve greater understanding, authority, and confidence as they engage with the tech revolution unfolding in their living rooms.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Born Liars : Why We Can&#8217;t Live Without Deceit &#8211; Ian Leslie, Read by Rich Keeble (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/born-liars-why-we-cant-live-without-deceit-ian-leslie-read-by-rich-keeble-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/born-liars-why-we-cant-live-without-deceit-ian-leslie-read-by-rich-keeble-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Born Liars, Ian Leslie takes the reader on an exhilarating tour of ideas that brings the latest news about deception back from the frontiers of psychology, neuroscience, and philosophy, and explores the role played by lies &#8211; both black and white &#8211; in our childhoods, our careers, and our health, as well as in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/born-liars-why-we-cant-live-without-deceit-ian-leslie-read-by-rich-keeble-abridged/">Born Liars : Why We Can&#8217;t Live Without Deceit &#8211; Ian Leslie, Read by Rich Keeble (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Born Liars, Ian Leslie takes the reader on an exhilarating tour of ideas that brings the latest news about deception back from the frontiers of psychology, neuroscience, and philosophy, and explores the role played by lies &#8211; both black and white &#8211; in our childhoods, our careers, and our health, as well as in advertising, politics, sport and war. Drawing on thinkers as varied as Augustine, Charles Darwin, Sigmund Freud and Joni Mitchell, the author argues that, far from being a bug in the human software, lying is central to who we are; that we cannot understand ourselves without first understanding the dynamics of deceit.     </p>
<p>                    After reading Born Liars you&#8217;ll never think about lies &#8211; or life &#8211; in quite the same way again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/born-liars-why-we-cant-live-without-deceit-ian-leslie-read-by-rich-keeble-abridged/">Born Liars : Why We Can&#8217;t Live Without Deceit &#8211; Ian Leslie, Read by Rich Keeble (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Book of the Year for The Economist and the Observer Our world seems to be collapsing. The daily news cycle reports the deterioration: divisive politics across the Western world, racism, poverty, war, inequality, hunger. While politicians, journalists and activists from all sides talk about the damage done, Johan Norberg offers an illuminating and heartening [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/">Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Book of the Year for The Economist and the Observer    </p>
<p>                    Our world seems to be collapsing. The daily news cycle reports the deterioration: divisive politics across the Western world, racism, poverty, war, inequality, hunger. While politicians, journalists and activists from all sides talk about the damage done, Johan Norberg offers an illuminating and heartening analysis of just how far we have come in tackling the greatest problems facing humanity. In the face of fear-mongering, darkness and division, the facts are unequivocal: the golden age is now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/">Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In private life, we try to induce or suppress love, envy, and anger through deep acting or &#8220;emotion work&#8221;, just as we manage our outer expressions of feeling through surface acting. In trying to bridge a gap between what we feel and what we &#8220;ought&#8221; to feel, we take guidance from &#8220;feeling rules&#8221; about what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In private life, we try to induce or suppress love, envy, and anger through deep acting or &#8220;emotion work&#8221;, just as we manage our outer expressions of feeling through surface acting. In trying to bridge a gap between what we feel and what we &#8220;ought&#8221; to feel, we take guidance from &#8220;feeling rules&#8221; about what is owing to others in a given situation. Based on our private mutual understandings of feeling rules, we make a &#8220;gift exchange&#8221; of acts of emotion management. We bow to each other not simply from the waist, but from the heart. But what occurs when emotion work, feeling rules, and the gift of exchange are introduced into the public world of work? In search of the answer, Arlie Russell Hochschild closely examines two groups of public-contact workers: flight attendants and bill collectors. The flight attendant&#8217;s job is to deliver a service and create further demand for it, to enhance the status of the customer and be &#8220;nicer than natural&#8221;. The bill collector&#8217;s job is to collect on the service, and if necessary, to deflate the status of the customer by being &#8220;nastier than natural.&#8221;<br />
                    Between these extremes, roughly one-third of American men and one-half of American women hold jobs that call for substantial emotional labor. In many of these jobs, they are trained to accept feeling rules and techniques of emotion management that serve the company&#8217;s commercial purpose. Just as we have seldom recognized or understood emotional labor, we have not appreciated its cost to those who do it for a living. Like a physical laborer who becomes estranged from what he or she makes, an emotional laborer, such as a flight attendant, can become estranged not only from her own expressions of feeling (her smile is not &#8220;her&#8221; smile), but also from what she actually feels (her managed friendliness). This estrangement, though a valuable defense against stress, is also an important occupational hazard, because it is through our feelings that we are connected with those around us. On the basis of this book, Hochschild was featured in Key Sociological Thinkers, edited by Rob Stones. This book was also the winner of the Charles Cooley Award in 1983, awarded by the American Sociological Association and received an honorable mention for the C. Wright Mills Award.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managed-heart-commercialization-of-human-feeling-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">The Managed Heart : Commercialization of Human Feeling &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leisure: The Basis of Culture : Including the Philosophical Act &#8211; Josef Pieper (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leisure-the-basis-of-culture-including-the-philosophical-act-josef-pieper-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leisure-the-basis-of-culture-including-the-philosophical-act-josef-pieper-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the most important philosophy titles published in the twentieth century, Josef Pieper&#8217;s Leisure, the Basis of Culture is more significant, even more crucial, today than it was when it first appeared more than fifty years ago. This edition also includes his work The Philosophical Act. Leisure is an attitude of the mind and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leisure-the-basis-of-culture-including-the-philosophical-act-josef-pieper-abridged/">Leisure: The Basis of Culture : Including the Philosophical Act &#8211; Josef Pieper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the most important philosophy titles published in the twentieth century, Josef Pieper&#8217;s Leisure, the Basis of Culture is more significant, even more crucial, today than it was when it first appeared more than fifty years ago. This edition also includes his work The Philosophical Act. Leisure is an attitude of the mind and a condition of the soul that fosters a capacity to perceive the reality of the world. Pieper shows that the Greeks and medieval Europeans, understood the great value and importance of leisure. He also points out that religion can be born only in leisure &#8212; a leisure that allows time for the contemplation of the nature of God. Leisure has been, and always will be, the first foundation of any culture. Pieper maintains that our bourgeois world of total labor has vanquished leisure, and issues a startling warning: Unless we regain the art of silence and insight, the ability for non-activity, unless we substitute true leisure for our hectic amusements, we will destroy our culture &#8212; and ourselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leisure-the-basis-of-culture-including-the-philosophical-act-josef-pieper-abridged/">Leisure: The Basis of Culture : Including the Philosophical Act &#8211; Josef Pieper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agnosticism & Atheism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eclectic & Esoteric Religions & Belief Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom ___ For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom<br />
                    ___    </p>
<p>                    For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and psychology.    </p>
<p>                     Throughout the book, Harris argues that there are important truths to be found in the experience of contemplatives such as Jesus, Buddha and other saints and sages of history-and, therefore, that there is more to understanding reality than science and secular culture generally allow.    </p>
<p>                    Waking Up is part seeker&#8217;s memoir and part exploration of the scientific underpinnings of spirituality. No other book marries contemplative wisdom and modern science in this way, and no author other than Sam Harris-a scientist, philosopher, and famous sceptic-could write it.<br />
                     ___    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A demanding, illusion-shattering book.&#8217; Kirkus Reviews<br />
                    &#8216;A pleasure to read.&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Farsighted : How We Make the Decisions that Matter the Most &#8211; Steven Johnson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/farsighted-how-we-make-the-decisions-that-matter-the-most-steven-johnson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/farsighted-how-we-make-the-decisions-that-matter-the-most-steven-johnson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Plenty of books offer useful advice on how to get better at making quick-thinking, intuitive choices. But what about more consequential decisions, the ones that affect our lives for years, or centuries, to come? Our most powerful stories revolve around these kinds of decisions: where to live, whom to marry, what to believe, whether to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/farsighted-how-we-make-the-decisions-that-matter-the-most-steven-johnson-abridged/">Farsighted : How We Make the Decisions that Matter the Most &#8211; Steven Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Plenty of books offer useful advice on how to get better at making quick-thinking, intuitive choices. But what about more consequential decisions, the ones that affect our lives for years, or centuries, to come? Our most powerful stories revolve around these kinds of decisions: where to live, whom to marry, what to believe, whether to start a company, how to end a war.    </p>
<p>                    Full of the beautifully crafted storytelling and novel insights that Steven Johnson&#8217;s fans know to expect, Farsighted draws lessons from cognitive science, social psychology, military strategy, environmental planning, and great works of literature. Everyone thinks we are living in an age of short attention spans, but we&#8217;ve actually learned a lot about making long-term decisions over the past few decades. Johnson makes a compelling case for a smarter and more deliberative decision-making approach. He argues that we choose better when we break out of the myopia of single-scale thinking and develop methods for considering all the factors involved.    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s no one-size-fits-all model for the important decisions that can alter the course of a life, an organization, or a civilization. But Farsighted explains how we can approach these choices more effectively, and how we can appreciate the subtle intelligence of choices that shaped our broader social history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/farsighted-how-we-make-the-decisions-that-matter-the-most-steven-johnson-abridged/">Farsighted : How We Make the Decisions that Matter the Most &#8211; Steven Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose. This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose.    </p>
<p>                    This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is among mankind&#8217;s great masterpieces-a massive work of art. As an idea, it rivals monotheism. But its cultural potential and its societal impact often elude us. In this deep and thoughtful book, Virginia Heffernan reveals the logic and aesthetics behind the Internet, just as Susan Sontag did for photography and Marshall McLuhan did for television.    </p>
<p>                    Life online, in the highly visual, social, portable, and global incarnation rewards certain virtues. The new medium favors speed, accuracy, wit, prolificacy, and versatility, and its form and functions are changing how we perceive, experience, and understand the world. In &#8220;sumptuous writing, saturated with observations that are simultaneously personal, cultural, and strikingly original&#8221; (The New Republic), Heffernan presents &#8220;a revealing look at how the Internet continues to reshape our lives emotionally, visually, and culturally&#8221; (The Smithsonian Magazine). &#8220;Magic and Loss is an illuminating guide to the Internet&#8230;it is impossible to come away from this book without sharing some of Heffernan&#8217;s awe for this brave new world&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>White Fragility : Why It&#8217;s So Hard for White People to Talk About Racism &#8211; Robin DiAngelo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/white-fragility-why-its-so-hard-for-white-people-to-talk-about-racism-robin-diangelo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/white-fragility-why-its-so-hard-for-white-people-to-talk-about-racism-robin-diangelo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The International Bestseller &#8216;With clarity and compassion, DiAngelo allows us to understand racism as a practice not restricted to &#8220;bad people.&#8221; In doing so, she moves our national discussions forward. This is a necessary book for all people invested in societal change&#8217; Claudia Rankine Anger. Fear. Guilt. Denial. Silence. These are the ways in which [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/white-fragility-why-its-so-hard-for-white-people-to-talk-about-racism-robin-diangelo-abridged/">White Fragility : Why It&#8217;s So Hard for White People to Talk About Racism &#8211; Robin DiAngelo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The International Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;With clarity and compassion,  DiAngelo allows us to understand racism as  a practice not restricted to  &#8220;bad people.&#8221; In doing so, she moves our  national discussions forward.  This is a necessary book for all people  invested in societal change&#8217;  Claudia Rankine    </p>
<p>                    Anger. Fear. Guilt. Denial. Silence. These  are the ways in which  ordinary white people react when it is pointed  out to them that they  have done or said something that has &#8211;  unintentionally &#8211; caused racial  offence or hurt. After, all, a racist  is the worst thing a person can  be, right? But these reactions only  serve to silence people of colour,  who cannot give honest feedback to  &#8216;liberal&#8217; white people lest they  provoke a dangerous emotional  reaction.     </p>
<p>                    Robin DiAngelo coined  the term &#8216;White Fragility&#8217; in  2011 to describe this process and is here  to show us how it serves to  uphold the system of white supremacy. Using  knowledge and insight  gained over decades of running racial awareness  workshops and working  on this idea as a Professor of Whiteness Studies,  she shows us how we  can start having more honest conversations, listen  to each other better  and react to feedback with grace and humility. It  is not enough to  simply hold abstract progressive views and condemn the  obvious racists  on social media &#8211; change starts with us all at a  practical, granular  level, and it is time for all white people to take  responsibility for  relinquishing their own racial supremacy.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;By turns mordant  and  then inspirational, an argument that powerful  forces and tragic   histories stack the deck fully against racial justice  alongside one  that  we need only to be clearer, try harder, and do  better&#8217; David  Roediger, Los Angeles Review of Books    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The value in White Fragility    lies in its methodical, irrefutable exposure of racism in thought and    action, and its call for humility and vigilance&#8217; Katy Waldman, New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A vital, necessary, and beautiful book&#8217; Michael Eric Dyson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/white-fragility-why-its-so-hard-for-white-people-to-talk-about-racism-robin-diangelo-abridged/">White Fragility : Why It&#8217;s So Hard for White People to Talk About Racism &#8211; Robin DiAngelo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Language]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite 21st-century fears of an &#8216;epidemic&#8217; of loneliness, its history has been sorely neglected. A Biography of Loneliness offers a radically new interpretation of loneliness as an emotional language and experience. Using letters and diaries, philosophical tracts, political discussions, and medical literature from the eighteenth century to the present, historian of the emotions Fay Bound [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/">A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite 21st-century fears of an &#8216;epidemic&#8217; of loneliness, its history has been sorely neglected. A Biography of Loneliness offers a radically new interpretation of loneliness as an emotional language and experience. Using letters and diaries, philosophical tracts, political discussions, and medical literature from the eighteenth century to the present, historian of the emotions Fay Bound Alberti argues that loneliness is not an ahistorical, universal<br />
                    phenomenon. It is, in fact, a modern emotion: before 1800, its language did not exist. And where loneliness is identified, it is not always bad, but a complex emotional state that differs according to class, gender, ethnicity and experience.    </p>
<p>                    Looking at informative case studies such as Sylvia Plath, Queen Victoria, and Virginia Woolf, A Biography of Loneliness charts the emergence of loneliness as a modern and embodied emotional state.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/">A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral codes and public policies. Illustrations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans. Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests? By studying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans.      </p>
<p>                    Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests?     </p>
<p>                    By studying social behaviors in animals, such as bonding, the herd instinct, the forming of trusting alliances, expressions of consolation, and conflict resolution, Frans de Waal demonstrates that animals-and humans-are preprogrammed to reach out. He has found that chimpanzees care for mates that are wounded by leopards, elephants offer reassuring rumbles to youngsters in distress, and dolphins support sick companions near the water&#8217;s surface to prevent them from drowning. From day one humans have innate sensitivities to faces, bodies, and voices; we&#8217;ve been designed to feel for one another.     </p>
<p>                    De Waal&#8217;s theory runs counter to the assumption that humans are inherently selfish, which can be seen in the fields of politics, law, and finance. But he cites the public&#8217;s outrage at the U.S. government&#8217;s lack of empathy in the wake of Hurricane Katrina as a significant shift in perspective-one that helped Barack Obama become elected and ushered in what perhaps could become an Age of Empathy. Through a better understanding of empathy&#8217;s survival value in evolution, de Waal suggests, we can work together toward a more just society based on a more generous and accurate view of human nature.     </p>
<p>                    Written in layman&#8217;s prose with a wealth of anecdotes, wry humor, and incisive intelligence, The Age of Empathy is essential reading for our embattled times.     </p>
<p>                    An important and timely message about the biological roots of human kindness.&#8211;Desmond Morris, author of The Naked Ape</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bad Feminist &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bad-feminist-roxane-gay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bad-feminist-roxane-gay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Roxane Gay is so great at weaving the intimate and personal with what is most bewildering and upsetting at this moment in culture. She is always looking, always thinking, always passionate, always careful, always right there.&#8221; &#8212; Sheila Heti, author of How Should a Person Be? A New York Times Bestseller Best Book of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bad-feminist-roxane-gay-abridged/">Bad Feminist &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Roxane Gay is so great at weaving the intimate and personal with what is most bewildering and upsetting at this moment in culture. She is always looking, always thinking, always passionate, always careful, always right there.&#8221; &#8212; Sheila Heti, author of How Should a Person Be?    </p>
<p>                    A New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Best Book of the Year: NPR &#8211; Boston Globe &#8211; Newsweek &#8211; Time Out New York &#8211; Oprah.com &#8211; Miami Herald &#8211; Book Riot &#8211; Buzz Feed &#8211; Globe and Mail (Toronto) &#8211; The Root &#8211; Shelf Awareness    </p>
<p>                    A collection of essays spanning politics, criticism, and feminism from one of the most-watched cultural observers of her generation    </p>
<p>                    In these funny and insightful essays, Gay takes us through the journey of her evolution as a woman (Sweet Valley High) of color (The Help) while also taking readers on a ride through culture of the last few years (Girls, Django in Chains) and commenting on the state of feminism today (abortion, Chris Brown). The portrait that emerges is not only one of an incredibly insightful woman continually growing to understand herself and our society, but also one of our culture.    </p>
<p>                    Bad Feminist is a sharp, funny, and spot-on look at the ways in which the culture we consume becomes who we are, and an inspiring call-to-arms of all the ways we still need to do better, coming from one of our most interesting and important cultural critics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bad-feminist-roxane-gay-abridged/">Bad Feminist &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Necessity : Adventures In The World Of Human Waste &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Produced behind closed doors, disposed of discreetly, hidden by euphemism, shit is rarely out in the open in &#8216;civilized&#8217; society, but the world of waste &#8211; and the people who deal with it, work with it and in it &#8211; is a rich one.This book takes us underground to the sewers of New York and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/">The Big Necessity : Adventures In The World Of Human Waste &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Produced behind closed doors, disposed of discreetly, hidden by euphemism, shit is rarely out in the open in &#8216;civilized&#8217; society, but the world of waste &#8211; and the people who deal with it, work with it and in it &#8211; is a rich one.This book takes us underground to the sewers of New York and London and overground to meet the heroes of India&#8217;s sanitation movement, American sewage schoolteachers, the Japanese genius at the cutting edge of toilet technology and the biosolids lobbying team. With a journalist&#8217;s nose for story and a campaigner&#8217;s desire for change, Rose George also addresses the politics of this under-reported social and environmental effluent, and the consequences of our reluctance to talk about it. Witty and original, The Big Necessity proves that shit doesn&#8217;t have to be a dirty word.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-necessity-adventures-in-the-world-of-human-waste-rose-george-abridged/">The Big Necessity : Adventures In The World Of Human Waste &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A personal and powerful essay from Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie, the bestselling author of Americanah and Half of a Yellow Sun. &#8216;I would like to ask that we begin to dream about and plan for a different world. A fairer world. A world of happier men and happier women who are truer to themselves. And this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A personal and powerful essay from Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie, the bestselling author of Americanah and Half of a Yellow Sun.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;I would like to ask that we begin to dream about and plan for a different world. A fairer world. A world of happier men and happier women who are truer to themselves. And this is how to start: we must raise our daughters differently. We must also raise our sons differently&#8230;&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              What does &#8220;feminism&#8221; mean today?    </p>
<p>                              In this personal, eloquently argued essay &#8211; adapted from her much-admired Tedx talk of the same name &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie offers readers a unique definition of feminism for the twenty-first century, one rooted in inclusion and awareness. Drawing extensively on her own experiences and her deep understanding of the often masked realities of sexual politics, here is one remarkable author&#8217;s exploration of what it means to be a woman now &#8211; an of-the-moment rallying cry for why we should all be feminists.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-should-all-be-feminists-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">We Should All Be Feminists &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Seinfeldia : How a Show About Nothing Changed Everything &#8211; Jennifer Keishin Armstrong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/seinfeldia-how-a-show-about-nothing-changed-everything-jennifer-keishin-armstrong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celebrity Biographies & Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/seinfeldia-how-a-show-about-nothing-changed-everything-jennifer-keishin-armstrong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller about two guys who went out for coffee and dreamed up Seinfeld-&#8220;A wildly entertaining must-read not only for Seinfeld fans but for anyone who wants a better understanding of how television series are made&#8221; (Booklist, starred review). Comedians Larry David and Jerry Seinfeld never thought anyone would watch their sitcom [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/seinfeldia-how-a-show-about-nothing-changed-everything-jennifer-keishin-armstrong-abridged/">Seinfeldia : How a Show About Nothing Changed Everything &#8211; Jennifer Keishin Armstrong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller about two guys who went out for coffee and dreamed up Seinfeld-&#8220;A wildly entertaining must-read not only for Seinfeld fans but for anyone who wants a better understanding of how television series are made&#8221; (Booklist, starred review).    </p>
<p>                    Comedians Larry David and Jerry Seinfeld never thought anyone would watch their sitcom about a New York comedian sitting around talking to his friends. But against all odds, viewers did watch-first a few and then many, until nine years later nearly forty million Americans were tuning in weekly. Fussy Jerry, neurotic George, eccentric Kramer, and imperious Elaine-people embraced them with love.    </p>
<p>                    Seinfeldia, Jennifer Keishin Armstrong&#8217;s intimate history is full of gossipy details, show trivia, and insights into how famous episodes came to be. Armstrong celebrates the creators and fans of this American television phenomenon, bringing readers into the writers&#8217; room and into a world of devotees for whom it never stopped being relevant. Seinfeld created a strange new reality, one where years after the show had ended the Soup Nazi still spends his days saying &#8220;No soup for you!&#8221;, Joe Davola gets questioned every day about his sanity, and Kenny Kramer makes his living giving tours of New York sites from the show.    </p>
<p>                    Seinfeldia is an outrageous cultural history. Dwight Garner of The New York Times Book Review wrote: &#8220;Armstrong has an eye for detail&#8230;.Perhaps the highest praise I can give Seinfeldia is that it made me want to buy a loaf of marbled rye and start watching again, from the beginning.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/seinfeldia-how-a-show-about-nothing-changed-everything-jennifer-keishin-armstrong-abridged/">Seinfeldia : How a Show About Nothing Changed Everything &#8211; Jennifer Keishin Armstrong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trying Not to Try : The Ancient Art of Effortlessness and the Surprising Power of Spontaneity &#8211; Edward Slingerland (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trying-not-to-try-the-ancient-art-of-effortlessness-and-the-surprising-power-of-spontaneity-edward-slingerland-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trying-not-to-try-the-ancient-art-of-effortlessness-and-the-surprising-power-of-spontaneity-edward-slingerland-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Guardian Best Book of 2014 A 2014 Brain Pickings Best Book on Psychology, Philosophy, and How to Live Meaningfully Why is it hard to fall asleep the night before an important meeting? Or be charming and relaxed on a first date? What is it about a comedian whose jokes fall flat or an athlete [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trying-not-to-try-the-ancient-art-of-effortlessness-and-the-surprising-power-of-spontaneity-edward-slingerland-abridged/">Trying Not to Try : The Ancient Art of Effortlessness and the Surprising Power of Spontaneity &#8211; Edward Slingerland (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Guardian Best Book of 2014<br />
                    A 2014 Brain Pickings Best Book on Psychology, Philosophy, and How to Live Meaningfully    </p>
<p>                    Why is it hard to fall asleep the night before an important meeting? Or be charming and relaxed on a first date? What is it about a comedian whose jokes fall flat or an athlete who chokes?     </p>
<p>                    What if, contrary to what we have long been told, spontaneity &#8211; not striving &#8211; is the answer to success? Through stories of mythical creatures and drunken cart riders, jazz musicians and Japanese motorcycle gangs, Slingerland effortlessly blends Eastern thought and cutting-edge science to show us how we can embody a spontaneous way of being and live more fulfilling lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trying-not-to-try-the-ancient-art-of-effortlessness-and-the-surprising-power-of-spontaneity-edward-slingerland-abridged/">Trying Not to Try : The Ancient Art of Effortlessness and the Surprising Power of Spontaneity &#8211; Edward Slingerland (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Misfit Economy : Lessons in Creativity from Pirates, Hackers, Gangsters and Other Informal Entrepreneurs &#8211; Alexa Clay, Kyra Maya Phillips (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-misfit-economy-lessons-in-creativity-from-pirates-hackers-gangsters-and-other-informal-entrepreneurs-alexa-clay-kyra-maya-phillips-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-misfit-economy-lessons-in-creativity-from-pirates-hackers-gangsters-and-other-informal-entrepreneurs-alexa-clay-kyra-maya-phillips-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Misfit Economy is about people who are just as innovative, entrepreneurial, and visionary as the Jobses, Edisons, and Fords of the world, except they&#8217;re not operating out of Silicon Valley. They&#8217;re in the street markets of Sao Paulo and Guangzhou, the rubbish dumps of Lagos, the flooded coastal towns of Thailand. They are pirates, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-misfit-economy-lessons-in-creativity-from-pirates-hackers-gangsters-and-other-informal-entrepreneurs-alexa-clay-kyra-maya-phillips-abridged/">The Misfit Economy : Lessons in Creativity from Pirates, Hackers, Gangsters and Other Informal Entrepreneurs &#8211; Alexa Clay, Kyra Maya Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Misfit Economy is about people who are just as innovative, entrepreneurial, and visionary as the Jobses, Edisons, and Fords of the world, except they&#8217;re not operating out of Silicon Valley. They&#8217;re in the street markets of Sao Paulo and Guangzhou, the rubbish dumps of Lagos, the flooded coastal towns of Thailand. They are pirates, slum dwellers, computer hackers, dissidents, and inner city gang members.<br />
                         Across the globe, diverse innovators are working in the black, grey, and informal economies to develop solutions to myriad challenges. Far from being &#8220;deviant entrepreneurs&#8221; that pose threats to our social and economic stability, these innovators display remarkable ingenuity, pioneering original methods and best practices that we can learn from and apply to formal markets in urgent need of change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-misfit-economy-lessons-in-creativity-from-pirates-hackers-gangsters-and-other-informal-entrepreneurs-alexa-clay-kyra-maya-phillips-abridged/">The Misfit Economy : Lessons in Creativity from Pirates, Hackers, Gangsters and Other Informal Entrepreneurs &#8211; Alexa Clay, Kyra Maya Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Death of Truth &#8211; Michiko Kakutani (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-death-of-truth-michiko-kakutani-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-death-of-truth-michiko-kakutani-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a Pulitzer Prize-winning critic comes an impassioned critique of the West&#8217;s retreat from reason. &#8216;The Death of Truth is destined to become the defining treatise of our age&#8217; David Grann &#8216;The first great book of the Trump administration &#8230; essential reading&#8217; Rolling Stone We live in a time when the very idea of objective [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-truth-michiko-kakutani-abridged/">The Death of Truth &#8211; Michiko Kakutani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a Pulitzer Prize-winning critic comes an impassioned critique of the West&#8217;s retreat from reason.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;The Death of Truth is destined to become the defining treatise of our age&#8217; David Grann    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;The first great book of the Trump administration &#8230; essential reading&#8217; Rolling Stone    </p>
<p>                              We live in a time when the very idea of objective truth is mocked and discounted by the US President. Discredited conspiracy theories and ideologies have resurfaced, proven science is once more up for debate, and Russian propaganda floods our screens. The wisdom of the crowd has usurped research and expertise, and we are each left clinging to the beliefs that best confirm our biases.    </p>
<p>                              How did truth become an endangered species? This decline began decades ago, and in The Death of Truth, former New York Times critic Michiko Kakutani takes a penetrating look at the cultural forces that contributed to this gathering storm. In social media and literature, television, academia, and political campaigns, Kakutani identifies the trends &#8211; originating on both the right and the left &#8211; that have combined to elevate subjectivity over factuality, science, and common values. And she returns us to the words of the great critics of authoritarianism, writers like George Orwell and Hannah Arendt, whose work is newly and eerily relevant.    </p>
<p>                              With remarkable erudition and insight, Kakutani offers a provocative diagnosis of our current condition and presents a path forward for our truth-challenged times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-truth-michiko-kakutani-abridged/">The Death of Truth &#8211; Michiko Kakutani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable. We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable.    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the time of Columbus, Copernicus, Gutenberg and others, redrew all maps of the world, liberated information and shifted Western civilization from the medieval to the early modern era. Such change came at a price: social division, political extremism, economic shocks, pandemics and other unintended consequences of human endeavour.    </p>
<p>                    Now is our second Renaissance. In the face of terrorism, Brexit, refugee crises and the global impact of a Trump presidency, we can flourish-if we heed the urgent lessons of history. Age of Discovery, revised and updated for this paperback edition, shows us how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thick And Other Essays &#8211; Tressie McMillan Cottom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thick-and-other-essays-tressie-mcmillan-cottom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thick-and-other-essays-tressie-mcmillan-cottom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In eight highly praised treatises on beauty, media, money, and more, Tressie McMillan Cottom &#8211; award-winning professor and acclaimed author of Lower Ed &#8211; is unapologetically &#8216;thick&#8217;: deemed &#8216;thick where I should have been thin, more where I should have been less,&#8217; McMillan Cottom refuses to shy away from blending the personal with the political, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thick-and-other-essays-tressie-mcmillan-cottom-abridged/">Thick And Other Essays &#8211; Tressie McMillan Cottom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In eight highly praised treatises on beauty, media, money, and more, Tressie McMillan Cottom &#8211; award-winning professor and acclaimed author of Lower Ed &#8211; is unapologetically &#8216;thick&#8217;: deemed &#8216;thick where I should have been thin, more where I should have been less,&#8217; McMillan Cottom refuses to shy away from blending the personal with the political, from bringing her full self and voice to the fore of her analytical work.In eight highly praised treatises on beauty, media, money, and more, Tressie McMillan Cottom &#8211; award-winning professor and acclaimed author of Lower Ed &#8211; is unapologetically &#8216;thick&#8217;: deemed &#8216;thick where I should have been thin, more where I should have been less,&#8217; McMillan Cottom refuses to shy away from blending the personal with the political, from bringing her full self and voice to the fore of her analytical work. Collected in an indispensable volume that speaks to the everywoman and the erudite alike, these unforgettable essays never fail to be &#8216;painfully honest and</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thick-and-other-essays-tressie-mcmillan-cottom-abridged/">Thick And Other Essays &#8211; Tressie McMillan Cottom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Will Be My Undoing : Living at the Intersection of Black, Female, and Feminist in (White) America &#8211; Morgan Jerkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-will-be-my-undoing-living-at-the-intersection-of-black-female-and-feminist-in-white-america-morgan-jerkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-will-be-my-undoing-living-at-the-intersection-of-black-female-and-feminist-in-white-america-morgan-jerkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;I can&#8217;t wait to read&#8230;This Will Be My Undoing.&#8221;-Roxane Gay One of the sharpest, fiercest, and most eloquent critics writing right now, Morgan Jerkins&#8217;s byline has appeared around the Internet for The New Yorker&#8217;s Page-Turner, Vogue, the New York Times, the Atlantic, Buzzfeed, and more; in this highly anticipated collection of linked essays perfect for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-will-be-my-undoing-living-at-the-intersection-of-black-female-and-feminist-in-white-america-morgan-jerkins-abridged/">This Will Be My Undoing : Living at the Intersection of Black, Female, and Feminist in (White) America &#8211; Morgan Jerkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;I can&#8217;t wait to read&#8230;This Will Be My Undoing.&#8221;-Roxane Gay     </p>
<p>                    One of the sharpest, fiercest, and most eloquent critics writing right now, Morgan Jerkins&#8217;s byline has appeared around the Internet for The New Yorker&#8217;s Page-Turner, Vogue, the New York Times, the Atlantic, Buzzfeed, and more; in this highly anticipated collection of linked essays perfect for fans of Bad Feminist, Rebecca Solnit&#8217;s Men Explain Things to Me, and Chimamanda Ngozie Adichie&#8217;s We Should All Be Feminists, Jerkins interweaves the incisive commentary on pop culture, feminism, black history, misogyny, and racism that she&#8217;s known for with her own experiences to confront the very real challenges of being a black woman today.    </p>
<p>                              &#8220;Growing up as a black woman is different. It prepares you to remember that you have to navigate two worlds. In this predominantly white, male-dominated world, you will never be white or male. Within the black community, belonging to the world of black women demands strength, wit, and aggression, because space for and by ourselves is small. You either assert yourself or learn to do so through humiliation, a constant shedding of respectability necessary to expose who you really are: just another black girl fighting to exist.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                              Morgan Jerkins is only in her twenties, but she has already established herself as an insightful, brutally honest writer who isn&#8217;t afraid of tackling tough, controversial subjects. In This Will Be My Undoing, she takes on perhaps one of the most provocative contemporary topics: What does it mean to &#8220;be&#8221;-to live as, to exist as-a black woman today? This is a book about black women, but it&#8217;s necessary reading for all Americans.     </p>
<p>                              Doubly disenfranchised by race and gender, often deprived of a place within the mostly white mainstream feminist movement, black women are objectified, silenced, and marginalized with devastating consequences, in ways both obvious and subtle, that are rarely acknowledged in our country&#8217;s larger discussion about inequality. In This Will Be My Undoing, Jerkins becomes both narrator and subject to expose the social, cultural, and historical story of black female oppression that influences the black community as well the white, male-dominated world at large.     </p>
<p>                              Whether she&#8217;s writing about Sailor Moon; Rachel Dolezal; the stigma of therapy; her complex relationship with her own physical body; the pain of dating when men say they don&#8217;t &#8220;see color&#8221;; being a black visitor in Russia; the specter of &#8220;the fast-tailed girl&#8221; and the paradox of black female sexuality; or disabled black women in the context of the &#8220;Black Girl Magic&#8221; movement, Jerkins is concise, compelling, and often revelatory.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-will-be-my-undoing-living-at-the-intersection-of-black-female-and-feminist-in-white-america-morgan-jerkins-abridged/">This Will Be My Undoing : Living at the Intersection of Black, Female, and Feminist in (White) America &#8211; Morgan Jerkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Listening Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you? This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever. At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation. On social media, we shape our personal narratives. At parties, we talk over one another. So do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show    </p>
<p>                    When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you?     </p>
<p>                    This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever.    </p>
<p>                     At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation.    </p>
<p>                     On social media, we shape our personal narratives.    </p>
<p>                     At parties, we talk over one another. So do our politicians.    </p>
<p>                     We&#8217;re not listening.    </p>
<p>                     And no one is listening to us.    </p>
<p>                    Now more than ever, we need to listen to those around us. New York Times contributor Kate Murphy draws on countless conversations she has had with everyone from priests to CIA interrogators, focus group moderators to bartenders, her great-great aunt to her friend&#8217;s toddler, to show how only by listening well can we truly connect with others.    </p>
<p>                     Listening has the potential to transform our relationships and our working lives, improve our self-knowledge, and increase our creativity and happiness. While it may take some effort, it&#8217;s a skill that can be learnt and perfected.    </p>
<p>                     When all we crave is to understand and be understood, You&#8217;re Not Listening shows us how.    </p>
<p>                    * With a new afterword by the author *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book couldn&#8217;t be more timely. Inspiringly profound&#8230;smart and playful&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ll be adopting Murphy&#8217;s advice&#8217; Sunday Times, Style</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good and Mad : The Revolutionary Power of Women&#8217;s Anger &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-and-mad-the-revolutionary-power-of-womens-anger-rebecca-traister-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-and-mad-the-revolutionary-power-of-womens-anger-rebecca-traister-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>***NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER*** ***BEST BOOKS OF 2018 SELECTION BY*** * WASHINGTON POST * People * NPR * ESQUIRE * ELLE * WIRED * REFINERY 29 * &#8220;In a year when issues of gender and sexuality dominated the national conversation, no one shaped that exchange more than Rebecca Traister. Her wise and provocative columns helped [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-and-mad-the-revolutionary-power-of-womens-anger-rebecca-traister-abridged/">Good and Mad : The Revolutionary Power of Women&#8217;s Anger &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>***NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER***    </p>
<p>                    ***BEST BOOKS OF 2018 SELECTION BY***<br />
                     * WASHINGTON POST  * People * NPR * ESQUIRE * ELLE * WIRED * REFINERY 29 *    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In a year when issues of gender and sexuality dominated the national conversation, no one shaped that exchange more than Rebecca Traister. Her wise and provocative columns helped make sense of a cultural transformation.&#8221;-National Magazine Award Citation, 2018    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The most brilliant voice on feminism in this country.&#8221;-Anne Lamott, author of Bird by Bird    </p>
<p>                    From Rebecca Traister, the New York Times bestselling author of All the Single Ladies comes a vital, incisive exploration into the transformative power of female anger and its ability to transcend into a political movement.     </p>
<p>                    In the year 2018, it seems as if women&#8217;s anger has suddenly erupted into the public conversation. But long before Pantsuit Nation, before the Women&#8217;s March, and before the #MeToo movement, women&#8217;s anger was not only politically catalytic-but politically problematic. The story of female fury and its cultural significance demonstrates the long history of bitter resentment that has enshrouded women&#8217;s slow rise to political power in America, as well as the ways that anger is received when it comes from women as opposed to when it comes from men.    </p>
<p>                     With eloquence and fervor, Rebecca tracks the history of female anger as political fuel-from suffragettes marching on the White House to office workers vacating their buildings after Clarence Thomas was confirmed to the Supreme Court. Here Traister explores women&#8217;s anger at both men and other women; anger between ideological allies and foes; the varied ways anger is perceived based on its owner; as well as the history of caricaturing and delegitimizing female anger; and the way women&#8217;s collective fury has become transformative political fuel-as is most certainly occurring today. She deconstructs society&#8217;s (and the media&#8217;s) condemnation of female emotion (notably, rage) and the impact of their resulting repercussions.    </p>
<p>                     Highlighting a double standard perpetuated against women by all sexes, and its disastrous, stultifying effect, Traister&#8217;s latest is timely and crucial. It offers a glimpse into the galvanizing force of women&#8217;s collective anger, which, when harnessed, can change history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-and-mad-the-revolutionary-power-of-womens-anger-rebecca-traister-abridged/">Good and Mad : The Revolutionary Power of Women&#8217;s Anger &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Were Eight Years in Power : An American Tragedy &#8211; Ta-Nehisi Coates (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-were-eight-years-in-power-an-american-tragedy-ta-nehisi-coates-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Administration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-were-eight-years-in-power-an-american-tragedy-ta-nehisi-coates-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this &#8220;urgently relevant&#8221;* collection featuring the landmark essay &#8220;The Case for Reparations,&#8221; the National Book Award-winning author of Between the World and Me &#8220;reflects on race, Barack Obama&#8217;s presidency and its jarring aftermath&#8221;*&#8211;including the election of Donald Trump. New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Finalist for the PEN/Jean Stein Book Award, the Los Angeles Times [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-were-eight-years-in-power-an-american-tragedy-ta-nehisi-coates-abridged/">We Were Eight Years in Power : An American Tragedy &#8211; Ta-Nehisi Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this &#8220;urgently relevant&#8221;* collection featuring the landmark essay &#8220;The Case for Reparations,&#8221; the National Book Award-winning author of Between the World and Me &#8220;reflects on race, Barack Obama&#8217;s presidency and its jarring aftermath&#8221;*&#8211;including the election of Donald Trump.      </p>
<p>                    New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Finalist for the PEN/Jean Stein Book Award, the Los Angeles Times Book Prize, and the Dayton Literary Peace Prize     </p>
<p>                     Named One of the Best Books of the Year by The New York Times &#8211; USA Today &#8211; Time &#8211; Los Angeles Times &#8211; San Francisco Chronicle &#8211; Essence &#8211; O: The Oprah Magazine &#8211; The Week &#8211; Kirkus Reviews     </p>
<p>                     *Kirkus Reviews (starred review)    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;We were eight years in power&#8221; was the lament of Reconstruction-era black politicians as the American experiment in multiracial democracy ended with the return of white supremacist rule in the South. In this sweeping collection of new and selected essays, Ta-Nehisi Coates explores the tragic echoes of that history in our own time: the unprecedented election of a black president followed by a vicious backlash that fueled the election of the man Coates argues is America&#8217;s &#8220;first white president.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     But the story of these present-day eight years is not just about presidential politics. This book also examines the new voices, ideas, and movements for justice that emerged over this period&#8211;and the effects of the persistent, haunting shadow of our nation&#8217;s old and unreconciled history. Coates powerfully examines the events of the Obama era from his intimate and revealing perspective&#8211;the point of view of a young writer who begins the journey in an unemployment office in Harlem and ends it in the Oval Office, interviewing a president.     </p>
<p>                     We Were Eight Years in Power features Coates&#8217;s iconic essays first published in The Atlantic,  including &#8220;Fear of a Black President,&#8221; &#8220;The Case for Reparations,&#8221; and &#8220;The Black Family in the Age of Mass Incarceration,&#8221; along with eight fresh essays that revisit each year of the Obama administration through Coates&#8217;s own experiences, observations, and intellectual development, capped by a bracingly original assessment of the election that fully illuminated the tragedy of the Obama era. We Were Eight Years in Power is a vital account of modern America, from one of the definitive voices of this historic moment.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-were-eight-years-in-power-an-american-tragedy-ta-nehisi-coates-abridged/">We Were Eight Years in Power : An American Tragedy &#8211; Ta-Nehisi Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happiness : A Guide to Developing Life&#8217;s Most Important Skill &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Although we are materially better off than ever before, surveys show that we are depressed and listless. In his revolutionary book, Buddhist monk Matthieu Ricard shows that happiness is not just an emotion, but a skill that can be developed. Free of jargon, Happiness contains simple exercises that will train the mind to recognize and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Happiness : A Guide to Developing Life&#8217;s Most Important Skill &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although we are materially better off than ever before, surveys show that we are depressed and listless. In his revolutionary book, Buddhist monk Matthieu Ricard shows that happiness is not just an emotion, but a skill that can be developed. Free of jargon, Happiness contains simple exercises that will train the mind to recognize and pursue happiness by concentrating on the fundamental things in life, and in doing so change the way we view the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happiness-a-guide-to-developing-lifes-most-important-skill-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Happiness : A Guide to Developing Life&#8217;s Most Important Skill &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Logic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order to coordinate its actions, a group of people must form &#8220;common knowledge.&#8221; Each person wants to participate only if others also participate. Members must have knowledge of each other, knowledge of that knowledge, knowledge of the knowledge of that knowledge, and so on. Michael Chwe applies this insight, with striking erudition, to analyze a range of rituals across history and cultures. He shows that public ceremonies are powerful not simply because they transmit meaning from a central source to each audience member but because they let audience members know what other members know. For instance, people watching the Super Bowl know that many others are seeing precisely what they see and that those people know in turn that many others are also watching.<br />
                    This creates common knowledge, and advertisers selling products that depend on consensus are willing to pay large sums to gain access to it. Remarkably, a great variety of rituals and ceremonies, such as formal inaugurations, work in much the same way. By using a rational-choice argument to explain diverse cultural practices, Chwe argues for a close reciprocal relationship between the perspectives of rationality and culture. He illustrates how game theory can be applied to an unexpectedly broad spectrum of problems, while showing in an admirably clear way what game theory might hold for scholars in the social sciences and humanities who are not yet acquainted with it. In a new afterword, Chwe delves into new applications of common knowledge, both in the real world and in experiments, and considers how generating common knowledge has become easier in the digital age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FULLY REVISED &#038; UPDATED, WITH A NEW EPILOGUE &#8220;Delightful.&#8221;-The Economist There&#8217;s Santa Claus, Shakespeare, Mickey Mouse, the Bible, and then there&#8217;s Star Wars. Nothing quite compares to sitting down with a young child and hearing the sound of John Williams&#8217;s score as those beloved golden letters fill the screen. In this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/">The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    FULLY REVISED &#038; UPDATED, WITH A NEW EPILOGUE    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Delightful.&#8221;-The Economist    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s Santa Claus, Shakespeare, Mickey Mouse, the Bible, and then there&#8217;s Star Wars. Nothing quite compares to sitting down with a young child and hearing the sound of John Williams&#8217;s score as those beloved golden letters fill the screen. In this fun, erudite, and often moving book, Cass R. Sunstein explores the lessons of Star Wars as they relate to childhood, fathers, the Dark Side, rebellion, and redemption. As it turns out, Star Wars also has a lot to teach us about constitutional law, economics, and political uprisings.    </p>
<p>                              In rich detail, Sunstein tells the story of the films&#8217; wildly unanticipated success and explores why some things succeed while others fail. Ultimately, Sunstein argues, Star Wars is about freedom of choice and our never-ending ability to make the right decision when the chips are down. Written with buoyant prose and considerable heart, The World According to Star Wars shines a bright new light on the most beloved story of our time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/">The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes. &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world. Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen. 54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves. Norway is the richest country on earth. 5 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world.    </p>
<p>                    Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen.    </p>
<p>                    54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves.    </p>
<p>                    Norway is the richest country on earth.    </p>
<p>                    5 per cent of Danish men have had sex with an animal.    </p>
<p>                    Michael Booth has lived among the Scandinavians, on and off, for over ten years, perplexed by their many strange paradoxes and character traits and equally bemused by the unquestioning enthusiasm for all things Nordic and hygge that has engulfed the rest of the world.     </p>
<p>                    He leaves his adopted home of Denmark and embarks on a journey through all five of the Nordic countries to discover who these curious tribes are, the secrets of their success and, most intriguing of all, what they think of each other. Along the way a more nuanced, often darker picture emerges of a region plagued by taboos, characterised by suffocating parochialism and populated by extremists of various shades.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The next Bill Bryson.&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Best Narrative Travel Book Award from the British Guild of Travel Writers</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control  chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;brilliant and provocative&#8221; (Walter Isaacson) guide shares nine principles to adapt and survive the technological changes shaping our future from the director of the MIT Media Lab and a veteran Wired journalist. The world is more complex and volatile today than at any other time in our history. The tools of our modern existence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/">Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;brilliant and provocative&#8221; (Walter Isaacson) guide shares nine principles to adapt and survive the technological changes shaping our future from the director of the MIT Media Lab and a veteran Wired journalist.  The world is more complex and volatile today than at any other time in our history. The tools of our modern existence are getting faster, cheaper, and smaller at an exponential rate, transforming every aspect of society, from business to culture and from the public sphere to our most private moments. The people who succeed will be the ones who learn to think differently.  In Whiplash, Joi Ito and Jeff Howe distill that logic into nine organizing principles for navigating and surviving this tumultuous period: Emergence over Authority Pull over Push Compasses over Maps Risk over Safety Disobedience over Compliance Practice over Theory Diversity over Ability Resilience over Strength Systems over Objects   Filled with incredible case studies and cutting-edge research and philosophies from the MIT Media Lab and beyond, Whiplash will help you adapt and succeed in this unpredictable world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/">Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All the Single Ladies : Unmarried Women and the Rise of an Independent Nation &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/all-the-single-ladies-unmarried-women-and-the-rise-of-an-independent-nation-rebecca-traister-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/all-the-single-ladies-unmarried-women-and-the-rise-of-an-independent-nation-rebecca-traister-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOKS OF 2016 SELECTION * BEST BOOKS OF 2016 SELECTION BY THE BOSTON GLOBE * ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY * NPR * CHICAGO PUBLIC LIBRARY * The New York Times bestselling investigation into the sexual, economic, and emotional lives of women is &#8220;an informative and thought-provoking book for anyone-not just the single [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-the-single-ladies-unmarried-women-and-the-rise-of-an-independent-nation-rebecca-traister-abridged/">All the Single Ladies : Unmarried Women and the Rise of an Independent Nation &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOKS OF 2016 SELECTION * BEST BOOKS OF 2016 SELECTION BY THE BOSTON GLOBE * ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY * NPR * CHICAGO PUBLIC LIBRARY *    </p>
<p>                     The New York Times bestselling investigation into the sexual, economic, and emotional lives of women is &#8220;an informative and thought-provoking book for anyone-not just the single ladies-who want to gain a greater understanding of this pivotal moment in the history of the United States&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review).    </p>
<p>                    In 2009, award-winning journalist Rebecca Traister started All the Single Ladies about the twenty-first century phenomenon of the American single woman. It was the year the proportion of American women who were married dropped below fifty percent; and the median age of first marriages, which had remained between twenty and twenty-two years old for nearly a century (1890-1980), had risen dramatically to twenty-seven.    </p>
<p>                    But over the course of her vast research and more than a hundred interviews with academics and social scientists and prominent single women, Traister discovered a startling truth: the phenomenon of the single woman in America is not a new one. And historically, when women were given options beyond early heterosexual marriage, the results were massive social change-temperance, abolition, secondary education, and more. Today, only twenty percent of Americans are married by age twenty-nine, compared to nearly sixty percent in 1960.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An informative and thought-provoking book for anyone-not just single ladies&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review), All the Single Ladies is a remarkable portrait of contemporary American life and how we got here, through the lens of the unmarried American woman. Covering class, race, sexual orientation, and filled with vivid anecdotes from fascinating contemporary and historical figures, &#8220;we&#8217;re better off reading Rebecca Traister on women, politics, and America than pretty much anyone else&#8221; (The Boston Globe).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-the-single-ladies-unmarried-women-and-the-rise-of-an-independent-nation-rebecca-traister-abridged/">All the Single Ladies : Unmarried Women and the Rise of an Independent Nation &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller that explains why certain products and ideas become popular. &#8220;Jonah Berger knows more about what makes information &#8216;go viral&#8217; than anyone in the world.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, author of the bestseller Stumbling on Happiness What makes things popular? If you said advertising, think again. People don&#8217;t listen to advertisements, they listen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/">Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller that explains why certain products and ideas become popular.      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jonah Berger knows more about what makes information &#8216;go viral&#8217; than anyone in the world.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, author of the bestseller Stumbling on Happiness     </p>
<p>                    What makes things popular? If you said advertising, think again. People don&#8217;t listen to advertisements, they listen to their peers. But why do people talk about certain products and ideas more than others? Why are some stories and rumors more infectious? And what makes online content go viral?     </p>
<p>                    Wharton marketing professor Jonah Berger has spent the last decade answering these questions. He&#8217;s studied why New York Times articles make the paper&#8217;s own Most E-mailed list, why products get word of mouth, and how social influence shapes everything from the cars we buy to the clothes we wear to the names we give our children.     </p>
<p>                    In Contagious, Berger reveals the secret science behind word-of-mouth and social transmission. Discover how six basic principles drive all sorts of things to become contagious, from consumer products and policy initiatives to workplace rumors and YouTube videos. Learn how a luxury steakhouse found popularity through the lowly cheesesteak, why anti-drug commercials might have actually increased drug use, and why more than 200 million consumers shared a video about one of the most boring products there is: a blender.     </p>
<p>                    Contagious provides specific, actionable techniques for helping information spread&#8211;for designing messages, advertisements, and content that people will share. Whether you&#8217;re a manager at a big company, a small business owner trying to boost awareness, a politician running for office, or a health official trying to get the word out, Contagious will show you how to make your product or idea catch on.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/">Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A People&#8217;s History of the United States &#8211; Howard Zinn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-peoples-history-of-the-united-states-howard-zinn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American Civil War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-peoples-history-of-the-united-states-howard-zinn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE CLASSIC NATIONAL BESTSELLER A wonderful, splendid book&#8211;a book that should be read by every American, student or otherwise, who wants to understand his country, its true history, and its hope for the future. -Howard Fast Historian Howard Zinn&#8217;s A People&#8217;s History of the United States chronicles American history from the bottom up, throwing out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-peoples-history-of-the-united-states-howard-zinn-abridged/">A People&#8217;s History of the United States &#8211; Howard Zinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE CLASSIC NATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    A wonderful, splendid book&#8211;a book that should be read by every American, student or otherwise, who wants to understand his country, its true history, and its hope for the future. -Howard Fast    </p>
<p>                    Historian Howard Zinn&#8217;s A People&#8217;s History of the United States chronicles American history from the bottom up, throwing out the official narrative taught in schools&#8211;with its emphasis on great men in high places&#8211;to focus on the street, the home, and the workplace.    </p>
<p>                    Known for its lively, clear prose as well as its scholarly research, it is the only volume to tell America&#8217;s story from the point of view of&#8211;and in the words of&#8211;America&#8217;s women, factory workers, African-Americans, Native Americans, the working poor, and immigrant laborers. As Zinn shows, many of our country&#8217;s greatest battles&#8211;the fights for a fair wage, an eight-hour workday, child-labor laws, health and safety standards, universal suffrage, women&#8217;s rights, racial equality&#8211;were carried out at the grassroots level, against bloody resistance.     </p>
<p>                    Covering Christopher Columbus&#8217;s arrival through President Clinton&#8217;s first term, A People&#8217;s History of the United States features insightful analysis of the most important events in our history. This edition also includes an introduction by Anthony Arnove, who wrote, directed, and produced The People Speak with Zinn and who coauthored, with Zinn, Voices of a People&#8217;s History of the United States.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-peoples-history-of-the-united-states-howard-zinn-abridged/">A People&#8217;s History of the United States &#8211; Howard Zinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
