<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Pollution &amp; Threats To The Environment Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/pollution-threats-to-the-environment/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/pollution-threats-to-the-environment/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Pollution &amp; Threats To The Environment Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/pollution-threats-to-the-environment/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Command and Control &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/command-and-control-eric-schlosser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Weapons]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pollution & Threats To The Environment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/command-and-control-eric-schlosser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Command and Control interweaves the minute-by-minute story of an accident at a missile silo in rural Arkansas, where a single crew struggled to prevent the explosion of the most powerful nuclear warhead ever built by the United States, with a historical narrative that spans more than fifty years. It depicts the urgent effort to ensure [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/command-and-control-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Command and Control &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Command and Control interweaves the minute-by-minute story of an accident at a missile silo in rural Arkansas, where a single crew struggled to prevent the explosion of the most powerful nuclear warhead ever built by the United States, with a historical narrative that spans more than fifty years. It depicts the urgent effort to ensure that nuclear weapons can&#8217;t be stolen, sabotaged, used without permission, or detonated inadvertently. Schlosser also looks at the Cold War from a new perspective, offering history from the ground up, telling the stories of bomber pilots, missile commanders, maintenance crews, and other ordinary servicemen who risked their lives to avert a nuclear holocaust. Drawing on recently declassified documents and interviews with men who designed and routinely handled nuclear weapons, Command and Control takes readers into a terrifying but fascinating world that, until now, has been largely hidden from view.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/command-and-control-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Command and Control &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Radium Girls : They paid with their lives. Their final fight was for justice. &#8211; Kate Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-radium-girls-they-paid-with-their-lives-their-final-fight-was-for-justice-kate-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pollution & Threats To The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-radium-girls-they-paid-with-their-lives-their-final-fight-was-for-justice-kate-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Emma Watson&#8217;s Our Shared Shelf book club choice New York Times bestseller &#8216;Fascinating.&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Thrilling.&#8217; Mail on Sunday All they wanted was the chance to shine. Be careful what you wish for&#8230; &#8216;The first thing we asked was, &#8220;Does this stuff hurt you?&#8221; And they said, &#8220;No.&#8221; The company said that it wasn&#8217;t dangerous, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-radium-girls-they-paid-with-their-lives-their-final-fight-was-for-justice-kate-moore-abridged/">The Radium Girls : They paid with their lives. Their final fight was for justice. &#8211; Kate Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Emma Watson&#8217;s Our Shared Shelf book club choice<br />
                    New York Times bestseller    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fascinating.&#8217; Sunday Times<br />
                     &#8216;Thrilling.&#8217;       Mail on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    All they wanted was the chance to shine.    </p>
<p>                     Be careful what you wish for&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The first thing we asked was, &#8220;Does this stuff hurt you?&#8221; And they said, &#8220;No.&#8221; The company said that it wasn&#8217;t dangerous, that we didn&#8217;t need to be afraid.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     As the First World War spread across the world, young American women flocked to work in factories, painting clocks, watches and military dials with a special luminous substance made from radium. It was a fun job, lucrative and glamorous &#8211; the girls shone brightly in the dark, covered head to toe in dust from the paint.    </p>
<p>                     However, as the years passed, the women began to suffer from mysterious and crippling illnesses. It turned out that the very thing that had made them feel alive &#8211; their work &#8211; was slowly killing them: the radium paint was poisonous.    </p>
<p>                     Their employers denied all responsibility, but these courageous women &#8211; in the face of unimaginable suffering &#8211; refused to accept their fate quietly, and instead became determined to fight for justice.<br />
                     Drawing on previously unpublished diaries, letters and interviews, The Radium Girls is an intimate narrative of an unforgettable true story. It is the powerful tale of a group of ordinary women from the Roaring Twenties, who themselves learned how to roar.    </p>
<p>                    Further praise for The Radium Girls    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The importance of the brave and blighted dial-painters cannot be overstated.&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A perfect blend of the historical, the scientific and the personal.&#8217; Bustle    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Thrilling and carefully crafted.&#8217; Mail on Sunday</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-radium-girls-they-paid-with-their-lives-their-final-fight-was-for-justice-kate-moore-abridged/">The Radium Girls : They paid with their lives. Their final fight was for justice. &#8211; Kate Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pollution & Threats To The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When the U.S. Public Health Service endorsed water fluoridation in 1950, there was little evidence of its safety. Now, six decades later and after most countries have rejected the practice, more than 70 percent of Americans, as well as 200 million people worldwide, are drinking fluoridated water. The Center for Disease Control and the American [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/">The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When the U.S. Public Health Service endorsed water fluoridation in 1950, there was little evidence of its safety. Now, six decades later and after most countries have rejected the practice, more than 70 percent of Americans, as well as 200 million people worldwide, are drinking fluoridated water. The Center for Disease Control and the American Dental Association continue to promote it&#8211;and even mandatory statewide water fluoridation&#8211;despite increasing evidence that it is not only unnecessary, but potentially hazardous to human health.    </p>
<p>                    In this timely and important book, Dr. Paul Connett, Dr. James Beck, and Dr. H. Spedding Micklem take a new look at the science behind water fluoridation and argue that just because the dental and medical establishments endorse a public health measure doesn&#8217;t mean it&#8217;s safe. In the case of water fluoridation, the chemicals that go into the drinking water that more than 180 million people drink each day are not even pharmaceutical grade, but rather a hazardous waste product of the phosphate fertilizer industry. It is illegal to dump this waste into the sea or local surface water, and yet it is allowed in our drinking water. To make matters worse, this program receives no oversight from the Food and Drug Administration, and the Environmental Protection Agency takes no responsibility for the practice. And from an ethical standpoint, say the authors, water fluoridation is a bad medical practice: individuals are being forced to take medication without their informed consent, there is no control over the dose, and no monitoring of possible side effects.    </p>
<p>                    At once painstakingly documented and also highly readable, The Case Against Fluoride brings new research to light, including links between fluoride and harm to the brain, bones, and endocrine system, and argues that the evidence that fluoridation reduces tooth decay is surprisingly weak.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/">The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
