<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Autobiography: Sport Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/autobiography-sport/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/autobiography-sport/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Autobiography: Sport Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/autobiography-sport/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Eleven Rings : The Soul of Success &#8211; Phil Jackson</title>
		<link>/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Through candor and comprehensiveness, Jackson writes a convincing revisionist take, in which he emerges as an excellent coach . . . highly readable . . . reflects Jackson&#8217;s polymathy.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review &#8220;Part sports memoir, part New Age spirit quest, part pseudo-management tract . . . But the primary thing with Jackson-as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/">Eleven Rings : The Soul of Success &#8211; Phil Jackson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Through candor and comprehensiveness, Jackson writes a convincing revisionist take, in which he emerges as an excellent coach . . . highly readable . . . reflects Jackson&#8217;s polymathy.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Part sports memoir, part New Age spirit quest, part pseudo-management tract . . . But the primary thing with Jackson-as with all the old bards, who were also known for repeating themselves-is the voice.&#8221; -Sam Anderson, The New York Times Magazine</p>
<p>                    A New York Times Bestseller</p>
<p>                    The inside story of one of basketball&#8217;s most legendary and game-changing figures </p>
<p>                    During his storied career as head coach of the Chicago Bulls and Los Angeles Lakers, Phil Jackson won more championships than any coach in the history of professional sports. Even more important, he succeeded in never wavering from coaching his way, from a place of deep values. Jackson was tagged as the &#8220;Zen master&#8221; half in jest by sportswriters, but the nickname speaks to an important truth: this is a coach who inspired, not goaded; who led by awakening and challenging the better angels of his players&#8217; nature, not their egos, fear, or greed.</p>
<p>                     This is the story of a preacher&#8217;s kid from North Dakota who grew up to be one of the most innovative leaders of our time. In his quest to reinvent himself, Jackson explored everything from humanistic psychology and Native American philosophy to Zen meditation. In the process, he developed a new approach to leadership based on freedom, authenticity, and selfless teamwork that turned the hypercompetitive world of professional sports on its head.</p>
<p>                     In Eleven Rings, Jackson candidly describes how he: </p>
<p>                       *  Learned the secrets of mindfulness and team chemistry while playing for the champion New York Knicks in the 1970s<br />
                       *  Managed Michael Jordan, the greatest player in the world, and got him to embrace selflessness, even if it meant losing a scoring title<br />
                       *  Forged successful teams out of players of varying abilities by getting them to trust one another and perform in sync<br />
                       *  Inspired Dennis Rodman and other &#8220;uncoachable&#8221; personalities to devote themselves to something larger than themselves<br />
                       *  Transformed Kobe Bryant from a rebellious teenager into a mature leader of a championship team. </p>
<p>                     Eleven times, Jackson led his teams to the ultimate goal: the NBA championship-six times with the Chicago Bulls and five times with the Los Angeles Lakers. We all know the legendary stars on those teams, or think we do. What Eleven Rings shows us, however, is that when it comes to the most important lessons, we don&#8217;t know very much at all. This book is full of revelations: about fascinating personalities and their drive to win; about the wellsprings of motivation and competition at the highest levels; and about what it takes to bring out the best in ourselves and others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/">Eleven Rings : The Soul of Success &#8211; Phil Jackson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unstoppable : My Life So Far &#8211; Maria Sharapova (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fiercely honest, fearless, darkly funny autobiography of global tennis star Maria Sharapova In the middle of the night, a father and his daughter step off a Greyhound bus in Florida and head straight to the Nick Bollettieri Tennis Academy. They ring the bell, though no one is expecting them and they don&#8217;t speak English. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/">Unstoppable : My Life So Far &#8211; Maria Sharapova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fiercely honest, fearless, darkly funny autobiography of global tennis star Maria Sharapova    </p>
<p>                    In the middle of the night, a father and his daughter step off a Greyhound bus in Florida and head straight to the Nick Bollettieri Tennis Academy. They ring the bell, though no one is expecting them and they don&#8217;t speak English. They have arrived from Russia with just seven hundred dollars and the conviction that this six-year-old girl will be the world&#8217;s next great tennis star. They are right.    </p>
<p>                    This is Maria Sharapova&#8217;s gripping and fearless autobiography, telling her story from her roots in the small Siberian town her parents fled to after the Chernobyl disaster, through her arrival in the US with nothing and her phenomenal rise to success &#8211; winning Wimbledon aged just seventeen &#8211; to the disasters that threatened her career and her fight back.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling memoir&#8217; David Shaftel, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An illuminating account &#8230; This is the bildungsroman of a controversial champion, a portrait of the athlete as an uncommonly driven young woman&#8217; Julia Felsenthal, Vogue</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/">Unstoppable : My Life So Far &#8211; Maria Sharapova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Boating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olympic Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rowing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism, Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Sports & Recreations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year, this is the bestselling story about a rowing team&#8217;s quest for Olympic gold in Nazi Germany. Cast aside by his family at an early age, abandoned and left to fend for himself in the woods of Washington State, young Joe Rantz turns to rowing as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/">The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year, this is the bestselling story about a rowing team&#8217;s quest for Olympic gold in Nazi Germany.     </p>
<p>                    Cast aside by his family at an early age, abandoned and left to fend for himself in the woods of Washington State, young Joe Rantz turns to rowing as a way of escaping his past.    </p>
<p>                     What follows is an extraordinary journey, as Joe and eight other working-class boys exchange the sweat and dust of life in 1930s America for the promise of glory at the heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin. Stroke by stroke, a remarkable young man strives to regain his shattered self-regard, to dare again to trust in others &#8211; and to find his way back home.    </p>
<p>                     Told against the backdrop of the Great Depression, Daniel James Brown&#8217;s The Boys in the Boat is narrative non-fiction of the first order; a personal story full of lyricism and unexpected beauty that rises above the grand sweep of history, and captures instead the purest essence of what it means to be alive.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;I really can&#8217;t rave enough about this book . . . I read the last fifty pages with white knuckles, and the last twenty-five with tears in my eyes&#8217; &#8211; David Laskin, author of The Children&#8217;s Blizzard and The Long Way Home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/">The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
