<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Child Care &amp; Upbringing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/child-care-upbringing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/child-care-upbringing/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Child Care &amp; Upbringing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/child-care-upbringing/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>If I Have to Tell You One More Time&#8230; : The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids to Listen without Nagging, Reminding or Yelling &#8211; Amy McCready</title>
		<link>/if-i-have-to-tell-you-one-more-time-the-revolutionary-program-that-gets-your-kids-to-listen-without-nagging-reminding-or-yelling-amy-mccready/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/if-i-have-to-tell-you-one-more-time-the-revolutionary-program-that-gets-your-kids-to-listen-without-nagging-reminding-or-yelling-amy-mccready/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids To Listen Without Nagging, Reminding, or Yelling Why does it feel sometimes as if our children have special powers that enable them to tune us out completely? You ask your child to do her homework, get ready for school or bedtime. You think she heard you but . [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/if-i-have-to-tell-you-one-more-time-the-revolutionary-program-that-gets-your-kids-to-listen-without-nagging-reminding-or-yelling-amy-mccready/">If I Have to Tell You One More Time&#8230; : The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids to Listen without Nagging, Reminding or Yelling &#8211; Amy McCready</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids To Listen Without Nagging, Reminding, or Yelling     </p>
<p>                    Why does it feel sometimes as if our children have special powers that enable them to tune us out completely? You ask your child to do her homework, get ready for school or bedtime. You think she heard you but . . . no response. You&#8217;ve tried everything&#8211;time-outs, nagging, counting to three&#8211;and nothing seems to work. In this invaluable book, Amy McCready, founder of the popular online parenting course Positive Parenting Solutions, presents a nag-and-scream-free program for compassionately yet effectively, correcting your children&#8217;s bad behavior.    </p>
<p>                    McCready draws on Adlerian psychology and Positive Discipline, which focuses on the central idea that every human being has a basic need to feel connected and empowered&#8211;children being no exception to the rule. According to McCready, when this need isn&#8217;t met in positive ways, kids resort to negative methods. In this book she provides parents with a virtual toolbox of strategies they can use to give their children the attention and power they crave&#8211;and do away with the misbehaving that adults dread.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/if-i-have-to-tell-you-one-more-time-the-revolutionary-program-that-gets-your-kids-to-listen-without-nagging-reminding-or-yelling-amy-mccready/">If I Have to Tell You One More Time&#8230; : The Revolutionary Program That Gets Your Kids to Listen without Nagging, Reminding or Yelling &#8211; Amy McCready</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee and Po Bronson and Ashley Merryman&#8217;s Nurture Shock, New York Times &#8220;Your Money&#8221; columnist Ron Lieber delivers a taboo-shattering manifesto that explains how talking openly to children about money can help parents raise modest, patient, grounded young adults who are financially wise beyond [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/">The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee and Po Bronson and Ashley Merryman&#8217;s Nurture Shock, New York Times &#8220;Your Money&#8221; columnist Ron Lieber delivers a taboo-shattering manifesto that explains how talking openly to children about money can help parents raise modest, patient, grounded young adults who are financially wise beyond their years.  For Ron Lieber, a personal finance columnist and father, good parenting means talking about money with our kids. Children are hyper-aware of money, and they have scores of questions about its nuances. But when parents shy away from the topic, they lose a tremendous opportunity-not just to model the basic financial behaviors that are increasingly important for young adults but also to imprint lessons about what the family truly values.  Written in a warm, accessible voice, grounded in real-world experience and stories from families with a range of incomes, The Opposite of Spoiled is both a practical guidebook and a values-based philosophy.<br />
                    The foundation of the book is a detailed blueprint for the best ways to handle the basics: the tooth fairy, allowance, chores, charity, saving, birthdays, holidays, cell phones, checking accounts, clothing, cars, part-time jobs, and college tuition. It identifies a set of traits and virtues that embody the opposite of spoiled, and shares how to embrace the topic of money to help parents raise kids who are more generous and less materialistic.  But The Opposite of Spoiled is also a promise to our kids that we will make them better with money than we are. It is for all of the parents who know that honest conversations about money with their curious children can help them become more patient and prudent, but who don&#8217;t know how and when to start.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/">The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Whole-Brain Child : 12 Revolutionary Strategies to Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-whole-brain-child-12-revolutionary-strategies-to-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-whole-brain-child-12-revolutionary-strategies-to-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; More than 1 million copies in print! &#8211; The authors of No-Drama Discipline and The Yes Brain explain the new science of how a child&#8217;s brain is wired and how it matures in this pioneering, practical book. &#8220;Simple, smart, and effective solutions to your child&#8217;s struggles.&#8221;&#8211;Harvey Karp, M.D. In this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-whole-brain-child-12-revolutionary-strategies-to-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/">The Whole-Brain Child : 12 Revolutionary Strategies to Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; More than 1 million copies in print! &#8211; The authors of No-Drama Discipline and The Yes Brain explain the new science of how a child&#8217;s brain is wired and how it matures in this pioneering, practical book.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Simple, smart, and effective solutions to your child&#8217;s struggles.&#8221;&#8211;Harvey Karp, M.D.     </p>
<p>                     In this pioneering, practical book, Daniel J. Siegel, neuropsychiatrist and author of the bestselling Mindsight, and parenting expert Tina Payne Bryson offer a revolutionary approach to child rearing with twelve key strategies that foster healthy brain development, leading to calmer, happier children. The authors explain&#8211;and make accessible&#8211;the new science of how a child&#8217;s brain is wired and how it matures. The &#8220;upstairs brain,&#8221; which makes decisions and balances emotions, is under construction until the mid-twenties. And especially in young children, the right brain and its emotions tend to rule over the logic of the left brain. No wonder kids throw tantrums, fight, or sulk in silence. By applying these discoveries to everyday parenting, you can turn any outburst, argument, or fear into a chance to integrate your child&#8217;s brain and foster vital growth.     </p>
<p>                     Complete with age-appropriate strategies for dealing with day-to-day struggles and illustrations that will help you explain these concepts to your child, The Whole-Brain Child shows you how to cultivate healthy emotional and intellectual development so that your children can lead balanced, meaningful, and connected lives.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;[A] useful child-rearing resource for the entire family . . . The authors include a fair amount of brain science, but they present it for both adult and child audiences.&#8221;&#8211;Kirkus Reviews    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Strategies for getting a youngster to chill out [with] compassion.&#8221;&#8211;The Washington Post    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This erudite, tender, and funny book is filled with fresh ideas based on the latest neuroscience research. I urge all parents who want kind, happy, and emotionally healthy kids to read The Whole-Brain Child. This is my new baby gift.&#8221;&#8211;Mary Pipher, Ph.D., author of Reviving Ophelia and The Shelter of Each Other     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Gives parents and teachers ideas to get all parts of a healthy child&#8217;s brain working together.&#8221;&#8211;Parent to Parent</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-whole-brain-child-12-revolutionary-strategies-to-nurture-your-childs-developing-mind-daniel-j-siegel-tina-payne-bryson-abridged/">The Whole-Brain Child : 12 Revolutionary Strategies to Nurture Your Child&#8217;s Developing Mind &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel, Tina Payne Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brain Rules for Baby (Updated and Expanded): How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five : How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five &#8211; John Medina (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brain-rules-for-baby-updated-and-expanded-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-john-medina-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brain-rules-for-baby-updated-and-expanded-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-john-medina-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s the single most important thing you can do during pregnancy? What does watching TV do to a child&#8217;s brain? What&#8217;s the best way to handle temper tantrums? Scientists know. In his New York Times bestseller Brain Rules, Dr. John Medina showed us how our brains really work&#8211;and why we ought to redesign our workplaces [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-rules-for-baby-updated-and-expanded-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-john-medina-abridged/">Brain Rules for Baby (Updated and Expanded): How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five : How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five &#8211; John Medina (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s the single most important thing you can do during pregnancy? What does watching TV do to a child&#8217;s brain? What&#8217;s the best way to handle temper tantrums? Scientists know. In his New York Times bestseller Brain Rules, Dr. John Medina showed us how our brains really work&#8211;and why we ought to redesign our workplaces and schools. Now, in Brain Rules for Baby, he shares what the latest science says about how to raise smart and happy children from zero to five. This book is destined to revolutionize parenting. Just one of the surprises: The best way to get your children into the college of their choice? Teach them impulse control. Brain Rules for Baby bridges the gap between what scientists know and what parents practice. Through fascinating and funny stories, Medina, a developmental molecular biologist and dad, unravels how a child&#8217;s brain develops &#8212; and what you can do to optimize it. You will view your children&#8211;and how to raise them&#8211;in a whole new light. You&#8217;ll learn: Where nature ends and nurture begins Why men should do more household chores What you do when emotions run hot affects how your baby turns out, because babies need to feel safe above all TV is harmful for children under 2 Your child&#8217;s ability to relate to others predicts her future math performance Smart and happy are inseparable. Pursuing your child&#8217;s intellectual success at the expense of his happiness achieves neither Praising effort is better than praising intelligence The best predictor of academic performance is not IQ. It&#8217;s self-control What you do right now&#8211;before pregnancy, during pregnancy, and through the first five years&#8211;will affect your children for the rest of their lives. Brain Rules for Baby is an indispensable guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-rules-for-baby-updated-and-expanded-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-how-to-raise-a-smart-and-happy-child-from-zero-to-five-john-medina-abridged/">Brain Rules for Baby (Updated and Expanded): How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five : How to Raise a Smart and Happy Child from Zero to Five &#8211; John Medina (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Strength Switch : how the new science of strength-based parenting helps your child and your teen flourish &#8211; Lea Waters (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your child&#8217;s potential by helping them build their strengths. As a strengths-based scientist for more than 20 years, Dr Lea Waters has witnessed first-hand how focusing on our children&#8217;s strengths, rather than correcting their weaknesses, can help build resilience and optimism, and offer protection from depression and anxiety. In this game-changing book, she argues [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/">The Strength Switch : how the new science of strength-based parenting helps your child and your teen flourish &#8211; Lea Waters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your child&#8217;s potential by helping them build their strengths.    </p>
<p>                    As a strengths-based scientist for more than 20 years, Dr Lea Waters has witnessed first-hand how focusing on our children&#8217;s strengths, rather than correcting their weaknesses, can help build resilience and optimism, and offer protection from depression and anxiety.     </p>
<p>                    In this game-changing book, she argues that by throwing the &#8216;strength switch&#8217; parents can encourage creativity, develop their children&#8217;s self-esteem and energy, and enhance achievement &#8211; and she offers easy-to-follow steps to teach parents how.    </p>
<p>                    With specific tips for interacting with your kids and your teens, The Strength Switch offers all the tools parents need to discover talents in their children, use positive emotions as a resource, build strong brains, and deal with problem behaviours and difficult emotions. This essential book will show parents how a small shift can yield enormous results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/">The Strength Switch : how the new science of strength-based parenting helps your child and your teen flourish &#8211; Lea Waters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UnSelfie : Why Empathetic Kids Succeed in Our All-About-Me World &#8211; Michele Borba (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unselfie-why-empathetic-kids-succeed-in-our-all-about-me-world-michele-borba-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unselfie-why-empathetic-kids-succeed-in-our-all-about-me-world-michele-borba-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Teens today are forty percent less empathetic than they were thirty years ago. Why is a lack of empathy-which goes hand-in-hand with the self-absorption epidemic Dr. Michele Borba calls the Selfie Syndrome-so dangerous? First, it hurts kids&#8217; academic performance and leads to bullying behaviours. Also, it correlates with more cheating and less resilience. And once [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unselfie-why-empathetic-kids-succeed-in-our-all-about-me-world-michele-borba-abridged/">UnSelfie : Why Empathetic Kids Succeed in Our All-About-Me World &#8211; Michele Borba (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Teens today are forty percent less empathetic than they were thirty years ago. Why is a lack of empathy-which goes hand-in-hand with the self-absorption epidemic Dr. Michele Borba calls the Selfie Syndrome-so dangerous? First, it hurts kids&#8217; academic performance and leads to bullying behaviours. Also, it correlates with more cheating and less resilience. And once children grow up, a lack of empathy hampers their ability to collaborate, innovate and problem-solve-all must-have skills for the global economy.<br />
                         In UnSelfie Dr. Borba pinpoints the forces causing the empathy crisis and shares a revolutionary, researched-based, nine-step plan for reversing it. Empathy is a trait that can be taught and nurtured. Dr. Borba offers a framework for parenting that yields the results we all want: successful, happy kids who also are kind, moral, courageous, and resilient. UnSelfie is a blueprint for parents and educators who want to kids shift their focus from I, me, and mine&#8230;to we, us, and ours.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unselfie-why-empathetic-kids-succeed-in-our-all-about-me-world-michele-borba-abridged/">UnSelfie : Why Empathetic Kids Succeed in Our All-About-Me World &#8211; Michele Borba (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Simplicity Parenting : Using the Extraordinary Power of Less to Raise Calmer, Happier, and More Secure Kids &#8211; Kim John Payne, Lisa M. Ross (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s busier, faster society is waging an undeclared war on childhood. With too much stuff, too many choices, and too little time, children can become anxious, have trouble with friends and school, or even be diagnosed with behavioral problems. Now internationally renowned family consultant Kim John Payne helps parents reclaim for their children the space [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/">Simplicity Parenting : Using the Extraordinary Power of Less to Raise Calmer, Happier, and More Secure Kids &#8211; Kim John Payne, Lisa M. Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today&#8217;s busier, faster society is waging an undeclared war on childhood. With too much stuff, too many choices, and too little time, children can become anxious, have trouble with friends and school, or even be diagnosed with behavioral problems. Now internationally renowned family consultant Kim John Payne helps parents reclaim for their children the space and freedom that all kids need for their attention to deepen and their individuality to flourish. Simplicity Parenting offers inspiration, ideas, and a blueprint for change:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Streamline your home environment. Reduce the amount of toys, books, and clutter&#8211;as well as the lights, sounds, and general sensory overload.<br />
                    &#8211; Establish rhythms and rituals. Discover ways to ease daily tensions, create battle-free mealtimes and bedtimes, and tell if your child is overwhelmed.<br />
                    &#8211; Schedule a break in the schedule. Establish intervals of calm and connection in your child&#8217;s daily torrent of constant doing.<br />
                    &#8211; Scale back on media and parental involvement. Manage your children&#8217;s &#8220;screen time&#8221; to limit the endless deluge of information and stimulation.     </p>
<p>                    A manifesto for protecting the grace of childhood, Simplicity Parenting is an eloquent guide to bringing new rhythms to bear on the lifelong art of raising children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/simplicity-parenting-using-the-extraordinary-power-of-less-to-raise-calmer-happier-and-more-secure-kids-kim-john-payne-lisa-m-ross-abridged/">Simplicity Parenting : Using the Extraordinary Power of Less to Raise Calmer, Happier, and More Secure Kids &#8211; Kim John Payne, Lisa M. Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The founder and director of the Thirty Million Words Initiative, Professor Dana Suskind, explains why the most important&#8211;and astoundingly simple&#8211;thing you can do for your child&#8217;s future success in life is to to talk to them. What nurtures the brain to optimum intelligence and stability? It is a secret hiding in plain sight: the most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/">Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The founder and director of the Thirty Million Words Initiative, Professor Dana Suskind, explains why the most important&#8211;and astoundingly simple&#8211;thing you can do for your child&#8217;s future success in life is to to talk to them.     </p>
<p>                    What nurtures the brain to optimum intelligence and stability?     </p>
<p>                    It is a secret hiding in plain sight: the most important thing we can do for our children is to have conversations with them. The way you talk with your growing child literally builds his or her brain. Parent talk can drastically improve school readiness and lifelong learning in everything from math to art. Indeed, parent-child talk is a fundamental, critical factor in building grit, self-control, leadership skills, and generosity. It is crucial to making the most in life of the luck you have with your genes.     </p>
<p>                    This landmark account of a new scientific perspective describes what works and what doesn&#8217;t (baby talk is fine; relentless correction isn&#8217;t). Discover how to create the best language environments for children by following the simple structure of the Three Ts: Tune In; Talk More; Take Turns. Dr. Suskind and her colleagues around the country have worked with thousands of families; now their insights and successful, measured approaches are available to all.     </p>
<p>                    This is the first book to reveal how and why the first step in nurturing successful lives is talking to children in ways that build their brains. Your family&#8211;and our nation&#8211;need to know.     </p>
<p>                    *Nominated for the Books for a Better Life Award*</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/">Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Hidden Chimp : From the best-selling author of The Chimp Paradox &#8211; Prof Steve Peters (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-hidden-chimp-from-the-best-selling-author-of-the-chimp-paradox-prof-steve-peters-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self-Esteem]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-hidden-chimp-from-the-best-selling-author-of-the-chimp-paradox-prof-steve-peters-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how TEN habits can help children to understand and manage their emotions and behaviour &#8211; the NEW book from the creator of the chimp management mind model and author of the million copy selling The Chimp Paradox . My Hidden Chimp is an effective and powerful new educational book that offers parents, teachers and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-hidden-chimp-from-the-best-selling-author-of-the-chimp-paradox-prof-steve-peters-abridged/">My Hidden Chimp : From the best-selling author of The Chimp Paradox &#8211; Prof Steve Peters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how TEN habits can help children to understand and manage their emotions and behaviour &#8211; the NEW book from the creator of the chimp management mind model and author of the million copy selling The Chimp Paradox .    </p>
<p>                    My Hidden Chimp is an effective and powerful new educational book that offers parents, teachers and carers some ideas and thoughts on how to help children to develop healthy habits for life. The science behind the habits is discussed in a practical way with exercises and activities to help children think the habits through and start putting them into practice. The neuroscience of the mind is simplified for children to understand and then use to their advantage.    </p>
<p>                    Professor Steve Peters explains neuroscience in a straightforward and intuitive way &#8211; offering up 10 simple habits that we as adults and children should have in our arsenal to deal with everyday life.    </p>
<p>                    They include:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Smiling<br />
                    &#8211; The importance of talking through your feelings<br />
                    &#8211; Learning how to say sorry<br />
                    &#8211; Knowing how to ask for help    </p>
<p>                    By also explaining the developing &#8216;chimp&#8217; brain in children, he shows us how 10 habits can help children to understand and manage their emotions and behaviour. These 10 habits should and can be retained for life.    </p>
<p>                    This is an important and another groundbreaking new book from the bestselling author of The Chimp Paradox and the creator of the chimp management mind model.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-hidden-chimp-from-the-best-selling-author-of-the-chimp-paradox-prof-steve-peters-abridged/">My Hidden Chimp : From the best-selling author of The Chimp Paradox &#8211; Prof Steve Peters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Raise Successful People: Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient : Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient &#8211; Esther Wojcicki (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-raise-successful-people-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-esth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secondary Schools]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-raise-successful-people-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-esth/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Godmother of Silicon Valley, legendary teacher, and mother of a Super Family shares her tried-and-tested methods for raising happy, healthy, successful children using Trust, Respect, Independence, Collaboration, and Kindness: TRICK. Esther Wojcicki&#8211;&#8220;Woj&#8221; to her many friends and admirers&#8211;is famous for three things: teaching a high school class that has changed the lives of thousands [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-successful-people-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-esth/">How to Raise Successful People: Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient : Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient &#8211; Esther Wojcicki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Godmother of Silicon Valley, legendary teacher, and mother of a Super Family shares her tried-and-tested methods for raising happy, healthy, successful children using Trust, Respect, Independence, Collaboration, and Kindness: TRICK.    </p>
<p>                    Esther Wojcicki&#8211;&#8220;Woj&#8221; to her many friends and admirers&#8211;is famous for three things: teaching a high school class that has changed the lives of thousands of kids, inspiring Silicon Valley legends like Steve Jobs, and raising three daughters who have each become famously successful. What do these three accomplishments have in common? They&#8217;re the result of TRICK, Woj&#8217;s secret to raising successful people: Trust, Respect, Independence, Collaboration, and Kindness.     </p>
<p>                    Simple lessons, but the results are radical. Wojcicki&#8217;s methods are the opposite of helicopter parenting. As we face an epidemic of parental anxiety, Woj is here to say: relax. Talk to infants as if they are adults. Allow teenagers to pick projects that relate to the real world and their own passions, and let them figure out how to complete them. Above all, let your child lead. How to Raise Successful People offers essential lessons for raising, educating, and managing people to their highest potential. Change your parenting, change the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-successful-people-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-simple-lessons-to-help-your-child-become-self-driven-respectful-and-resilient-esth/">How to Raise Successful People: Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient : Simple Lessons to Help Your Child Become Self-Driven, Respectful, and Resilient &#8211; Esther Wojcicki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weird Parenting Wins : Bathtub Dining, Family Screams, and Other Hacks from the Parenting Trenches &#8211; Hillary Frank (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unconventional&#8211;yet effective&#8211;parenting strategies, carefully curated by the creator of the popular podcast The Longest Shortest Time Some of the best parenting advice that Hillary Frank ever received did not come from parenting experts, but from friends and podcast listeners who acted on a whim, often in moments of desperation. These weird parenting wins were born [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/">Weird Parenting Wins : Bathtub Dining, Family Screams, and Other Hacks from the Parenting Trenches &#8211; Hillary Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unconventional&#8211;yet effective&#8211;parenting strategies, carefully curated by the creator of the popular podcast The Longest Shortest Time     </p>
<p>                    Some of the best parenting advice that Hillary Frank ever received did not come from parenting experts, but from friends and podcast listeners who acted on a whim, often in moments of desperation. These weird parenting wins were born of moments when the expert advice wasn&#8217;t working, and instead of freaking out, these parents had a stroke of genius. For example, there&#8217;s the dad who pig-snorted in his baby&#8217;s ear to get her to stop crying, and the mom who made a flat daddy out of cardboard and sat it at the dinner table when her kids were missing their deployed military father.<br />
                     Every parent and kid is unique, and as we get to know our kids, we can figure out what makes them tick. Because this is an ongoing process, Weird Parenting Wins covers children of all ages, ranging in topics from The Art of Getting Your Kid to Act Like a Person (on hygiene, potty training, and manners) to The Art of Getting Your Kid to Tell You Things (because eventually, they&#8217;re going to be tight-lipped). You may find that someone else&#8217;s weird parenting win works for you, or you might be inspired to try something new the next time you&#8217;re stuck in a parenting rut. Or maybe you&#8217;ll just get a good laugh out of the mom who got her kid to try beets because&#8230;it might turn her poop pink.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weird-parenting-wins-bathtub-dining-family-screams-and-other-hacks-from-the-parenting-trenches-hillary-frank-abridged/">Weird Parenting Wins : Bathtub Dining, Family Screams, and Other Hacks from the Parenting Trenches &#8211; Hillary Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiest Baby on the Block; Fully Revised and Updated Second Edition : The New Way to Calm Crying and Help Your Newborn Baby Sleep Longer &#8211; Harvey Karp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Never again will you have to stand by helplessly while your little baby cries and cries. There is a way to calm most crying babies . . . usually in minutes! Thousands of parents, from regular moms and dads to Hollywood superstars, have come to baby expert Dr. Harvey Karp to learn his remarkable techniques [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/">The Happiest Baby on the Block; Fully Revised and Updated Second Edition : The New Way to Calm Crying and Help Your Newborn Baby Sleep Longer &#8211; Harvey Karp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Never again will you have to stand by helplessly while your little baby cries and cries. There is a way to calm most crying babies . . . usually in minutes!      </p>
<p>                     Thousands of parents, from regular moms and dads to Hollywood superstars, have come to baby expert Dr. Harvey Karp to learn his remarkable techniques for soothing babies and increasing sleep. Now his landmark book&#8211;fully revised and updated with the latest insights into infant sleep, bedsharing, breastfeeding, swaddling, and SIDS risk&#8211;can teach you too! Dr. Karp&#8217;s highly successful method is based on four revolutionary concepts:     </p>
<p>                     1. The Fourth Trimester: Why babies still yearn for a womblike atmosphere . . . even after birth<br />
                     2. The Calming Reflex: An &#8220;off switch&#8221; all babies are born with<br />
                     3. The 5 S&#8217;s: Five easy steps to turn on your baby&#8217;s amazing calming reflex<br />
                     4. The Cuddle Cure:  How to combine the 5 S&#8217;s to calm even colicky babies     </p>
<p>                     With Dr. Karp&#8217;s sensible advice, parents and grandparents, nurses and nannies, will be able to transform even the fussiest infant into the happiest baby on the block!     </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Happiest Baby on the Block     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Dr. Karp&#8217;s book is fascinating and will guide new parents for years to come.&#8221;&#8211;Julius Richmond, M.D., Harvard Medical School, former Surgeon General of the United States     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Happiest Baby on the Block is fun and convincing. I highly recommend it.&#8221;&#8211;Elisabeth Bing, co-founder of Lamaze International     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Will fascinate anyone who wants to know how babies experience the world, and wants to answer their cries lovingly and effectively.&#8221;&#8211;The San Diego Union-Tribune</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/">The Happiest Baby on the Block; Fully Revised and Updated Second Edition : The New Way to Calm Crying and Help Your Newborn Baby Sleep Longer &#8211; Harvey Karp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER From the UK&#8217;s favourite therapist, as seen on Channel 4&#8217;s Grayson&#8217;s Art Club. &#8216;A wonderful book&#8217; Richard Osman &#8216;So clear and true &#8230; Helpful for all relationships in life&#8217; Nigella Lawson &#8216;A fascinating read on the emotional baggage we all carry&#8217; Elizabeth Day ______________________________________________________________________________________ How can we have better relationships? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/">The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    From the UK&#8217;s favourite therapist, as seen on Channel 4&#8217;s Grayson&#8217;s Art Club.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wonderful book&#8217; Richard Osman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;So clear and true &#8230; Helpful for all relationships in life&#8217; Nigella Lawson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fascinating read on the emotional baggage we all carry&#8217; Elizabeth Day<br />
                    ______________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    How can we have better relationships?    </p>
<p>                    In this Sunday Times bestseller, leading psychotherapist Philippa Perry reveals the vital do&#8217;s and don&#8217;ts of relationships. This is a book for us all. Whether you are interested in understanding how your upbringing has shaped you, looking to handle your child&#8217;s feelings or wishing to support your partner, you will find indispensable information and realistic tips in these pages. Philippa Perry&#8217;s sane, sage and judgement-free advice is an essential resource on how to have the best possible relationships with the people who matter to you most.<br />
                    _____________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It gave me hope as a new parent&#8217; Babita Sharma    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This has genuinely had such a positive impact on my life and my relationship with my daughter&#8217; Josh Widdicombe    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;She writes with an inquisitive elegance rarely found in parenting guides &#8230; it is forgiving and persuasive&#8217;   Hadley Freeman, the Guardian      </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Philippa Perry is one of the wisest, most sane and secure people I&#8217;ve ever met&#8217; Decca Aitkenhead, Sunday Times Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-you-wish-your-parents-had-read-and-your-children-will-be-glad-that-you-did-the-1-sunday-times-bestseller-philippa-perry-abridged/">The Book You Wish Your Parents Had Read (and Your Children Will Be Glad That You Did) : THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Philippa Perry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Importance Of Being Little : What Preschoolers Really Need from Grownups &#8211; Erika Christakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pre-school & Kindergarten]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Christakis . . . expertly weaves academic research, personal experience and anecdotal evidence into her book . . . a bracing and convincing case that early education has reached a point of crisis . . . her book is a rare thing: a serious work of research that also happens to be well-written and personal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/">The Importance Of Being Little : What Preschoolers Really Need from Grownups &#8211; Erika Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Christakis . . . expertly weaves academic research, personal experience and anecdotal evidence into her book . . . a bracing and convincing case that early education has reached a point of crisis . . . her book is a rare thing: a serious work of research that also happens to be well-written and personal . . . engaging and important.&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;Washington Post     </p>
<p>                    What kids need from grown-ups (but aren&#8217;t getting)&#8230;an impassioned plea for educators and parents to put down the worksheets and flash cards, ditch the tired craft projects (yes, you, Thanksgiving Handprint Turkey) and exotic vocabulary lessons, and double-down on one, simple word: play.<br />
                    &#8211;NPR     </p>
<p>                    The New York Times bestseller that provides a bold challenge to the conventional wisdom about early childhood, with a pragmatic program to encourage parents and teachers to rethink how and where young children learn best by taking the child&#8217;s eye view of the learning environment     </p>
<p>                     To a four-year-old watching bulldozers at a construction site or chasing butterflies in flight, the world is awash with promise. Little children come into the world hardwired to learn in virtually any setting and about any matter. Yet in today&#8217;s preschool and kindergarten classrooms, learning has been reduced to scripted lessons and suspect metrics that too often undervalue a child&#8217;s intelligence while overtaxing the child&#8217;s growing brain. These mismatched expectations wreak havoc on the family: parents fear that if they choose the &#8220;wrong&#8221; program, their child won&#8217;t get into the &#8220;right&#8221; college. But Yale early childhood expert Erika Christakis says our fears are wildly misplaced. Our anxiety about preparing and safeguarding our children&#8217;s future seems to have reached a fever pitch at a time when, ironically, science gives us more certainty than ever before that young children are exceptionally strong thinkers.<br />
                     In her pathbreaking book, Christakis explains what it&#8217;s like to be a young child in America today, in a world designed by and for adults, where we have confused schooling with learning. She offers real-life solutions to real-life issues, with nuance and direction that takes us far beyond the usual prescriptions for fewer tests, more play. She looks at children&#8217;s use of language, their artistic expressions, the way their imaginations grow, and how they build deep emotional bonds to stretch the boundaries of their small worlds. Rather than clutter their worlds with more and more stuff, sometimes the wisest course for us is to learn how to get out of their way.<br />
                     Christakis&#8217;s message is energizing and reassuring: young children are inherently powerful, and they (and their parents) will flourish when we learn new ways of restoring the vital early learning environment to one that is best suited to the littlest learners. This bold and pragmatic challenge to the conventional wisdom peels back the mystery of childhood, revealing a place that&#8217;s rich with possibility.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/">The Importance Of Being Little : What Preschoolers Really Need from Grownups &#8211; Erika Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common Sense Pregnancy : Navigating a Healthy Pregnancy and Birth for Mother and Baby &#8211; Jeanne Faulkner, Foreword byChristy Turlington Burns, Foreword byErin Thornton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/common-sense-pregnancy-navigating-a-healthy-pregnancy-and-birth-for-mother-and-baby-jeanne-faulkner-foreword-by-christy-turlington-burns-foreword-by-erin-thornton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/common-sense-pregnancy-navigating-a-healthy-pregnancy-and-birth-for-mother-and-baby-jeanne-faulkner-foreword-by-christy-turlington-burns-foreword-by-erin-thornton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Become a mama without the drama When you&#8217;re pregnant, your friends, the Internet, and even your doctor often give advice that leaves you anxious and overwhelmed. You deserve a calm, straightforward, no-nonsense pregnancy. It&#8217;s time to dial down the stress and dial up the common sense. Common Sense Pregnancy is a breath of fresh air: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-pregnancy-navigating-a-healthy-pregnancy-and-birth-for-mother-and-baby-jeanne-faulkner-foreword-by-christy-turlington-burns-foreword-by-erin-thornton-abridged/">Common Sense Pregnancy : Navigating a Healthy Pregnancy and Birth for Mother and Baby &#8211; Jeanne Faulkner, Foreword byChristy Turlington Burns, Foreword byErin Thornton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Become a mama without the drama    </p>
<p>                     When you&#8217;re pregnant, your friends, the Internet, and even your doctor often give advice that leaves you anxious and overwhelmed. You deserve a calm, straightforward, no-nonsense pregnancy. It&#8217;s time to dial down the stress and dial up the common sense. Common Sense Pregnancy is a breath of fresh air: accessible, authoritative, funny, reassuring, and personable, while still chock-full of comprehensive, medically-sound advice. Women&#8217;s health expert, labor nurse, mother of four, and Fit Pregnancy.com columnist Jeanne Faulkner has been at the bedside for thousands of deliveries and provides the honest insider advice you need during pregnancy, labor, birth, and beyond, including straight talk on:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Which prenatal tests you actually need, and which you don&#8217;t.<br />
                     &#8211; Who&#8217;s on your labor team&#8211;and how to keep your labor room drama free.<br />
                     &#8211; What about sex?<br />
                     &#8211; How to deal with feeling lousy.<br />
                     &#8211; What works and what doesn&#8217;t for starting labor naturally.<br />
                     &#8211; How to avoid unnecessary and risky medical interventions.     </p>
<p>                     Whether you want your pregnancy and birth to be all natural, all medical, or something in between, Common Sense Pregnancy eliminates the fear and puts you in charge of your body and prenatal experience, and helps you make the right choices for you and your baby.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-pregnancy-navigating-a-healthy-pregnancy-and-birth-for-mother-and-baby-jeanne-faulkner-foreword-by-christy-turlington-burns-foreword-by-erin-thornton-abridged/">Common Sense Pregnancy : Navigating a Healthy Pregnancy and Birth for Mother and Baby &#8211; Jeanne Faulkner, Foreword byChristy Turlington Burns, Foreword byErin Thornton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indistractable : How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life &#8211; Nir Eyal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A must-read&#8217; Mark Manson We are living through a crisis of distraction. Plans get sidetracked, friends are ignored, work never seems to get done. Why does it feel like we&#8217;re distracting our lives away? In Indistractable, behavioural designer Nir Eyal reveals the hidden psychology driving you to distraction. Empowering and optimistic, this is the book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/">Indistractable : How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life &#8211; Nir Eyal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A must-read&#8217; Mark Manson    </p>
<p>                    We are living through a crisis of distraction. Plans get sidetracked, friends are ignored, work never seems to get done.     </p>
<p>                    Why does it feel like we&#8217;re distracting our lives away?    </p>
<p>                    In Indistractable, behavioural designer Nir Eyal reveals the hidden psychology driving you to distraction. Empowering and optimistic, this is the book that will help you design your time, realise your ambitions, and live the life you really want.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you value your time, your focus or your relationships, this book is essential reading&#8217; Jonathan Haidt, author of The Righteous Mind    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A guide to staying focused in an age of constant distraction&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Exactly what most of us need in order to focus on what is important, rather than the dazzling, illuminated, unsatisfying distractions of modern life&#8217; Matt Haig    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Does exactly as it promises. Amazing&#8217; Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The best guide I&#8217;ve read for reclaiming our attention, our focus and our lives&#8217; Arianna Huffington</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/">Indistractable : How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life &#8211; Nir Eyal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cribsheet : A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting, from Birth to Preschool &#8211; Emily Oster (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Emily Oster is the non-judgemental girlfriend holding our hand and guiding us through pregnancy and motherhood. She has done the work to get us the hard facts in a soft, understandable way&#8217; Amy Schumer Parenting is full of decisions, nearly all of which can be agonized over. There is an abundance of often-conflicting advice hurled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/">Cribsheet : A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting, from Birth to Preschool &#8211; Emily Oster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Emily Oster is the non-judgemental girlfriend holding our hand and guiding us through pregnancy and motherhood. She has done the work to get us the hard facts in a soft, understandable way&#8217; Amy Schumer    </p>
<p>                    Parenting is full of decisions, nearly all of which can be agonized over. There is an abundance of often-conflicting advice hurled at you from doctors, family, friends, and strangers on the internet. But the benefits of these choices can be overstated, and the trade-offs can be profound. How do you make your own best decision?     </p>
<p>                     Armed with the data, Oster finds that the conventional wisdom doesn&#8217;t always hold up. She debunks myths and offers non-judgemental ways to consider our options in light of the facts. Cribsheet is a thinking parent&#8217;s guide that empowers us to make better, less fraught decisions &#8211; and stay sane in the years before preschool.    </p>
<p>                    *Now you can navigate the primary school years with Emily Oster too, in her new book The Family Firm, out now*</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/">Cribsheet : A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting, from Birth to Preschool &#8211; Emily Oster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chika Jeune was born three days before the devastating earthquake that decimated Haiti in 2010. She spent her infancy in extreme poverty, and when her mother died giving birth to a baby brother, Chika was brought to the Have Faith Haiti Orphanage that Mitch and his wife, Janine operate. Chika&#8217;s arrival made a quick impression. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/">Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chika Jeune was born three days before the devastating earthquake that decimated Haiti in 2010. She spent her infancy in extreme poverty, and when her mother died giving birth to a baby brother, Chika was brought to the Have Faith Haiti Orphanage that Mitch and his wife, Janine operate.    </p>
<p>                    Chika&#8217;s arrival made a quick impression. Brave and self-assured, even as a three-year-old, she delighted the other kids and teachers. But at age five, Chika was suddenly diagnosed with a terminal disease that no doctor in Haiti could help with.    </p>
<p>                    Mitch and Janine took Chika to America, hoping that treatment there would enable her to go back home.  Instead, Chika became a permanent part of their lives, as they embarked on a two-year, around-the-world journey to find a cure. As Chika&#8217;s boundless optimism and humour taught Mitch the joys of caring for a child, he learnt that a relationship built on love, no matter what blows it takes, can never be lost.    </p>
<p>                    This is Mitch Albom at his most poignant, powerful and personal. Chika is a celebration of a girl, her adoptive guardians, and the incredible bond they formed &#8211; a devastatingly beautiful portrait of what it means to be a family, regardless of how it is made.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/">Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Untangled : Guiding Teenage Girls Through the Seven Transitions into Adulthood &#8211; Lisa Damour (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leading clinical psychologist Lisa Damour identifies the seven key phases marking the journey from girlhood to womanhood, and offers practical advice for those raising teenage girls. We expect an enormous amount from our teenage girls in a world where they are bombarded with messages about how they should look, behave, succeed. Yet we also speak [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/">Untangled : Guiding Teenage Girls Through the Seven Transitions into Adulthood &#8211; Lisa Damour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading clinical psychologist Lisa Damour identifies the seven key phases marking the journey from girlhood to womanhood, and offers practical advice for those raising teenage girls.    </p>
<p>                    We expect an enormous amount from our teenage girls in a world where they are bombarded with messages about how they should look, behave, succeed. Yet we also speak as though adolescence is a nightmare rollercoaster ride for both parent and child, to be endured rather than enjoyed.     </p>
<p>                    In Untangled, world authority and clinical psychologist Lisa Damour provides an accessible, detailed, comprehensive guide to parenting teenage girls. She believes there is a predictable blueprint for how girls grow; seven easily recognisable &#8216;strands&#8217; of transition from childhood through adolescence and on to adulthood. Girls naturally develop at different rates, typically on more than one front, and the transition will be unique to every girl.     </p>
<p>                    Each chapter describes a phase, such as &#8216;contending with adult authority&#8217; and &#8216;entering the romantic world&#8217;, with hints and tips for parents and daughters, and a &#8216;when to worry&#8217; section. Damour writes sympathetically and clearly, providing a practical and helpful guide for any parent, and for teenage girls too.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/untangled-guiding-teenage-girls-through-the-seven-transitions-into-adulthood-lisa-damour-abridged/">Untangled : Guiding Teenage Girls Through the Seven Transitions into Adulthood &#8211; Lisa Damour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where You Go Is Not Who You&#8217;ll Be : An Antidote to the College Admissions Mania &#8211; Frank Bruni (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/where-you-go-is-not-who-youll-be-an-antidote-to-the-college-admissions-mania-frank-bruni-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/where-you-go-is-not-who-youll-be-an-antidote-to-the-college-admissions-mania-frank-bruni-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Read award-winning journalist Frank Bruni&#8217;s New York Times bestseller: an inspiring manifesto about everything wrong with today&#8217;s frenzied college admissions process and how to make the most of your college years. Over the last few decades, Americans have turned college admissions into a terrifying and occasionally devastating process, preceded by test prep, tutors, all sorts [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/where-you-go-is-not-who-youll-be-an-antidote-to-the-college-admissions-mania-frank-bruni-abridged/">Where You Go Is Not Who You&#8217;ll Be : An Antidote to the College Admissions Mania &#8211; Frank Bruni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read award-winning journalist Frank Bruni&#8217;s New York Times bestseller: an inspiring manifesto about everything wrong with today&#8217;s frenzied college admissions process and how to make the most of your college years.     </p>
<p>                     Over the last few decades, Americans have turned college admissions into a terrifying and occasionally devastating process, preceded by test prep, tutors, all sorts of stratagems, all kinds of rankings, and a conviction among too many young people that their futures will be determined and their worth established by which schools say yes and which say no.     </p>
<p>                     In Where You Go is Not Who You&#8217;ll Be, Frank Bruni explains why this mindset is wrong, giving students and their parents a new perspective on this brutal, deeply flawed competition and a path out of the anxiety that it provokes.     </p>
<p>                     Bruni, a bestselling author and a columnist for the New York Times, shows that the Ivy League has no monopoly on corner offices, governors&#8217; mansions, or the most prestigious academic and scientific grants. Through statistics, surveys, and the stories of hugely successful people, he demonstrates that many kinds of colleges serve as ideal springboards. And he illuminates how to make the most of them. What matters in the end are students&#8217; efforts in and out of the classroom, not the name on their diploma.     </p>
<p>                     Where you go isn&#8217;t who you&#8217;ll be. Americans need to hear that&#8211;and this indispensable manifesto says it with eloquence and respect for the real promise of higher education.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/where-you-go-is-not-who-youll-be-an-antidote-to-the-college-admissions-mania-frank-bruni-abridged/">Where You Go Is Not Who You&#8217;ll Be : An Antidote to the College Admissions Mania &#8211; Frank Bruni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend. A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend.<br />
                              A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. Dear Ijeawele is Adichie&#8217;s letter of response.    </p>
<p>                              Here are fifteen invaluable suggestions-compelling, direct, wryly funny, and perceptive-for how to empower a daughter to become a strong, independent woman. From encouraging her to choose a helicopter, and not only a doll, as a toy if she so desires; having open conversations with her about clothes, makeup, and sexuality; debunking the myth that women are somehow biologically arranged to be in the kitchen making dinner, and that men can &#8220;allow&#8221; women to have full careers, Dear Ijeawele goes right to the heart of sexual politics in the twenty-first century. It will start a new and urgently needed conversation about what it really means to be a woman today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s Going on in There? : How the Brain and Mind Develop in the First Five Years of Life &#8211; Lise Eliot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As a research neuroscientist, Lise Eliot has made the study of the human brain her life&#8217;s work. But it wasn&#8217;t until she was pregnant with her first child that she became intrigued with the study of brain development. She wanted to know precisely how the baby&#8217;s brain is formed, and when and how each sense, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/">What&#8217;s Going on in There? : How the Brain and Mind Develop in the First Five Years of Life &#8211; Lise Eliot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As a research neuroscientist, Lise Eliot has made the study of the human brain her life&#8217;s work. But it wasn&#8217;t until she was pregnant with her first child that she became intrigued with the study of brain development. She wanted to know precisely how the baby&#8217;s brain is formed, and when and how each sense, skill, and cognitive ability is developed. And just as important, she was interested in finding out how her role as a nurturer can affect this complex process. How much of her baby&#8217;s development is genetically ordained&#8211;and how much is determined by environment? Is there anything parents can do to make their babies&#8217; brains work better&#8211;to help them become smarter, happier people? Drawing upon the exploding research in this field as well as the stories of real children, What&#8217;s Going On in There? is a lively and thought-provoking book that charts the brain&#8217;s development from conception through the critical first five years. In examining the many factors that play crucial roles in that process, What&#8217;s Going On in There? explores the evolution of the senses, motor skills, social and emotional behaviors, and mental functions such as attention, language, memory, reasoning, and intelligence. This remarkable book also discusses:     </p>
<p>                     how a baby&#8217;s brain is &#8220;assembled&#8221; from scratch<br />
                    the critical prenatal factors that shapebrain development<br />
                    how the birthing process itself affects the brain<br />
                    which forms of stimulation are most effective at promoting cognitive development<br />
                    how boys&#8217; and girls&#8217; brains develop differently<br />
                    how nutrition, stress, and other physical and social factors can permanently affect a child&#8217;s brain     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly blending cutting-edge science with a mother&#8217;s wisdom and insight, What&#8217;s Going On in There? is an invaluable contribution to the nature versus nurture debate. Children&#8217;s development is determined both by the genes they are born with and the richness of their early environment. This timely and important book shows parents the innumerable ways in which they can actually help their children grow better brains.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/">What&#8217;s Going on in There? : How the Brain and Mind Develop in the First Five Years of Life &#8211; Lise Eliot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Call of the Wild and Free : Reclaiming the Wonder in Your Child&#8217;s Education, A New Way to Homeschool &#8211; Ainsley Arment (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-call-of-the-wild-and-free-reclaiming-the-wonder-in-your-childs-education-a-new-way-to-homeschool-ainsley-arment-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Learning, Home Learning, Distance Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary & Middle Schools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of A Specific Subject]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-call-of-the-wild-and-free-reclaiming-the-wonder-in-your-childs-education-a-new-way-to-homeschool-ainsley-arment-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Allow your children to experience the adventure, freedom, and wonder of childhood with this practical guide that provides all the information, inspiration, and advice you need for creating a modern, quality homeschool education. Inspired by the spirit of Henry David Thoreau-&#8220;All good things are wild and free&#8221;-mother of five Ainsley Arment founded Wild + Free. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-call-of-the-wild-and-free-reclaiming-the-wonder-in-your-childs-education-a-new-way-to-homeschool-ainsley-arment-abridged/">The Call of the Wild and Free : Reclaiming the Wonder in Your Child&#8217;s Education, A New Way to Homeschool &#8211; Ainsley Arment (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Allow your children to experience the adventure, freedom, and wonder of childhood with this practical guide that provides all the information, inspiration, and advice you need for creating a modern, quality homeschool education.    </p>
<p>                    Inspired by the spirit of Henry David Thoreau-&#8220;All good things are wild and free&#8221;-mother of five Ainsley Arment founded Wild + Free. This growing online community of mothers and families want their children to receive a quality education at home by challenging their intellectual abilities and nurturing their sense of curiosity, joy and awe-the essence of a positive childhood.     </p>
<p>                    The homeschool approach of past generations is gone-including the stigma of socially awkward kids, conservative clothes, and a classroom setting replicated in the home. The Wild + Free movement is focused on a love of nature, reading great books, pursuing interests and hobbies, making the entire world a classroom, and prolonging the wonder of childhood, an appealing philosophy that is unpacked in the pages of this book    </p>
<p>                    The Call of the Wild and Free offers advice, information, and positive encouragement for parents considering homeschooling, those currently in the trenches looking for inspiration, as well as parents, educators, and caregivers who want supplementary resources to enhance their kids&#8217; traditional educations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-call-of-the-wild-and-free-reclaiming-the-wonder-in-your-childs-education-a-new-way-to-homeschool-ainsley-arment-abridged/">The Call of the Wild and Free : Reclaiming the Wonder in Your Child&#8217;s Education, A New Way to Homeschool &#8211; Ainsley Arment (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother &#8211; Amy Chua (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/battle-hymn-of-the-tiger-mother-amy-chua-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/battle-hymn-of-the-tiger-mother-amy-chua-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated with a new postscript by Amy Chua and a letter from her eldest daughter, Sophia Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother is a story about a mother, two daughters, and two dogs. It was supposed to be a story of how Chinese parents are better at raising kids than Western ones. But instead, it&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/battle-hymn-of-the-tiger-mother-amy-chua-abridged/">Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother &#8211; Amy Chua (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated with a new postscript by Amy Chua and a letter from her eldest daughter, Sophia    </p>
<p>                    Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother is a story about a mother, two daughters, and two dogs. It was supposed to be a story of how Chinese parents are better at raising kids than Western ones. But instead, it&#8217;s about a bitter clash of cultures, a fleeting taste of glory, and how you can be humbled by a thirteen-year-old.    </p>
<p>                    Witty, entertaining and provocative, this is a unique and important book that will transform your perspective of parenting forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/battle-hymn-of-the-tiger-mother-amy-chua-abridged/">Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother &#8211; Amy Chua (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Talk so Kids Will Listen and Listen so Kids Will Talk &#8211; Adele Faber, Elaine Mazlish (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-and-listen-so-kids-will-talk-adele-faber-elaine-mazlish-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-and-listen-so-kids-will-talk-adele-faber-elaine-mazlish-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this international bestseller, discover the number one practical guide to family life. Parenting experts Adele Faber and Elaine Mazlish provide effective step by step techniques to help you improve and enrich your relationships with your children. Learn how to: * Break a pattern of arguments * Cope with your child&#8217;s negative feelings * Engage [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-and-listen-so-kids-will-talk-adele-faber-elaine-mazlish-abridged/">How to Talk so Kids Will Listen and Listen so Kids Will Talk &#8211; Adele Faber, Elaine Mazlish (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this international bestseller, discover the number one practical guide to family life.    </p>
<p>                    Parenting experts Adele Faber and Elaine Mazlish provide effective step by step techniques to help you improve and enrich your relationships with your children.     </p>
<p>                    Learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    * Break a pattern of arguments<br />
                    * Cope with your child&#8217;s negative feelings<br />
                    * Engage your child&#8217;s co-operation<br />
                    * Set clear limits and still maintain goodwill<br />
                    * Express your anger without being hurtful<br />
                    * Resolve family conflicts peacefully</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-talk-so-kids-will-listen-and-listen-so-kids-will-talk-adele-faber-elaine-mazlish-abridged/">How to Talk so Kids Will Listen and Listen so Kids Will Talk &#8211; Adele Faber, Elaine Mazlish (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happy Kids Handbook : How to Raise Joyful Children in a Stressful World &#8211; Katie Hurley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With all the parenting information out there and the constant pressure to be the &#8220;perfect&#8221; parent, it seems as if many parents have lost track of one very important piece of the parenting puzzle: raising happy kids. Parenting today has gotten far too complicated. It&#8217;s never been the easiest job in the world, but with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/">The Happy Kids Handbook : How to Raise Joyful Children in a Stressful World &#8211; Katie Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With all the parenting information out there and the constant pressure to be the &#8220;perfect&#8221; parent, it seems as if many parents have lost track of one very important piece of the parenting puzzle: raising happy kids.     </p>
<p>                     Parenting today has gotten far too complicated. It&#8217;s never been the easiest job in the world, but with all the &#8220;parenting advice&#8221; parents are met with at every corner, it&#8217;s hard not to become bewildered. It seems that in the past it was a good deal simpler. You made sure there was dinner on the table and the kids got to school on time and no one set anything on fire, and you called it a success. But today everybody has a different method for dealing with the madness&#8211;attachment parenting, free-range parenting, mindful parenting. And who is to say one is more right or better than another? How do you choose?     </p>
<p>                     The truth is that whatever drumbeat you march to, all parents would agree that we just want our kids to be happy. It seems like a no-brainer, right? But in the face of all the many parenting theories out there, happiness feels like it has become incidental. That&#8217;s where The Happy Kid Handbook by child and adolescent psychotherapist and parenting expert Katie Hurley comes in. She shows parents how happiness is the key to raising confident, capable children. It&#8217;s not about giving in every time your child wants something so they won&#8217;t feel bad when you say no, or making sure that they&#8217;re taking that art class, and the ballet class, and the soccer class (to help with their creativity and their coordination and all that excess energy). Happiness is about parenting the individual, because not every child is the same, and not every child will respond to parenting the same way. By exploring the differences among introverts, extroverts, and everything in between, this definitive guide to parenting offers parents the specific strategies they need to meet their child exactly where he or she needs to be met from a social-emotional perspective. A back-to-basics guide to parenting, The Happy Kid Handbook is a must-have for any parent hoping to be the best parent they can be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/">The Happy Kids Handbook : How to Raise Joyful Children in a Stressful World &#8211; Katie Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Audiology & Otology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Speech & Language Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A skilled science translator, Denworth makes decibels, teslas and brain plasticity understandable to all.&#8221;-Washington Post Lydia Denworth&#8217;s third son, Alex, was nearly two when he was identified with significant hearing loss that was likely to get worse. Denworth knew the importance of enrichment to the developing brain but had never contemplated the opposite: deprivation. How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/">I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A skilled science translator, Denworth makes decibels, teslas and brain plasticity understandable to all.&#8221;-Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    Lydia Denworth&#8217;s third son, Alex, was nearly two when he was identified with significant hearing loss that was likely to get worse. Denworth knew the importance of enrichment to the developing brain but had never contemplated the opposite: deprivation. How would a child&#8217;s brain grow outside the world of sound? How would he communicate? Would he learn to read and write?    </p>
<p>                    An acclaimed science journalist as well as a mother, Denworth made it her mission to find out, interviewing experts on language development, inventors of groundbreaking technology, Deaf leaders, and neuroscientists at the frontiers of brain plasticity research. I Can Hear You Whisper chronicles Denworth&#8217;s search for answers-and her new understanding of Deaf culture and the exquisite relationship between sound, language, and learning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/">I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Geography & Topography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel With Children / Family Holidays]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>By the beloved and wildly popular host of the PBS Kids show Dinosaur Train, here is the book every parent needs: a rousing call to connect our kids to the natural world, filled with tips and advice. The average North American child now spends about seven hours a day staring at screens and mere minutes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/">How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By the beloved and wildly popular host of the PBS Kids show Dinosaur Train, here is the book every parent needs: a rousing call to connect our kids to the natural world, filled with tips and advice.    </p>
<p>                    The average North American child now spends about seven hours a day staring at screens and mere minutes engaged in unstructured play outdoors. Yet recent research indicates that experiences in nature are essential for healthy growth.     </p>
<p>                    Regular exposure to nature can help relieve stress, depression, and attention deficits. It can reduce bullying, combat obesity, and boost academic scores. Most critical of all, abundant time in natural settings seems to yield long-term benefits in kids&#8217; cognitive, emotional, and social development.     </p>
<p>                    How to Raise a Wild Child is a timely and engaging antidote, offering teachers, parents, and other caregivers the necessary tools to engender a meaningful, lasting connection between children and the natural world.     </p>
<p>                    Distilling the latest research in multiple disciplines, Sampson reveals how adults can help kids fall in love with nature&#8211;enlisting technology as an ally, taking advantage of urban nature, and instilling a sense of place along the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In a time when the connection between humans and the rest of nature is most vulnerable, Scott offers parents and teachers a book of encouragement and knowledge, and to children, the priceless gift of wonder.&#8221;&#8211;Richard Louv, author of Last Child in the Woods and The Nature Principle</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-raise-a-wild-child-the-art-and-science-of-falling-in-love-with-nature-professor-scott-d-sampson-abridged/">How to Raise a Wild Child : The Art and Science of Falling in Love with Nature &#8211; Professor Scott D Sampson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gift of Failure : How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed &#8211; Jessica Lahey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gift-of-failure-how-the-best-parents-learn-to-let-go-so-their-children-can-succeed-jessica-lahey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gift-of-failure-how-the-best-parents-learn-to-let-go-so-their-children-can-succeed-jessica-lahey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8220;Gripping&#8230;how can teachers snatch back their critical role and give children the necessary space to fail? They could start by making parents read Lahey.&#8221; &#8212; New York Times Book Review In the tradition of Paul Tough&#8217;s How Children Succeed and Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee, this groundbreaking manifesto [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gift-of-failure-how-the-best-parents-learn-to-let-go-so-their-children-can-succeed-jessica-lahey-abridged/">The Gift of Failure : How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed &#8211; Jessica Lahey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Gripping&#8230;how can teachers snatch back their critical role and give children the necessary space to fail? They could start by making parents read Lahey.&#8221; &#8212; New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of Paul Tough&#8217;s How Children Succeed and Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee, this groundbreaking manifesto focuses on the critical school years when parents must learn to allow their children to experience the disappointment and frustration that occur from life&#8217;s inevitable problems so that they can grow up to be successful, resilient, and self-reliant adults.    </p>
<p>                    Modern parenting is defined by an unprecedented level of overprotectiveness: parents who rush to school at the whim of a phone call to deliver forgotten assignments, who challenge teachers on report card disappointments, mastermind children&#8217;s friendships, and interfere on the playing field. As teacher and writer Jessica Lahey explains, even though these parents see themselves as being highly responsive to their children&#8217;s well being, they aren&#8217;t giving them the chance to experience failure&#8211;or the opportunity to learn to solve their own problems.    </p>
<p>                    Overparenting has the potential to ruin a child&#8217;s confidence and undermine their education, Lahey reminds us. Teachers don&#8217;t just teach reading, writing, and arithmetic. They teach responsibility, organization, manners, restraint, and foresight&#8211;important life skills children carry with them long after they leave the classroom.    </p>
<p>                    Providing a path toward solutions, Lahey lays out a blueprint with targeted advice for handling homework, report cards, social dynamics, and sports. Most importantly, she sets forth a plan to help parents learn to step back and embrace their children&#8217;s failures. Hard-hitting yet warm and wise, The Gift of Failure is essential reading for parents, educators, and psychologists nationwide who want to help children succeed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gift-of-failure-how-the-best-parents-learn-to-let-go-so-their-children-can-succeed-jessica-lahey-abridged/">The Gift of Failure : How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed &#8211; Jessica Lahey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
