<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Separation &amp; Divorce Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/separation-divorce/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/separation-divorce/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Separation &amp; Divorce Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/separation-divorce/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Separation & Divorce]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>_____________________________ Is having &#8216;somebody to love&#8217; the most important thing in your life? Do you constantly believe in Mr Right, and that being with him would guarantee you would no longer feel depressed or lonely? Are you bored with &#8216;nice guys&#8217; who are open, honest and dependable? If being in love means being in pain, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/">Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>_____________________________<br />
                    Is having &#8216;somebody to love&#8217; the most important thing in your life?<br />
                    Do you constantly believe in Mr Right, and that being with him would guarantee you would no longer feel depressed or lonely?<br />
                    Are you bored with &#8216;nice guys&#8217; who are open, honest and dependable?     </p>
<p>                    If being in love means being in pain, this book was written for you. Leading relationship and marriage therapist Robin Norwood describes loving too much as a pattern of thoughts and behaviour, which certain women develop as a response to problems from childhood.     </p>
<p>                    Many women find themselves repeatedly drawn into unhappy and destructive relationships with men. They then struggle to make these doomed relationships work. This bestselling relationship self-help book investigates and reveals how powerfully addictive these unhealthy relationships are &#8211; but also gives a very specific programme for recovery from the disease of loving too much, a problem that plagues women everywhere.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-who-love-too-much-robin-norwood-abridged/">Women Who Love Too Much &#8211; Robin Norwood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jog On : How Running Saved My Life &#8211; Bella Mackie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/jog-on-how-running-saved-my-life-bella-mackie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Separation & Divorce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Track & Field Sports, Athletics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/jog-on-how-running-saved-my-life-bella-mackie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Bella&#8217;s brilliant love letter to running turns into an extraordinarily brave and frank account of her battle with anxiety. A compassionate and important book&#8217; Joe Lycett &#8216;Perfect for resetting a glum January mindset&#8217; Alexandra Heminsley &#8216;My kind of role model&#8217; Ben Fogle Divorced and struggling with deep-rooted mental health problems, Bella [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jog-on-how-running-saved-my-life-bella-mackie-abridged/">Jog On : How Running Saved My Life &#8211; Bella Mackie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Bella&#8217;s brilliant love letter to running turns into an extraordinarily brave and frank account of her battle with anxiety. A compassionate and important book&#8217; Joe Lycett    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Perfect for resetting a glum January mindset&#8217; Alexandra Heminsley    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;My kind of role model&#8217; Ben Fogle    </p>
<p>                              Divorced and struggling with deep-rooted mental health problems, Bella Mackie ended her twenties in tears. She could barely find the strength to get off the sofa, let alone piece her life back together. Until one day she did something she had never done of her own free will &#8211; she pulled on a pair of trainers and went for a run.    </p>
<p>                              That first attempt didn&#8217;t last very long. But to her surprise, she was back out there the next day. And the day after that. She began to set herself achievable goals &#8211; to run 5k in under 30 minutes, to walk to work every day for a week, to attempt 10 push-ups in a row. Before she knew it, her mood was lifting for the first time in years.    </p>
<p>                              In Jog On, Bella explains with hilarious and unfiltered honesty how she used running to battle crippling anxiety and depression, without having to sacrifice her main loves: booze, cigarettes and ice cream. With the help of a supporting cast of doctors, psychologists, sportspeople and friends, she shares a wealth of inspirational stories, research and tips that show how exercise often can be the best medicine. This funny, moving and motivational book will encourage you to say &#8216;jog on&#8217; to your problems and get your life back on track &#8211; no matter how small those first steps may be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jog-on-how-running-saved-my-life-bella-mackie-abridged/">Jog On : How Running Saved My Life &#8211; Bella Mackie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sacred Cows : The Truth About Divorce and Marriage &#8211; M.D. Danielle Teller, Astro Teller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sacred-cows-the-truth-about-divorce-and-marriage-m-d-danielle-teller-astro-teller-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Separation & Divorce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sacred-cows-the-truth-about-divorce-and-marriage-m-d-danielle-teller-astro-teller-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Astro Teller currently oversees Google[x] and Danielle Teller is a physician specializing in the fields of intensive care and lung medicine. Together, they bring a fresh and startling perspective on marriage and divorce in SACRED COWS. Drs. Astro and Danielle Teller know better than most that finding the right partner in life doesn&#8217;t always happen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sacred-cows-the-truth-about-divorce-and-marriage-m-d-danielle-teller-astro-teller-abridged/">Sacred Cows : The Truth About Divorce and Marriage &#8211; M.D. Danielle Teller, Astro Teller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Astro Teller currently oversees Google[x] and Danielle Teller is a physician specializing in the fields of intensive care and lung medicine. Together, they bring a fresh and startling perspective on marriage and divorce in SACRED COWS.    </p>
<p>                     Drs. Astro and Danielle Teller know better than most that finding the right partner in life doesn&#8217;t always happen the first time around. Through their own divorces they learned how widely held cultural assumptions and misinformation that nobody thinks to question-what they refer to as &#8220;sacred cows&#8221;-create unnecessary heartache for people who are already suffering through a terrible time.    </p>
<p>                     Do you think, for example, that the divorce rate in the United States is rising? Or that children are harmed by divorce? Most people do, but it turns out that neither of these notions is supported by the data. Combining the rigor that has established them as leaders in their respective fields along with a dose of good-natured humor, the Tellers ask readers to take a fresh look at seven common sacred cows: the Holy Cow, the Expert Cow, the Selfish Cow, the Defective Cow, the Innocent Victim Cow, the One True Cow, and the Other Cow. This is not a book that is &#8220;for&#8221; marriage or &#8220;for&#8221; divorce, but &#8220;for&#8221; the freedom to decide how to live most honestly and happily either as part of a couple or a single person.    </p>
<p>                     In the same way that Esther Perel&#8217;s bestselling MATING IN CAPTIVITY gave couples a fresh perspective on their married life, so SACRED COWS invites readers to question assumptions and conventional wisdom. It offers a smart, insightful, and sympathetic view for those in a marital crisis, marriage counsellors, or anyone looking to gain a fresh perspective on one of our most cherished and misunderstood institutions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sacred-cows-the-truth-about-divorce-and-marriage-m-d-danielle-teller-astro-teller-abridged/">Sacred Cows : The Truth About Divorce and Marriage &#8211; M.D. Danielle Teller, Astro Teller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting Past Your Breakup : How to Turn a Devastating Loss into the Best Thing That Ever Happened to You &#8211; Susan Elliott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-past-your-breakup-how-to-turn-a-devastating-loss-into-the-best-thing-that-ever-happened-to-you-susan-elliott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Separation & Divorce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-past-your-breakup-how-to-turn-a-devastating-loss-into-the-best-thing-that-ever-happened-to-you-susan-elliott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s over- and it really hurts. But as unbelievable as it may seem when you are in the throes of heartache, you can move past your breakup. Forget about trying to win your ex back. Forget about losing yourself and trying to make this person love you. Forget it! Starting today, this breakup is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-past-your-breakup-how-to-turn-a-devastating-loss-into-the-best-thing-that-ever-happened-to-you-susan-elliott-abridged/">Getting Past Your Breakup : How to Turn a Devastating Loss into the Best Thing That Ever Happened to You &#8211; Susan Elliott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s over- and it really hurts. But as unbelievable as it may seem when you are in the throes of heartache, you  can  move past your breakup. Forget about trying to win your ex back. Forget about losing yourself and trying to make this person love you. Forget it! Starting today, this breakup is the best time to change your life for the better, inside and out.   Getting Past Your Breakup  is a proven roadmap for overcoming the painful end of any romantic relationship, even divorce. Through her workshops and popular blog, Susan Elliott has helped thousands of clients and readers transform their love lives. Now, she&#8217;ll help you put your energy back where it belongs- on you. Her plan includes:    The rules of disengagement: how and why to go &#8220;no contact&#8221; with your ex  How to work through grief, move past fear, and take back your life  The secret to breaking the pattern of failed relationships  What to do when you can&#8217;t stop thinking about your ex, texting, calling, checking social networking sites, or driving by the house  Complete with inspiring stories from real people and strategies to jump-start the moving-on process,  Getting Past Your Breakup  is the most effective plan for getting permanently past a breakup, getting your confidence back, and opening yourself to true love.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-past-your-breakup-how-to-turn-a-devastating-loss-into-the-best-thing-that-ever-happened-to-you-susan-elliott-abridged/">Getting Past Your Breakup : How to Turn a Devastating Loss into the Best Thing That Ever Happened to You &#8211; Susan Elliott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
