<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Economic Forecasting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/economic-forecasting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/economic-forecasting/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Economic Forecasting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/economic-forecasting/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Predictive Analytics : The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die &#8211; Eric Siegel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Mesmerizing &#038; fascinating&#8230;&#8221; -The Seattle Post-Intelligencer &#8220;The Freakonomics of big data.&#8221; -Stein Kretsinger, founding executive of Advertising.com Award-winning &#124; Used by over 30 universities &#124; Translated into 9 languages An introduction for everyone. In this rich, fascinating &#8211; surprisingly accessible &#8211; introduction, leading expert Eric Siegel reveals how predictive analytics (aka machine learning) works, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/">Predictive Analytics : The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die &#8211; Eric Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Mesmerizing &#038; fascinating&#8230;&#8221; -The Seattle Post-Intelligencer    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Freakonomics of big data.&#8221; -Stein Kretsinger, founding executive of Advertising.com    </p>
<p>                     Award-winning | Used by over 30 universities | Translated into 9 languages    </p>
<p>                     An introduction for everyone. In this rich, fascinating &#8211; surprisingly accessible &#8211; introduction, leading expert Eric Siegel reveals how predictive analytics (aka machine learning) works, and how it affects everyone every day. Rather than a &#8220;how to&#8221; for hands-on techies, the book serves lay readers and experts alike by covering new case studies and the latest state-of-the-art techniques.    </p>
<p>                     Prediction is booming. It reinvents industries and runs the world. Companies, governments, law enforcement, hospitals, and universities are seizing upon the power. These institutions predict whether you&#8217;re going to click, buy, lie, or die.    </p>
<p>                    Why? For good reason: predicting human behavior combats risk, boosts sales, fortifies healthcare, streamlines manufacturing, conquers spam, optimizes social networks, toughens crime fighting, and wins elections.    </p>
<p>                    How? Prediction is powered by the world&#8217;s most potent, flourishing unnatural resource: data. Accumulated in large part as the by-product of routine tasks, data is the unsalted, flavorless residue deposited en masse as organizations churn away. Surprise! This heap of refuse is a gold mine. Big data embodies an extraordinary wealth of experience from which to learn.    </p>
<p>                    Predictive analytics(aka machine learning) unleashes the power of data. With this technology, the computer literally learns from data how to predict the future behavior of individuals. Perfect prediction is not possible, but putting odds on the future drives millions of decisions more effectively, determining whom to call, mail, investigate, incarcerate, set up on a date, or medicate.    </p>
<p>                    In this lucid, captivating introduction &#8211; now in its Revised and Updated edition &#8211; former Columbia University professor and Predictive Analytics World founder Eric Siegel reveals the power and perils of prediction:    </p>
<p>                    What type of mortgage risk Chase Bank predicted before the recession.<br />
                    Predicting which people will drop out of school, cancel a subscription, or get divorced before they even know it themselves.<br />
                    Why early retirement predicts a shorter life expectancy and vegetarians miss fewer flights.<br />
                    Five reasons why organizations predict death &#8211; including one health insurance company.<br />
                    How U.S. Bank and Obama for America calculated the way to most strongly persuade each individual.<br />
                    Why the NSA wants all your data: machine learning supercomputers to fight terrorism.<br />
                    How IBM&#8217;s Watson computer used predictive modeling to answer questions and beat the human champs on TV&#8217;s Jeopardy!<br />
                    How companies ascertain untold, private truths &#8211; how Target figures out you&#8217;re pregnant and Hewlett-Packard deduces you&#8217;re about to quit your job.<br />
                    How judges and parole boards rely on crime-predicting computers to decide how long convicts remain in prison.<br />
                    182 examples from Airbnb, the BBC, Citibank, ConEd, Facebook, Ford, Google, the IRS, LinkedIn, Match.com, MTV, Netflix, PayPal, Pfizer, Spotify, Uber, UPS, Wikipedia, and more.    </p>
<p>                     How does predictive analytics work? This jam-packed book satisfies by demystifying the intriguing science under the hood. For future hands-on practitioners pursuing a career in the field, it sets a strong foundation, delivers the prerequisite knowledge, and whets your appetite for more.    </p>
<p>                     A truly omnipresent science, predictive analytics constantly affects our daily lives. Whether you are a consumer of it &#8211; or consumed by it &#8211; get a handle on the power of Predictive Analytics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/">Predictive Analytics : The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die &#8211; Eric Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Attacker&#8217;s Advantage : Turning Uncertainty into Breakthrough Opportunities &#8211; Ram Charan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-attackers-advantage-turning-uncertainty-into-breakthrough-opportunities-ram-charan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-attackers-advantage-turning-uncertainty-into-breakthrough-opportunities-ram-charan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A Wall Street Journal bestseller*The forces driving today&#8217;s world of structural change create sharp bends in the road that can lead to major explosions in your existing market space. But exponential change also offers exponential opportunities. How do you leverage change to go on the offense? The Attacker&#8217;s Advantage is the game plan for winning [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-attackers-advantage-turning-uncertainty-into-breakthrough-opportunities-ram-charan-abridged/">The Attacker&#8217;s Advantage : Turning Uncertainty into Breakthrough Opportunities &#8211; Ram Charan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A  Wall Street Journal  bestseller*The forces driving today&#8217;s world of structural change create sharp bends in the road that can lead to major explosions in your existing market space. But exponential change also offers exponential opportunities. How do you leverage change to go on the offense?  The Attacker&#8217;s Advantage  is the game plan for winning in an era of ambiguity, volatility, and complexity, when every leader and every business is being challenged in new and unexpected ways.Ram Charan, harnessing an unequalled depth and breadth of experience working with leaders and companies around the globe, provides tested, practical tools to help you:Build the perceptual acuity to see around corners and detect, ahead of others, those forces,especially people, who are the catalysts of change,that could radically reshape a company or industryHave the mindset to see opportunity in uncertaintyCommit to a new path forward despite the unknowns, positioning your business to make the next move ahead of competitorsBreak the blockages that can hold your company backKnow when to accelerate and when to shift the short-term and long-term balanceMake your organization agile and steerable by aligning people, priorities, decision-making power, budgeting and capital allocation, and key performance indicators to the new realities of the marketplace The Attacker&#8217;s Advantage  provides a stark and simple challenge: stay in a legacy world of incremental gains or defensiveness, or be an attacker by creating a new world, scaling it up quickly, ahead of the traditional players.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-attackers-advantage-turning-uncertainty-into-breakthrough-opportunities-ram-charan-abridged/">The Attacker&#8217;s Advantage : Turning Uncertainty into Breakthrough Opportunities &#8211; Ram Charan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new, evolutionary explanation of markets and investor behavior Half of all Americans have money in the stock market, yet economists can&#8217;t agree on whether investors and markets are rational and efficient, as modern financial theory assumes, or irrational and inefficient, as behavioral economists believe&#8211;and as financial bubbles, crashes, and crises suggest. This is one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/">Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new, evolutionary explanation of markets and investor behavior  Half of all Americans have money in the stock market, yet economists can&#8217;t agree on whether investors and markets are rational and efficient, as modern financial theory assumes, or irrational and inefficient, as behavioral economists believe&#8211;and as financial bubbles, crashes, and crises suggest. This is one of the biggest debates in economics and the value or futility of investment management and financial regulation hang on the outcome. In this groundbreaking book, Andrew Lo cuts through this debate with a new framework, the Adaptive Markets Hypothesis, in which rationality and irrationality coexist. Drawing on psychology, evolutionary biology, neuroscience, artificial intelligence, and other fields, Adaptive Markets shows that the theory of market efficiency isn&#8217;t wrong but merely incomplete. When markets are unstable, investors react instinctively, creating inefficiencies for others to exploit. Lo&#8217;s new paradigm explains how financial evolution shapes behavior and markets at the speed of thought&#8211;a fact revealed by swings between stability and crisis, profit and loss, and innovation and regulation.<br />
                    A fascinating intellectual journey filled with compelling stories, Adaptive Markets starts with the origins of market efficiency and its failures, turns to the foundations of investor behavior, and concludes with practical implications&#8211;including how hedge funds have become the Galapagos Islands of finance, what really happened in the 2008 meltdown, and how we might avoid future crises. An ambitious new answer to fundamental questions in economics, Adaptive Markets is essential reading for anyone who wants to know how markets really work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/">Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anticipate : The Art of Leading by Looking Ahead &#8211; Rob-Jan Jong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anticipate-the-art-of-leading-by-looking-ahead-rob-jan-jong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anticipate-the-art-of-leading-by-looking-ahead-rob-jan-jong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vision . . . All the best business schools, books, and gurus say that leaders absolutely must have it&#8211;so why does it appear that many of today&#8217;s leaders were absent the day that was taught? Because the sad truth is, most leaders today have not developed the visionary capacity necessary to look ahead and explore [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anticipate-the-art-of-leading-by-looking-ahead-rob-jan-jong-abridged/">Anticipate : The Art of Leading by Looking Ahead &#8211; Rob-Jan Jong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vision . . . All the best business schools, books, and gurus say that leaders absolutely must have it&#8211;so why does it appear that many of today&#8217;s leaders were absent the day that was taught? Because the sad truth is, most leaders today have not developed the visionary capacity necessary to look ahead and explore strategic futures. Or at least their so-called vision is not one that compels, inspires, and energizes their people. Vision may sound like a rare quality, attainable by only a select few&#8211;but nothing could be further from the truth. In Anticipate, strategy and leadership expert Rob-Jan de Jong explains how anyone can develop in themselves a visionary leadership. It simply boils down to sharpening two key skills: 1) the ability to see things early, and 2) the power to connect the dots. Using the author&#8217;s trademarked FuturePriming process, which helps distinguish signal from noise, readers geared toward fine-tuning these two basic but essential skills will discover how to: &#8211; Tap into their imagination and open themselves up to the unconventional &#8211; Become better at seeing things early &#8211; Frame the big-picture view that provides direction for the future &#8211; Communicate your vision in a way that engages others and provokes action &#8211; And more When you can anticipate change before your competitors, you create enormous strategic advantage. That&#8217;s what visionaries do . . . and now so can you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anticipate-the-art-of-leading-by-looking-ahead-rob-jan-jong-abridged/">Anticipate : The Art of Leading by Looking Ahead &#8211; Rob-Jan Jong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks&#8217;s The Most Important Thing distilled the investing insight of his celebrated client memos into a single volume and, for the first time, made his time-tested philosophy available to general readers. In this edition, Marks&#8217;s wisdom is joined by the comments, insights, and counterpoints of four renowned investors and investment educators: Christopher C. Davis [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/">The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks&#8217;s The Most Important Thing distilled the investing insight of his celebrated client memos into a single volume and, for the first time, made his time-tested philosophy available to general readers. In this edition, Marks&#8217;s wisdom is joined by the comments, insights, and counterpoints of four renowned investors and investment educators: Christopher C. Davis (Davis Funds), Joel Greenblatt (Gotham Capital), Paul Johnson (Nicusa Capital), and Seth A. Klarman (Baupost Group). These experts lend insight into such concepts as &#8220;second-level thinking,&#8221; the price/value relationship, patient opportunism, and defensive investing. Marks also adds his own annotations, expanding on his book&#8217;s original themes and issues. A new chapter addresses the importance of reasonable expectations, and a foreword by Bruce C. Greenwald, called &#8220;a guru to Wall Street&#8217;s gurus&#8221; by the New York Times, speaks on value investing, productivity, and the economics of information.  ***  Howard Marks, the chairman and cofounder of Oaktree Capital Management, is renowned for his insightful assessments of market opportunity and risk.<br />
                    After four decades spent ascending to the top of the investment management profession, he is today sought out by the world&#8217;s leading value investors, and his client memos brim with insightful commentary and a time-tested, fundamental philosophy. Now for the first time, all readers can benefit from Marks&#8217;s wisdom, concentrated into a single volume that speaks to both the amateur and seasoned investor.  Informed by a lifetime of experience and study, The Most Important Thing explains the keys to successful investment and the pitfalls that can destroy capital or ruin a career. Utilizing passages from his memos to illustrate his ideas, Marks teaches by example, detailing the development of an investment philosophy that fully acknowledges the complexities of investing and the perils of the financial world. Brilliantly applying insight to today&#8217;s volatile markets, Marks offers a volume that is part memoir, part creed, with a number of broad takeaways.  Marks expounds on such concepts as &#8220;second-level thinking,&#8221; the price/value relationship, patient opportunism, and defensive investing.<br />
                    Frankly and honestly assessing his own decisions&#8211;and occasional missteps&#8211;he provides valuable lessons for critical thinking, risk assessment, and investment strategy. Encouraging investors to be &#8220;contrarian,&#8221; Marks wisely judges market cycles and achieves returns through aggressive yet measured action. Which element is the most essential? Successful investing requires thoughtful attention to many separate aspects, and each of Marks&#8217;s subjects proves to be the most important thing.  &#8220;This is that rarity, a useful book.&#8221;&#8211;Warren Buffett</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/">The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Non-Obvious 2018 Edition : How To Predict Trends And Win The Future &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Seller (2015 Edition) Gold Medal: Non-Fiction Book Awards (2018 Edition) Winner: IPPY Book Awards Silver Medal (2018 Edition) Winner: Axiom Business Theory Silver Medal (2017 Edition) Official Selection: Gary&#8217;s Book Club at CES (2017 Edition) #1 AMAZON OVERALL BUSINESS BEST SELLER (2015 Edition) What secrets can a 400-year-old Turkish cymbal maker [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Non-Obvious 2018 Edition : How To Predict Trends And Win The Future &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Seller (2015 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Gold Medal: Non-Fiction Book Awards (2018 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Winner: IPPY Book Awards Silver Medal (2018 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Winner: Axiom Business Theory Silver Medal (2017 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Official Selection: Gary&#8217;s Book Club at CES (2017 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    #1 AMAZON OVERALL BUSINESS BEST SELLER (2015 Edition)     </p>
<p>                    What secrets can a 400-year-old Turkish cymbal maker and an Icelandic hot tub etiquette video teach you about the power of storytelling?     </p>
<p>                    How do Michelin-ranked food stalls in Singapore and the decline of Swiss watches force all luxury brands to rethink their business models?     </p>
<p>                    What insights can the world&#8217;s quietest place and a clothing dye produced by former tobacco farmers reveal about serving enlightened consumers?    </p>
<p>                    The answers to these questions may not be all that obvious. And that&#8217;s exactly the point. For the past eight years, innovation expert Rohit Bhargava and his team have predicted 15 &#8220;Non-Obvious&#8221; trends each year. In this book, get a sneak peek at the proven methods exclusively taught to thousands of executives at leading brands, organizations and governments to develop unexpected solutions to critical problems. The power of non-obvious thinking can help you see what others miss, grow your business and make a bigger impact in the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this all-new eighth edition, discover what more than a million readers already have: how to use the power of non-obvious thinking to grow your business and make a bigger impact in the world.    </p>
<p>                    In total, the Non-Obvious 2018 Edition features 15 all-new trends across 5 categories including Culture &#038; Consumer Behavior, Marketing &#038; Social Media, Media &#038; Education, Technology &#038; Design plus Economics &#038; Entrepreneurship. The book also features a detailed section with a review and rating for more than 100 previously predicted trends &#8211; with longevity ratings for each.    </p>
<p>                    As with the original version, this new edition of Non-Obvious also delves into the curation process the author has used for years to build his Trend Reports and takes readers behind the scenes of trend curation (much to the delight of past readers who have been asking about this for years), and show them the methodology they can use to predict the future for themselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Non-Obvious 2018 Edition : How To Predict Trends And Win The Future &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller The Next 100 Years now focuses his geopolitical forecasting acumen on the next decade and the imminent events and challenges that will test America and the world, specifically addressing the skills that will be required by the decade&#8217;s leaders. In the long view, history is seen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/">The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller The Next 100 Years now focuses his geopolitical forecasting acumen on the next decade and the imminent events and challenges that will test America and the world, specifically addressing the skills that will be required by the decade&#8217;s leaders.     </p>
<p>                    In the long view, history is seen as a series of events&#8211;but the course of those events is determined by individuals and their actions. During the next ten years, individual leaders will face significant transitions for their nations: the United States&#8217; relationships with Iran and Israel will be undergoing changes, China will likely confront a major crisis, and the wars in the Islamic world will subside. Unexpected energy and technology developments will emerge, and labor shortages will begin to matter more than financial crises. Distinguished geopolitical forecaster George Friedman analyzes these events from the perspectives of the men and women leading these global changes, focusing in particular on the American president, who will require extraordinary skills to shepherd the United States through this transitional period. The Next Decade is a provocative and fascinating look at the conflicts and opportunities that lie ahead.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/">The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a rational explanation of the ways in which the AI revolution will affect us all. Tackling the implications of Artificial Intelligence on growth, productivity, inflation and the distribution of wealth and power, THE AI ECONOMY also examines coming changes to the the way we educate, work and spend our leisure time.    </p>
<p>                    A fundamentally optimistic view which will help you plan for changing times, this book explains AI and leads you towards a more certain future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Numbers Rule Your World: The Hidden Influence of Probabilities and Statistics on Everything You Do &#8211; Kaiser Fung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WHAT ARE THE ODDS YOU&#8217;LL WIN THE LOTTERY? How long will your kids wait in line at Disney World?Who decides that &#8220;standardized tests&#8221; are fair?Why do highway engineers build slow-moving ramps?What does it mean, statistically, to be an &#8220;Average Joe&#8221;?NUMBERS RULE YOUR WORLD In the popular tradition of eye-opening bestsellers like Freakonomics, The Tipping Point, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/">Numbers Rule Your World: The Hidden Influence of Probabilities and Statistics on Everything You Do &#8211; Kaiser Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WHAT ARE THE ODDS YOU&#8217;LL WIN THE LOTTERY?<br />
                    How long will your kids wait in line at Disney World?Who decides that &#8220;standardized tests&#8221; are fair?Why do highway engineers build slow-moving ramps?What does it mean, statistically, to be an &#8220;Average Joe&#8221;?NUMBERS RULE YOUR WORLD<br />
                    In the popular tradition of eye-opening bestsellers like Freakonomics, The Tipping Point, and Super Crunchers, this fascinating book from renowned statistician and blogger Kaiser Fung takes you inside the hidden world of facts and figures that affect you every day, in every way. These are the statistics that rule your life, your job, your commute, your vacation, your food, your health, your money, and your success. This is how engineers calculate your quality of living, how corporations determine your needs, and how politicians estimate your opinions. These are the numbers you never think about-even though they play a crucial role in every single aspect of your life.What you learn may surprise you, amuse you, or even enrage you. But there&#8217;s one thing you won&#8217;t be able to deny: Numbers Rule Your World&#8230;&#8221;An easy read with a big benefit.&#8221;<br />
                    -Fareed Zakaria, CNN    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;For those who have anxiety about how organization data-mining is impacting their world,  Kaiser Fung pulls back the curtain to reveal the good and the bad of predictive analytics.&#8221;<br />
                    -Ian Ayres,Yale professor and author of Super Crunchers:  Why Thinking By Numbers is the New Way to Be Smart<br />
                     &#8220;A book that engages us with stories that a journalist would write, the compelling stories behind the stories as illuminated by the numbers, and the dynamics that the numbers reveal.&#8221;<br />
                    -John Sall, Executive Vice President, SAS Institute  &#8220;Little did I suspect, when I picked up Kaiser Fung&#8217;s book, that I would become so entranced by it &#8211; an illuminating and accessible exploration of the power of statistical analysis for those of us who have no prior training in a field that he explores so ably.&#8221;<br />
                    -Peter Clarke, author of  Keynes: The Rise, Fall, and Return of the 20th Century&#8217;s Most Influential Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A tremendous book. . . . If you want to understand how to use statistics, how to think with numbers and yet to do this without getting lost in equations, if you&#8217;ve been looking for the book to unlock the door to logical thinking about problems, well, you will be pleased to know that you are holding that book in your hands.&#8221;<br />
                    -Daniel Finkelstein, Executive Editor, The Times of London&#8221;I thoroughly enjoyed this accessible book and enthusiastically recommendit to anyone looking to understand and appreciate the role of statistics and dataanalysis in solving problems and in creating a better world.&#8221;<br />
                     -Michael Sherman, Texas A&#038;M University, American Statistician</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/">Numbers Rule Your World: The Hidden Influence of Probabilities and Statistics on Everything You Do &#8211; Kaiser Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Prepare a Business Plan : Your Guide to Creating an Excellent Strategy, Forecasting Your Finances and Producing a Persuasive Plan &#8211; Edward Blackwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An excellent business plan impresses financial backers, provides a clear blueprint for the future of your company and functions as a benchmark against which to measure future growth. How to Prepare a Business Plan explains the process of creating an excellent business plan in an engaging and accessible way. It includes essential coverage of producing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/">How to Prepare a Business Plan : Your Guide to Creating an Excellent Strategy, Forecasting Your Finances and Producing a Persuasive Plan &#8211; Edward Blackwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An excellent business plan impresses financial backers, provides a clear blueprint for the future of your company and functions as a benchmark against which to measure future growth. How to Prepare a Business Plan explains the process of creating an excellent business plan in an engaging and accessible way. It includes essential coverage of producing cash flow forecasts, planning a business expansion, planning your borrowing and monitoring business progress.     </p>
<p>                    Global case studies containing real business plans provide inspiration and real-life practical insight by analyzing the plans, monitoring the business&#8217; progress and discussing their problems. Sample business plans also show you the process in action and provide useful examples for creating your own. How to Prepare a Business Plan helps new business owners to consider what they really want out of their business, and to map their own journey and gain a new understanding of their product&#8217;s place in the market, as well as writing a business plan with the clarity, brevity and logic to keep bank managers interested and convinced.     </p>
<p>                    Whether looking to start up or expand, this practical advice will help anyone to prepare a plan that is tailored to the requirements of their business &#8211; one that will get the financial backing they need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-prepare-a-business-plan-your-guide-to-creating-an-excellent-strategy-forecasting-your-finances-and-producing-a-persuasive-plan-edward-blackwell-abridged/">How to Prepare a Business Plan : Your Guide to Creating an Excellent Strategy, Forecasting Your Finances and Producing a Persuasive Plan &#8211; Edward Blackwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE ECONOMIST &#8220;The most important book on decision making since Daniel Kahneman&#8217;s Thinking, Fast and Slow.&#8221;&#8211;Jason Zweig, The Wall Street Journal Everyone would benefit from seeing further into the future, whether buying stocks, crafting policy, launching a new product, or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/">Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE ECONOMIST      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The most important book on decision making since Daniel Kahneman&#8217;s Thinking, Fast and Slow.&#8221;&#8211;Jason Zweig, The Wall Street Journal     </p>
<p>                     Everyone would benefit from seeing further into the future, whether buying stocks, crafting policy, launching a new product, or simply planning the week&#8217;s meals. Unfortunately, people tend to be terrible forecasters. As Wharton professor Philip Tetlock showed in a landmark 2005 study, even experts&#8217; predictions are only slightly better than chance. However, an important and underreported conclusion of that study was that some experts do have real foresight, and Tetlock has spent the past decade trying to figure out why. What makes some people so good? And can this talent be taught?     </p>
<p>                     In Superforecasting, Tetlock and coauthor Dan Gardner offer a masterwork on prediction, drawing on decades of research and the results of a massive, government-funded forecasting tournament. The Good Judgment Project involves tens of thousands of ordinary people&#8211;including a Brooklyn filmmaker, a retired pipe installer, and a former ballroom dancer&#8211;who set out to forecast global events. Some of the volunteers have turned out to be astonishingly good. They&#8217;ve beaten other benchmarks, competitors, and prediction markets. They&#8217;ve even beaten the collective judgment of intelligence analysts with access to classified information. They are superforecasters.     </p>
<p>                     In this groundbreaking and accessible book, Tetlock and Gardner show us how we can learn from this elite group. Weaving together stories of forecasting successes (the raid on Osama bin Laden&#8217;s compound) and failures (the Bay of Pigs) and interviews with a range of high-level decision makers, from David Petraeus to Robert Rubin, they show that good forecasting doesn&#8217;t require powerful computers or arcane methods. It involves gathering evidence from a variety of sources, thinking probabilistically, working in teams, keeping score, and being willing to admit error and change course.     </p>
<p>                    Superforecasting offers the first demonstrably effective way to improve our ability to predict the future&#8211;whether in business, finance, politics, international affairs, or daily life&#8211;and is destined to become a modern classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/">Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
