<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Energy Industries &amp; Utilities Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/energy-industries-utilities/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/energy-industries-utilities/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Energy Industries &amp; Utilities Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/energy-industries-utilities/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Company Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Industries & Utilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What went wrong with American business at the end of the 20th century? Until the spring of 2001, Enron epitomized the triumph of the New Economy. Feared by rivals, worshipped by investors, Enron seemingly could do no wrong. Its profits rose every year; its stock price surged ever upward; its leaders were hailed as visionaries. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/">The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What went wrong with American business at the end of the 20th century?    </p>
<p>                    Until the spring of 2001, Enron epitomized the triumph of the New Economy. Feared by rivals, worshipped by investors, Enron seemingly could do no wrong. Its profits rose every year; its stock price surged ever upward; its leaders were hailed as visionaries.      </p>
<p>                    Then a young Fortune writer, Bethany McLean, wrote an article posing a simple question &#8211;  how, exactly, does Enron make its money?    </p>
<p>                    Within a year Enron was facing humiliation and bankruptcy, the largest in US history, which caused Americans to lose faith in a system that rewarded top insiders with millions of dollars, while small investors lost everything. It was revealed that Enron was a company whose business was an illusion, an illusion that Wall Street was willing to accept even though they knew what the real truth was.  This book &#8211; fully updated for the paperback &#8211; tells the extraordinary story of Enron&#8217;s fall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/">The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moral Case For Fossil Fuels &#8211; Afterword by Alex Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/moral-case-for-fossil-fuels-afterword-by-alex-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Industries & Utilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fossil Fuel Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/moral-case-for-fossil-fuels-afterword-by-alex-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Could everything we know about fossil fuels be wrong? For decades, environmentalists have told us that using fossil fuels is a self-destructive addiction that will destroy our planet. Yet at the same time, by every measure of human well-being, from life expectancy to clean water to climate safety, life has been getting better and better. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moral-case-for-fossil-fuels-afterword-by-alex-epstein-abridged/">Moral Case For Fossil Fuels &#8211; Afterword by Alex Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Could everything we know about fossil fuels be wrong?     </p>
<p>                    For decades, environmentalists have told us that using fossil fuels is a self-destructive addiction that will destroy our planet. Yet at the same time, by every measure of human well-being, from life expectancy to clean water to climate safety, life has been getting better and better.     </p>
<p>                    How can this be?     </p>
<p>                    The explanation, energy expert Alex Epstein argues in The Moral Case for Fossil Fuels, is that we usually hear only one side of the story. We&#8217;re taught to think only of the negatives of fossil fuels, their risks and side effects, but not their positives&#8211;their unique ability to provide cheap, reliable energy for a world of seven billion people. And the moral significance of cheap, reliable energy, Epstein argues, is woefully underrated. Energy is our ability to improve every single aspect of life, whether economic or environmental.     </p>
<p>                    If we look at the big picture of fossil fuels compared with the alternatives, the overall impact of using fossil fuels is to make the world a far better place. We are morally obligated to use more fossil fuels for the sake of our economy and our environment.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on original insights and cutting-edge research, Epstein argues that most of what we hear about fossil fuels is a myth. For instance . . .     </p>
<p>                    Myth Fossil fuels are dirty.<br />
                    Truth The environmental benefits of using fossil fuels far outweigh the risks. Fossil fuels don&#8217;t take a naturally clean environment and make it dirty; they take a naturally dirty environment and make it clean. They don&#8217;t take a naturally safe climate and make it dangerous; they take a naturally dangerous climate and make it ever safer.     </p>
<p>                    Myth Fossil fuels are unsustainable, so we should strive to use &#8220;renewable&#8221; solar and wind.<br />
                    Truth The sun and wind are intermittent, unreliable fuels that always need backup from a reliable source of energy&#8211;usually fossil fuels. There are huge amounts of fossil fuels left, and we have plenty of time to find something cheaper.     </p>
<p>                    Myth Fossil fuels are hurting the developing world.<br />
                    Truth Fossil fuels are the key to improving the quality of life for billions of people in the developing world. If we withhold them, access to clean water plummets, critical medical machines like incubators become impossible to operate, and life expectancy drops significantly. Calls to &#8220;get off fossil fuels&#8221; are calls to degrade the lives of innocent people who merely want the same opportunities we enjoy in the West.     </p>
<p>                    Taking everything into account, including the facts about climate change, Epstein argues that &#8220;fossil fuels are easy to misunderstand and demonize, but they are absolutely good to use. And they absolutely need to be championed. . . . Mankind&#8217;s use of fossil fuels is supremely virtuous&#8211;because human life is the standard of value and because using fossil fuels transforms our environment to make it wonderful for human life.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moral-case-for-fossil-fuels-afterword-by-alex-epstein-abridged/">Moral Case For Fossil Fuels &#8211; Afterword by Alex Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
