<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Slavery &amp; Abolition Of Slavery Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/slavery-abolition-of-slavery/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/slavery-abolition-of-slavery/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Slavery &amp; Abolition Of Slavery Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/slavery-abolition-of-slavery/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</title>
		<link>/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Worship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Koran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Slavery & Abolition Of Slavery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when authorities you venerate condone something you know is wrong? Every major religion and philosophy once condoned or approved of slavery, but in modern times nothing is seen as more evil. Americans confront this crisis of authority when they erect statues of Founding Fathers who slept with their slaves. And Muslims faced it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/">Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when authorities you venerate condone something you know is wrong?</p>
<p>                    Every major religion and philosophy once condoned or approved of slavery, but in modern times nothing is seen as more evil. Americans confront this crisis of authority when they erect statues of Founding Fathers who slept with their slaves. And Muslims faced it when ISIS revived sex slavery, justifying it with verses from the Quran and the practice of Muhammad.</p>
<p>                    Exploring the moral and ultimately theological problem of slavery, Jonathan A.C. Brown traces how the Christian, Jewish and Islamic traditions have tried to reconcile modern moral certainties with the infallibility of God&#8217;s message. He lays out how Islam viewed slavery in theory, and the reality of how it was practiced across Islamic civilization. Finally, Brown carefully examines arguments put forward by Muslims for the abolition of slavery.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slavery-and-islam-jonathan-a-c-brown/">Slavery and Islam &#8211; Jonathan A.C. Brown</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Harriet Tubman : The Road to Freedom &#8211; Catherine Clinton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/harriet-tubman-the-road-to-freedom-catherine-clinton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American Civil War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Slavery & Abolition Of Slavery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/harriet-tubman-the-road-to-freedom-catherine-clinton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the most important and enduring figures in the history of 19th century America, the legendary conductor on the Underground Railroad whose courageous exploits have been described in countless books for young readers, is here revealed for the first time as a singular and complex character, a woman who defied simple categorisation. &#124;In this, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/harriet-tubman-the-road-to-freedom-catherine-clinton-abridged/">Harriet Tubman : The Road to Freedom &#8211; Catherine Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the most important and enduring figures in the history of 19th century America, the legendary conductor on the Underground Railroad whose courageous exploits have been described in countless books for young readers, is here revealed for the first time as a singular and complex character, a woman who defied simple categorisation. |In this, the first major biography of Harriet Tubman in more than 100 years, we see the heroine of children&#8217;s books and biopics with a new clarity and richness of detail.| &#8211; Time</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/harriet-tubman-the-road-to-freedom-catherine-clinton-abridged/">Harriet Tubman : The Road to Freedom &#8211; Catherine Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frederick Douglass : Prophet of Freedom &#8211; David W. Blight (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/frederick-douglass-prophet-of-freedom-david-w-blight-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Slavery & Abolition Of Slavery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/frederick-douglass-prophet-of-freedom-david-w-blight-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**Winner of the Pulitzer Prize in History** &#8220;Extraordinary&#8230;a great American biography&#8221; (The New Yorker) of the most important African-American of the nineteenth century: Frederick Douglass, the escaped slave who became the greatest orator of his day and one of the leading abolitionists and writers of the era. As a young man Frederick Douglass (1818-1895) escaped [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/frederick-douglass-prophet-of-freedom-david-w-blight-abridged/">Frederick Douglass : Prophet of Freedom &#8211; David W. Blight (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**Winner of the Pulitzer Prize in History**    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Extraordinary&#8230;a great American biography&#8221; (The New Yorker) of the most important African-American of the nineteenth century: Frederick Douglass, the escaped slave who became the greatest orator of his day and one of the leading abolitionists and writers of the era.    </p>
<p>                    As a young man Frederick Douglass (1818-1895) escaped from slavery in Baltimore, Maryland. He was fortunate to have been taught to read by his slave owner mistress, and he would go on to become one of the major literary figures of his time. His very existence gave the lie to slave owners: with dignity and great intelligence he bore witness to the brutality of slavery.    </p>
<p>                    Initially mentored by William Lloyd Garrison, Douglass spoke widely, using his own story to condemn slavery. By the Civil War, Douglass had become the most famed and widely travelled orator in the nation. In his unique and eloquent voice, written and spoken, Douglass was a fierce critic of the United States as well as a radical patriot. After the war he sometimes argued politically with younger African Americans, but he never forsook either the Republican party or the cause of black civil and political rights.    </p>
<p>                    In this &#8220;cinematic and deeply engaging&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) biography, David Blight has drawn on new information held in a private collection that few other historian have consulted, as well as recently discovered issues of Douglass&#8217;s newspapers. &#8220;Absorbing and even moving&#8230;a brilliant book that speaks to our own time as well as Douglass&#8217;s&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal), Blight&#8217;s biography tells the fascinating story of Douglass&#8217;s two marriages and his complex extended family. &#8220;David Blight has written the definitive biography of Frederick Douglass&#8230;a powerful portrait of one of the most important American voices of the nineteenth century&#8221; (The Boston Globe).    </p>
<p>                    In addition to the Pulitzer Prize, Frederick Douglass won the Bancroft, Parkman, Los Angeles Times (biography), Lincoln, Plutarch, and Christopher awards and was named one of the Best Books of 2018 by The New York Times Book Review, The Wall Street Journal, The Boston Globe, The Chicago Tribune, The San Francisco Chronicle, and Time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/frederick-douglass-prophet-of-freedom-david-w-blight-abridged/">Frederick Douglass : Prophet of Freedom &#8211; David W. Blight (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
