<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Health Systems &amp; Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/health-systems-services/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/health-systems-services/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Health Systems &amp; Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/health-systems-services/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Compassionomics : The Revolutionary Scientific Evidence That Caring Makes a Difference &#8211; Stephen Trzeciak, Anthony Mazzarelli</title>
		<link>/compassionomics-the-revolutionary-scientific-evidence-that-caring-makes-a-difference-stephen-trzeciak-anthony-mazzarelli/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Ethics & Professional Conduct]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/compassionomics-the-revolutionary-scientific-evidence-that-caring-makes-a-difference-stephen-trzeciak-anthony-mazzarelli/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 34-year-old man fighting for his life in the Intensive Care Unit is on an artificial respirator for over a month. Could it be that his chance of getting off the respirator is not how much his nurses know, but rather how much they care? A 75-year-old woman is heroically saved by a major trauma [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/compassionomics-the-revolutionary-scientific-evidence-that-caring-makes-a-difference-stephen-trzeciak-anthony-mazzarelli/">Compassionomics : The Revolutionary Scientific Evidence That Caring Makes a Difference &#8211; Stephen Trzeciak, Anthony Mazzarelli</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A 34-year-old man fighting for his life in the Intensive Care Unit is on an artificial respirator for over a month. Could it be that his chance of getting off the respirator is not how much his nurses know, but rather how much they care? A 75-year-old woman is heroically saved by a major trauma center only to be discharged and fatally struck by a car while walking home from the hospital. Could a lack of compassion from the hospital staff have been a factor in her death? Compelling new research shows that health care is in the midst of a compassion crisis.But the pivotal question is this: Does compassion really matter? In Compassionomics: The Revolutionary Scientific Evidence that Caring Makes a Difference, physician scientists Stephen Trzeciak and Anthony Mazzarelli uncover the eye-opening data that compassion could be a wonder drug for the 21st century.Now, for the first time ever, a rigorous review of the science &#8211; coupled with captivating stories from the front lines of medicine &#8211; demonstrates that human connection in health care matters in astonishing ways. Never before has all the evidence been synthesized together in one place.You will see compelling evidence that: &#8211; Compassion has vast benefits for patients across a wide variety of conditions &#8211; Missed opportunities for compassion can have devastating health effects &#8211; Compassion can help reverse the cost crisis in health care &#8211; Compassion can be an antidote for burnout among health care providers &#8211; 40 seconds of compassion can save a life After seeing all the evidence, the answer is crystal clear: Compassion matters&#8230;in not only meaningful but measurable ways.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/compassionomics-the-revolutionary-scientific-evidence-that-caring-makes-a-difference-stephen-trzeciak-anthony-mazzarelli/">Compassionomics : The Revolutionary Scientific Evidence That Caring Makes a Difference &#8211; Stephen Trzeciak, Anthony Mazzarelli</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wuhan Diary : Dispatches from a Quarantined City &#8211; Fang Fang</title>
		<link>/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aid & Relief Programmes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Disasters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From one of China&#8217;s most acclaimed and decorated writers comes a powerful first-person account of life in Wuhan during the COVID-19 outbreak. On January 25, 2020, after the central government imposed a lockdown in Wuhan, acclaimed Chinese writer Fang Fang began publishing an online diary. In the days and weeks that followed, Fang Fang&#8217;s nightly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/">Wuhan Diary : Dispatches from a Quarantined City &#8211; Fang Fang</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From one of China&#8217;s most acclaimed and decorated writers comes a powerful first-person account of life in Wuhan during the COVID-19 outbreak.</p>
<p>                    On January 25, 2020, after the central government imposed a lockdown in Wuhan, acclaimed Chinese writer Fang Fang began publishing an online diary. In the days and weeks that followed, Fang Fang&#8217;s nightly postings gave voice to the fears, frustrations, anger, and hope of millions of her fellow citizens, reflecting on the psychological impact of forced isolation, the role of the internet as both community lifeline and source of misinformation, and most tragically, the lives of neighbors and friends taken by the deadly virus. </p>
<p>                    A fascinating eyewitness account of events as they unfold, Wuhan Diary captures the challenges of daily life and the changing moods and emotions of being quarantined without reliable information. Fang Fang finds solace in small domestic comforts and is inspired by the courage of friends, health professionals and volunteers, as well as the resilience and perseverance of Wuhan&#8217;s nine million residents. But, by claiming the writer´s duty to record she also speaks out against social injustice, abuse of power, and other problems which impeded the response to the epidemic and gets herself embroiled in online controversies because of it.</p>
<p>                    As Fang Fang documents the beginning of the global health crisis in real time, we are able to identify patterns and mistakes that many of the countries dealing with the novel coronavirus have later repeated. She reminds us that, in the face of the new virus, the plight of the citizens of Wuhan is also that of citizens everywhere. As Fang Fang writes: &#8220;The virus is the common enemy of humankind; that is a lesson for all humanity. The only way we can conquer this virus and free ourselves from its grip is for all members of humankind to work together.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    Blending the intimate and the epic, the profound and the quotidian, Wuhan Diary is a remarkable record of an extraordinary time. </p>
<p>                    Translated from the Chinese by Michael Berry</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/">Wuhan Diary : Dispatches from a Quarantined City &#8211; Fang Fang</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</title>
		<link>/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Giving Up Smoking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Respiratory Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Funding & Policy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19. Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19.    </p>
<p>                    Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns and border closings causing widespread business closures, economic collapse, and massive unemployment; and an unprecedented curtailment of civil liberties and freedoms in the name of keeping people safe by locking them up in their homes.    </p>
<p>                    We are now living in a world that is increasingly ruled, not by our democratic systems and institutions, but by public health fiat, carried out by politicians who rule by instilling fear and panic.    </p>
<p>                    In The Truth About COVID-19, Dr. Mercola and Cummins reveal new and emerging evidence that:    </p>
<p>                    The SARS-CoV-2 virus was, indeed, lab-engineered and emerged from a negligently managed bioweapons lab in Wuhan, China<br />
                    The global pandemic was long anticipated by global elites who have used it to facilitate and hide the largest upward transfer of wealth in human history<br />
                    PCR testing, case counts, morbidity, and vaccine safety and efficacy data have been widely manipulated and misrepresented<br />
                    Obesity, diabetes, and heart disease are known to worsen COVID-19 outcomes, but the junk food industry continues to push its agenda at the expense of public health<br />
                    Safe, simple, and inexpensive treatment and prevention for COVID-19 have been censored and suppressed to create a clear path for vaccine acceptance<br />
                    Effectiveness of the vaccines has been wildly exaggerated and major safety questions have gone unanswered    </p>
<p>                    The good news in all of this is that we can take control of our health and that, together, we have the power to unite and fight back for our health, democracy, and freedom. The time is now for a global awakening. As Dr. Mercola and Cummins remind us, this is the fight of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey from harmless microbe to world-changing pandemic, from its 1817 emergence in the South Asian hinterlands to its rapid dispersal across the nineteenth-century world and its latest beachhead in Haiti. She reports on the pathogens following in cholera&#8217;s footsteps, from the MRSA bacterium that besieges her own family to the never-before-seen killers emerging from China&#8217;s wet markets, the surgical wards of New Delhi, the slums of Port-au-Prince, and the suburban backyards of the East Coast. A deep-dive into the convoluted science, strange politics, and checkered history of one of the world&#8217;s deadliest diseases, Pandemic reveals what the next epidemic might look like&#8211;and what we can do to prevent it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Equipment & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nursing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Telemedicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy & Therapeutics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they indicate further (and more invasive) tests, most of which will probably prove unnecessary (much like physicals themselves). And your bill will be astronomical.In  The Patient Will See You Now , Eric Topol, one of the nation&#8217;s top physicians, shows why medicine does not have to be that way. Instead, you could use your smartphone to get rapid test results from one drop of blood, monitor your vital signs both day and night, and use an artificially intelligent algorithm to receive a diagnosis without having to see a doctor, all at a small fraction of the cost imposed by our modern healthcare system. The change is powered by what Topol calls medicine&#8217;s &#8220;Gutenberg moment.&#8221; Much as the printing press took learning out of the hands of a priestly class, the mobile internet is doing the same for medicine, giving us unprecedented control over our healthcare. With smartphones in hand, we are no longer beholden to an impersonal and paternalistic system in which &#8220;doctor knows best.&#8221; Medicine has been digitized, Topol argues now it will be democratized. Computers will replace physicians for many diagnostic tasks, citizen science will give rise to citizen medicine, and enormous data sets will give us new means to attack conditions that have long been incurable. Massive, open, online medicine, where diagnostics are done by Facebook-like comparisons of medical profiles, will enable real-time, real-world research on massive populations. There&#8217;s no doubt the path forward will be complicated: the medical establishment will resist these changes, and digitized medicine inevitably raises serious issues surrounding privacy. Nevertheless, the result,better, cheaper, and more human health care,will be worth it.Provocative and engrossing,  The Patient Will See You Now  is essential reading for anyone who thinks they deserve better health care. That is, for all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twas The Nightshift Before Christmas : Festive hospital diaries from the author of multi-million-copy hit This is Going to Hurt &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/twas-the-nightshift-before-christmas-festive-hospital-diaries-from-the-author-of-multi-million-copy-hit-this-is-going-to-hurt-adam-kay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diaries, Letters & Journals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/twas-the-nightshift-before-christmas-festive-hospital-diaries-from-the-author-of-multi-million-copy-hit-this-is-going-to-hurt-adam-kay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The number one Sunday Times bestseller &#8211; with a new, fantastically festive front cover! Twas the Nightshift Before Christmas is a short gift book of festive diaries from the author of multi-million-copy bestseller This is Going to Hurt. Christmas is coming, the goose is getting fat . . . but 1.4 million NHS staff are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/twas-the-nightshift-before-christmas-festive-hospital-diaries-from-the-author-of-multi-million-copy-hit-this-is-going-to-hurt-adam-kay-abridged/">Twas The Nightshift Before Christmas : Festive hospital diaries from the author of multi-million-copy hit This is Going to Hurt &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The number one Sunday Times bestseller &#8211; with a new, fantastically festive front cover! Twas the Nightshift Before Christmas is a short gift book of festive diaries from the author of multi-million-copy bestseller This is Going to Hurt.    </p>
<p>                    Christmas is coming, the goose is getting fat . . . but 1.4 million NHS staff are heading off to work. In this perfect present for anyone who has ever set foot in a hospital, Adam Kay delves back into his diaries for a hilarious, horrifying and sometimes heartbreaking peek behind the blue curtain at Christmastime.    </p>
<p>                    This is a love letter to all those who spend their festive season on the front line, removing babies and baubles from the various places they get stuck, at the most wonderful time of the year.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The perfect surgical stocking-filler&#8217; &#8211; The Times    </p>
<p>                    Two different covers of Twas the Nightshift Before Christmas have been printed: one has a special festive design, and the other is our original hardback design. You will either receive the festive design or the original (as shown here) in your order. Specific covers cannot be requested.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/twas-the-nightshift-before-christmas-festive-hospital-diaries-from-the-author-of-multi-million-copy-hit-this-is-going-to-hurt-adam-kay-abridged/">Twas The Nightshift Before Christmas : Festive hospital diaries from the author of multi-million-copy hit This is Going to Hurt &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pollution & Threats To The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When the U.S. Public Health Service endorsed water fluoridation in 1950, there was little evidence of its safety. Now, six decades later and after most countries have rejected the practice, more than 70 percent of Americans, as well as 200 million people worldwide, are drinking fluoridated water. The Center for Disease Control and the American [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/">The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When the U.S. Public Health Service endorsed water fluoridation in 1950, there was little evidence of its safety. Now, six decades later and after most countries have rejected the practice, more than 70 percent of Americans, as well as 200 million people worldwide, are drinking fluoridated water. The Center for Disease Control and the American Dental Association continue to promote it&#8211;and even mandatory statewide water fluoridation&#8211;despite increasing evidence that it is not only unnecessary, but potentially hazardous to human health.    </p>
<p>                    In this timely and important book, Dr. Paul Connett, Dr. James Beck, and Dr. H. Spedding Micklem take a new look at the science behind water fluoridation and argue that just because the dental and medical establishments endorse a public health measure doesn&#8217;t mean it&#8217;s safe. In the case of water fluoridation, the chemicals that go into the drinking water that more than 180 million people drink each day are not even pharmaceutical grade, but rather a hazardous waste product of the phosphate fertilizer industry. It is illegal to dump this waste into the sea or local surface water, and yet it is allowed in our drinking water. To make matters worse, this program receives no oversight from the Food and Drug Administration, and the Environmental Protection Agency takes no responsibility for the practice. And from an ethical standpoint, say the authors, water fluoridation is a bad medical practice: individuals are being forced to take medication without their informed consent, there is no control over the dose, and no monitoring of possible side effects.    </p>
<p>                    At once painstakingly documented and also highly readable, The Case Against Fluoride brings new research to light, including links between fluoride and harm to the brain, bones, and endocrine system, and argues that the evidence that fluoridation reduces tooth decay is surprisingly weak.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/">The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Going to Hurt : Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optometry / Opticians]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now A Major BBC Series Starring Ben Whishaw. The multi-million copy bestseller and Book of the Year at The National Book Awards. &#8216;Painfully funny. The pain and the funniness somehow add up to something entirely good, entirely noble and entirely loveable.&#8217; &#8211; Stephen Fry Welcome to the life of a junior doctor: 97-hour weeks, life [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/">This is Going to Hurt : Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now A Major BBC Series Starring Ben Whishaw.    </p>
<p>                    The multi-million copy bestseller and Book of the Year at The National Book Awards.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Painfully funny. The pain and the funniness somehow add up to something entirely good, entirely noble and entirely loveable.&#8217; &#8211; Stephen Fry    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the life of a junior doctor: 97-hour weeks, life and death decisions, a constant tsunami of bodily fluids, and the hospital parking meter earns more than you.    </p>
<p>                    Scribbled in secret after endless days, sleepless nights and missed weekends, Adam Kay&#8217;s This is Going to Hurt provides a no-holds-barred account of his time on the NHS front line. Hilarious, horrifying and heartbreaking, this diary is everything you wanted to know &#8211; and more than a few things you didn&#8217;t &#8211; about life on and off the hospital ward.    </p>
<p>                    Sunday Times Number One Bestseller for over eight months and winner of a record FOUR National Book Awards: Book of the Year, Non-Fiction Book of the Year, New Writer of the Year and Zoe Ball Book Club Book of the Year.    </p>
<p>                    This edition includes extra diary entries and an afterword by the author.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/">This is Going to Hurt : Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller from the author of How to Change Your Mind, The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, and Food Rules Food. There&#8217;s plenty of it around, and we all love to eat it. So why should anyone need to defend it? Because in the so-called Western diet, food has been replaced by nutrients, and common [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/">In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller from the author of How to Change Your Mind, The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, and Food Rules      </p>
<p>                     Food. There&#8217;s plenty of it around, and we all love to eat it. So why should anyone need to defend it?     </p>
<p>                     Because in the so-called Western diet, food has been replaced by nutrients, and common sense by confusion&#8211;most of what we&#8217;re consuming today is longer the product of nature but of food science. The result is what Michael Pollan calls the American Paradox: The more we worry about nutrition, the less healthy we see to become. With In Defense of Food, Pollan proposes a new (and very old) answer to the question of what we should eat that comes down to seven simple but liberating words: Eat food. Not too much. Mostly plants. Pollan&#8217;s bracing and eloquent manifesto shows us how we can start making thoughtful food choices that will enrich our lives, enlarge our sense of what it means to be healthy, and bring pleasure back to eating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/">In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insurance & Actuarial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicolegal Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017 &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene At a moment of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene      </p>
<p>                    At a moment of drastic political upheaval, An American Sickness is a shocking investigation into our dysfunctional healthcare system &#8211; and offers practical solutions to its myriad problems.    </p>
<p>                     In these troubled times, perhaps no institution has unraveled more quickly and more completely than American medicine. In only a few decades, the medical system has been overrun by organizations seeking to exploit for profit the trust that vulnerable and sick Americans place in their healthcare. Our politicians have proven themselves either unwilling or incapable of reining in the increasingly outrageous costs faced by patients, and market-based solutions only seem to funnel larger and larger sums of our money into the hands of corporations. Impossibly high insurance premiums and inexplicably large bills have become facts of life; fatalism has set in. Very quickly Americans have been made to accept paying more for less. How did things get so bad so fast?     </p>
<p>                     Breaking down this monolithic business into the individual industries-the hospitals, doctors, insurance companies, and drug manufacturers-that together constitute our healthcare system, Rosenthal exposes the recent evolution of American medicine as never before. How did healthcare, the caring endeavor, become healthcare, the highly profitable industry? Hospital systems, which are managed by business executives, behave like predatory lenders, hounding patients and seizing their homes. Research charities are in bed with big pharmaceutical companies, which surreptitiously profit from the donations made by working people. Patients receive bills in code, from entrepreneurial doctors they never even saw.     </p>
<p>                     The system is in tatters, but we can fight back. Dr. Elisabeth Rosenthal doesn&#8217;t just explain the symptoms, she diagnoses and treats the disease itself. In clear and practical terms, she spells out exactly how to decode medical doublespeak, avoid the pitfalls of the pharmaceuticals racket, and get the care you and your family deserve. She takes you inside the doctor-patient relationship and to hospital C-suites, explaining step-by-step the workings of a system badly lacking transparency. This is about what we can do, as individual patients, both to navigate the maze that is American healthcare and also to demand far-reaching reform. An American Sickness is the frontline defense against a healthcare system that no longer has our well-being at heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking prescription for health care reform&#8211;from a legendaryleader in innovation . . . Our health care system is in critical condition. Each year, fewer Americans can afford it, fewer businesses can provide it, and fewer government programs can promise it for future generations. We need a cure, and we need it now. Harvard Business [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking prescription for health care reform&#8211;from a legendaryleader in innovation . . .    </p>
<p>                    Our health care system is in critical condition. Each year, fewer Americans can afford it, fewer businesses can provide it, and fewer government programs can promise it for future generations.    </p>
<p>                    We need a cure, and we need it now.    </p>
<p>                    Harvard Business School&#8217;s Clayton M. Christensen-whose bestselling The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma revolutionized the business world-presents The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription, a comprehensive analysis of the strategies that will improvehealth care and make it affordable.    </p>
<p>                    Christensen applies the principles of disruptive innovation to the broken health care system with two pioneers in the field-Dr. Jerome Grossman and Dr. Jason Hwang. Together, they examine arange of symptoms and offer proven solutions.    </p>
<p>                    YOU&#8217;LL DISCOVER HOW    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Precision medicine&#8221; reduces costs and makes good on the promise of personalized careDisruptive business models improve quality, accessibility, and affordability by changing the way hospitals and doctors workPatient networks enable better treatment of chronic diseasesEmployers can change the roles they play in health care to compete effectively in the era of globalizationInsurance and regulatory reforms stimulate disruption in health care</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
