<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>People &amp; Places Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/people-places/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/people-places/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>People &amp; Places Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/people-places/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>City of Girls : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Elizabeth Gilbert</title>
		<link>/city-of-girls-the-sunday-times-bestseller-elizabeth-gilbert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/city-of-girls-the-sunday-times-bestseller-elizabeth-gilbert/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER &#8216;Stunning&#8217; Lisa Taddeo, author of THREE WOMEN &#8216;Warm and wise&#8217; Stephanie Merritt, Observer &#8216;Glamorous, sexy, compelling&#8217; Dolly Alderton, Sunday Times &#8216;I fell in love with Vivian from page one&#8217; Daisy Buchanan &#8216;An education in love, and an iridescent delight&#8217; Rowan Pelling, Spectator New York, 1940. Young, glamorous and inseparable, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/city-of-girls-the-sunday-times-bestseller-elizabeth-gilbert/">City of Girls : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Elizabeth Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Stunning&#8217; Lisa Taddeo, author of THREE WOMEN<br />
                    &#8216;Warm and wise&#8217; Stephanie Merritt, Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Glamorous, sexy, compelling&#8217; Dolly Alderton, Sunday Times<br />
                    &#8216;I fell in love with Vivian from page one&#8217; Daisy Buchanan<br />
                    &#8216;An education in love, and an iridescent delight&#8217; Rowan Pelling, Spectator</p>
<p>                    New York, 1940. Young, glamorous and inseparable, Vivian and Celia are chasing trouble from one end of the city to the other. But there is risk in all this play &#8211; that&#8217;s what makes it so fun, and so dangerous. Sometimes, the world may feel like it&#8217;s ending, but for Vivian and Celia, life is just beginning.</p>
<p>                    City of Girls is about daring to break conventions and follow your desires: a celebration of glamour, resilience, growing up, and the joys of female friendship &#8211; and about the freedom that comes from finding a place you truly belong.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/city-of-girls-the-sunday-times-bestseller-elizabeth-gilbert/">City of Girls : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Elizabeth Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boy : Tales of Childhood &#8211; Roald Dahl</title>
		<link>/boy-tales-of-childhood-roald-dahl/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jokes & Humour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nonfiction History Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boy-tales-of-childhood-roald-dahl/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Find out where the bestselling author of Charlie and the Chocolate Factory and The BFG got all his wonderful story ideas in this autobiographical account of his childhood! From his own life, of course! As full of excitement and the unexpected as his world-famous, best-selling books, Roald Dahl&#8217;s tales of his own childhood are completely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-tales-of-childhood-roald-dahl/">Boy : Tales of Childhood &#8211; Roald Dahl</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Find out where the bestselling author of Charlie and the Chocolate Factory and The BFG got all his wonderful story ideas in this autobiographical account of his childhood!      </p>
<p>                    From his own life, of course! As full of excitement and the unexpected as his world-famous, best-selling books, Roald Dahl&#8217;s tales of his own childhood are completely fascinating and fiendishly funny. Did you know that Roald Dahl nearly lost his nose in a car accident? Or that he was once a chocolate candy tester for Cadbury&#8217;s? Have you heard about his involvement in the Great Mouse Plot of 1924? If not, you don&#8217;t yet know all there is to know about Roald Dahl. Sure to captivate and delight you, the boyhood antics of this master storyteller are not to be missed!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-tales-of-childhood-roald-dahl/">Boy : Tales of Childhood &#8211; Roald Dahl</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Medio Rey &#8211; Joe Abercrombie</title>
		<link>/medio-rey-joe-abercrombie/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/medio-rey-joe-abercrombie/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jure vengarme de los asesinos de mi padre. Sere medio hombre, pero pronuncie un juramento entero. Yarvi, el hijo menor del rey, nacio con una malformacion en una mano que ha llevado a todo el mundo, incluso a su propio padre, a considerarlo medio hombre. Por eso, en lugar de formarse como guerrero, al igual [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/medio-rey-joe-abercrombie/">Medio Rey &#8211; Joe Abercrombie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jure vengarme de los asesinos de mi padre. Sere medio hombre, pero pronuncie un juramento entero. Yarvi, el hijo menor del rey, nacio con una malformacion en una mano que ha llevado a todo el mundo, incluso a su propio padre, a considerarlo medio hombre. Por eso, en lugar de formarse como guerrero, al igual que el re sto de varones de su estirpe, se ha dedicado a estudiar para convertirse en uno de los clerigos del reino. Sin embargo, en la vispera de la ultima prueba para ingresar en esta poderosa orden de sabios, a Yarvi le llega la noticia de que su padre y su hermano han sido asesinados. El es el nuevo rey. Pero tras una terrible traicion a manos de sus seres queridos, Yarvi se encontrara solo en un mundo regido por la fuerza fisica y los corazones frios. Incapaz de llevar armadura o de levantar un hacha, debera afilar y agudizar su mente. Cuando se juntan a su alrededor una extrana hermandad de almas perdidas, descubrira que esos companeros inesperados tal vez puedan ayudarle a convertirse en el hombre que quiere ser. ENGLISH DESCRIPTION &#8220;I swore an oath to be avenged on the killers of my father. I may be half a man, but I swore a whole oath&#8221; Prince Yarvi has vowed to regain a throne he never wanted. But first he must survive cruelty, chains and the bitter waters of the Shattered Sea itself. And he must do it all with only one good hand. The deceived will become the deceiver Born a weakling in the eyes of his father, Yarvi is alone in a world where a strong arm and a cold heart rule. He cannot grip a shield or swing an axe, so he must sharpen his mind to a deadly edge. The betrayed will become the betrayer Gathering a strange fellowship of the outcast and the lost, he finds they can do more to help him become the man he needs to be than any court of nobles could. Will the usurped become the usurper? But even with loyal friends at his side, Yarvi&#8217;s path may end as it began &#8211; in twists, and traps and tragedy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/medio-rey-joe-abercrombie/">Medio Rey &#8211; Joe Abercrombie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Lion King (Disney The Lion King) &#8211; Justine Korman</title>
		<link>/the-lion-king-disney-the-lion-king-justine-korman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Characters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's General Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-lion-king-disney-the-lion-king-justine-korman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The exciting tale of Simba, a young cub who earns his place in the Circle of Life, is retold in the classic Little Golden Book format. Children ages 2-5 will roar with excitement as they read this retelling of Disney&#8217;s The Lion King.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-lion-king-disney-the-lion-king-justine-korman/">The Lion King (Disney The Lion King) &#8211; Justine Korman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The exciting tale of Simba, a young cub who earns his place in the Circle of Life, is retold in the classic Little Golden Book format. Children ages 2-5 will roar with excitement as they read this retelling of Disney&#8217;s The Lion King.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-lion-king-disney-the-lion-king-justine-korman/">The Lion King (Disney The Lion King) &#8211; Justine Korman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book of Why : The New Science of Cause and Effect &#8211; Judea Pearl, Dana Mackenzie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Methodology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The hugely influential book on how the understanding of causality revolutionized science and the world, by the pioneer of artificial intelligence &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; illuminating and fun to read&#8217; Daniel Kahneman, Nobel Prize-winner and author of Thinking, Fast and Slow &#8216;Correlation does not imply causation.&#8217; For decades, this mantra was invoked by scientists in order to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/">The Book of Why : The New Science of Cause and Effect &#8211; Judea Pearl, Dana Mackenzie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The hugely influential book on how the understanding of causality revolutionized science and the world, by the pioneer of artificial intelligence    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; illuminating and fun to read&#8217; Daniel Kahneman, Nobel Prize-winner and author of Thinking, Fast and Slow    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Correlation  does not imply causation.&#8217; For decades, this mantra was invoked by scientists in order to avoid taking positions as to whether one thing  caused another, such as smoking and cancer, or carbon dioxide and global  warming. But today, that taboo is dead. The causal revolution, sparked  by world-renowned computer scientist Judea Pearl and his colleagues, has  cut through a century of confusion and placed cause and effect on a  firm scientific basis. Now, Pearl and science journalist Dana Mackenzie explain causal thinking to general readers for the first time, showing  how it allows us to explore the world that is and the worlds that could  have been. It is the essence of human and artificial intelligence. And  just as Pearl&#8217;s discoveries have enabled machines to think better, The  Book of Why explains how we too can think better.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Pearl&#8217;s accomplishments over the last 30 years have provided the theoretical basis for progress in artificial intelligence and have redefined the term &#8220;thinking machine&#8221;&#8216; Vint Cerf</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/">The Book of Why : The New Science of Cause and Effect &#8211; Judea Pearl, Dana Mackenzie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leadership in Turbulent Times : Lessons from the Presidents &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leadership-in-turbulent-times-lessons-from-the-presidents-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leadership-in-turbulent-times-lessons-from-the-presidents-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this culmination of five decades of acclaimed studies in presidential history, Doris Kearns Goodwin offers an illuminating exploration of the origin, uncertain growth, and finally, the exercise of fully developed leadership. Are leaders born or made? Where does ambition come from? How does adversity affect the growth of leadership? Does the man make the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-in-turbulent-times-lessons-from-the-presidents-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">Leadership in Turbulent Times : Lessons from the Presidents &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this culmination of five decades of acclaimed studies in presidential history, Doris Kearns Goodwin offers an illuminating exploration of the origin, uncertain growth, and finally, the exercise of fully developed leadership.    </p>
<p>                    Are leaders born or made? Where does ambition come from? How does adversity affect the growth of leadership? Does the man make the times or does the times make the man?    </p>
<p>                    In Leadership Goodwin draws upon four of the presidents she has studied &#8211; Abraham Lincoln, Theodore Roosevelt, Franklin D. Roosevelt and Lyndon B. Johnson &#8211; to show how they first recognized leadership qualities within themselves, and were recognized as leaders by others. By looking back to their first entry into public life, when their paths were filled with confusion, hope, and fear, we can share their struggles and follow their development into leaders.    </p>
<p>                    Leadership tells the story of how they all collided with dramatic reversals that disrupted their lives and threatened to forever shatter their ambitions. Nonetheless, they all emerged fitted to confront the contours and dilemmas of their times.     </p>
<p>                    No common pattern describes the trajectory of leadership. Although set apart in background, abilities and temperament, they shared a fierce ambition, a hunger to succeed beyond expectations. All four, at their best, were guided by a sense of moral purpose that led them at moments of great challenge to summon their talents to enlarge the opportunities and lives of others.    </p>
<p>                    This seminal work provides a roadmap for aspiring and established leaders. In today&#8217;s polarized world, these stories of authentic leadership in time of surpassing fracture and fear take on a singular urgency.    </p>
<p>                    (Previously published as: &#8216;Leadership: Lessons from the Presidents for Turbulent Times&#8217;)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-in-turbulent-times-lessons-from-the-presidents-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">Leadership in Turbulent Times : Lessons from the Presidents &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TED Talks : The official TED guide to public speaking: Tips and tricks for giving unforgettable speeches and presentations &#8211; Chris Anderson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ted-talks-the-official-ted-guide-to-public-speaking-tips-and-tricks-for-giving-unforgettable-speeches-and-presentations-chris-anderson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ted-talks-the-official-ted-guide-to-public-speaking-tips-and-tricks-for-giving-unforgettable-speeches-and-presentations-chris-anderson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is not just the most insightful book ever written on public speaking-it&#8217;s also a brilliant, profound look at how to communicate&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, author of ORIGINALS In Ted Talks Chris Anderson, Head of TED, reveals the inside secrets of how to give a first-class presentation. Where books like Talk Like TED and TED [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ted-talks-the-official-ted-guide-to-public-speaking-tips-and-tricks-for-giving-unforgettable-speeches-and-presentations-chris-anderson-abridged/">TED Talks : The official TED guide to public speaking: Tips and tricks for giving unforgettable speeches and presentations &#8211; Chris Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is not just the most insightful book  ever written on public speaking-it&#8217;s also a brilliant, profound look at  how to communicate&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, author of ORIGINALS    </p>
<p>                    In Ted Talks Chris Anderson, Head of TED, reveals the inside secrets of how to give a first-class presentation. Where books like Talk Like TED and TED Talks Storytelling whetted the appetite, here is the official TED guide to public speaking from the man who put TED talks on the world&#8217;s stage. &#8216;Nobody in the world better understands the art and science of public speaking than Chris Anderson. He is absolutely the best person to have written this book&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert.    </p>
<p>                    Anderson shares his five key techniques to presentation success: Connection, Narration, Explanation, Persuasion and Revelation (plus the three to avoid). He also answers the most frequently asked questions about giving a talk, from &#8216;What should I wear?&#8217; to &#8216;How do I handle my nerves?&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    Ted Talks is also full of presentation tips from such TED notable speakers as Sir Ken Robinson, Bill Gates, Mary Roach, Amy Cuddy, Elizabeth Gilbert, Dan Gilbert, Amanda Palmer, Matt Ridley and many more. This is a lively, fun read with great practical application from the man who knows what goes into a truly memorable speech. In Ted Talks Anderson pulls back the TED curtain for anyone who wants to learn how to prepare an exceptional presentation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ted-talks-the-official-ted-guide-to-public-speaking-tips-and-tricks-for-giving-unforgettable-speeches-and-presentations-chris-anderson-abridged/">TED Talks : The official TED guide to public speaking: Tips and tricks for giving unforgettable speeches and presentations &#8211; Chris Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rising Strong &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rising-strong-brene-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rising-strong-brene-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to Brene Brown I learned how to be vulnerable&#8230; a life changer&#8217; Miranda Hart The physics of vulnerability is simple: If we are brave enough often enough, we will fall. This is a book about what it takes to get back up and how owning our stories of disappointment, failure, and heartbreak gives us [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rising-strong-brene-brown-abridged/">Rising Strong &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thanks to Brene Brown I learned how to be vulnerable&#8230; a life changer&#8217; Miranda Hart    </p>
<p>                    The physics of vulnerability is simple: If we are brave enough often enough, we will fall. This is a book about what it takes to get back up and how owning our stories of disappointment, failure, and heartbreak gives us the power to write a daring new ending. Struggle can be our greatest call to courage and Rising Strong, our clearest path to deeper meaning, wisdom and hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rising-strong-brene-brown-abridged/">Rising Strong &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
