<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>TV Tie-in Humour Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/tv-tie-in-humour/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/tv-tie-in-humour/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>TV Tie-in Humour Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/tv-tie-in-humour/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</title>
		<link>/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Home Renovation & Extension]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV Tie-in Humour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE ENTERTAINING AND HEARTWARMING SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER. Like many couples, Dick and Angel had long dreamed of living in France, but where others might settle for a modest bolthole in the French countryside, the Strawbridges fell in love with a 19th-century fairytale chateau, complete with 45 rooms, seven outbuildings, 12 acres of land and its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/">A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE ENTERTAINING AND HEARTWARMING SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER.</p>
<p>                    Like many couples, Dick and Angel had long dreamed of living in France, but where others might settle for a modest bolthole in the French countryside, the Strawbridges fell in love with a 19th-century fairytale chateau, complete with 45 rooms, seven outbuildings, 12 acres of land and its own moat.</p>
<p>                    Throwing caution to the wind, Dick and Angel swapped their two-bedroom flat in East London for an abandoned and derelict castle in the heart of the Loire valley and embarked on the adventure of a lifetime with their two young children Arthur and Dorothy.</p>
<p>                    Sharing their full journey for the first time, A Year at the Chateau follows Dick and Angel from when they first moved to France in the depths of winter and found bedrooms infested with flies, turrets inhabited by bats, the wind rattling through cracked windows, and just one working toilet, which flushed into the moat, through to the monumental efforts that went into readying the chateau for their unforgettable wedding and their incredibly special first Christmas.</p>
<p>                    Along the way we&#8217;ll read glorious descriptions of rural life in France, with charming characters, delicious food and wonderful seasonal produce, together with the extraordinary list of renovations and restorations Dick and Angel completed, many of which were never shown on TV.</p>
<p>                    As warm and entertaining as their much-loved show, A Year at the Chateau is a truly irresistible story of adventure and heart, epic ambitions and a huge amount of hard graft.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/">A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing &#8211; Bob Mortimer</title>
		<link>/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Angling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fishing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV Tie-in Humour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller Two comedy greats talk life, friendship and the joys of fishing&#8230; Bob Mortimer and Paul Whitehouse have been friends for 30 years, but when life intervened, what was once a joyous and spontaneous friendship dwindled to the odd phone call or occasional catch up. Then, Glory Be! They were both diagnosed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/">Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing &#8211; Bob Mortimer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller</p>
<p>                    Two comedy greats talk life, friendship and the joys of fishing&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Bob Mortimer and Paul Whitehouse have been friends for 30 years, but when life intervened, what was once a joyous and spontaneous friendship dwindled to the odd phone call or occasional catch up. Then, Glory Be! They were both diagnosed with heart disease and realised that time is short. They&#8217;d better spend it fishing&#8230;</p>
<p>                    So they dusted off their kits, chucked on their waders and ventured into the achingly beautiful British countryside to fish, rediscover the joys of their friendship and ruminate on some of life&#8217;s most profound questions, such as: How did we get so old? Where are all the fish? What are your favourite pocket meats? What should we do if we find a corpse?   </p>
<p>                    Following the success of the BBC&#8217;s Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing series, this wonderful book by two lifelong friends is a love letter to the joys of angling, the thrill of the catch and the virtue of having a right daft laff with your mates. On the fish, the equipment, the food, and the locations, Gone Fishing is the perfect book for fans of Bob Mortimer, Paul Whitehouse and for anyone who wants to read a brilliantly written and endlessly funny joint memoir on life, friendship and joys of fishing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/">Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing &#8211; Bob Mortimer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Still Just a Geek &#8211; Wil Wheaton</title>
		<link>/still-just-a-geek-wil-wheaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Acting Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diaries, Letters & Journals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV Tie-in Humour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/still-just-a-geek-wil-wheaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Celebrated actor, personality, and all-around nerd Wil Wheaton updates his memoir of collected blog posts with all new material and annotations as he reexamines one of the most interesting lives in Hollywood and fandom! Wil Wheaton grew up. Ideally, this is what everyone does. But most of us don&#8217;t do it in front of millions [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/still-just-a-geek-wil-wheaton/">Still Just a Geek &#8211; Wil Wheaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celebrated actor, personality, and all-around nerd Wil Wheaton updates his memoir of collected blog posts with all new material and annotations as he reexamines one of the most interesting lives in Hollywood and fandom!<br />
                              Wil Wheaton grew up.    </p>
<p>                              Ideally, this is what everyone does. But most of us don&#8217;t do it in front of millions of people. Wil was a very famous kid &#8211; right up until he wasn&#8217;t. After that, he wasn&#8217;t sure who he was at all.    </p>
<p>                              So, in 2001, he started a blog. It was less about being a famous child than about being a not-so-famous grownup. He wrote about his pets and his hobbies, punk rock and parenting, board games and birthdays and (most importantly) burritos.    </p>
<p>                              He thought he was writing for an audience of one: himself. To be fair, he was only off by about 3 million people. In Still Just a Geek, an older, somewhat wiser Wil revisits Just a Geek, his 2004 collection of posts from that blog, with all-new reflections on nerd culture, fame, love, trauma, tragedy, and confronting the worst parts of yourself.    </p>
<p>                                Equal parts funny and poignant, Still Just a Geek explores the folly of youth and the pain of experience &#8211; and all the strange, awful, beautiful adventures in between.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/still-just-a-geek-wil-wheaton/">Still Just a Geek &#8211; Wil Wheaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
