<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Distributive Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/distributive-industries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/distributive-industries/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Distributive Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/distributive-industries/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review</p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.</p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.</p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.</p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rule of Logistics : Walmart and the Architecture of Fulfillment &#8211; Jesse LeCavalier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rule-of-logistics-walmart-and-the-architecture-of-fulfillment-jesse-lecavalier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Building Construction & Materials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Buildings: Civic, Commercial, Industrial, Etc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rule-of-logistics-walmart-and-the-architecture-of-fulfillment-jesse-lecavalier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every time you wheel a shopping cart through one of Walmart&#8217;s more than 10,000 stores worldwide, or swipe your credit card or purchase something online, you enter a mind-boggling logistical regime. Even if you&#8217;ve never shopped at Walmart, its logistics have probably affected your life. The Rule of Logistics makes sense of its spatial and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rule-of-logistics-walmart-and-the-architecture-of-fulfillment-jesse-lecavalier-abridged/">The Rule of Logistics : Walmart and the Architecture of Fulfillment &#8211; Jesse LeCavalier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every time you wheel a shopping cart through one of Walmart&#8217;s more than 10,000 stores worldwide, or swipe your credit card or purchase something online, you enter a mind-boggling logistical regime. Even if you&#8217;ve never shopped at Walmart, its logistics have probably affected your life. The Rule of Logistics makes sense of its spatial and architectural ramifications by analyzing the stores, distribution centers, databases, and inventory practices of the world&#8217;s largest corporation.    </p>
<p>                    The Rule of Logistics tells the story of Walmart&#8217;s buildings in the context of the corporation&#8217;s entire operation, itself characterized by an obsession with logistics. Beginning with the company&#8217;s founding in 1962, Jesse LeCavalier reveals how logistics-as a branch of knowledge, an area of work, and a collection of processes-takes shape and changes our built environment. Weaving together archival material with original drawings, LeCavalier shows how a diverse array of ideas, people, and things-military theory and chewing gum, Howard Dean and satellite networks, Hudson River School painters and real estate software, to name a few-are all connected through Walmart&#8217;s logistical operations and in turn are transforming how its buildings are conceptualized, located, built, and inhabited.    </p>
<p>                    A major new contribution to architectural history and theory, The Rule of Logistics helps us understand how retailing today is changing our bodies, brains, buildings, and cities and predicts what future forms architecture might take when shaped by systems that exceed its current capacities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rule-of-logistics-walmart-and-the-architecture-of-fulfillment-jesse-lecavalier-abridged/">The Rule of Logistics : Walmart and the Architecture of Fulfillment &#8211; Jesse LeCavalier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to convert website visitors into customers Part science and part art, conversion optimization is designed to turn visitors into customers. Carefully developed testing procedures are necessary to help you fine-tune images, headlines, navigation, colors, buttons, and every other element, creating a website that encourages visitors to take the action you seek. This book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/">You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to convert website visitors into customers Part science and part art, conversion optimization is designed to turn visitors into customers. Carefully developed testing procedures are necessary to help you fine-tune images, headlines, navigation, colors, buttons, and every other element, creating a website that encourages visitors to take the action you seek. This book guides you through creating an optimization strategy that supports your business goals, using appropriate analytics tools, generating quality testing ideas, running online experiments, and making the adjustments that work.<br />
                    * Conversion optimization is part science and part art; this guide provides step-by-step guidance to help you optimize your website for maximum conversion rates * Explains how to analyze data, prioritize experiment opportunities, and choose the right testing methods * Helps you learn what to adjust, how to do it, and how to analyze the results * Features hands-on exercises, case studies, and a full-color insert reinforcing key tactics * Author has used these techniques to assist Fortune 500 clients You Should Test That explains both the &#8220;why&#8221; and the &#8220;how&#8221; of conversion optimization, helping you maximize the value of your website.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/">You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Walton : Made In America &#8211; Sam Walton, Contributions by John Huey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meet a genuine American folk hero cut from the homespun cloth of America&#8217;s heartland: Sam Walton, who parlayed a single dime store in a hardscrabble cotton town into Wal-Mart, the largest retailer in the world. The undisputed merchant king of the late twentieth century, Sam never lost the common touch. Here, finally, inimitable words. Genuinely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/">Sam Walton : Made In America &#8211; Sam Walton, Contributions by John Huey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meet a genuine American folk hero cut from the homespun cloth of America&#8217;s heartland: Sam Walton, who parlayed a single dime store in a hardscrabble cotton town into Wal-Mart, the largest retailer in the world. The undisputed merchant king of the late twentieth century, Sam never lost the common touch. Here, finally, inimitable words. Genuinely modest, but always sure if his ambitions and achievements. Sam shares his thinking in a candid, straight-from-the-shoulder style.     </p>
<p>                    In a story rich with anecdotes and the &#8220;rules of the road&#8221; of both Main Street and Wall Street, Sam Walton chronicles the inspiration, heart, and optimism that propelled him to lasso the American Dream.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/">Sam Walton : Made In America &#8211; Sam Walton, Contributions by John Huey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212; Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International    </p>
<p>                      &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! There, I learned the fundamentals of guest service that consistently gave Disney a tremendous advantage in the marketplace. Now, anyone can know these secrets of success thanks to Doug Lipp&#8217;s informative book. No matter what your business, the lessons taught at DisneyUniversity will prove invaluable.&#8221; &#8212; Michael Eisner, Former CEO and Chairman, The Walt Disney Company    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to world-class employees, few organizations rival Disney. Famous for their friendliness, knowledge, passion, and superior customer service, Disney&#8217;s employees have been fueling the iconic brand&#8217;s wild success for more than 50 years.    </p>
<p>                    How has Disney succeeded in maintaining such a powerful workforce for so many years? Why are so many corporations and executives drawn to study how Disney continues to exemplify service and leadership standards?    </p>
<p>                    The Disney University, founded by Van France, trains the supporting cast that helps create the world-famous Disney Magic. Now, for the first time, the secrets of this exemplary institution are revealed. In Disney U, Doug Lipp examines how Van perpetuated Walt Disney&#8217;s timeless company values and leadership lessons, creating a training and development dynasty. It contains never-before-told stories from numerous Disney legends. These pioneers share behind-the-scenes success stories of how they helped bring Walt Disney&#8217;s dream to life.    </p>
<p>                    Disney U reveals the heart of the Disney culture and describes the company&#8217;s values and operational philosophies that support the iconic brand. Doug Lipp lays out 13 timeless lessons Disney has used to drive profits and growth worldwide for more than half a century.    </p>
<p>                    To this day, the Disney University continues to turn out some of the most engaged, loyal, and customer-centered employees the business world has ever seen. Using the lessons outlined in Disney U will set your organization on a path of sustained success.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR Disney U:    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I highly recommend Disney U to anyone interested in building an enduring market presence and brand.&#8221; &#8212; Stephen Cannon, President and Chief Executive Officer, Mercedes-Benz USA    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lipp&#8217;s narratives reveal how Van and other Disney visionaries set the stage for a world-class organization by skillfully balancing both &#8216;people&#8217; and &#8216;technology.'&#8221; &#8212; Debi Aubee, Vice President of Sales, Bose Corporation    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every leader should have the equivalent of a Van France at his or her side. Thanks to Doug Lipp, we can now tap into the brilliance of a man who helped Walt createThe Happiest Place on Earth.&#8221; &#8212; David Overton, Founder and Chief Executive Officer, The Cheesecake Factory    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;How does Disney University create such enthusiastic, loyal, and customer-centered employees, year after year? Now, for the first time, Doug Lipp takes us on a journey backstage to answer this pivotal question.&#8221; &#8212; John G. Veres III, Ph.D., Chancellor, Auburn University at Montgomery    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Doug Lipp shares terrific stories about Disney that underscore the importance of creating an organizational culture with an unwavering dedication to superlativeservice and exceptional quality, both for employees and customers. He then takes it a step further by explaining how to bring these values to life for your organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Christine A. Morena, Executive Vice President of Human Resources, Saks Incorporated</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selling The Invisible : A Field Guide to Modern Marketing &#8211; Harry Beckwith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SELLING THE INVISIBLE is a succinct and often entertaining look at the unique characteristics of services and their prospects, and how any service, from a home-based consultancy to a multinational brokerage, can turn more prospects into clients and keep them. SELLING THE INVISIBLE covers service marketing from start to finish. Filled with wonderful insights and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/">Selling The Invisible : A Field Guide to Modern Marketing &#8211; Harry Beckwith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SELLING THE INVISIBLE is a succinct and often entertaining look at the unique characteristics of services and their prospects, and how any service, from a home-based consultancy to a multinational brokerage, can turn more prospects into clients and keep them. SELLING THE INVISIBLE covers service marketing from start to finish. Filled with wonderful insights and written in a roll-up-your-sleeves, jargon-free, accessible style, such as:    </p>
<p>                    Greatness May Get You Nowhere; Focus Groups Don&#8217;ts; The More You Say, the Less People Hear; Seeing the Forest Around the Falling Trees</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/">Selling The Invisible : A Field Guide to Modern Marketing &#8211; Harry Beckwith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investing with Impact: Why Finance Is a Force for Good outlines the roadmap to reinvigorating a skeptical public and demoralized financial services industry by making the case that, contrary to popular misconception, finance is not the cause of the world&#8217;s problems; in fact, it can provide the solution. Author Jeremy Balkin presents the case that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/">Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investing with Impact: Why Finance Is a Force for Good outlines the roadmap to reinvigorating a skeptical public and demoralized financial services industry by making the case that, contrary to popular misconception, finance is not the cause of the world&#8217;s problems; in fact, it can provide the solution. Author Jeremy Balkin presents the case that the finance industry can improve the state of the world by positively influencing the allocation of capital.  Investing With Impact explains the methodology of Balkin&#8217;s 6 E Paradigm, opening the toolbox to this revolutionary framework for the first time. In so doing, Balkin expands the impact investment universe, enabling mainstream capital to flow where opportunities generate positive investment returns and have demonstrable social impact.  Described by the Huffington Post as the &#8220;Anti-Wolf of Wall Street,&#8221; Balkin is challenging the status quo on Wall Street by leading the intellectual debate embracing the $1 trillion frontier impact investment market opportunity. The book demonstrates conclusively that, if we can change the culture in finance, we can change the world for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/">Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019    </p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review    </p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.    </p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.    </p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walmart : Key Insights and Practical Lessons from the World&#8217;s Largest Retailer &#8211; Bryan Roberts, Natalie Berg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multinationals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Purchasing & Supply Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Walmart provides a detailed assessment of the world&#8217;s largest retailer that forever changed the face of retailing. The book examines Walmart&#8217;s successes, failures, and whether it can stay ahead for the next 50 years. Despite being a source for best practice in procurement, logistics, systems and store format innovation, the retail giant is now facing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/">Walmart : Key Insights and Practical Lessons from the World&#8217;s Largest Retailer &#8211; Bryan Roberts, Natalie Berg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Walmart provides a detailed assessment of the world&#8217;s largest retailer that forever changed the face of retailing. The book examines Walmart&#8217;s successes, failures, and whether it can stay ahead for the next 50 years. Despite being a source for best practice in procurement, logistics, systems and store format innovation, the retail giant is now facing several issues that affect its future development. Starting from its inception in rural Arkansas in 1962, this objective analysis of Walmart&#8217;s history addresses the rapid change of retail, including the rise of e-commerce and multi-channel retailing; Walmart International and its &#8216;everyday low prices&#8217; philosophy; the saturation of the superstore format, and much more.     </p>
<p>                    In a time of rapid change, will the world&#8217;s largest retailer be able to reconfigure? Walmart provides the necessary insights for retailers, advertisers, other business professionals and students to understand how Walmart became a retail giant, the lessons that can be learned, and what is in store for the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/">Walmart : Key Insights and Practical Lessons from the World&#8217;s Largest Retailer &#8211; Bryan Roberts, Natalie Berg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Be Our Guest (10th Anniversary Updated Edition) : Perfecting the Art of Customer Service &#8211; Ted Kinni, Edited by Wendy Lefkon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exceeding expectations rather than simply satisfying them is the cornerstone of the Disney approach to customer service. Disney Institute specializes in helping professionals see new possibilities through concepts not found in the typical workplace, is revealing even more of the business behind the magic of quality service. During the last twenty-five years, thousands of professionals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/">Be Our Guest (10th Anniversary Updated Edition) : Perfecting the Art of Customer Service &#8211; Ted Kinni, Edited by Wendy Lefkon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exceeding expectations rather than simply satisfying them is the cornerstone of the Disney approach to customer service.<br />
                    Disney Institute specializes in helping professionals see new possibilities through concepts not found in the typical workplace, is revealing even more of the business behind the magic of quality service. During the last twenty-five years, thousands of professionals from more than thirty-five countries and more than forty industries have attended business programs at Disney Institute and learned how to adapt the Disney approach for their own organizations.Be Our Guest highlights the successes many of these companies have achieved, plus the key processes and best practices that have made Disney a trusted and revered brand around the world for more than eighty-five years.<br />
                    Want more insight on The Walt Disney Company, its founder, and its driving creative forces? Explore these behind-the-scenes stories from Disney Editions: Travels with Figment: On the Road in Search of Disney Dreams (By Disney Legend Marty Sklar)<br />
                    One Little Spark! Mickey&#8217;s Ten Commandments and The Road to Imagineering (By Disney Legend Marty Sklar)<br />
                    Magic Journey: My Fantastical Walt Disney Imagineering Career (By Kevin Rafferty)<br />
                    Travels with Walt Disney: A Photographic Voyage Around the World (By Jeff Kurtti)<br />
                    Eat Like Walt: The Wonderful World of Disney Food (By Marcy Carriker Smothers)<br />
                    Walt Disney: An American Original (By Bob Thomas)<br />
                    Disney A to Z: The Official Encyclopedia, Fifth Edition (By Disney Legend Dave Smith)<br />
                    Disney Facts Revealed: Answers to Fans&#8217; Curious Questions (By Disney Legend Dave Smith)<br />
                    Disney Trivia from the Vault: Secrets Revealed and Questions Answered (By Disney Legend Dave Smith)<br />
                    My Pride: Mastering Life&#8217;s Daily Performance from Broadway&#8217;s Record-Breaking Lion King (By Alton Fitzgerald White)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/">Be Our Guest (10th Anniversary Updated Edition) : Perfecting the Art of Customer Service &#8211; Ted Kinni, Edited by Wendy Lefkon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Fed the World &#8211; Leon Hesser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agronomy & Crop Production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Novels: Literary & Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Norman Borlaug was the only person during the twentieth century who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize for work in agriculture and food. There is no Nobel Food Prize, so the Nobel Committee chose Dr. Borlaug as the 1970 recipient of the Peace Prize based on his dramatic scientific breakthroughs and wheat production technology that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/">The Man Who Fed the World &#8211; Leon Hesser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Norman Borlaug was the only person during the twentieth century who was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize for work in agriculture and food. There is no Nobel Food Prize, so the Nobel Committee chose Dr. Borlaug as the 1970 recipient of the Peace Prize based on his dramatic scientific breakthroughs and wheat production technology that relieved hunger in much of the world. During the previous decade, many people on the planet Earth, most notably in China and the Asian Subcontinent, were facing starvation, even famine. Borlaug&#8217;s revolutionary achievements relieved widespread human suffering and brought peace.    </p>
<p>                    Dr. Borlaug was hailed as the person who saved the lives of more people&#8211;hundreds of millions&#8211;from starvation than any person in history. He earned the distinction as one of the 100 most influential individuals of the 20th century. His is an inspiring story; he went from an unpretentious Iowa farm boy to scientist-cum-humanist of world acclaim.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-fed-the-world-leon-hesser-abridged/">The Man Who Fed the World &#8211; Leon Hesser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217; Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene amounts of money &#8212; as well as how to dress, talk, date, drink, and schmooze like real financiers. Young Money is the exclusive, inside story of this well-guarded world.<br />
                    Investigative reporter Kevin Roose shadows eight rookies as they are exposed to the exhausting workloads, huge bonuses, and recreational drugs that have always characterized Wall Street life. But they experience something new, too: an industry forever changed by the massive financial collapse of 2008. And as they get their Wall Street educations, they face hard questions about morality, prestige, and the value of their work.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A great new read that doubles as a post-crash update to Michael Lewis&#8217; Liar&#8217;s Poker &#8211; Mother Jones    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fun fast read that will make you laugh out loud&#8217; Fortune Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related to the way managers treat employees.    </p>
<p>                    Kelsey Young is an optimistic but disillusioned sales associate working her way through college. Her world opens up when one of her professors challenges her to create a culture of service at her workplace by putting the five components of Legendary Service into practice. AlthoughFerguson&#8217;s, the store where Kelsey works, certainly isn&#8217;t known for service excellence, Kelsey believes she can make a positive difference. She quickly learns that culture change isn&#8217;t easy&#8211;and that her role as a frontline employee is more significant than she ever could have imagined.    </p>
<p>                    In characteristic Blanchard style, Legendary Service: The Key Is to Care is a quick and entertainingread for people at all organizational levels in every industry. When applied, its lessons will have a profound impact on the service experience your customers will receive. Whether a CEO or a part-time employee, every person can make a difference&#8211;and customer service iseveryone&#8217;s job.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR LEGENDARY SERVICE:&#8221;Read this book and establish a service culture in your organization.&#8221; &#8212; Horst Schulze, Chairman/CEO, Capella Hotel Group    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Legendary Service has great learnings for people at all organizational levels: for executives and managers, the value of a service culture; and for frontlinestaff, the reality that they are the face of the company and can make a difference. Legendary service&#8211;it&#8217;s everyone, always.&#8221; &#8212; Mark King, CEO and President, TaylorMade Golf    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Everything I know about service I learned from my career at Hilton Hotels, Marriott International, The Walt Disney Company, and Ken Blanchard. The One Minute Manager dramatically changed my thinking 32 years ago. LegendaryService will teach the next generation how to deliver sensational service. Buy it, study it, implement it.&#8221; &#8212; Lee Cockerell, Executive Vice President, Walt Disney World (Retired &#038; Inspired), and author of Creating Magic and The Customer Rules    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Kathy Cuff and Vicki Halsey have created a fantastic customer service model called ICARE. When you add their voices to that of the master storyteller KenBlanchard, you have a masterpiece entitled Legendary Service. It is a must-read for everyone who, like me, has a passion for service.&#8221; &#8212; Colleen Barrett, President Emeritus, Southwest Airlines, and coauthor of Lead with LUV    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken Blanchard has done it again and delivered the right book at the right time. Legendary Service provides the essentials of hospitality and servant leadership in a way that everyone can adopt&#8211;right now&#8211;today!&#8221; &#8212; John Caparella, President and COO,The Venetian, The Palazzo, and Sands Expo    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken, Kathy, and Vicki show us how to change everyday service events into memorable experiences. Their book is a must-read for anyone unwilling to acceptmediocrity.&#8221; &#8212; Leonardo Inghilleri, coauthor ofExceptional Service, Exceptional Profit</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Airbnb Story : How Three Guys Disrupted an Industry, Made Billions of Dollars &#8230; and Plenty of Enemies &#8211; Leigh Gallagher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-airbnb-story-how-three-guys-disrupted-an-industry-made-billions-of-dollars-and-plenty-of-enemies-leigh-gallagher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hospitality Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-airbnb-story-how-three-guys-disrupted-an-industry-made-billions-of-dollars-and-plenty-of-enemies-leigh-gallagher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing story of audacious entrepreneurism&#8217; &#8212; Charles Duhigg &#8216;Captures the remarkable journey of Airbnb exceedingly well&#8217; &#8212; Reid Hoffman &#8216;fast paced, fun dive into one of the seminal firms of our time&#8217; &#8212; Rana Foroohar In 2008, two broke art school graduates and their coder-whiz friend set up a platform that &#8211; in less [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-airbnb-story-how-three-guys-disrupted-an-industry-made-billions-of-dollars-and-plenty-of-enemies-leigh-gallagher-abridged/">The Airbnb Story : How Three Guys Disrupted an Industry, Made Billions of Dollars &#8230; and Plenty of Enemies &#8211; Leigh Gallagher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing story of audacious entrepreneurism&#8217; &#8212; Charles Duhigg    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captures the remarkable journey of Airbnb exceedingly well&#8217; &#8212; Reid Hoffman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;fast paced, fun dive into one of the seminal firms of our time&#8217; &#8212; Rana Foroohar     </p>
<p>                    In 2008, two broke art school graduates and their coder-whiz friend set up a platform that &#8211; in less than a decade &#8211; became one of the largest provider of accommodations in the world.  Now valued at $31 billion, Airbnb is in the very top tier of Silicon Valley&#8217;s &#8216;unicorn&#8217; startups.    </p>
<p>                    Yet the company has not been without controversy &#8211; disrupting a $500 billion hotel industry makes you a few enemies.  This is also a story of regulators who want to shut it down, hotel industry leaders who want it to disappear and neighbourhoods that struggle with private homes open for public rental.  But beyond the headlines and the horror stories, Airbnb has changed the terms of travel for a whole generation &#8211; where a sense of belonging has built trust between hosts and guests seeking a more original travel experience that hotels have struggled to replicate.    </p>
<p>                    This is the first, definitive book to tell the remarkable story behind Airbnb in all its forms &#8211; cultural zeitgeist, hotel disruptor, enemy to regulators &#8211; and the first in-depth character study of its leader Brian Chesky, the company&#8217;s curious co-founder and CEO.  It reveals what got Airbnb where it is today, why they are nothing like Uber, and where they are going next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-airbnb-story-how-three-guys-disrupted-an-industry-made-billions-of-dollars-and-plenty-of-enemies-leigh-gallagher-abridged/">The Airbnb Story : How Three Guys Disrupted an Industry, Made Billions of Dollars &#8230; and Plenty of Enemies &#8211; Leigh Gallagher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon : How the World&#8217;s Most Relentless Retailer will Continue to Revolutionize Commerce &#8211; Natalie Berg, Miya Knights (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is the secret to Amazon&#8217;s success? What does the ecommerce giant have in store for the future? Explore the disruptive new retail strategies of the world&#8217;s most relentless retailer and gain valuable lessons that can be applied to any business in the ecommerce sector, with original insight from the company as it continues to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/">Amazon : How the World&#8217;s Most Relentless Retailer will Continue to Revolutionize Commerce &#8211; Natalie Berg, Miya Knights (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is the secret to Amazon&#8217;s success? What does the ecommerce giant have in store for the future? Explore the disruptive new retail strategies of the world&#8217;s most relentless retailer and gain valuable lessons that can be applied to any business in the ecommerce sector, with original insight from the company as it continues to revolutionize itself even further.    </p>
<p>                    The retail industry is facing unprecedented challenges. Across all sectors and markets, retailers are shifting their business models and customer engagement strategies to ensure they survive. The rise of online shopping, and its primary player, Amazon, is at the heart of these changes and opportunities.    </p>
<p>                    Amazon&#8217;s relentless dissatisfaction with the status quo is what makes it such an extraordinary retailer. This book explores whether Amazon has what it takes to become a credible grocery retailer, and as it transitions to bricks and mortar retailing, investigates whether Amazon&#8217;s stores can be as compelling as its online offering.    </p>
<p>                    Exploring the ecommerce giant&#8217;s strategies, Amazon offers unique insight into how innovations such voice technology, checkout-free stores and its Prime ecosystem, will fundamentally change the way consumers shop.    </p>
<p>                    Written by industry leading retail analysts who have spent decades providing research-based analysis and opinion on retail strategy and enterprise technology use in retail, Amazon analyzes the impact these initiatives will have on the wider retail sector and the lessons that can be learned from its unprecedented rise to dominance &#8211; as stores of the future become less about transactions and more about experiences.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/">Amazon : How the World&#8217;s Most Relentless Retailer will Continue to Revolutionize Commerce &#8211; Natalie Berg, Miya Knights (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
