<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Diets &amp; Dieting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/diets-dieting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/diets-dieting/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 09:12:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Diets &amp; Dieting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/diets-dieting/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fat for Fuel : A Revolutionary Diet to Combat Cancer, Boost Brain Power, and Increase Your Energy &#8211; Joseph Mercola</title>
		<link>/fat-for-fuel-a-revolutionary-diet-to-combat-cancer-boost-brain-power-and-increase-your-energy-joseph-mercola/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 03:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fat-for-fuel-a-revolutionary-diet-to-combat-cancer-boost-brain-power-and-increase-your-energy-joseph-mercola/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For over a century, we&#8217;ve accepted the scientific consensus that cancer results from genetic disease due to chromosomal damage in cell nuclei. But what if cancer isn&#8217;t a genetic disease after all? What if scientists are chasing a flawed paradigm, and cancer isn&#8217;t a disease of damaged DNA but rather of defective metabolism as a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fat-for-fuel-a-revolutionary-diet-to-combat-cancer-boost-brain-power-and-increase-your-energy-joseph-mercola/">Fat for Fuel : A Revolutionary Diet to Combat Cancer, Boost Brain Power, and Increase Your Energy &#8211; Joseph Mercola</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For over a century, we&#8217;ve accepted the scientific consensus that cancer results from genetic disease due to chromosomal damage in cell nuclei. But what if cancer isn&#8217;t a genetic disease after all? What if scientists are chasing a flawed paradigm, and cancer isn&#8217;t a disease of damaged DNA but rather of defective metabolism as a result of mitochondrial dysfunction? What if that startling truth could revolutionize our understanding of other diseases as well&#8211;and show us a radical new path to optimal health? In this ground-breaking guide, the first of its kind, New York Times best-selling author and leading natural-health practitioner Joseph Mercola explains how nearly all disease is caused by defective metabolic processes. Then he reveals what&#8217;s really causing your metabolism to go haywire: damage and dysfunction in the mitochondria, thousands of which are at work in nearly every cell in your body, generating 90 percent of the energy you need to stay alive and well. When mitochondria become damaged in large numbers, it is impossible to stay healthy. Dr.<br />
                    Mercola shows you that you can to take control of your health simply by giving your body the proper fuel&#8211;and it&#8217;s not what you&#8217;ve likely been led to believe. A ketogenic diet, very low in carbohydrates and high in healthy fats, is the way to optimize the biochemical pathways that suppress disease and support healing. And the benefits can be astonishing&#8211;not only in treating or preventing serious illness, but in boosting your brainpower, increasing your energy, helping you lose weight and keep it off, and much more. As you read this book, you&#8217;ll learn in clear, rational terms how your body works at a molecular level. You&#8217;ll finally understand the type of fuel it&#8217;s designed to burn in the most efficient way possible. You&#8217;ll find detailed guidelines for starting and sticking with a ketogenic eating plan. And you won&#8217;t have to wait a decade or two for metabolic mitochondrial therapy to make its way into the mainstream. You can build a healthier body and brain at the cutting edge of this exciting new discipline, starting right now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fat-for-fuel-a-revolutionary-diet-to-combat-cancer-boost-brain-power-and-increase-your-energy-joseph-mercola/">Fat for Fuel : A Revolutionary Diet to Combat Cancer, Boost Brain Power, and Increase Your Energy &#8211; Joseph Mercola</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</title>
		<link>/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Break the rules, not the fast with world-renowned biohacker and New York Times bestselling author Dave Asprey. For more than a decade, the Bulletproof founder Dave Asprey has shared his unique point of view and expertise to help fans become the best versions of themselves. From living longer to getting smarter, maximising performance to practising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/">Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Break the rules, not the fast with world-renowned biohacker and New York Times bestselling author Dave Asprey.</p>
<p>                              For more than a decade, the Bulletproof founder Dave Asprey has shared his unique point of view and expertise to help fans become the best versions of themselves. From living longer to getting smarter, maximising performance to practising mindfulness, Dave&#8217;s followers look to him for his take on the most effective techniques to become healthier and more powerful than most doctors think is possible.</p>
<p>                              Asprey has been fasting for years, long before it gained widespread popularity, and if you&#8217;re a fan of The Bulletproof Diet, you have been enjoying some of the benefits of Intermittent Fasting too.</p>
<p>                              In Fast This Way, Dave asks readers to forget everything they think they know about the ancient practice and takes them on a journey through cutting-edge science to examine the ways novice fasters and Intermittent Fasting loyalists can up-end their relationship with food and upgrade their fasting game beyond calorie restriction.  </p>
<p>                     What IF eating the right foods at the right time can actually enhance your fast?<br />
                     What IF how you work out and sleep could trick your body into thinking you are fasting?<br />
                     What IF it were easy to skip a meal, or two, or three?<br />
                     What IF fasting is different for women, can be personalised to your genes, and can impact your mental health?<br />
                     What IF all fasts could be created equal?</p>
<p>                              Fast This Way is a compelling read through the latest thinking on fasting and gives readers the manual and toolkit to make the most of their fasts and their personal biology.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/">Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The UltraMind Solution : The Simple Way to Defeat Depression, Overcome Anxiety, and Sharpen Your Mind &#8211; Mark Hyman</title>
		<link>/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Ultramind Solutionspeaks directly to the massive generation of boomers who, for the first time, are encountering diminishing memory and focus, among other affects of life on earth and the human brain. Like all of Dr. Hyman&#8217;s work, this latest instalment in the &#8220;Ultra&#8221; series teaches the reader how to use the body to heal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/">The UltraMind Solution : The Simple Way to Defeat Depression, Overcome Anxiety, and Sharpen Your Mind &#8211; Mark Hyman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ultramind Solutionspeaks directly to the massive generation of boomers who, for the first time, are encountering diminishing memory and focus, among other affects of life on earth and the human brain. Like all of Dr. Hyman&#8217;s work, this latest instalment in the &#8220;Ultra&#8221; series teaches the reader how to use the body to heal the body, this time making lifestyle changes that will foster brain function, including memory, mood, and attention span as well as battle everything from brain fatigue to depression.     </p>
<p>                    Like all of Dr. Hyman&#8217;s books, Ultramindincludes the 7 Keys to Brain Health and a simple 6 week program that will cleanse, heal and strengthen the brain. Each section has a quiz for the reader to access the affect of each particular key on their brain function, provides a list of diagnostic tests for clinical treatments as well as a how to implement healing solutions from changes in nutrition to supplements, hormones, detoxification, and fighting brain &#8220;allergies.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    The Ultramind Solutionincludes a brain workout and recipes for &#8220;brain&#8221; foods that stimulate performance.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/">The UltraMind Solution : The Simple Way to Defeat Depression, Overcome Anxiety, and Sharpen Your Mind &#8211; Mark Hyman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food    </p>
<p>                    There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; whole grains are healthy, whole grains are a disaster; eat everything in moderation; eat only certain foods&#8212;and on and on. In 100 Million Years of Food, biological anthropologist Stephen Le explains how cuisines of different cultures are a result of centuries of evolution, finely tuned to our biology and surroundings. Today many cultures have strayed from their ancestral diets, relying instead on mass-produced food often made with chemicals that may be contributing to a rise in so-called Western diseases, such as cancer, heart disease, and obesity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Vitamin Solution : Two Doctors Clear the Confusion about Vitamins and Your Health &#8211; Dr. Romy Block, Dr. Arielle Levitan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-vitamin-solution-two-doctors-clear-the-confusion-about-vitamins-and-your-health-dr-romy-block-dr-arielle-levitan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-vitamin-solution-two-doctors-clear-the-confusion-about-vitamins-and-your-health-dr-romy-block-dr-arielle-levitan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you confused about vitamins? Unsure of which ones you need for optimal health, and what levels are safe? You&#8217;re not alone. Many people&#8217;s health issues could be improved with vitamins-if they only knew how to use them. In this award-winning book, The Vitamin Solution, Drs. Romy Block and Arielle Levitan provide a common-sense, medically [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-vitamin-solution-two-doctors-clear-the-confusion-about-vitamins-and-your-health-dr-romy-block-dr-arielle-levitan-abridged/">The Vitamin Solution : Two Doctors Clear the Confusion about Vitamins and Your Health &#8211; Dr. Romy Block, Dr. Arielle Levitan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you confused about vitamins? Unsure of which ones you need for optimal health, and what levels are safe? You&#8217;re not alone. Many people&#8217;s health issues could be improved with vitamins-if they only knew how to use them.     </p>
<p>                    In this award-winning book, The Vitamin Solution, Drs. Romy Block and Arielle Levitan provide a common-sense, medically sound approach to using vitamins to improve your diet, exercise plan, and overall health. In clear, accessible, language, they explain which vitamins and supplements can be helpful, which can be harmful, and which are altogether unnecessary; explore health topics including migraine, hair loss, fatigue, irritable bowel syndrome, hot flashes, and more; and address preventive care, providing insights on topics such as screening tests, weight loss, and preserving memory. Illuminating and accessible, The Vitamin Solution is an indispensable guide to safely incorporating vitamins and supplements into any lifestyle-one that will leave readers educated, informed, and armed with simple, everyday strategies for bettering their health.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-vitamin-solution-two-doctors-clear-the-confusion-about-vitamins-and-your-health-dr-romy-block-dr-arielle-levitan-abridged/">The Vitamin Solution : Two Doctors Clear the Confusion about Vitamins and Your Health &#8211; Dr. Romy Block, Dr. Arielle Levitan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mindless Eating &#8211; Brian Wansink (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mindless-eating-brian-wansink-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mindless-eating-brian-wansink-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every day, we each make around 200 decisions about eating. But studies have shown that 90% of these decisions are made without any conscious choice. Dr Brian Wansink lays bare the facts about our true eating habits to show that awareness of our patterns can allow us to lose weight effectively and without serious changes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindless-eating-brian-wansink-abridged/">Mindless Eating &#8211; Brian Wansink (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every day, we each make around 200 decisions about eating. But studies have shown that 90% of these decisions are made without any conscious choice. Dr Brian Wansink lays bare the facts about our true eating habits to show that awareness of our patterns can allow us to lose weight effectively and without serious changes to our lives.   Dr Wansink&#8217;s revelations include:    </p>
<p>                      *       Food mistakes we all make in restaurants, supermarkets and at home<br />
                      *        How we are manipulated by brand, appearance and parental habits more than price and our choices<br />
                      *       Our emotional relationship with food and how we can overcome it to revitalise our diets.    </p>
<p>                      Forget calorie counting and starving yourself and learn the truth about why we overeat in this fascinating, innovative guide. Mindless Eating has become a breakout hit from the diet and fitness field and this fantastic new package will bring it to a new audience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindless-eating-brian-wansink-abridged/">Mindless Eating &#8211; Brian Wansink (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fight back against a modern culture that is rewiring our brains and damaging our health with this practical, doctor-approved plan for healing that includes a ten-day boot camp and forty delicious recipes. Contemporary life provides us with infinite opportunities, along with endless temptations. We can eat whatever we want, whenever we want. We can immerse [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fight back against a modern culture that is rewiring our brains and damaging our health with this practical, doctor-approved plan for healing that includes a ten-day boot camp and forty delicious recipes.<br />
                    Contemporary life provides us with infinite opportunities, along with endless temptations. We can eat whatever we want, whenever we want. We can immerse ourselves in the vast, enticing world of digital media. We can buy goods and services for rapid delivery with our fingertips or voice commands. But living in this 24/7 hyper-reality poses serious risks to our physical and mental states, our connections to others, and even to the world at large.<br />
                    Brain Wash builds from a simple premise: Our brains are being gravely manipulated, resulting in behaviors that leave us more lonely, anxious, depressed, distrustful, illness-prone, and overweight than ever before.<br />
                    Based on the latest science, the book identifies the mental hijacking that undermines each and every one of us, and presents the tools necessary to think more clearly, make better decisions, strengthen bonds with others, and develop healthier habits. Featuring a 10-day bootcamp program, including a meal plan and 40 delicious original recipes, Brain Wash is the key to cultivating a more purposeful and fulfilling life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners : Your Essential Guide to Living the Keto Lifestyle &#8211; Amy Ramos, Rockridge Press, Foreword by Amanda C Hughes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The simple, friendly way to start the ketogenic diet and lifestyle Starting the ketogenic diet can be overwhelming―so much to learn, so many resources to choose from. So why doesn&#8217;t somebody make it easy? We did with this must-have cookbook. The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners makes it easy to start, and stick with, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/">The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners : Your Essential Guide to Living the Keto Lifestyle &#8211; Amy Ramos, Rockridge Press, Foreword by Amanda C Hughes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The simple, friendly way to start the ketogenic diet and lifestyle    </p>
<p>                    Starting the ketogenic diet can be overwhelming―so much to learn, so many resources to choose from. So why doesn&#8217;t somebody make it easy? We did with this must-have cookbook. The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners makes it easy to start, and stick with, the ketogenic diet. You get exactly what you need for surprisingly simple keto: meal plans, shopping lists, support, and lots of keto-licious recipes.    </p>
<p>                    What sets this ketogenic cookbook apart from other keto books for beginners:<br />
                    75 scrumptious recipes―From Bacon-Artichoke Omelets to Pesto Zucchini Noodles, these easy-to-follow recipes can be prepared in 30 minutes or less.14-day meal plan―With breakfast, lunch, dinner, and snack suggestions, this book takes the guesswork out of starting your ketogenic diet.The big picture―An overview explaining the fundamentals of the ketogenic diet and handy charts illustrating nutritional information help you master keto in no time.    </p>
<p>                    Easy meets delicious meets healthy in this ketogenic diet and healthy lifestyle guide and cookbook. Start eating keto today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/">The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners : Your Essential Guide to Living the Keto Lifestyle &#8211; Amy Ramos, Rockridge Press, Foreword by Amanda C Hughes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What shall we have for dinner? Such a simple question has grown to have a very complicated answer. We can eat almost anything nature has to offer, but deciding what we should eat stirs anxiety. Should we choose the organic apple or the conventional? If organic, local or imported? Wild fish or farmed? Low-carb or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What shall we have for dinner? Such a simple question has grown to have a very complicated answer. We can eat almost anything nature has to offer, but deciding what we should eat stirs anxiety. Should we choose the organic apple or the conventional? If organic, local or imported? Wild fish or farmed? Low-carb or low-cal? As the American culture of fast food and unlimited choice invades the world, Pollan follows his next meal from land to table, tracing the origin of everything consumed and the implications for ourselves and our planet. His astonishing findings will shock all who care about what they put on their plate.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed &#8211; Jon Ronson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Jon Ronson, the Sunday Times top ten bestselling author of The Psychopath Test, this is a captivating and brilliant exploration of one of our world&#8217;s most underappreciated forces: shame. &#8216;It&#8217;s about the terror, isn&#8217;t it?&#8217; &#8216;The terror of what?&#8217; I said. &#8216;The terror of being found out.&#8217; Jon Ronson has travelled the world meeting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/">So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed &#8211; Jon Ronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Jon Ronson, the Sunday Times top ten bestselling author of The Psychopath Test, this is a captivating and brilliant exploration of one of our world&#8217;s most underappreciated forces: shame.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s about the terror, isn&#8217;t it?&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;The terror of what?&#8217; I said.<br />
                    &#8216;The terror of being found out.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Jon Ronson has travelled the world meeting recipients of high-profile public shamings. The shamed are people like us &#8211; people who, say, made a joke on social media that came out badly, or made a mistake at work. Once their transgression is revealed, collective outrage circles with the force of a hurricane and the next thing they know they&#8217;re being torn apart by an angry mob, jeered at, demonized, sometimes even fired from their job.    </p>
<p>                    A great renaissance of public shaming is sweeping our land. Justice has been democratized. The silent majority are getting a voice. But what are we doing with our voice? We are mercilessly finding people&#8217;s faults. We are defining the boundaries of normality by ruining the lives of those outside it. We are using shame as a form of social control.    </p>
<p>                    Simultaneously powerful and hilarious in the way only Jon Ronson can be, So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed is a deeply honest book about modern life, full of eye-opening truths about the escalating war on human flaws &#8211; and the very scary part we all play in it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/">So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed &#8211; Jon Ronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bulletproof Diet : Lose up to a Pound a Day, Reclaim Energy and Focus, Upgrade Your Life &#8211; Dave Asprey, Foreword by J. J. Virgin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bulletproof-diet-lose-up-to-a-pound-a-day-reclaim-energy-and-focus-upgrade-your-life-dave-asprey-foreword-by-j-j-virgin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bulletproof-diet-lose-up-to-a-pound-a-day-reclaim-energy-and-focus-upgrade-your-life-dave-asprey-foreword-by-j-j-virgin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When his excess fat started causing brain fog and food cravings sapped his energy and willpower, Asprey turned to the same hacking techniques that made his fortune to &#8220;hack&#8221; his own biology, investing more than $300,000 and 15 years to uncover what was hindering his energy, performance, appearance, and happiness. From private brain EEG facilities [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bulletproof-diet-lose-up-to-a-pound-a-day-reclaim-energy-and-focus-upgrade-your-life-dave-asprey-foreword-by-j-j-virgin-abridged/">The Bulletproof Diet : Lose up to a Pound a Day, Reclaim Energy and Focus, Upgrade Your Life &#8211; Dave Asprey, Foreword by J. J. Virgin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When his excess fat started causing brain fog and food cravings sapped his energy and willpower, Asprey turned to the same hacking techniques that made his fortune to &#8220;hack&#8221; his own biology, investing more than $300,000 and 15 years to uncover what was hindering his energy, performance, appearance, and happiness. From private brain EEG facilities to remote monasteries in Tibet, through radioactive brain scans, blood chemistry work, nervous system testing and more, he explored traditional and alternative technologies to reach his physical and mental prime. The result? The Bulletproof Diet, an anti-inflammatory program for hunger-free, rapid weight loss and peak performance. The Bulletproof Diet will change what you think you know about weight loss and wellness. You will skip breakfast, stop counting calories, eat a high-fat diet, work out and sleep less, and handle stress with ease. By ditching traditional &#8220;diet&#8221; thinking, Asprey has maintained a 100-pound weight loss, increased his IQ, and reached a level of health that seemed unattainable. His 40s are truly better than his 20s, and The Bulletproof Diet brings his best hacks to the masses.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bulletproof-diet-lose-up-to-a-pound-a-day-reclaim-energy-and-focus-upgrade-your-life-dave-asprey-foreword-by-j-j-virgin-abridged/">The Bulletproof Diet : Lose up to a Pound a Day, Reclaim Energy and Focus, Upgrade Your Life &#8211; Dave Asprey, Foreword by J. J. Virgin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Go Wild : Free Your Body and Mind from the Afflictions of Civilization &#8211; Dr. John J. Ratey, Richard Manning (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/go-wild-free-your-body-and-mind-from-the-afflictions-of-civilization-dr-john-j-ratey-richard-manning-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/go-wild-free-your-body-and-mind-from-the-afflictions-of-civilization-dr-john-j-ratey-richard-manning-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The scientific evidence behind why we should maintain a lifestyle more like that of our ancestors to restore our health and well-being. In GO WILD, Harvard Medical School professor John Ratey, MD, and journalist Richard Manning reveal that although civilization has rapidly evolved, our bodies stopped changing long ago&#8211;creating a disconnect between how we live [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/go-wild-free-your-body-and-mind-from-the-afflictions-of-civilization-dr-john-j-ratey-richard-manning-abridged/">Go Wild : Free Your Body and Mind from the Afflictions of Civilization &#8211; Dr. John J. Ratey, Richard Manning (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The scientific evidence behind why we should maintain a lifestyle more like that of our ancestors to restore our health and well-being.     </p>
<p>                    In GO WILD, Harvard Medical School professor John Ratey, MD, and journalist Richard Manning reveal that although civilization has rapidly evolved, our bodies stopped changing long ago&#8211;creating a disconnect between how we live and what is best for us. This disconnect affects every area of our lives, from our energy levels to our relationships to our general health. Only by using ancient evolutionary instructions to navigate modern life can we realize our true potential in everything including strength, health and well-being, intelligence, happiness, and more. The book addresses modern diseases (from diabetes to cancer to addiction); the problems of the modern diet; exercise; sleep; mindfulness and relationships; and much more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/go-wild-free-your-body-and-mind-from-the-afflictions-of-civilization-dr-john-j-ratey-richard-manning-abridged/">Go Wild : Free Your Body and Mind from the Afflictions of Civilization &#8211; Dr. John J. Ratey, Richard Manning (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wild Diet : Go Beyond Paleo to Burn Fat and Drop Up to 20 Pounds in 40 Days &#8211; Abel James (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Abel James, the ABC star and creator of the #1 Fat-Burning Man Show, shares his revolutionary weight-loss program in The Wild Diet &#8211; now a New York Times Bestseller! Can you really lose 20 pounds in 40 days while enjoying real butter, juicy burgers, chicken parmesan, chocolate, and even cheesecake? The answer might surprise you. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/">The Wild Diet : Go Beyond Paleo to Burn Fat and Drop Up to 20 Pounds in 40 Days &#8211; Abel James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Abel James, the ABC star and creator of the #1 Fat-Burning Man Show, shares his revolutionary weight-loss program in The Wild Diet &#8211; now a New York Times Bestseller!      </p>
<p>                    Can you really lose 20 pounds in 40 days while enjoying real butter, juicy burgers, chicken parmesan, chocolate, and even cheesecake?     </p>
<p>                    The answer might surprise you.     </p>
<p>                    By focusing on simple, fresh ingredients and nutrient-dense meals, The Wild Diet programs your body to burn fat as its main fuel source. Eating Wild, thousands of people across the world have dropped 20, 60, or even more than 100+ pounds without hunger&#8230; and often with minimal exercise.     </p>
<p>                    In The Wild Diet, you&#8217;ll find that we are not meant to starve ourselves, count calories, or avoid delicious food. We&#8217;re wired to eat luxuriously and live well without getting fat.     </p>
<p>                    If you think that you&#8217;re stuck with the genes you inherited and there&#8217;s nothing you can do about it, read closely. The Wild Diet paints a different picture, one in which we have the power to influence our genetic expression by taking control of the quality of food we eat, the way we move, and the environment around us.     </p>
<p>                    We once had access to an immense variety of fresh seasonal foods from small, local sources. Now we have access to few varieties of processed foods from a massive industrial system often thousands of miles from where we live. The secret to great health simply getting back to our wild roots and enjoying real, Wild foods grown on a farm and not in a factory.     </p>
<p>                    By prioritizing foods found in the natural world, rich in fiber and nutrients, your body will burn fat instead of sugar for energy. When you reduce your consumption of processed grains, sugars and other simple carbohydrates in favor of healthy plants and animals, you will be shocked by how quickly you can reverse the damage of decades of poor eating.     </p>
<p>                    The Wild Diet proves that it&#8217;s possible to get in best shape of your life while eating delicious foods like chicken parmesan, bacon cheeseburgers, and even chocolate pudding. If you want to know how to burn more fat by indulging in incredible meals and exercising less, it&#8217;s time to treat yourself to The Wild Diet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/">The Wild Diet : Go Beyond Paleo to Burn Fat and Drop Up to 20 Pounds in 40 Days &#8211; Abel James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Obesity Code : the bestselling guide to unlocking the secrets of weight loss &#8211; Dr Jason Fung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-obesity-code-the-bestselling-guide-to-unlocking-the-secrets-of-weight-loss-dr-jason-fung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Obesity: Treatment & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy & Therapeutics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-obesity-code-the-bestselling-guide-to-unlocking-the-secrets-of-weight-loss-dr-jason-fung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are in the midst of an obesity epidemic, but despite being inundated with diet advice we are only getting fatter. We count calories and exercise regularly, yet still the pounds won&#8217;t budge. Why? In this highly readable and provocative book, Dr Jason Fung sets out a groundbreaking new theory: that obesity is caused by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-obesity-code-the-bestselling-guide-to-unlocking-the-secrets-of-weight-loss-dr-jason-fung-abridged/">The Obesity Code : the bestselling guide to unlocking the secrets of weight loss &#8211; Dr Jason Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are in the midst of an obesity epidemic, but despite being inundated with diet advice we are only getting fatter. We count calories and exercise regularly, yet still the pounds won&#8217;t budge. Why?    </p>
<p>                    In this highly readable and provocative book, Dr Jason Fung sets out a groundbreaking new theory: that obesity is caused by our hormones, rather than a lack of self-control.    </p>
<p>                    He reveals that overproduction of insulin in the body is the root cause of obesity and obesity-related illnesses including type 2 diabetes, and offers robust scientific evidence that reversing insulin resistance is the only way to lose weight in the long term.    </p>
<p>                    It turns out that when we eat is just as important as what we eat, so in addition to his five basic steps &#8211; a set of life-long eating habits that will improve your health and control your insulin levels &#8211; Dr Fung explains how to use intermittent fasting to break the cycle of insulin resistance and reach a healthy weight &#8211; for good.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-obesity-code-the-bestselling-guide-to-unlocking-the-secrets-of-weight-loss-dr-jason-fung-abridged/">The Obesity Code : the bestselling guide to unlocking the secrets of weight loss &#8211; Dr Jason Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Always Hungry? : Conquer Cravings, Retrain Your Fat Cells, and Lose Weight Permanently &#8211; David Ludwig, Read by Dawn Ludwig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/always-hungry-conquer-cravings-retrain-your-fat-cells-and-lose-weight-permanently-david-ludwig-read-by-dawn-ludwig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/always-hungry-conquer-cravings-retrain-your-fat-cells-and-lose-weight-permanently-david-ludwig-read-by-dawn-ludwig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leading Harvard Medical School expert and obesity warrior (Time magazine) Dr. David Ludwig rewrites the rules on weight loss, diet, and health in this guide to retraining your cells and reclaiming your health for life. Forget everything you&#8217;ve been taught about dieting. In Always Hungry?, renowned endocrinologist Dr. David Ludwig explains why traditional diets don&#8217;t [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/always-hungry-conquer-cravings-retrain-your-fat-cells-and-lose-weight-permanently-david-ludwig-read-by-dawn-ludwig-abridged/">Always Hungry? : Conquer Cravings, Retrain Your Fat Cells, and Lose Weight Permanently &#8211; David Ludwig, Read by Dawn Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading Harvard Medical School expert and obesity warrior (Time magazine) Dr. David Ludwig rewrites the rules on weight loss, diet, and health in this guide to retraining your cells and reclaiming your health for life.<br />
                    Forget everything you&#8217;ve been taught about dieting. In Always Hungry?, renowned endocrinologist Dr. David Ludwig explains why traditional diets don&#8217;t work and presents a radical new plan to help you lose weight without hunger, improve your health, and feel great.<br />
                    For over two decades, Dr. Ludwig has been at the forefront of research into weight control. His groundbreaking studies show that overeating doesn&#8217;t make you fat; the process of getting fat makes you overeat. That&#8217;s because fat cells play a key role in determining how much weight you gain or lose. Low-fat diets work against you by triggering fat cells to hoard more calories for themselves, leaving too few for the rest of the body. This hungry fat sets off a dangerous chain reaction that leaves you feeling ravenous as your metabolism slows down. Cutting calories only makes the situation worse by creating a battle between mind and metabolism that we&#8217;re destined to lose. You gain more weight even as you struggle to eat less food.<br />
                    Always Hungry? turns dieting on its head with a three-phase program that ignores calories and targets fat cells directly. The recipes and meal plan include luscious high-fat foods (like nuts and nut butters, full-fat dairy, avocados, and dark chocolate), savory proteins, and natural carbohydrates. The result? Fat cells release their excess calories, and you lose weight &#8211; and inches &#8211; without battling cravings and constant hunger. This is dieting without deprivation.<br />
                    Forget calories. Forget cravings. Forget dieting. Always hungry? reveals a liberating new way to tame hunger and lose weight for good.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/always-hungry-conquer-cravings-retrain-your-fat-cells-and-lose-weight-permanently-david-ludwig-read-by-dawn-ludwig-abridged/">Always Hungry? : Conquer Cravings, Retrain Your Fat Cells, and Lose Weight Permanently &#8211; David Ludwig, Read by Dawn Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deep Nutrition : Why Your Genes Need Traditional Food &#8211; Catherine Shanahan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/deep-nutrition-why-your-genes-need-traditional-food-catherine-shanahan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deep-nutrition-why-your-genes-need-traditional-food-catherine-shanahan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Physician and biochemist Cate Shanahan, M.D. examined diets around the world known to help people live longer, healthier lives &#8211; diets like the Mediterranean, Okinawa, and &#8220;Blue Zone&#8221; &#8211; and identified the four common nutritional habits, developed over millennia, that unfailingly produce strong, healthy, intelligent children, and active, vital elders, generation after generation. These four [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-nutrition-why-your-genes-need-traditional-food-catherine-shanahan-abridged/">Deep Nutrition : Why Your Genes Need Traditional Food &#8211; Catherine Shanahan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Physician and biochemist Cate Shanahan, M.D. examined diets around the world known to help people live longer, healthier lives &#8211; diets like the Mediterranean, Okinawa, and &#8220;Blue Zone&#8221; &#8211; and identified the four common nutritional habits, developed over millennia, that unfailingly produce strong, healthy, intelligent children, and active, vital elders, generation after generation. These four nutritional strategies &#8211; fresh food, fermented and sprouted foods, meat cooked on the bone, and organ meats &#8211; form the basis of what Dr. Cate calls &#8220;The Human Diet.&#8221; Rooted in her experience as an elite athlete who used traditional foods to cure her own debilitating injuries, and combining her research with the latest discoveries in the field of epigenetics, Dr. Cate shows how all calories are not created equal; food is information that directs our cellulargrowth. Our family history does not determine our destiny: what you eat and how you live can alter your DNA in ways that affect your health and the health of your future children. Deep Nutrition offers a prescriptive planfor how anyone can begin eating The Human Diet to: Improve mood, Eliminate cravings and the need to snack, Boost fertility and have healthier children, Sharpen cognition and memory, Eliminate allergies and disease, Build stronger bones and joints, Get younger, smoother skin</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-nutrition-why-your-genes-need-traditional-food-catherine-shanahan-abridged/">Deep Nutrition : Why Your Genes Need Traditional Food &#8211; Catherine Shanahan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oncology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases. Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases.      </p>
<p>                    Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to identify the strategies and dosages for using food to transform your resilience and health in Eat to Beat Disease.     </p>
<p>                    We have radically underestimated our body&#8217;s power to transform and restore our health. Pioneering physician scientist, Dr. William Li, empowers readers by showing them the evidence behind over 200 health-boosting foods that can starve cancer, reduce your risk of dementia, and beat dozens of avoidable diseases. Eat to Beat Disease isn&#8217;t about what foods to avoid, but rather is a life-changing guide to the hundreds of healing foods to add to your meals that support the body&#8217;s defense systems, including: PlumsCinnamonJasmine teaRed wine and beerBlack BeansSan Marzano tomatoesOlive oilPacific oystersCheeses like Jarlsberg, Camembert and cheddarSourdough bread<br />
                    The book&#8217;s plan shows you how to integrate the foods you already love into any diet or health plan to activate your body&#8217;s health defense systems-Angiogenesis, Regeneration, Microbiome, DNA Protection, and Immunity-to fight cancer, diabetes, cardiovascular, neurodegenerative autoimmune diseases, and other debilitating conditions.     </p>
<p>                    Both informative and practical, Eat to Beat Disease explains the science of healing and prevention, the strategies for using food to actively transform health, and points the science of wellbeing and disease prevention in an exhilarating new direction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beat Sugar Addiction Now! : The Cutting-Edge Program That Cures Your Type of Sugar Addiction and Puts You on the Road to Feeling Great &#8211; and Losing Weight! &#8211; Jacob Teitelbaum, Chrystle Fiedler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Normal0MicrosoftInternetExplorer4 The No-Fail Plan to Beating Sugar Addiction! With one-third of our calories coming from sugar and white flour added to processed foods, sugar addiction is a rapidly growing epidemic. However, unlike other addictions, going &#8220;cold turkey&#8221; won&#8217;t fix it. In this groundbreaking book, nationally recognized physician Dr. Jacob Teitelbaum uncovers four types of sugar [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/">Beat Sugar Addiction Now! : The Cutting-Edge Program That Cures Your Type of Sugar Addiction and Puts You on the Road to Feeling Great &#8211; and Losing Weight! &#8211; Jacob Teitelbaum, Chrystle Fiedler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Normal0MicrosoftInternetExplorer4    </p>
<p>                    The No-Fail Plan to Beating Sugar Addiction!    </p>
<p>                    With one-third of our calories coming from sugar and white flour added to processed foods, sugar addiction is a rapidly growing epidemic. However, unlike other addictions, going &#8220;cold turkey&#8221; won&#8217;t fix it. In this groundbreaking book, nationally recognized physician Dr. Jacob Teitelbaum uncovers four types of sugar addiction and gives a step-by-step plan for resolving their underlying causes, breaking sugar cravings forever, and achieving dramatically improved health and energy levels&#8211;while also making it easier to lose weight!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/">Beat Sugar Addiction Now! : The Cutting-Edge Program That Cures Your Type of Sugar Addiction and Puts You on the Road to Feeling Great &#8211; and Losing Weight! &#8211; Jacob Teitelbaum, Chrystle Fiedler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clean : The Revolutionary Program to Restore the Body&#8217;s Natural Ability to Heal Itself &#8211; Alejandro Junger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Life-Changing Medical Breakthrough Clean is an M.D.&#8217;s program designed to be easily incorporated into our busy schedule while providing all the practical tools necessary to support and rejuvenate our bodies. The effect is transformative: nagging health problems will suddenly disappear, extra weight will drop away, and for the first time in our lives, we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/">Clean : The Revolutionary Program to Restore the Body&#8217;s Natural Ability to Heal Itself &#8211; Alejandro Junger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Life-Changing Medical Breakthrough Clean is an M.D.&#8217;s program designed to be easily incorporated into our busy schedule while providing all the practical tools necessary to support and rejuvenate our bodies. The effect is transformative: nagging health problems will suddenly disappear, extra weight will drop away, and for the first time in our lives, we will experience what it truly means to feel healthy.  Expanded Edition Includes: New Introduction * New Recipes * How to Become Clean for Life</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/">Clean : The Revolutionary Program to Restore the Body&#8217;s Natural Ability to Heal Itself &#8211; Alejandro Junger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What to Eat When : A Strategic Plan to Improve Your Health and Life Through Food &#8211; Michael F. Roizen, Michael Crupain, With Ted Spiker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-to-eat-when-a-strategic-plan-to-improve-your-health-and-life-through-food-michael-f-roizen-michael-crupain-with-ted-spiker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celebrity Chefs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-to-eat-when-a-strategic-plan-to-improve-your-health-and-life-through-food-michael-f-roizen-michael-crupain-with-ted-spiker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now in paperback, NY Times best-selling author Dr. Michael Roizen&#8217;s groundbreaking book reveals how the food choices you make each day&#8211;and when you make them&#8211;can affect your health, your energy, your sex life, your waistline, your attitude, and how you age. What if eating two cups of blueberries a day could prevent cancer? If drinking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-eat-when-a-strategic-plan-to-improve-your-health-and-life-through-food-michael-f-roizen-michael-crupain-with-ted-spiker-abridged/">What to Eat When : A Strategic Plan to Improve Your Health and Life Through Food &#8211; Michael F. Roizen, Michael Crupain, With Ted Spiker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now in paperback, NY Times best-selling author Dr. Michael Roizen&#8217;s groundbreaking book reveals how the food choices you make each day&#8211;and when you make them&#8211;can affect your health, your energy, your sex life, your waistline, your attitude, and how you age.    </p>
<p>                     What if eating two cups of blueberries a day could prevent cancer? If drinking a kale-infused smoothie could counteract missing an hour&#8217;s worth of sleep? When is the right time of day to eat that chocolate chip cookies? And would you actually drink that glass of water if it meant skipping the gym? This revolutionary guide&#8211;Dr. Mehmet Oz&#8217;s 2019 Diet of the Year&#8211;reveals how to use food to enhance our personal and professional lives, and increase our longevity to boot.     </p>
<p>                     What to Eat When is not a diet book. Instead, acclaimed Cleveland Clinic internist Michael Roizen and certified physician Michael Crupain offer reader the choices that will benefit them the most&#8211;whether it&#8217;s meals to help them look younger or snacks that prevent diseases&#8211;based on the science that governs them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-eat-when-a-strategic-plan-to-improve-your-health-and-life-through-food-michael-f-roizen-michael-crupain-with-ted-spiker-abridged/">What to Eat When : A Strategic Plan to Improve Your Health and Life Through Food &#8211; Michael F. Roizen, Michael Crupain, With Ted Spiker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maturation & Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life. From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life.    </p>
<p>                    From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of his career. He knows that everyone thinks they want to live forever, until they hit middle age and witness the suffering of their parents and even their peers. So how do we solve the paradox of wanting to live to a ripe old age-but enjoy the benefits of youth?    </p>
<p>                    This groundbreaking book holds the answer. Working with thousands of patients, Dr. Gundry has discovered that the &#8220;diseases of aging&#8221; we most fear are not simply a function of age; rather, they are a byproduct of the way we have lived over the decades. In The Longevity Paradox, he maps out a new approach to aging well-one that is based on supporting the health of the &#8220;oldest&#8221; parts of us: the microorganisms that live within our bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Our gut bugs-the bacteria that make up the microbiome-largely determine our health over the years. From diseases like cancer and Alzheimer&#8217;s to common ailments like arthritis to our weight and the appearance of our skin, these bugs are in the driver&#8217;s seat, controlling our quality of life as we age.    </p>
<p>                    The good news is, it&#8217;s never too late to support these microbes and give them what they need to help them-and you-thrive. In The Longevity Paradox, Dr. Gundry outlines a nutrition and lifestyle plan to support gut health and live well for decades to come. A progressive take on the new science of aging, The Longevity Paradox offers an action plan to prevent and reverse disease as well as simple hacks to help anyone look and feel younger and more vital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report, Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report,  Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by Medicare when offered virtually at home.     </p>
<p>                     Dean Ornish, M.D., has directed revolutionary research proving, for the first time, that lifestyle changes can often reverse&#8211;undo!&#8211;the progression of many of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level.     </p>
<p>                     Medicare and many insurance companies now cover Dr. Ornish&#8217;s lifestyle medicine program for reversing chronic disease because it consistently achieves bigger changes in lifestyle, better clinical outcomes, larger cost savings, and greater adherence than have ever been reported&#8211;based on forty years of research published in the leading peer-reviewed medical and scientific journals.     </p>
<p>                     Now, in this landmark book, he and Anne Ornish present a simple yet powerful new unifying theory explaining why these same lifestyle changes can reverse so many different chronic diseases and how quickly these benefits occur. They describe what it is, why it works, and how you can do it:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Eat well a whole foods, plant-based diet naturally low in fat and sugar and high in flavor. The &#8220;Ornish diet&#8221; has been rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report for eleven years since 2011.<br />
                     &#8211; Move more moderate exercise such as walking<br />
                     &#8211; Stress less including meditation and gentle yoga practices<br />
                     &#8211; Love more how love and intimacy transform loneliness into healing     </p>
<p>                    With seventy recipes, easy-to-follow meal plans, tips for stocking your kitchen and eating out, recommended exercises, stress-reduction advice, and inspiring patient stories of life-transforming benefits&#8211;for example, several people improved so much after only nine weeks they were able to avoid a heart transplant&#8211;Undo It! empowers readers with new hope and new choices.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Undo It!     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Ornishes&#8217; work is elegant and simple and deserving of a Nobel Prize, since it can change the world!&#8221;&#8211;Richard Carmona, M.D., MPH, FACS, seventeenth Surgeon General of the United States     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;If you want to see what medicine will be like ten years from now, read this book today.&#8221;&#8211;Rita F. Redberg, M.D., editor in chief, JAMA Internal Medicine     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This is one of the most important books on health ever written.&#8221;&#8211;John Mackey, CEO, Whole Foods Market</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genius Foods : Become Smarter, Happier, and More Productive, While Protecting Your Brain Health for Life &#8211; Max Lugavere (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller Discover the critical link between your brain and the food you eat and change the way your brain ages, in this cutting-edge, practical guide to eliminating brain fog, optimizing brain health, and achieving peak mental performance from media personality and leading voice in health Max Lugavere. After his mother was diagnosed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/">Genius Foods : Become Smarter, Happier, and More Productive, While Protecting Your Brain Health for Life &#8211; Max Lugavere (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Discover the critical link between your brain and the food you eat and change the way your brain ages, in this cutting-edge, practical guide to eliminating brain fog, optimizing brain health, and achieving peak mental performance from media personality and leading voice in health Max Lugavere.     </p>
<p>                    After his mother was diagnosed with a mysterious form of dementia, Max Lugavere put his successful media career on hold to learn everything he could about brain health and performance. For the better half of a decade, he consumed the most up-to-date scientific research, talked to dozens of leading scientists and clinicians around the world, and visited the country&#8217;s best neurology departments-all in the hopes of understanding his mother&#8217;s condition.     </p>
<p>                    Now, in Genius Foods, Lugavere presents a comprehensive guide to brain optimization. He uncovers the stunning link between our dietary and lifestyle choices and our brain functions, revealing how the foods you eat directly affect your ability to focus, learn, remember, create, analyze new ideas, and maintain a balanced mood.     </p>
<p>                    Weaving together pioneering research on dementia prevention, cognitive optimization, and nutritional psychiatry, Lugavere distills groundbreaking science into actionable lifestyle changes. He shares invaluable insights into how to improve your brain power, including     </p>
<p>                    the nutrients that can boost your memory and improve mental clarity (and where to find them);<br />
                    the foods and tactics that can energize and rejuvenate your brain, no matter your age;<br />
                    a brain-boosting fat-loss method so powerful it has been called &#8220;biochemical liposuction&#8221;; and<br />
                    the foods that can improve your happiness, both now and for the long term.    </p>
<p>                    With Genius Foods, Lugavere offers a cutting-edge yet practical road map to eliminating brain fog and optimizing the brain&#8217;s health and performance today-and decades into the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/">Genius Foods : Become Smarter, Happier, and More Productive, While Protecting Your Brain Health for Life &#8211; Max Lugavere (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Plant Ecology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Comfortably Unaware, Dr. Richard Oppenlander tackles the crucial issue of global depletion as it relates to food choice. We should all be committed, he tells us, to understanding the reality and consequences of our diet, the footprint it makes on our environment, and seek food products that are in the best interest of all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/">Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Comfortably Unaware, Dr. Richard Oppenlander tackles the crucial issue of global depletion as it relates to food choice. We should all be committed, he tells us, to understanding the reality and consequences of our diet, the footprint it makes on our environment, and seek food products that are in the best interest of all living things. His forthright information and stark mental images are often disturbing-and that&#8217;s how it should be. As the guardians of Planet Earth, we need to be shaken out of our complacency, to stop being comfortably unaware, and to understand the measures we must take to ensure the health and well-being of our planet-and of ourselves. Oppenlander</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/comfortably-unaware-what-we-choose-to-eat-is-killing-us-and-our-planet-richard-oppenlander-abridged/">Comfortably Unaware : What We Choose to Eat Is Killing Us and Our Planet &#8211; Richard Oppenlander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dr. Gundry is a true trailblazer, always at the forefront of scientific knowledge. The Plant Paradox shows the world what pioneer thinking is about and is a must-read book for anyone interested in being as healthy as nature has designed them to be.&#8221; -Alejandro Junger MD, New York Times bestselling author of Clean, Clean Gut [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dr. Gundry is a true trailblazer, always at the forefront of scientific knowledge. The Plant Paradox shows the world what pioneer thinking is about and is a must-read book for anyone interested in being as healthy as nature has designed them to be.&#8221; -Alejandro Junger MD, New York Times bestselling author of Clean, Clean Gut and Clean Eats  &#8220;The Plant Paradox elegantly explains how plants defend themselves from being consumed by humans, and how eating the wrong ones at the wrong times immeasurably hurts our health. An eye-opening read.&#8221; -Mehmet Oz, MD, Professor of Surgery, New York Presbyterian/Columbia University  Most of us have heard of gluten-a protein found in wheat that causes widespread inflammation in the body. Americans spend billions of dollars on gluten-free diets in an effort to protect their health. But what if we&#8217;ve been missing the root of the problem? In The Plant Paradox, renowned cardiologist Dr. Steven Gundry reveals that gluten is just one variety of a common, and highly toxic, plant-based protein called lectin.<br />
                    Lectins are found not only in grains like wheat but also in the &#8220;gluten-free&#8221; foods most of us commonly regard as healthy, including many fruits, vegetables, nuts, beans, and conventional dairy products. These proteins, which are found in the seeds, grains, skins, rinds, and leaves of plants, are designed by nature to protect them from predators (including humans). Once ingested, they incite a kind of chemical warfare in our bodies, causing inflammatory reactions that can lead to weight gain and serious health conditions.  At his waitlist-only clinics in California, Dr. Gundry has successfully treated tens of thousands of patients suffering from autoimmune disorders, diabetes, leaky gut syndrome, heart disease, and neurodegenerative diseases with a protocol that detoxes the cells, repairs the gut, and nourishes the body. Now, in The Plant Paradox, he shares this clinically proven program with readers around the world.  The simple (and daunting) fact is, lectins are everywhere. Thankfully, Dr. Gundry offers simple hacks we easily can employ to avoid them, including: * Peel your veggies.<br />
                    Most of the lectins are contained in the skin and seeds of plants; simply peeling and de-seeding vegetables (like tomatoes and peppers) reduces their lectin content.* Shop for fruit in season. Fruit contain fewer lectins when ripe, so eating apples, berries, and other lectin-containing fruits at the peak of ripeness helps minimize your lectin consumption.* Swap your brown rice for white. Whole grains and seeds with hard outer coatings are designed by nature to cause digestive distress-and are full of lectins. With a full list of lectin-containing foods and simple substitutes for each, a step-by-step detox and eating plan, and delicious lectin-free recipes, The Plant Paradox illuminates the hidden dangers lurking in your salad bowl-and shows you how to eat whole foods in a whole new way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and shines a bright light on the profound impact that diet&#8211;both good and bad&#8211;can have on our health and that of the planet.     </p>
<p>                     In A Bone to Pick, Mark&#8217;s most memorable and thought-provoking columns are compiled into a single volume for the first time. As abundant and safe as the American food supply appears to be, the state of our health reveals the presence of staggering deficiencies in both the system that produces food and the forces that regulate it. Bittman leaves no issue unexamined; agricultural practices, government legislation, fad diets, and corporate greed all come under scrutiny and show that the issues governing what ends up in our market basket and on our tables are both complex and often deliberately confusing. Unabashedly opinionated and invariably thought provoking, Bittman&#8217;s columns have helped readers decipher arcane policy, unpack scientific studies, and deflate affronts to common sense when it comes to determining what &#8220;eating well&#8221; truly means. As urgent as the situation is, Mark contends that we can be optimistic about the future of our food and its impact on our health, as slow-food movements, better school-lunch programs, and even &#8220;healthy fast food&#8221; become part of the norm.     </p>
<p>                     At once inspiring, enraging, and enlightening, A Bone to Pick is an essential resource for every reader eager to understand not only the complexities inherent in the American food system, but also the many opportunities that exist to improve it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book. Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book.     </p>
<p>                    Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. Why suffer from disease and ill health when the right food is proven to keep you healthy, and without the side effects of drugs? We can avoid heart disease, cancer and our other biggest killers if we use food as medicine, and the How Not To Die Cookbook offers a sustainable and delicious guide to preparing and eating the foods that will prevent and reverse fatal diseases.    </p>
<p>                    Featuring over 100 easy-to-follow, beautifully photographed plant-based recipes, with plenty of recipes suitable for vegetarians and vegans, the How Not To Die Cookbook merges cutting-edge science with everyday ingredients from the supermarket to help you and your family eat your way to better health and a longer life.    </p>
<p>                    All recipes in this cookbook have been fully anglicized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whole : Rethinking the Science of Nutrition &#8211; T. Colin Campbell, Howard Jacobson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller What happens when you eat an apple? The answer is vastly more complex than you imagine. Every apple contains thousands of antioxidants whose names, beyond a few like vitamin C, are unfamiliar to us, and each of these powerful chemicals has the potential to play an important role in supporting our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/">Whole : Rethinking the Science of Nutrition &#8211; T. Colin Campbell, Howard Jacobson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller  What happens when you eat an apple? The answer is vastly more complex than you imagine.  Every apple contains thousands of antioxidants whose names, beyond a few like vitamin C, are unfamiliar to us, and each of these powerful chemicals has the potential to play an important role in supporting our health. They impact thousands upon thousands of metabolic reactions inside the human body. But calculating the specific influence of each of these chemicals isn&#8217;t nearly sufficient to explain the effect of the apple as a whole. Because almost every chemical can affect every other chemical, there is an almost infinite number of possible biological consequences.  And that&#8217;s just from an apple.  Nutritional science, long stuck in a reductionist mindset, is at the cusp of a revolution. The traditional &#8220;gold standard&#8221; of nutrition research has been to study one chemical at a time in an attempt to determine its particular impact on the human body.<br />
                    These sorts of studies are helpful to food companies trying to prove there is a chemical in milk or pre-packaged dinners that is &#8220;good&#8221; for us, but they provide little insight into the complexity of what actually happens in our bodies or how those chemicals contribute to our health.  In The China Study, T. Colin Campbell (alongside his son, Thomas M. Campbell) revolutionized the way we think about our food with the evidence that a whole food, plant-based diet is the healthiest way to eat. Now, in Whole, he explains the science behind that evidence, the ways our current scientific paradigm ignores the fascinating complexity of the human body, and why, if we have such overwhelming evidence that everything we think we know about nutrition is wrong, our eating habits haven&#8217;t changed.  Whole is an eye-opening, paradigm-changing journey through cutting-edge thinking on nutrition, a scientific tour de force with powerful implications for our health and for our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/">Whole : Rethinking the Science of Nutrition &#8211; T. Colin Campbell, Howard Jacobson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now the subject of a film by Richard Linklater, Eric Schlosser&#8217;s explosive bestseller Fast Food Nation: What the All-American Meal is Doing to the World tells the story of our love affair with fast food. Britain eats more fast food than any other country in Europe. It looks good, tastes good, and it&#8217;s cheap. But [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now the subject of a film by Richard Linklater, Eric Schlosser&#8217;s explosive bestseller Fast Food Nation: What the All-American Meal is Doing to the World tells the story of our love affair with fast food.    </p>
<p>                      Britain eats more fast food than any other country in Europe. It looks good, tastes good, and it&#8217;s cheap. But the real cost never appears on the menu.    </p>
<p>                      Eric Schlosser visits the lab that re-creates the smell of strawberries; examines the safety records of abattoirs; reveals why the fries really taste so good and what lurks between the sesame buns &#8211; and shows how fast food is transforming not only our diets but our world.    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Fast Food Nation has lifted the polystyrene lid on the global fast food industry &#8230; and sparked a storm&#8217;<br />
                      Observer    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Has wiped that smirk off the Happy Meal &#8230; Thanks to this man, you&#8217;ll never eat a burger again&#8217;<br />
                      Evening Standard    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;Startling &#8230; Junk food, we learn, is just that &#8230; left this reader vowing never to set foot in one of those outlets again&#8217;<br />
                      Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                      &#8216;This book tells you more than you really want to know when you&#8217;re chomping on that hamburger &#8230; Have a nice day? Listen &#8211; you should live so long&#8217;<br />
                      The Times    </p>
<p>                      Eric Schlosser is a correspondent for the Atlantic Monthly. His first book, Fast Food Nation, was a major international bestseller. His work has appeared in the Atlantic Monthly, Rolling Stone and the Guardian. He has received a number of journalistic honours, including a National Magazine Award for an Atlantic Review article on the drug trade, which was later adapted into the book Reefer Madness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-food-nation-what-the-all-american-meal-is-doing-to-the-world-eric-schlosser-abridged/">Fast Food Nation : What The All-American Meal is Doing to the World &#8211; Eric Schlosser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What the Fork are You Eating? : An Action Plan for Your Pantry and Plate &#8211; Stefanie Sacks, Foreword by Kathie Madonna Swift (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s labeled natural, grass-fed, or free-roaming; yet it might be anything but. It&#8217;s time to find out what you&#8217;re actually eating&#8230; When your groceries are labeled &#8220;low-fat,&#8221; &#8220;sugar-free,&#8221; and even &#8220;natural&#8221; and antibiotic-free, it&#8217;s easy to assume that you&#8217;re making healthy choices. Yet even some of those seemingly wholesome offerings contain chemical preservatives, pesticides, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/">What the Fork are You Eating? : An Action Plan for Your Pantry and Plate &#8211; Stefanie Sacks, Foreword by Kathie Madonna Swift (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s labeled natural, grass-fed, or free-roaming; yet it might be anything but. It&#8217;s time to find out what you&#8217;re actually eating&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    When your groceries are labeled &#8220;low-fat,&#8221; &#8220;sugar-free,&#8221; and even &#8220;natural&#8221; and antibiotic-free, it&#8217;s easy to assume that you&#8217;re making healthy choices. Yet even some of those seemingly wholesome offerings contain chemical preservatives, pesticides, and artificial flavors and coloring that negatively affect your health. In What the Fork Are You Eating?, a practical guide written by certified chef and nutritionist Stefanie Sacks, MS, CNS, CDN, we learn exactly what the most offensive ingredients in our food are and how we can remove (or at least minimize) them in our diets. Sacks gives us an aisle-by-aisle rundown of how to shop for healthier items and create simple, nutritious, and delicious meals, including fifty original recipes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/">What the Fork are You Eating? : An Action Plan for Your Pantry and Plate &#8211; Stefanie Sacks, Foreword by Kathie Madonna Swift (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Paleo Manifesto : Ancient Wisdom for Lifelong Health &#8211; John Durant (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-paleo-manifesto-ancient-wisdom-for-lifelong-health-john-durant-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-paleo-manifesto-ancient-wisdom-for-lifelong-health-john-durant-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Paleo Manifesto: Ancient Wisdom for Lifelong Health, John Durant argues for an evolutionary &#8211; and revolutionary &#8211; approach to health. All animals, human or otherwise, thrive when they mimic key elements of life in their natural habitat. From diet to movement to sleep, this evolutionary perspective sheds light on some of our most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-paleo-manifesto-ancient-wisdom-for-lifelong-health-john-durant-abridged/">The Paleo Manifesto : Ancient Wisdom for Lifelong Health &#8211; John Durant (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Paleo Manifesto: Ancient Wisdom for Lifelong Health, John Durant argues for an evolutionary &#8211; and revolutionary &#8211; approach to health. All animals, human or otherwise, thrive when they mimic key elements of life in their natural habitat. From diet to movement to sleep, this evolutionary perspective sheds light on some of our most pressing health concerns. What is causing the rise of chronic conditions, such as obesity, diabetes, and depression? Is eating red meat going to kill you? Is avoiding the sun actually the best way to avoid skin cancer?     </p>
<p>                    Durant takes readers on a thrilling ride to the Paleolithic and beyond, unlocking the health secrets of our ancient ancestors. What do obese gorillas teach us about weight loss? How can Paleolithic skulls contain beautiful sets of teeth? Why is the Bible so obsessed with hygiene? What do NASA astronauts teach us about getting a good night&#8217;s sleep? And how are Silicon Valley techies hacking the human body?     </p>
<p>                    Blending science and culture, anthropology and philosophy, John Durant distills the lessons from his adventures and shows how to apply them to day-to-day life, teaching people how to construct their own personal &#8220;habitat&#8221; that will enable them to thrive. The book doesn&#8217;t just address what we eat, but why we eat it; not just how to exercise, but the purpose of functional movement; not just being healthy, but leading a purposeful life.     </p>
<p>                    Combining the best of ancient wisdom with cutting edge science, Durant crafts a vision of health that is both fresh and futuristic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-paleo-manifesto-ancient-wisdom-for-lifelong-health-john-durant-abridged/">The Paleo Manifesto : Ancient Wisdom for Lifelong Health &#8211; John Durant (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age. Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age.    </p>
<p>                              Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more than twenty years, he has been on a quest to find innovative, science-backed methods to upgrade human biology and redefine the limits of the mind, body, and spirit. The results speak for themselves. Now in his forties, Dave is smarter, happier, and more fit and successful than ever before.    </p>
<p>                              In Super Human, he shows how this is level of health and performance possible for all of us. While we assume we will peak in middle age and then decline, Asprey&#8217;s research reveals there is another way. It is possible to make changes on the sub-cellular level to dramatically extend life span. And the tools to live longer also give you more energy and brainpower right now.    </p>
<p>                              The answers lie in Dave&#8217;s Seven Pillars of Ageing that contribute to degeneration and disease while diminishing your performance in the moment. Using simple interventions &#8211; like diet, sleep, light, exercise, and little-known but powerful hacks from ozone therapy to proper jaw alignment, you can decelerate cellular ageing and supercharge your body&#8217;s ability to heal and rejuvenate.    </p>
<p>                              A self-proclaimed human guinea pig, Asprey arms readers with practical advice to maximize their lives at every age with his signature mix of science-geek wonder, candour, and enthusiasm. Getting older no longer has to mean decline. Now it&#8217;s an opportunity to become Super Human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wheat Belly : Lose the Wheat, Lose the Weight, and Find Your Path Back to Health &#8211; William Davis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Endocrinology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every day, over 200 million Americans consume food products made of wheat. As a result, over 100 million of them experience some form of adverse health effect, ranging from minor rashes and high blood sugar to the unattractive stomach bulges that preventive cardiologist William Davis calls &#8220;wheat bellies.&#8221; According to Davis, that excess fat has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/">Wheat Belly : Lose the Wheat, Lose the Weight, and Find Your Path Back to Health &#8211; William Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every day, over 200 million Americans consume food products made of wheat. As a result, over 100 million of them experience some form of adverse health effect, ranging from minor rashes and high blood sugar to the unattractive stomach bulges that preventive cardiologist William Davis calls &#8220;wheat bellies.&#8221; According to Davis, that excess fat has nothing to do with gluttony, sloth, or too much butter: It&#8217;s due to the whole grain wraps we eat for lunch. After witnessing over 2,000 patients regain their health after giving up wheat, Davis reached the disturbing conclusion that wheat is the single largest contributor to the nationwide obesity epidemic &#8211; and its elimination is key to dramatic weight loss and optimal health. In &#8220;Wheat Belly&#8221;, Davis exposes the harmful effects of what is actually a product of genetic tinkering and agribusiness being sold to the public as &#8220;wheat&#8221; &#8211; and provides readers with a user-friendly, step-by-step plan to navigate a new, wheat-free lifestyle.<br />
                    Informed by cutting-edge science and nutrition, along with case studies from men and women who have experienced life-changing transformations in their health after waving goodbye to wheat, &#8220;Wheat Belly&#8221; is an illuminating look at what is truly making people sick and an action plan to clear our plates of this seemingly benign ingredient.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/">Wheat Belly : Lose the Wheat, Lose the Weight, and Find Your Path Back to Health &#8211; William Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller from the author of How to Change Your Mind, The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, and Food Rules Food. There&#8217;s plenty of it around, and we all love to eat it. So why should anyone need to defend it? Because in the so-called Western diet, food has been replaced by nutrients, and common [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/">In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller from the author of How to Change Your Mind, The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, and Food Rules      </p>
<p>                     Food. There&#8217;s plenty of it around, and we all love to eat it. So why should anyone need to defend it?     </p>
<p>                     Because in the so-called Western diet, food has been replaced by nutrients, and common sense by confusion&#8211;most of what we&#8217;re consuming today is longer the product of nature but of food science. The result is what Michael Pollan calls the American Paradox: The more we worry about nutrition, the less healthy we see to become. With In Defense of Food, Pollan proposes a new (and very old) answer to the question of what we should eat that comes down to seven simple but liberating words: Eat food. Not too much. Mostly plants. Pollan&#8217;s bracing and eloquent manifesto shows us how we can start making thoughtful food choices that will enrich our lives, enlarge our sense of what it means to be healthy, and bring pleasure back to eating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/">In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4-Hour Body : An Uncommon Guide to Rapid Fat-loss, Incredible Sex and Becoming Superhuman &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to lose fat, double testosterone, get the perfect posterior or give your partner a fifteen-minute female orgasm? Whatever your physical goal, The 4-Hour Body eclipses every other health manual by sharing the best kept secrets in the latest science and research to provide new strategies for redesigning the human body. And you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">The 4-Hour Body : An Uncommon Guide to Rapid Fat-loss, Incredible Sex and Becoming Superhuman &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to lose fat, double testosterone, get the perfect posterior or give your partner a fifteen-minute female orgasm? Whatever your physical goal, The 4-Hour Body eclipses every other health manual by sharing the best kept secrets in the latest science and research to provide new strategies for redesigning the human body.     </p>
<p>                    And you don&#8217;t need to exhaust yourself. International bestselling author, Timothy Ferriss, helps you reach your true genetic potential in 3-6 months with a commitment of less than four hours per week. You can pick and choose from a menu of options, from simple to extreme, for dramatic body changes.     </p>
<p>                    Based on over 15 years of research and with personal stories, amazing before and after photos, recipes and sidebars, The 4-Hour Body will give unbelievable results and change the way you look forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">The 4-Hour Body : An Uncommon Guide to Rapid Fat-loss, Incredible Sex and Becoming Superhuman &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dreams & Their Interpretation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now! __________________________________________________________________________________ FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now!<br />
                    __________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver    </p>
<p>                    Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in his Sunday Times bestselling book, The 4 Pillar Plan, BBC One&#8217;s Dr Rangan Chatterjee creates an easily accessible plan for taking control of your health and your life.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Chatterjee believes that everyday health revolves around the following four pillars: relaxation, food, movement and sleep. By making small, achievable changes in each of these key areas you can create and maintain good health &#8211; and avoid illness. Top tips in each area include:     </p>
<p>                    * an electronic &#8216;sabbath&#8217; once a week<br />
                     * 12 hours every day without food<br />
                     * exposure to sunlight first thing each morning<br />
                     * walking at least 10,000 steps a day    </p>
<p>                    Based on cutting edge research and his own two decades&#8217; worth of experience as a doctor, this book contains fascinating case studies from real patients and is an inspiring and easy-to-follow guide to better health and happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nutrition and Physical Degeneration : A Comparison of Primitive and Modern Diets and Their Effects &#8211; Weston Price (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nutrition-and-physical-degeneration-a-comparison-of-primitive-and-modern-diets-and-their-effects-weston-price-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organic Gardening]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nutrition-and-physical-degeneration-a-comparison-of-primitive-and-modern-diets-and-their-effects-weston-price-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A compendium of ancestral wisdom, Weston Price&#8217;s &#8216;Nutrition and Physical Degeneration&#8217; is considered to be a masterpiece by many nutrition researchers who followed in his footsteps.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nutrition-and-physical-degeneration-a-comparison-of-primitive-and-modern-diets-and-their-effects-weston-price-abridged/">Nutrition and Physical Degeneration : A Comparison of Primitive and Modern Diets and Their Effects &#8211; Weston Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A compendium of ancestral wisdom, Weston Price&#8217;s &#8216;Nutrition and Physical Degeneration&#8217; is considered to be a masterpiece by many nutrition researchers who followed in his footsteps.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nutrition-and-physical-degeneration-a-comparison-of-primitive-and-modern-diets-and-their-effects-weston-price-abridged/">Nutrition and Physical Degeneration : A Comparison of Primitive and Modern Diets and Their Effects &#8211; Weston Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health    </p>
<p>                    Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, bacteria and human cells have co-existed in a relationship that has ensured the health and equilibrium of our body. But now, much like the natural world outside of us, our internal environment is being irrevocably destroyed. The culprit: some of our most revered medical advances &#8211; antibiotics &#8211; which appear to be linked to the epidemics of asthma, eczema, obesity, certain forms of cancer, and other diseases plaguing modern society.    </p>
<p>                    In a book that stands as the Silent Spring of its day, Blaser sounds a provocative alarm that we ignore at our peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It Starts With Food &#8211; Revised Edition : Discover the Whole30 and Change Your Life in Unexpected Ways &#8211; Dallas Hartwig, Melissa Hartwig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/it-starts-with-food-revised-edition-discover-the-whole30-and-change-your-life-in-unexpected-ways-dallas-hartwig-melissa-hartwig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/it-starts-with-food-revised-edition-discover-the-whole30-and-change-your-life-in-unexpected-ways-dallas-hartwig-melissa-hartwig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Food can change your life in unexpected ways. It Starts With Food will show you how by outlining a clear, balanced, sustainable plan to change the way you eat forever &#8211; and transform your life in unexpected ways. Your success story begins with The Whole30,&#8217; Dallas and Melissa Hartwig&#8217;s powerful 30-day nutritional reset. Since 2009, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-starts-with-food-revised-edition-discover-the-whole30-and-change-your-life-in-unexpected-ways-dallas-hartwig-melissa-hartwig-abridged/">It Starts With Food &#8211; Revised Edition : Discover the Whole30 and Change Your Life in Unexpected Ways &#8211; Dallas Hartwig, Melissa Hartwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Food can change your life in unexpected ways. It Starts With Food will show you how by outlining a clear, balanced, sustainable plan to change the way you eat forever &#8211; and transform your life in unexpected ways. Your success story begins with The Whole30,&#8217; Dallas and Melissa Hartwig&#8217;s powerful 30-day nutritional reset. Since 2009, their underground Whole30 program has quietly led tens of thousands of people to weight loss, improved quality of life and a healthier relationship with food.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-starts-with-food-revised-edition-discover-the-whole30-and-change-your-life-in-unexpected-ways-dallas-hartwig-melissa-hartwig-abridged/">It Starts With Food &#8211; Revised Edition : Discover the Whole30 and Change Your Life in Unexpected Ways &#8211; Dallas Hartwig, Melissa Hartwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, With Brendan Buhler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more. In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, With Brendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more.     </p>
<p>                    In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly within our intestines&#8211;has an astonishing impact on our lives. Your health, mood, sleep patterns, eating preferences&#8211;even your likelihood of getting bitten by mosquitoes&#8211;can be traced in part to the tiny creatures that live on and inside of us.     </p>
<p>                    In Follow Your Gut,  pioneering scientist Rob Knight pairs with award-winning science journalist Brendan Buhler to explain&#8211;with good humor and easy-to-grasp examples&#8211;why these new findings matter to everyone. They lead a detailed tour of the previously unseen world inside our bodies, calling out the diseases and conditions believed to be most directly impacted by them.     </p>
<p>                    With a practical eye toward deeper knowledge and better decisions, they also explore the known effects of antibiotics, probiotics, diet choice and even birth method on our children&#8217;s lifelong health. Ultimately, this pioneering book explains how to learn about your own microbiome and take steps toward understanding and improving your health, using the latest research as a guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, With Brendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking study that reveals how decades of misleading science and policy unjustly demonized the high-fat diet, which might actually be our healthiest option. For the past 60 years we have been told that a low-fat diet can protect against obesity, diabetes, and heart disease. Yet despite many of us taking this advice in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking study that reveals how decades of misleading science and policy unjustly demonized the high-fat diet, which<br />
                    might actually be our healthiest option.    </p>
<p>                    For the past 60 years we have been told that a low-fat diet can protect against obesity, diabetes, and heart disease. Yet despite<br />
                    many of us taking this advice in the developed West, we are now in the midst of an obesity epidemic that is breeding serious<br />
                    health problems.    </p>
<p>                    Recent more rigorous scientific work has overturned some of the shoddier theories of earlier decades to demonstrate conclusively that we have been needlessly avoiding red meat, cheese, whole milk, and eggs for decades, and that we can now, guilt-free, welcome these delicious foods back into our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Body Kindness : Transform Your Health from the Inside Out&#8211;and Never Say Diet Again &#8211; Rebecca Scritchfield (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/body-kindness-transform-your-health-from-the-inside-out-and-never-say-diet-again-rebecca-scritchfield-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/body-kindness-transform-your-health-from-the-inside-out-and-never-say-diet-again-rebecca-scritchfield-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is not a diet book &#8211; there are no menu plans or fitness routines here! Body Kindness addresses overall health (with a focus on both food and movement throughout) in four sections: What you do: the choices you make about food and nutrition, including mindful eating and eating with joy how you feel: your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/body-kindness-transform-your-health-from-the-inside-out-and-never-say-diet-again-rebecca-scritchfield-abridged/">Body Kindness : Transform Your Health from the Inside Out&#8211;and Never Say Diet Again &#8211; Rebecca Scritchfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is not a diet book &#8211; there are no menu plans or fitness routines here! Body Kindness addresses overall health (with a focus on both food and movement throughout) in four sections: What you do: the choices you make about food and nutrition, including mindful eating and eating with joy how you feel: your emotions, and how to change the voice in your head who you are: identifying your values and choices where you belong: finding your community each section includes inspiration as well as fun, scientifically based activities and exercises that focus on incremental, sustainable change. The exercises lead the emotions to &#8220;spiral up,&#8221; giving the reader insight and j rewards for positive change. The author makes a revolutionary yet scientifically proven declaration: You can lose weight only if you stop having weight loss as your goal. When you make choices about your health that are in line with your values, the result is a healthier body that you love. The goal of the book: to resolve the conflict where health and happiness diverge and help reconnect the two.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/body-kindness-transform-your-health-from-the-inside-out-and-never-say-diet-again-rebecca-scritchfield-abridged/">Body Kindness : Transform Your Health from the Inside Out&#8211;and Never Say Diet Again &#8211; Rebecca Scritchfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of The Willpower Instinct introduces a surprising science-based book that doesn&#8217;t tell us why we should exercise but instead shows us how to fall in love with movement. Exercise is health-enhancing and life-extending, yet many of us feel it&#8217;s a chore. But, as Kelly McGonigal reveals, it doesn&#8217;t have to be. Movement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of The Willpower Instinct introduces a surprising science-based book that doesn&#8217;t tell us why we should exercise but instead shows us how to fall in love with movement.    </p>
<p>                    Exercise is health-enhancing and life-extending, yet many of us feel it&#8217;s a chore. But, as Kelly McGonigal reveals, it doesn&#8217;t have to be. Movement can and should be a source of joy.    </p>
<p>                    Through her trademark blend of science and storytelling, McGonigal draws on insights from neuroscience, psychology, anthropology, and evolutionary biology, as well as memoirs, ethnographies, and philosophers. She shows how movement is intertwined with some of the most basic human joys, including self-expression, social connection, and mastery&#8211;and why it is a powerful antidote to the modern epidemics of depression, anxiety, and loneliness.    </p>
<p>                    McGonigal tells the stories of people who have found fulfillment and belonging through running, walking, dancing, swimming, weightlifting, and more, with examples that span the globe, from Tanzania, where one of the last hunter-gatherer tribes on the planet live, to a dance class at Juilliard for people with Parkinson&#8217;s disease, to the streets of London, where volunteers combine fitness and community service, to races in the remote wilderness, where athletes push the limits of what a human can endure. Along the way, McGonigal paints a portrait of human nature that highlights our capacity for hope, cooperation, and self-transcendence.    </p>
<p>                    The result is a revolutionary narrative that goes beyond familiar arguments in favor of exercise, to illustrate why movement is integral to both our happiness and our humanity. Readers will learn what they can do in their own lives and communities to harness the power of movement to create happiness, meaning, and connection.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grain Brain : The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar&#8211;Your Brain&#8217;s Silent Killers &#8211; David Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Allergies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The devastating truth about the effects of wheat, sugar, and carbs on the brain, with a 4-week plan to achieve optimum health. In Grain Brain, renowned neurologist David Perlmutter, MD, exposes a finding that&#8217;s been buried in the medical literature for far too long: carbs are destroying your brain. Even so-called healthy carbs like whole [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Grain Brain : The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar&#8211;Your Brain&#8217;s Silent Killers &#8211; David Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The devastating truth about the effects of wheat, sugar, and carbs on the brain, with a 4-week plan to achieve optimum health.     </p>
<p>                     In Grain Brain, renowned neurologist David Perlmutter, MD, exposes a finding that&#8217;s been buried in the medical literature for far too long: carbs are destroying your brain. Even so-called healthy carbs like whole grains can cause dementia, ADHD, epilepsy, anxiety, chronic headaches, depression, decreased libido, and much more.     </p>
<p>                     Groundbreaking and timely, Grain Brain shows that the fate of your brain is not in your genes. It&#8217;s in the food you eat. The cornerstone of all degenerative conditions, including brain disorders, is inflammation, which can be triggered by carbs, especially containing gluten or high in sugar. Dr. Perlmutter explains what happens when the brain encounters common ingredients in your daily bread and fruit bowls, how statin drugs may be erasing your memory, why a diet high in good fats is ideal, and how to spur the growth of new brain cells at any age.     </p>
<p>                     Dr. Perlmutter&#8217;s revolutionary 4-week plan shows you how to keep your brain healthy, vibrant, and sharp while dramatically reducing your risk for debilitating neurological diseases as well as relieving more common, everyday conditions &#8212; without drugs. Easy-to-follow strategies, delicious recipes, and weekly goals help you to put the plan into action. With a blend of anecdotes, cutting-edge research, and accessible, practical advice, Grain Brain teaches you how to take control of your smart genes, regain wellness, and enjoy lifelong health and vitality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Grain Brain : The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar&#8211;Your Brain&#8217;s Silent Killers &#8211; David Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice we receive from public health bodies is muddled, out of date, and frequently contradictory, and in many quarters still promotes the unproven hypothesis that fats are the greatest evil.    </p>
<p>                    With expert science and compelling storytelling, Gary Taubes investigates the history of nutritional science which, shaped by a handful of charismatic and misguided individuals, has for a hundred years denied the impact of sugar on our health. He exposes the powerful influence of the food industry which has lobbied for sugar&#8217;s ubiquity &#8211; the Sugar Association even today promoting &#8216;sugar&#8217;s goodness&#8217; &#8211;  and the extent that the industry has corrupted essential scientific research. He delves into the science of sugar, exposes conventional thinking that sugar is &#8217;empty calories&#8217; as a myth, and finds that its addictive pleasures are resulting in worldwide consumption as never experienced before, to devastating effect.     </p>
<p>                    The Case Against Sugar is a revelatory read, which will fundamentally change the way we eat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Addiction & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life    </p>
<p>                    We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can we kick bad habits &#8211; and stick with it?    </p>
<p>                    According to psychologist and behaviour researcher Dr Sean Young, the answer is to stop trying to change the person, and instead change the process. In Stick With It, Dr Young draws on his own research and that of other leading experts to explain how the mind often interferes with breaking bad habits, and how we can outsmart it, increasing the likelihood of lasting change by 200%.     </p>
<p>                    Packed with practical exercises and real-life case studies, Stick With It shows that it is possible to control spending, stick to a diet, exercise regularly and overcome problem behaviours &#8211; forever.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Scientifically grounded and personally implementable. It&#8217;s a winner&#8217; &#8211; Robert Cialdini, author of Influence and Pre-Suasion    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A must-read for anyone who&#8217;s been unable to keep a New Year&#8217;s resolution or failed at making a lasting change in any other area of their life or work. &#8211; Jonah Berger, author of Contagious    </p>
<p>                    Dr Sean Young is one of the world&#8217;s leading experts in the field of habit-forming. He is an acclaiedpsychologist and the founder and Executive Director of the UCLA Center for Digital Behavior. His research involves the study of cutting-edge ways of using social media and mobile technologies to change and predict human behaviour.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Diets Make Us Fat : the unintended consequences of our obsession with weight loss &#8211; Contributions by Sandra Aamodt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-diets-make-us-fat-the-unintended-consequences-of-our-obsession-with-weight-loss-contributions-by-sandra-aamodt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-diets-make-us-fat-the-unintended-consequences-of-our-obsession-with-weight-loss-contributions-by-sandra-aamodt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everything we know about dieting and weight loss is wrong. In the UK, almost two-thirds of adults are overweight. We think we know the answer: cut calories; eat less. We conclude that being fat is a failure of willpower, perhaps supplemented by a quirk of genetics. Yet research shows that losing weight by willpower alone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-diets-make-us-fat-the-unintended-consequences-of-our-obsession-with-weight-loss-contributions-by-sandra-aamodt-abridged/">Why Diets Make Us Fat : the unintended consequences of our obsession with weight loss &#8211; Contributions by Sandra Aamodt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything we know about dieting and weight loss is wrong.    </p>
<p>                    In the UK, almost two-thirds of adults are overweight. We think we know the answer: cut calories; eat less. We conclude that being fat is a failure of willpower, perhaps supplemented by a quirk of genetics. Yet research shows that losing weight by willpower alone is almost guaranteed to fail in the long run. In fact, there is no evidence that dieting improves long-term health, and some that suggests yo-yo dieting is more dangerous than being overweight.    </p>
<p>                    Combining deep research and brutal candour about her own experience as a yo-yo dieter, neuroscientist Sandra Aamodt explains the science of the obesity epidemic, including new findings about gut bacteria, why bariatric surgery works (it has more to do with your brain than your stomach), and what a real alternative to dieting and weight cycling might look like.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-diets-make-us-fat-the-unintended-consequences-of-our-obsession-with-weight-loss-contributions-by-sandra-aamodt-abridged/">Why Diets Make Us Fat : the unintended consequences of our obsession with weight loss &#8211; Contributions by Sandra Aamodt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat to Live : The Amazing Nutrient-Rich Program for Fast and Sustained Weight Loss &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hailed a &#8220;medical breakthrough&#8221; by Dr. Mehmet Oz, Eat to Live offers a highly effective, scientifically proven way to lose weight quickly. The key to Dr. Joel Fuhrman&#8217;s revolutionary six-week plan is simple: health = nutrients / calories. When the ratio of nutrients to calories in the food you eat is high, you lose weight. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Eat to Live : The Amazing Nutrient-Rich Program for Fast and Sustained Weight Loss &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hailed a &#8220;medical breakthrough&#8221; by Dr. Mehmet Oz, Eat to Live offers a highly effective, scientifically proven way to lose weight quickly.     </p>
<p>                     The key to Dr. Joel Fuhrman&#8217;s revolutionary six-week plan is simple: health = nutrients / calories. When the ratio of nutrients to calories in the food you eat is high, you lose weight. The more nutrient-dense food you eat, the less you crave fat, sweets, and high-caloric foods.     </p>
<p>                    Eat to Live has been revised to include inspiring success stories from people who have used the program to lose shockingly large amounts of weight and recover from life-threatening illnesses; Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s nutrient density index; up-to-date scientific research supporting the principles behind Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s plan; new recipes and meal ideas; and much more. This easy-to-follow, nutritionally sound diet can help anyone shed pounds quickly-and keep them off.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Furhman&#8217;s formula is simple, safe, and solid.&#8221; &#8211;Body and Soul</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Eat to Live : The Amazing Nutrient-Rich Program for Fast and Sustained Weight Loss &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle, from the bestselling author of How Not to Die. Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle,  from the bestselling author of How Not to Die.    </p>
<p>                    Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any happier or healthier. As obesity rates and associated disease and impairments continue to rise, it&#8217;s time for a different approach.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet is a treasure trove of buried data and cutting-edge dietary research that Dr Michael Greger has translated into accessible, actionable advice with exciting tools and tricks that will help you to safely lose weight and eliminate unwanted body fat &#8211; for good.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Greger, renowned nutrition expert, physician, and founder of the NutritionFacts website, explores the many causes of obesity &#8211; from our genes to the portions on our plate to other environmental factors &#8211; and the many consequences, from diabetes to cancer to mental health issues. From there, Dr Greger breaks down a variety of approaches to weight loss, honing in on the optimal criteria that enable success, including: a diet high in fibre and water, a diet low in fat, salt, and sugar, and diet full of anti-inflammatory foods.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet then goes beyond food to explore the many other weight-loss accelerators available to us in our body&#8217;s systems, revealing how plant-based meals can be eaten at specific times to maximize our bodies&#8217; natural fat-burning activities. Dr Greger provides a clear plan not only for the ultimate weight loss diet, but also the approach we must take to unlock its greatest efficacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diabetes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FROM NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR DR. JASON FUNG * &#8220;The doctor who invented intermittent fasting.&#8221;-The Daily Mail &#8220;Dr. Fung reveals how [type 2 diabetes] can be prevented and also reversed using natural dietary methods instead of medications &#8230; This is an important and timely book. Highly recommended.&#8221;-Dr. Mark Hyman, author of The Pegan Diet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FROM NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR DR. JASON FUNG * &#8220;The doctor who invented intermittent fasting.&#8221;-The Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Fung reveals how [type 2 diabetes] can be prevented and also reversed using natural dietary methods instead of medications &#8230; This is an important and timely book. Highly recommended.&#8221;-Dr. Mark Hyman, author of The Pegan Diet    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Jason Fung has done it again. &#8230; Get this book!&#8221;-Dr. Steven R. Gundry, author of The Plant Paradox    </p>
<p>                    Everything you believe about treating type 2 diabetes is wrong. Today, most doctors, dietitians, and even diabetes specialists consider type 2 diabetes to be a chronic and progressive disease-a life sentence with no possibility of parole. But the truth, as Dr. Fung reveals in this groundbreaking book, is that type 2 diabetes is reversible.     </p>
<p>                    Writing with clear, persuasive language, Dr. Fung explains why conventional treatments that rely on insulin or other blood-glucose-lowering drugs can actually exacerbate the problem, leading to significant weight gain and even heart disease. The only way to treat type 2 diabetes effectively, he argues, is proper dieting and intermittent fasting-not medication.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Diabetes Code is unabashedly provocative yet practical &#8230; a clear blueprint for everyone to take control of their blood sugar, their health, and their lives.&#8221;- Dr. Will Cole, author of Intuitive Fasting</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From world-renowned health expert and New York Times bestselling author of Eat to Live and Eat for Life Dr. Joel Fuhrman comes a practical nutritional plan to prevent and reverse disease&#8211;no shots, drugs or sick days required. Why do some of us get sick with greater frequency than others? What makes us more susceptible to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From world-renowned health expert and New York Times bestselling author of Eat to Live and Eat for Life Dr. Joel Fuhrman comes a practical nutritional plan to prevent and reverse disease&#8211;no shots, drugs or sick days required.    </p>
<p>                     Why do some of us get sick with greater frequency than others? What makes us more susceptible to illness? Is there a secret to staying healthy? Dr. Fuhrman doesn&#8217;t believe the secret to staying healthy lies in medical care&#8211;rather, the solution is to change the way we eat.    </p>
<p>                     With more than 85 plant-based recipes, a two-week menu plan, and lists of super foods that boost immunity, Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s proven strategies in Super Immunity combine the latest data from clinical tests, nutritional research, and results from thousands of patients .    </p>
<p>                    Inside Super Immunity, you&#8217;ll find: The big picture&#8211;Learn everything you need to know about healthy eating for a healthy life.A 2-week meal plan&#8211;Take the guesswork out of changing your diet with planned meals for breakfast, lunch, and dinner every day of the week.85 immunity-boosting recipes&#8211;These delicious plant based recipes make eating healthy easy and crave-worthy.    </p>
<p>                     Live longer, stronger, and disease free with this proven plan to change your diet and change your life.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Super Immunity is a much needed book that contains the key to ending the cycle of sickness that plagues many of our lives. This is enlightened medicine, at last!&#8221; (Dr. Alejandro Junger, New York Times bestselling author of CLEAN)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
