<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Classic Science Fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/classic-science-fiction/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/classic-science-fiction/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Classic Science Fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/classic-science-fiction/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Animal Farm : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</title>
		<link>/animal-farm-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/animal-farm-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The perfect edition for any Orwell enthusiasts&#8217; collection, discover Orwell&#8217;s classic dystopian masterpiece beautifully reimagined by renowned street artist Shepard Fairey &#8216;All animals are equal. But some animals are more equal than others.&#8217; Mr Jones of Manor Farm is so lazy and drunken that one day he forgets to feed his livestock. The ensuing rebellion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/animal-farm-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/">Animal Farm : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The perfect edition for any Orwell enthusiasts&#8217; collection, discover Orwell&#8217;s classic dystopian masterpiece beautifully reimagined by renowned street artist Shepard Fairey</p>
<p>                     &#8216;All animals are equal. But some animals are more equal than others.&#8217;</p>
<p>                     Mr Jones of Manor Farm is so lazy and drunken that one day he forgets to feed his livestock. The ensuing rebellion under the leadership of the pigs Napoleon and Snowball leads to the animals taking over the farm. Vowing to eliminate the terrible inequities of the farmyard, the renamed Animal Farm is organised to benefit all who walk on four legs. But as time passes, the ideals of the rebellion are corrupted, then forgotten. And something new and unexpected emerges. . .</p>
<p>                     First published in 1945, Animal Farm &#8211; the history of a revolution that went wrong &#8211; is George Orwell&#8217;s brilliant satire on the corrupting influence of power.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Remains our great satire of the darker face of modern history&#8217; Malcolm Bradbury </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prophet who thought the unthinkable and spoke the unspeakable, even when it offended conventional thought&#8217; Daily Express</p>
<p>                    &#8216;As valid today as it was fifty years ago&#8217; Ralph Steadman</p>
<p>                    COMPLETE THE TRIO WITH SHEPARD FAIREY&#8217;S NEW-LOOK 1984 AND DOWN AND OUT IN PARIS AND LONDON.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/animal-farm-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/">Animal Farm : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave New World &#8211; Aldous Huxley</title>
		<link>/brave-new-world-aldous-huxley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-new-world-aldous-huxley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With introductions by Margaret Atwood and David Bradshaw. Far in the future, the World Controllers have created the ideal society. Through clever use of genetic engineering, brainwashing and recreational sex and drugs all its members are happy consumers. Bernard Marx seems alone harbouring an ill-defined longing to break free. A visit to one of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-world-aldous-huxley/">Brave New World &#8211; Aldous Huxley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With introductions by Margaret Atwood and David Bradshaw. Far in the future, the World Controllers have created the ideal society. Through clever use of genetic engineering, brainwashing and recreational sex and drugs all its members are happy consumers. Bernard Marx seems alone harbouring an ill-defined longing to break free. A visit to one of the few remaining Savage Reservations where the old, imperfect life still continues, may be the cure for his distress&#8230;Huxley&#8217;s ingenious fantasy of the future sheds a blazing light on the present and is considered to be his most enduring masterpiece.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-world-aldous-huxley/">Brave New World &#8211; Aldous Huxley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Stand &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-stand-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-stand-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s apocalyptic vision of a world blasted by virus and tangled in an elemental struggle between good and evil remains as riveting and eerily plausible as when it was first published. Soon to be a television series. &#8216;THE STAND is a masterpiece&#8217; (Guardian). Set in a virus-decimated US, King&#8217;s thrilling American fantasy epic, is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stand-stephen-king/">The Stand &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s apocalyptic vision of a world blasted by virus and tangled in an elemental struggle between good and evil remains as riveting and eerily plausible as when it was first published.</p>
<p>                    Soon to be a television series.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;THE STAND is a masterpiece&#8217; (Guardian). Set in a virus-decimated US, King&#8217;s thrilling American fantasy epic, is a Classic.</p>
<p>                    First come the days of the virus. Then come the dreams.</p>
<p>                    Dark dreams that warn of the coming of the dark man. The apostate of death, his worn-down boot heels tramping the night roads. The warlord of the charnel house and Prince of Evil.</p>
<p>                    His time is at hand. His empire grows in the west and the Apocalypse looms.</p>
<p>                    When a man crashes his car into a petrol station, he brings with him the foul corpses of his wife and daughter. He dies and it doesn&#8217;t take long for the virus which killed him to spread across America and the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stand-stephen-king/">The Stand &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dune Messiah &#8211; Frank Herbert</title>
		<link>/dune-messiah-frank-herbert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dune-messiah-frank-herbert/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The extraordinary sequel to Dune, the greatest science fiction novel of all time. Twelve years after his victory over House Harkonnen, Paul Atreides rules as emperor from the desert planet Arrakis &#8211; but his victory has had profound consequences. War has been brought to the entire known universe, and billions have already perished. Despite having [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dune-messiah-frank-herbert/">Dune Messiah &#8211; Frank Herbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The extraordinary sequel to Dune, the greatest science fiction novel of all time. </p>
<p>                    Twelve years after his victory over House Harkonnen, Paul Atreides rules as emperor from the desert planet Arrakis &#8211; but his victory has had profound consequences. War has been brought to the entire known universe, and billions have already perished. Despite having become the most powerful emperor known to history, Paul is powerless to bring an end to the fighting.</p>
<p>                    While former allies conspire to dethrone Paul and even his own consort acts against him, Paul accepts a gift from the Tleilaxu, a guild of genetic manipulators, hoping to find a single spark of peace and friendship amidst the betrayal and chaos. But this act undermines Paul&#8217;s support from the Fremen, his own people. The Fremen are the true source of Paul&#8217;s power; losing them is the one thing that could truly topple his empire.</p>
<p>                    As matters escalate, Paul will be forced to chose between his throne, his wife, his people and his future &#8211; and the future of the entire universe.</p>
<p>                    An epic novel of the cost of victory . . . and the price of war.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brilliant . . . it is all that Dune was, and maybe a little more.&#8217; Galaxy Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dune-messiah-frank-herbert/">Dune Messiah &#8211; Frank Herbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1984 : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</title>
		<link>/1984-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/1984-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The perfect edition for any Orwell enthusiasts&#8217; collection, discover the classic dystopian masterpiece beautifully reimagined by renowned street artist Shepard Fairey Winston Smith works for the Ministry of Truth in London, chief city of Airstrip One. Big Brother stares out from every poster, the Thought Police uncover every act of betrayal. When Winston finds love [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/1984-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/">1984 : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The perfect edition for any Orwell enthusiasts&#8217; collection, discover the classic dystopian masterpiece beautifully reimagined by renowned street artist Shepard Fairey</p>
<p>                     Winston Smith works for the Ministry of Truth in London, chief city of Airstrip One. Big Brother stares out from every poster, the Thought Police uncover every act of betrayal. When Winston finds love with Julia, he discovers that life does not have to be dull and deadening, and awakens to new possibilities. Despite the police helicopters that hover and circle overhead, Winston and Julia begin to question the Party; they are drawn towards conspiracy. Yet Big Brother will not tolerate dissent &#8211; even in the mind. For those with original thoughts they invented Room 101. . .</p>
<p>                     First published in 1949, 1984 is George Orwell&#8217;s terrifying vision of a totalitarian future in which everything and everyone is slave to a tyrannical regime.</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Right up there among my favourite books . . . I read it again and again&#8217; Margaret Atwood</p>
<p>                     &#8216;More relevant to today than almost any other book that you can think of&#8217; Jo Brand</p>
<p>                    COMPLETE THE TRIO WITH SHEPARD FAIREY&#8217;S NEW-LOOK ANIMAL FARM AND DOWN AND OUT IN PARIS AND LONDON.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/1984-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/">1984 : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man in the High Castle &#8211; Philip K. Dick</title>
		<link>/the-man-in-the-high-castle-philip-k-dick/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-in-the-high-castle-philip-k-dick/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A dazzling speculative novel of &#8216;counterfactual history&#8217; from one of America&#8217;s most highly-regarded science fiction authors, Philip K. Dick&#8217;s The Man in the High Castle includes an introduction by Eric Brown in Penguin Modern Classics. Philip K. Dick&#8217;s acclaimed cult novel gives us a horrifying glimpse of an alternative world &#8211; one where the Allies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-in-the-high-castle-philip-k-dick/">The Man in the High Castle &#8211; Philip K. Dick</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A dazzling speculative novel of &#8216;counterfactual history&#8217; from one of America&#8217;s most highly-regarded science fiction authors, Philip K. Dick&#8217;s The Man in the High Castle includes an introduction by Eric Brown in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    Philip K. Dick&#8217;s acclaimed cult novel gives us a horrifying glimpse of an alternative world &#8211; one where the Allies have lost the Second World War. In this nightmare dystopia the Nazis have taken over New York, the Japanese control California and the African continent is virtually wiped out. In a neutral buffer zone in America that divides the world&#8217;s new rival superpowers, lives the author of an underground bestseller. His book offers a new vision of reality &#8211; an alternative theory of world history in which the Axis powers were defeated &#8211; giving hope to the disenchanted. Does &#8216;reality&#8217; lie with him, or is his world just one among many others?</p>
<p>                    Philip Kindred Dick (1928-82) was born in Chicago in 1928. His career as a science fiction writer comprised an early burst of short stories followed by a stream of novels, typically character studies incorporating androids, drugs, and hallucinations. His best works are generally agreed to be The Man in the High Castle and Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?, the inspiration for the movie Blade Runner.</p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed The Man in the High Castle, you might like Yevgeny Zamyatin&#8217;s We, also available in Penguin Classics.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The most brilliant science fiction mind on any planet&#8217;<br />
                    Rolling Stone</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Dick&#8217;s finest book, and one of the very best science fiction novels ever published&#8217;<br />
                    Eric Brown</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-in-the-high-castle-philip-k-dick/">The Man in the High Castle &#8211; Philip K. Dick</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
