<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Giving Up Smoking Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/giving-up-smoking/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/giving-up-smoking/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Giving Up Smoking Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/giving-up-smoking/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Easy Way for Women to Stop Smoking &#8211; Allen Carr</title>
		<link>/the-easy-way-for-women-to-stop-smoking-allen-carr/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Giving Up Smoking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-easy-way-for-women-to-stop-smoking-allen-carr/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In the Easy Way for Women to Stop Smoking Allen Carr addresses the difficulties that women smokers face when trying to quit, and shows how his technique successfully resolves them. Allen&#8217;s unique method removes the feeling of deprivation and works without using willpower. This book can enable any woman to escape the nicotine trap easily, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-easy-way-for-women-to-stop-smoking-allen-carr/">The Easy Way for Women to Stop Smoking &#8211; Allen Carr</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In the Easy Way for Women to Stop Smoking Allen Carr addresses the difficulties that women smokers face when trying to quit, and shows how his technique successfully resolves them. Allen&#8217;s unique method removes the feeling of deprivation and works without using willpower. This book can enable any woman to escape the nicotine trap easily, painlessly and permanently without putting on weight.&#8221;&#8211;Back cover.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-easy-way-for-women-to-stop-smoking-allen-carr/">The Easy Way for Women to Stop Smoking &#8211; Allen Carr</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</title>
		<link>/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Giving Up Smoking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Respiratory Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Funding & Policy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19. Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19.    </p>
<p>                    Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns and border closings causing widespread business closures, economic collapse, and massive unemployment; and an unprecedented curtailment of civil liberties and freedoms in the name of keeping people safe by locking them up in their homes.    </p>
<p>                    We are now living in a world that is increasingly ruled, not by our democratic systems and institutions, but by public health fiat, carried out by politicians who rule by instilling fear and panic.    </p>
<p>                    In The Truth About COVID-19, Dr. Mercola and Cummins reveal new and emerging evidence that:    </p>
<p>                    The SARS-CoV-2 virus was, indeed, lab-engineered and emerged from a negligently managed bioweapons lab in Wuhan, China<br />
                    The global pandemic was long anticipated by global elites who have used it to facilitate and hide the largest upward transfer of wealth in human history<br />
                    PCR testing, case counts, morbidity, and vaccine safety and efficacy data have been widely manipulated and misrepresented<br />
                    Obesity, diabetes, and heart disease are known to worsen COVID-19 outcomes, but the junk food industry continues to push its agenda at the expense of public health<br />
                    Safe, simple, and inexpensive treatment and prevention for COVID-19 have been censored and suppressed to create a clear path for vaccine acceptance<br />
                    Effectiveness of the vaccines has been wildly exaggerated and major safety questions have gone unanswered    </p>
<p>                    The good news in all of this is that we can take control of our health and that, together, we have the power to unite and fight back for our health, democracy, and freedom. The time is now for a global awakening. As Dr. Mercola and Cummins remind us, this is the fight of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
