<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Human-computer Interaction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/human-computer-interaction/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/human-computer-interaction/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Human-computer Interaction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/human-computer-interaction/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Superintelligence : Paths, Dangers, Strategies &#8211; Nick Bostrom</title>
		<link>/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Risk Assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The human brain has some capabilities that the brains of other animals lack. It is to these distinctive capabilities that our species owes its dominant position. Other animals have stronger muscles or sharper claws, but we have cleverer brains. If machine brains one day come to surpass human brains in general intelligence, then this new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/">Superintelligence : Paths, Dangers, Strategies &#8211; Nick Bostrom</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The human brain has some capabilities that the brains of other animals lack. It is to these distinctive capabilities that our species owes its dominant position. Other animals have stronger muscles or sharper claws, but we have cleverer brains.     </p>
<p>                    If machine brains one day come to surpass human brains in general intelligence, then this new superintelligence could become very powerful. As the fate of the gorillas now depends more on us humans than on the gorillas themselves, so the fate of our species then would come to depend on the actions of the machine superintelligence.     </p>
<p>                    But we have one advantage: we get to make the first move. Will it be possible to construct a seed AI or otherwise to engineer initial conditions so as to make an intelligence explosion survivable? How could one achieve a controlled detonation?     </p>
<p>                    To get closer to an answer to this question, we must make our way through a fascinating landscape of topics and considerations. Read the book and learn about oracles, genies, singletons; about boxing methods, tripwires, and mind crime; about humanity&#8217;s cosmic endowment and differential technological development; indirect normativity, instrumental convergence, whole brain emulation and technology couplings; Malthusian economics and dystopian evolution; artificial intelligence, and biological<br />
                    cognitive enhancement, and collective intelligence.     </p>
<p>                    This profoundly ambitious and original book picks its way carefully through a vast tract of forbiddingly difficult intellectual terrain. Yet the writing is so lucid that it somehow makes it all seem easy. After an utterly engrossing journey that takes us to the frontiers of thinking about the human condition and the future of intelligent life, we find in Nick Bostrom&#8217;s work nothing less than a reconceptualization of the essential task of our time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/">Superintelligence : Paths, Dangers, Strategies &#8211; Nick Bostrom</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Humility Is the New Smart &#8211; Edward D. Hess, Katherine Ludwig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Humility Is the New Smart Your job is at risk&#8211;if not now, then soon. We are on the leading edge of a Smart Machine Age led by artificial intelligence that will be as transformative for us as the Industrial Revolution was for our ancestors. Smart machines will take over millions of jobs in manufacturing, office [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/">Humility Is the New Smart &#8211; Edward D. Hess, Katherine Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Humility Is the New Smart     </p>
<p>                     Your job is at risk&#8211;if not now, then soon. We are on the leading edge of a Smart Machine Age led by artificial intelligence that will be as transformative for us as the Industrial Revolution was for our ancestors. Smart machines will take over millions of jobs in manufacturing, office work, the service sector, the professions, you name it. Not only can they know more data and analyze it faster than any mere human, say Edward Hess and Katherine Ludwig, but smart machines are free of the emotional, psychological, and cultural baggage that so often mars human thinking.     </p>
<p>                     So we can&#8217;t beat &#8217;em and we can&#8217;t join &#8217;em. To stay relevant, we have to play a different game. Hess and Ludwig offer us that game plan. We need to excel at critical, creative, and innovative thinking and at genuinely engaging with others&#8211;things machines can&#8217;t do well. The key is to change our definition of what it means to be smart. Hess and Ludwig call it being NewSmart. In this extraordinarily timely book, they offer detailed guidance for developing NewSmart attitudes and four critical behaviors that will help us adapt to the new reality.     </p>
<p>                     The crucial mindset underlying NewSmart is humility&#8211;not self-effacement but an accurate self-appraisal: acknowledging you can&#8217;t have all the answers, remaining open to new ideas, and committing yourself to lifelong learning. Drawing on extensive multidisciplinary research, Hess and Ludwig emphasize that the key to success in this new era is not to be more like the machines but to excel at the best of what makes us human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/">Humility Is the New Smart &#8211; Edward D. Hess, Katherine Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lean UX is synonymous with modern product design and development. By combining human-centric design, agile ways of working, and a strong business sense, designers, product managers, developers, and scrum masters around the world are making Lean UX the leading approach for digital product teams today In the third edition of this award-winning book, authors Jeff [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/">Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lean UX is synonymous with modern product design and development. By combining human-centric design, agile ways of working, and a strong business sense, designers, product managers, developers, and scrum masters around the world are making Lean UX the leading approach for digital product teams today    </p>
<p>                    In the third edition of this award-winning book, authors Jeff Gothelf and Josh Seiden help you focus on the product experience rather than deliverables. You&#8217;ll learn tactics for integrating user experience design, product discovery, agile methods, and product management. And you&#8217;ll discover how to drive your design in short, iterative cycles to assess what works best for businesses and users. Lean UX guides you through this change&#8211;for the better.    </p>
<p>                    Facilitate the Lean UX process with your team with the Lean UX Canvas<br />
                    Ensure every project starts with clear customer-centric success criteria<br />
                    Understand the role of the designer on an agile team<br />
                    Write and contribute design and experiment stories to the backlog<br />
                    Ensure design work takes place in every sprint<br />
                    Build product discovery into the team&#8217;s &#8220;velocity&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/">Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where Will Man Take Us? : The bold story of the man technology is creating &#8211; Atul Jalan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/where-will-man-take-us-the-bold-story-of-the-man-technology-is-creating-atul-jalan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/where-will-man-take-us-the-bold-story-of-the-man-technology-is-creating-atul-jalan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first person who will live to be 150 years old has already been born. The screen that we peer into will soon be within us. We could soon be taking happiness pills before breakfast. The perfect partner might need to be charged before bed. This is a new world we are walking into. And [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/where-will-man-take-us-the-bold-story-of-the-man-technology-is-creating-atul-jalan-abridged/">Where Will Man Take Us? : The bold story of the man technology is creating &#8211; Atul Jalan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first person who will live to be 150 years old has already been born.<br />
                    The screen that we peer into will soon be within us.<br />
                    We could soon be taking happiness pills before breakfast.<br />
                    The perfect partner might need to be charged before bed.    </p>
<p>                    This is a new world we are walking into. And the man who began this journey won&#8217;t be the man who ends this journey. Where Will Man Take Us? explores the changes technology is bringing about in us-as a society and as a species. What will the next generation turn into, what will it be like, how will the new Adam and Eve live and love?<br />
                    In this book, Atul Jalan tackles nanotechnology, artificial intelligence, quantum computing and genetics, seamlessly weaving the future of technology with the changing dynamics of human love, morality and ethics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/where-will-man-take-us-the-bold-story-of-the-man-technology-is-creating-atul-jalan-abridged/">Where Will Man Take Us? : The bold story of the man technology is creating &#8211; Atul Jalan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Surveillance Capitalism : The Fight for a Human Future at the New Frontier of Power: Barack Obama&#8217;s Books of 2019 &#8211; Professor Shoshana Zuboff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 10 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER A NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOK OF THE YEAR ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S TOP BOOKS OF THE YEAR Shortlisted for The Orwell Prize 2020 Shortlisted for the FT Business Book of the Year Award 2019 &#8216;Easily the most important book to be published this century. I find it hard [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/">The Age of Surveillance Capitalism : The Fight for a Human Future at the New Frontier of Power: Barack Obama&#8217;s Books of 2019 &#8211; Professor Shoshana Zuboff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 10 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S TOP BOOKS OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for The Orwell Prize 2020    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT Business Book of the Year Award 2019    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Easily the most  important book to be published this  century. I find it hard to take any  young activist seriously who hasn&#8217;t  at least familarised themselves  with Zuboff&#8217;s central ideas.&#8217; &#8211; Zadie Smith, The Guardian    </p>
<p>                    The challenges to humanity posed by the digital future, the first detailed examination of the unprecedented form of power called &#8220;surveillance capitalism,&#8221; and the quest by powerful corporations to predict and control us.    </p>
<p>                    The heady optimism of the Internet&#8217;s early days is gone. Technologies that were meant to liberate us have deepened inequality and stoked divisions. Tech companies gather our information online and sell it to the highest bidder, whether government or retailer. Profits now depend not only on predicting our behaviour but modifying it too. How will this fusion of capitalism and the digital shape our values and define our future?    </p>
<p>                    Shoshana Zuboff shows that we are at a crossroads. We still have the power to decide what kind of world we want to live in, and what we decide now will shape the rest of the century. Our choices: allow technology to enrich the few and impoverish the many, or harness it and distribute its benefits.    </p>
<p>                     The Age of Surveillance Capitalism is a deeply-reasoned examination of the threat of unprecedented power free from democratic oversight. As it explores this new capitalism&#8217;s impact on society, politics, business, and technology, it exposes the struggles that will decide both the next chapter of capitalism and the meaning of information civilization. Most critically, it shows how we can protect ourselves and our communities and ensure we are the masters of the digital rather than its slaves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/">The Age of Surveillance Capitalism : The Fight for a Human Future at the New Frontier of Power: Barack Obama&#8217;s Books of 2019 &#8211; Professor Shoshana Zuboff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Will the workplace of the future be overrun by machines and robots? Are the new frontiers of artificial intelligence (AI) on the cusp of dethroning us in efficiency, intelligence and innovative potential? Automation and AI will augment our human world and potential. The winners of the future of work are those that harness the power [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/">Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will the workplace of the future be overrun by machines and robots? Are the new frontiers of artificial intelligence (AI) on the cusp of dethroning us in efficiency, intelligence and innovative potential? Automation and AI will augment our human world and potential.     </p>
<p>                    The winners of the future of work are those that harness the power of machines to their advantage. Human/Machine is the only guide you need to understand the fourth industrial revolution. It sets out a road map to the challenges ahead, but also unlocks the wondrous opportunities that it offers.     </p>
<p>                    Human/Machine explores how we will work symbiotically with machines, detailing how institutions, companies, individuals and education providers will evolve to integrate seamlessly with new technologies. With exclusive case studies, this book offers a glimpse into the future and details how top companies are already thriving on this very special relationship. From gamification in job training to project management teams integrated with bots and predictive technologies that fix problems in the supply chain before they happen, the authors deliver a powerful manifesto for the adoption and celebration of automation and AI. In a much more fluid, skills-based economy, we will all need to prove our worth and future-proof our skills base. This book offers a blueprint to avoid being left behind and unearth the opportunities unique to human-machine partnership ecosystems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/">Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way we live. Kurzweil&#8217;s prophetic blueprint for the future takes us through the advances that inexorably result in computers exceeding the memory capacity and computational ability of the human brain by the year 2020 (with human-level capabilities not far behind); in relationships with automated personalities who will be our teachers, companions, and lovers; and in information fed straight into our brains along direct neural pathways. Optimistic and challenging, thought-provoking and engaging, The Age of Spiritual Machines is the ultimate guide on our road into the next century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets. Welcome to 2011. Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to 2011.    </p>
<p>                    Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers are following your every click. Your computer monitor is becoming a one-way mirror, reflecting your interests and reinforcing your prejudices.    </p>
<p>                    The internet is no longer a free, independent space. It is commercially controlled and ever more personalised. The Filter Bubble reveals how this hidden web is starting to control our lives &#8211; and shows what we can do about it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
