<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Econometrics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/econometrics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/econometrics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Econometrics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/econometrics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Predictive Analytics : The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die &#8211; Eric Siegel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Mesmerizing &#038; fascinating&#8230;&#8221; -The Seattle Post-Intelligencer &#8220;The Freakonomics of big data.&#8221; -Stein Kretsinger, founding executive of Advertising.com Award-winning &#124; Used by over 30 universities &#124; Translated into 9 languages An introduction for everyone. In this rich, fascinating &#8211; surprisingly accessible &#8211; introduction, leading expert Eric Siegel reveals how predictive analytics (aka machine learning) works, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/">Predictive Analytics : The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die &#8211; Eric Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Mesmerizing &#038; fascinating&#8230;&#8221; -The Seattle Post-Intelligencer    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Freakonomics of big data.&#8221; -Stein Kretsinger, founding executive of Advertising.com    </p>
<p>                     Award-winning | Used by over 30 universities | Translated into 9 languages    </p>
<p>                     An introduction for everyone. In this rich, fascinating &#8211; surprisingly accessible &#8211; introduction, leading expert Eric Siegel reveals how predictive analytics (aka machine learning) works, and how it affects everyone every day. Rather than a &#8220;how to&#8221; for hands-on techies, the book serves lay readers and experts alike by covering new case studies and the latest state-of-the-art techniques.    </p>
<p>                     Prediction is booming. It reinvents industries and runs the world. Companies, governments, law enforcement, hospitals, and universities are seizing upon the power. These institutions predict whether you&#8217;re going to click, buy, lie, or die.    </p>
<p>                    Why? For good reason: predicting human behavior combats risk, boosts sales, fortifies healthcare, streamlines manufacturing, conquers spam, optimizes social networks, toughens crime fighting, and wins elections.    </p>
<p>                    How? Prediction is powered by the world&#8217;s most potent, flourishing unnatural resource: data. Accumulated in large part as the by-product of routine tasks, data is the unsalted, flavorless residue deposited en masse as organizations churn away. Surprise! This heap of refuse is a gold mine. Big data embodies an extraordinary wealth of experience from which to learn.    </p>
<p>                    Predictive analytics(aka machine learning) unleashes the power of data. With this technology, the computer literally learns from data how to predict the future behavior of individuals. Perfect prediction is not possible, but putting odds on the future drives millions of decisions more effectively, determining whom to call, mail, investigate, incarcerate, set up on a date, or medicate.    </p>
<p>                    In this lucid, captivating introduction &#8211; now in its Revised and Updated edition &#8211; former Columbia University professor and Predictive Analytics World founder Eric Siegel reveals the power and perils of prediction:    </p>
<p>                    What type of mortgage risk Chase Bank predicted before the recession.<br />
                    Predicting which people will drop out of school, cancel a subscription, or get divorced before they even know it themselves.<br />
                    Why early retirement predicts a shorter life expectancy and vegetarians miss fewer flights.<br />
                    Five reasons why organizations predict death &#8211; including one health insurance company.<br />
                    How U.S. Bank and Obama for America calculated the way to most strongly persuade each individual.<br />
                    Why the NSA wants all your data: machine learning supercomputers to fight terrorism.<br />
                    How IBM&#8217;s Watson computer used predictive modeling to answer questions and beat the human champs on TV&#8217;s Jeopardy!<br />
                    How companies ascertain untold, private truths &#8211; how Target figures out you&#8217;re pregnant and Hewlett-Packard deduces you&#8217;re about to quit your job.<br />
                    How judges and parole boards rely on crime-predicting computers to decide how long convicts remain in prison.<br />
                    182 examples from Airbnb, the BBC, Citibank, ConEd, Facebook, Ford, Google, the IRS, LinkedIn, Match.com, MTV, Netflix, PayPal, Pfizer, Spotify, Uber, UPS, Wikipedia, and more.    </p>
<p>                     How does predictive analytics work? This jam-packed book satisfies by demystifying the intriguing science under the hood. For future hands-on practitioners pursuing a career in the field, it sets a strong foundation, delivers the prerequisite knowledge, and whets your appetite for more.    </p>
<p>                     A truly omnipresent science, predictive analytics constantly affects our daily lives. Whether you are a consumer of it &#8211; or consumed by it &#8211; get a handle on the power of Predictive Analytics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/">Predictive Analytics : The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die &#8211; Eric Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AN ECONOMIST BOOK OF THE YEAR A NEW STATESMAN BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8216;This book is about a whole new way of studying the mind &#8230; Endlessly fascinating&#8217; Steven Pinker &#8216;A whirlwind tour of the modern human psyche&#8217; Economist Everybody lies, to friends, lovers, doctors, pollsters &#8211; and to themselves. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/">Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    AN ECONOMIST BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    A NEW STATESMAN BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is about a whole new way of studying the mind &#8230; Endlessly fascinating&#8217; Steven Pinker    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A whirlwind tour of the modern human psyche&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                    Everybody lies, to friends, lovers, doctors, pollsters &#8211; and to themselves. In Internet searches, however, people confess the truth.    </p>
<p>                    Insightful, funny and always surprising, Everybody Lies explores how this huge collection of data, unprecedented in human history, could just be the most important ever collected. It offers astonishing insights into the human psyche, revealing the biases deeply embedded within us, the questions we&#8217;re afraid to ask that might be essential to our well-being, and the information we can use to change our culture for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/">Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A manual for the 21st-century citizen&#8230; accessible, refreshingly critical, relevant and urgent&#8217; &#8211; Financial Times &#8216;Fascinating and deeply disturbing&#8217; &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari, Guardian Books of the Year In this New York Times bestseller, Cathy O&#8217;Neil, one of the first champions of algorithmic accountability, sounds an alarm on the mathematical models that pervade modern life [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/">Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A manual for the 21st-century citizen&#8230; accessible, refreshingly critical, relevant and urgent&#8217; &#8211;  Financial Times     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating and deeply disturbing&#8217; &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari, Guardian Books of the Year     </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestseller, Cathy O&#8217;Neil, one of the first champions of algorithmic accountability, sounds an alarm on the mathematical models that pervade modern life &#8212; and threaten to rip apart our social fabric.    </p>
<p>                    We live in the age of the algorithm. Increasingly, the decisions that affect our lives &#8211; where we go to school, whether we get a loan, how much we pay for insurance &#8211; are being made not by humans, but by mathematical models. In theory, this should lead to greater fairness: everyone is judged according to the same rules, and bias is eliminated.     </p>
<p>                    And yet, as Cathy O&#8217;Neil reveals in this urgent and necessary book, the opposite is true. The models being used today are opaque, unregulated, and incontestable, even when they&#8217;re wrong. Most troubling, they reinforce discrimination. Tracing the arc of a person&#8217;s life, O&#8217;Neil exposes the black box models that shape our future, both as individuals and as a society. These &#8220;weapons of math destruction&#8221; score teachers and students, sort CVs, grant or deny loans, evaluate workers, target voters, and monitor our health.     </p>
<p>                    O&#8217;Neil calls on modellers to take more responsibility for their algorithms and on policy makers to regulate their use. But in the end, it&#8217;s up to us to become more savvy about the models that govern our lives. This important book empowers us to ask the tough questions, uncover the truth, and demand change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/">Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Statistics : Learning from Data &#8211; David Spiegelhalter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-statistics-learning-from-data-david-spiegelhalter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-statistics-learning-from-data-david-spiegelhalter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A statistical national treasure&#8217; Jeremy Vine, BBC Radio 2 &#8216;Required reading for all politicians, journalists, medics and anyone who tries to influence people (or is influenced) by statistics. A tour de force&#8217; Popular Science Do busier hospitals have higher survival rates? How many trees are there on the planet? Why do old men have big [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-statistics-learning-from-data-david-spiegelhalter-abridged/">The Art of Statistics : Learning from Data &#8211; David Spiegelhalter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A statistical national treasure&#8217; Jeremy Vine, BBC Radio 2    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Required reading for all politicians, journalists, medics and anyone who tries to influence people (or is influenced) by statistics. A tour de force&#8217; Popular Science    </p>
<p>                    Do busier hospitals have higher survival rates? How many trees are there on the planet? Why do old men have big ears? David Spiegelhalter reveals the answers to these and many other questions &#8211; questions that can only be addressed using statistical science.    </p>
<p>                    Statistics has played a leading role in our scientific understanding of the world for centuries, yet we are all familiar with the way statistical claims can be sensationalised, particularly in the media. In the age of big data, as data science becomes established as a discipline, a basic grasp of statistical literacy is more important than ever.     </p>
<p>                    In The Art of Statistics, David Spiegelhalter guides the reader through the essential principles we need in order to derive knowledge from data. Drawing on real world problems to introduce conceptual issues, he shows us how statistics can help us determine the luckiest passenger on the Titanic, whether serial killer Harold Shipman could have been caught earlier, and if screening for ovarian cancer is beneficial.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Shines a light on how we can use the ever-growing deluge of data to improve our understanding of the world&#8217; Nature</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-statistics-learning-from-data-david-spiegelhalter-abridged/">The Art of Statistics : Learning from Data &#8211; David Spiegelhalter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Numbers Rule Your World: The Hidden Influence of Probabilities and Statistics on Everything You Do &#8211; Kaiser Fung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WHAT ARE THE ODDS YOU&#8217;LL WIN THE LOTTERY? How long will your kids wait in line at Disney World?Who decides that &#8220;standardized tests&#8221; are fair?Why do highway engineers build slow-moving ramps?What does it mean, statistically, to be an &#8220;Average Joe&#8221;?NUMBERS RULE YOUR WORLD In the popular tradition of eye-opening bestsellers like Freakonomics, The Tipping Point, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/">Numbers Rule Your World: The Hidden Influence of Probabilities and Statistics on Everything You Do &#8211; Kaiser Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WHAT ARE THE ODDS YOU&#8217;LL WIN THE LOTTERY?<br />
                    How long will your kids wait in line at Disney World?Who decides that &#8220;standardized tests&#8221; are fair?Why do highway engineers build slow-moving ramps?What does it mean, statistically, to be an &#8220;Average Joe&#8221;?NUMBERS RULE YOUR WORLD<br />
                    In the popular tradition of eye-opening bestsellers like Freakonomics, The Tipping Point, and Super Crunchers, this fascinating book from renowned statistician and blogger Kaiser Fung takes you inside the hidden world of facts and figures that affect you every day, in every way. These are the statistics that rule your life, your job, your commute, your vacation, your food, your health, your money, and your success. This is how engineers calculate your quality of living, how corporations determine your needs, and how politicians estimate your opinions. These are the numbers you never think about-even though they play a crucial role in every single aspect of your life.What you learn may surprise you, amuse you, or even enrage you. But there&#8217;s one thing you won&#8217;t be able to deny: Numbers Rule Your World&#8230;&#8221;An easy read with a big benefit.&#8221;<br />
                    -Fareed Zakaria, CNN    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;For those who have anxiety about how organization data-mining is impacting their world,  Kaiser Fung pulls back the curtain to reveal the good and the bad of predictive analytics.&#8221;<br />
                    -Ian Ayres,Yale professor and author of Super Crunchers:  Why Thinking By Numbers is the New Way to Be Smart<br />
                     &#8220;A book that engages us with stories that a journalist would write, the compelling stories behind the stories as illuminated by the numbers, and the dynamics that the numbers reveal.&#8221;<br />
                    -John Sall, Executive Vice President, SAS Institute  &#8220;Little did I suspect, when I picked up Kaiser Fung&#8217;s book, that I would become so entranced by it &#8211; an illuminating and accessible exploration of the power of statistical analysis for those of us who have no prior training in a field that he explores so ably.&#8221;<br />
                    -Peter Clarke, author of  Keynes: The Rise, Fall, and Return of the 20th Century&#8217;s Most Influential Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A tremendous book. . . . If you want to understand how to use statistics, how to think with numbers and yet to do this without getting lost in equations, if you&#8217;ve been looking for the book to unlock the door to logical thinking about problems, well, you will be pleased to know that you are holding that book in your hands.&#8221;<br />
                    -Daniel Finkelstein, Executive Editor, The Times of London&#8221;I thoroughly enjoyed this accessible book and enthusiastically recommendit to anyone looking to understand and appreciate the role of statistics and dataanalysis in solving problems and in creating a better world.&#8221;<br />
                     -Michael Sherman, Texas A&#038;M University, American Statistician</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/">Numbers Rule Your World: The Hidden Influence of Probabilities and Statistics on Everything You Do &#8211; Kaiser Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
