<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Teaching Staff Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/teaching-staff/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/teaching-staff/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Teaching Staff Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/teaching-staff/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teacher Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Staff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching    </p>
<p>                     Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically and mentally ill, things have gone too far. Unsurprisingly, these effects are highest in difficult-to-fill positions such as math, science, and foreign languages, and in urban areas and secondary classrooms-places where we need our teachers to be especially motivated and engaged. This book offers a path to resiliency to help teachers weather the storms and bounce back-and work toward banishing the rain for good.    </p>
<p>                     This actionable framework gives you concrete steps toward rediscovering yourself, your energy, and your passion for teaching. You&#8217;ll learn how a simple shift in mindset can affect your outlook, and how taking care of yourself physically, mentally, and emotionally is one of the most important things you can do. The companion workbook helps you put the framework into action, streamlining your way toward renewal and strength.    </p>
<p>                    Cultivate resilience with a four-part framework based on 12 key habits<br />
                    Uncover your true self, understand emotions, and use your energy where it counts<br />
                    Adopt a mindful, story-telling approach to communication and community building<br />
                    Keep learning, playing, and creating to create an environment of collective celebration    </p>
<p>                     By cultivating resilience in schools, we help ensure that we are working in, teaching in, and leading organizations where every child thrives, and where the potential of every child is recognized and nurtured. Onward provides a step-by-step plan for reigniting that spark.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Be Heard : Secrets for Powerful Speaking and Listening &#8211; Julian Treasure (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-heard-secrets-for-powerful-speaking-and-listening-julian-treasure-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Staff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-heard-secrets-for-powerful-speaking-and-listening-julian-treasure-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Secrets of Communication Skills from a TED Talks Star &#8220;A must-read from the master of communication, Julian Treasure.&#8221; Michael Charnley-Heaton, Founder &#038; CEO, Radioworks 2019 Audie Award Winner for Best Audio Book in Business and Personal Development HuffPost 20 Best Business Books of 2017 Winner of the Best Voiceover-Audiobook Narration at the 2018 Voice Arts [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-heard-secrets-for-powerful-speaking-and-listening-julian-treasure-abridged/">How to Be Heard : Secrets for Powerful Speaking and Listening &#8211; Julian Treasure (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Secrets of Communication Skills from a TED Talks Star<br />
                    &#8220;A must-read from the master of communication, Julian Treasure.&#8221;  Michael Charnley-Heaton, Founder &#038; CEO, Radioworks    </p>
<p>                    2019 Audie Award Winner for Best Audio Book in Business and Personal Development<br />
                    HuffPost 20 Best Business Books of 2017<br />
                    Winner of the Best Voiceover-Audiobook Narration at the 2018 Voice Arts Awards    </p>
<p>                    Have you ever felt like you&#8217;re talking, but nobody is listening? Renowned five-time TED Talks speaker and author Julian Treasure reveals how to speak so that people listen-and how to listen so that people feel heard.    </p>
<p>                    Develop effective communication skills.  As this leading sound expert demonstrates via interviews with world-class speakers, professional performers and CEOs atop their field, the secret to how to be heard lies in developing simple habits that can transform your communication skills, the quality of your relationships and your impact in the world.    </p>
<p>                    Effective speaking, listening, and understanding skills. How to be Heard includes never-before-seen exercises to develop your communication skills that are as effective at home as in the boardroom or conference call. Julian Treasure offers an inspiring vision for a world of effective speaking, listening and understanding.    </p>
<p>                    Read How to be Heard and discover communication skills improvement tips and other secrets of good communication skills:    </p>
<p>                    How to make sound work for you<br />
                    Why listening matters<br />
                    The four cornerstones of powerful speaking and listening<br />
                    How to avoid the seven deadly sins of speaking and listening<br />
                    How to listen and why we don&#8217;t<br />
                    The power of your vocal toolbox and tricks of great speakers<br />
                    Exercises and methods to achieve clarity, precision and impact<br />
                    How to deliver a great talk    </p>
<p>                    If you have read books like Talk Like TED; Simply Said; 4 Essential Keys to Effective Communication in Love, Life, Work Anywhere; or Just Listen; you will want to read Julian Treasure&#8217;s How to be Heard.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-heard-secrets-for-powerful-speaking-and-listening-julian-treasure-abridged/">How to Be Heard : Secrets for Powerful Speaking and Listening &#8211; Julian Treasure (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Practicing Mind : Developing Focus and Discipline in Your Life &#8211; Master Any Skill or Challenge by Learning to Love the Process &#8211; Thomas M. Sterner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-practicing-mind-developing-focus-and-discipline-in-your-life-master-any-skill-or-challenge-by-learning-to-love-the-process-thomas-m-sterner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Staff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-practicing-mind-developing-focus-and-discipline-in-your-life-master-any-skill-or-challenge-by-learning-to-love-the-process-thomas-m-sterner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In those times when we want to acquire a new skill or face a formidable challenge we hope to overcome, what we need most are patience, focus, and discipline, traits that seem elusive or difficult to maintain. In this enticing and practical book, Thomas Sterner demonstrates how to learn skills for any aspect of life, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-practicing-mind-developing-focus-and-discipline-in-your-life-master-any-skill-or-challenge-by-learning-to-love-the-process-thomas-m-sterner-abridged/">The Practicing Mind : Developing Focus and Discipline in Your Life &#8211; Master Any Skill or Challenge by Learning to Love the Process &#8211; Thomas M. Sterner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In those times when we want to acquire a new skill or face a formidable challenge we hope to overcome, what we need most are patience, focus, and discipline, traits that seem elusive or difficult to maintain. In this enticing and practical book, Thomas Sterner demonstrates how to learn skills for any aspect of life, from golfing to business to parenting, by learning to love the process. Early life is all about trial-and-error practice. If we had given up in the face of failure, repetition, and difficulty, we would never have learned to walk or tie our shoes. So why, as adults, do we often give up on a goal when at first we don&#8217;t succeed? In his study of how we learn (prompted by his pursuit of disciplines such as music and golf), Sterner has found that we have forgotten the principles of practice &#8212; the process of picking a goal and applying steady effort to reach it. The methods Sterner teaches show that practice done properly isn&#8217;t drudgery on the way to mastery but a fulfilling process in and of itself, one that builds discipline and clarity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-practicing-mind-developing-focus-and-discipline-in-your-life-master-any-skill-or-challenge-by-learning-to-love-the-process-thomas-m-sterner-abridged/">The Practicing Mind : Developing Focus and Discipline in Your Life &#8211; Master Any Skill or Challenge by Learning to Love the Process &#8211; Thomas M. Sterner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pivot : The Only Move That Matters Is Your Next One &#8211; Jenny Blake (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pivot-the-only-move-that-matters-is-your-next-one-jenny-blake-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Staff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pivot-the-only-move-that-matters-is-your-next-one-jenny-blake-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to make a career change? Pivot is the book you will turn to again and again&#8217; Dan Pink, author of To Sell is Human and Drive &#8216;Now you, too, can think like a start-up and fix your ailing life&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;A guide for people who want a career change but are too scared [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pivot-the-only-move-that-matters-is-your-next-one-jenny-blake-abridged/">Pivot : The Only Move That Matters Is Your Next One &#8211; Jenny Blake (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking to make a career change? Pivot is the book you will turn to again and again&#8217; Dan Pink, author of To Sell is Human and Drive    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Now you, too, can think like a start-up and fix your ailing life&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A guide for people who want a career change but are too scared to really go for it&#8217; Elle    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s always the right time to think about your next move.    </p>
<p>                    In today&#8217;s economy the average job tenure is only four years, and falling. Roles change constantly. Even smart, motivated people hit professional plateaus.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;What&#8217;s next?&#8217; is a question we all have to answer more frequently. But how do you advance without getting stuck?    </p>
<p>                    In Pivot, Jenny Blake, co-creator of Google&#8217;s Career Guru Programme, shows you how to build upon your assets &#8211; your strengths, interests and networks &#8211; to launch a new career with meaning and adventure. You will learn how to redirect your energy, scan for opportunities and identify new skills without falling prey to &#8216;analysis paralysis&#8217; or &#8216;compare and despair&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    No matter your age, industry, or bank balance, pivoting is the crucial skill you need to stay agile and keep you moving forward.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Feeling stuck? It&#8217;s time to try something new. All that stands between you and your next adventure is a bit of strategy, planning, and preparation. If a change is in your future, Pivot is your guide&#8217; &#8211; Josh Kaufman, author of The Personal MBA and The First 20 Hours</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pivot-the-only-move-that-matters-is-your-next-one-jenny-blake-abridged/">Pivot : The Only Move That Matters Is Your Next One &#8211; Jenny Blake (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
