<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cookery For Dietary Conditions Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/cookery-for-dietary-conditions/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/cookery-for-dietary-conditions/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Cookery For Dietary Conditions Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/cookery-for-dietary-conditions/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners : Your Essential Guide to Living the Keto Lifestyle &#8211; Amy Ramos, Rockridge Press, Foreword by Amanda C Hughes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The simple, friendly way to start the ketogenic diet and lifestyle Starting the ketogenic diet can be overwhelming―so much to learn, so many resources to choose from. So why doesn&#8217;t somebody make it easy? We did with this must-have cookbook. The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners makes it easy to start, and stick with, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/">The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners : Your Essential Guide to Living the Keto Lifestyle &#8211; Amy Ramos, Rockridge Press, Foreword by Amanda C Hughes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The simple, friendly way to start the ketogenic diet and lifestyle    </p>
<p>                    Starting the ketogenic diet can be overwhelming―so much to learn, so many resources to choose from. So why doesn&#8217;t somebody make it easy? We did with this must-have cookbook. The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners makes it easy to start, and stick with, the ketogenic diet. You get exactly what you need for surprisingly simple keto: meal plans, shopping lists, support, and lots of keto-licious recipes.    </p>
<p>                    What sets this ketogenic cookbook apart from other keto books for beginners:<br />
                    75 scrumptious recipes―From Bacon-Artichoke Omelets to Pesto Zucchini Noodles, these easy-to-follow recipes can be prepared in 30 minutes or less.14-day meal plan―With breakfast, lunch, dinner, and snack suggestions, this book takes the guesswork out of starting your ketogenic diet.The big picture―An overview explaining the fundamentals of the ketogenic diet and handy charts illustrating nutritional information help you master keto in no time.    </p>
<p>                    Easy meets delicious meets healthy in this ketogenic diet and healthy lifestyle guide and cookbook. Start eating keto today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/">The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners : Your Essential Guide to Living the Keto Lifestyle &#8211; Amy Ramos, Rockridge Press, Foreword by Amanda C Hughes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bulletproof Diet : Lose up to a Pound a Day, Reclaim Energy and Focus, Upgrade Your Life &#8211; Dave Asprey, Foreword by J. J. Virgin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bulletproof-diet-lose-up-to-a-pound-a-day-reclaim-energy-and-focus-upgrade-your-life-dave-asprey-foreword-by-j-j-virgin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bulletproof-diet-lose-up-to-a-pound-a-day-reclaim-energy-and-focus-upgrade-your-life-dave-asprey-foreword-by-j-j-virgin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When his excess fat started causing brain fog and food cravings sapped his energy and willpower, Asprey turned to the same hacking techniques that made his fortune to &#8220;hack&#8221; his own biology, investing more than $300,000 and 15 years to uncover what was hindering his energy, performance, appearance, and happiness. From private brain EEG facilities [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bulletproof-diet-lose-up-to-a-pound-a-day-reclaim-energy-and-focus-upgrade-your-life-dave-asprey-foreword-by-j-j-virgin-abridged/">The Bulletproof Diet : Lose up to a Pound a Day, Reclaim Energy and Focus, Upgrade Your Life &#8211; Dave Asprey, Foreword by J. J. Virgin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When his excess fat started causing brain fog and food cravings sapped his energy and willpower, Asprey turned to the same hacking techniques that made his fortune to &#8220;hack&#8221; his own biology, investing more than $300,000 and 15 years to uncover what was hindering his energy, performance, appearance, and happiness. From private brain EEG facilities to remote monasteries in Tibet, through radioactive brain scans, blood chemistry work, nervous system testing and more, he explored traditional and alternative technologies to reach his physical and mental prime. The result? The Bulletproof Diet, an anti-inflammatory program for hunger-free, rapid weight loss and peak performance. The Bulletproof Diet will change what you think you know about weight loss and wellness. You will skip breakfast, stop counting calories, eat a high-fat diet, work out and sleep less, and handle stress with ease. By ditching traditional &#8220;diet&#8221; thinking, Asprey has maintained a 100-pound weight loss, increased his IQ, and reached a level of health that seemed unattainable. His 40s are truly better than his 20s, and The Bulletproof Diet brings his best hacks to the masses.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bulletproof-diet-lose-up-to-a-pound-a-day-reclaim-energy-and-focus-upgrade-your-life-dave-asprey-foreword-by-j-j-virgin-abridged/">The Bulletproof Diet : Lose up to a Pound a Day, Reclaim Energy and Focus, Upgrade Your Life &#8211; Dave Asprey, Foreword by J. J. Virgin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wild Diet : Go Beyond Paleo to Burn Fat and Drop Up to 20 Pounds in 40 Days &#8211; Abel James (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Abel James, the ABC star and creator of the #1 Fat-Burning Man Show, shares his revolutionary weight-loss program in The Wild Diet &#8211; now a New York Times Bestseller! Can you really lose 20 pounds in 40 days while enjoying real butter, juicy burgers, chicken parmesan, chocolate, and even cheesecake? The answer might surprise you. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/">The Wild Diet : Go Beyond Paleo to Burn Fat and Drop Up to 20 Pounds in 40 Days &#8211; Abel James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Abel James, the ABC star and creator of the #1 Fat-Burning Man Show, shares his revolutionary weight-loss program in The Wild Diet &#8211; now a New York Times Bestseller!      </p>
<p>                    Can you really lose 20 pounds in 40 days while enjoying real butter, juicy burgers, chicken parmesan, chocolate, and even cheesecake?     </p>
<p>                    The answer might surprise you.     </p>
<p>                    By focusing on simple, fresh ingredients and nutrient-dense meals, The Wild Diet programs your body to burn fat as its main fuel source. Eating Wild, thousands of people across the world have dropped 20, 60, or even more than 100+ pounds without hunger&#8230; and often with minimal exercise.     </p>
<p>                    In The Wild Diet, you&#8217;ll find that we are not meant to starve ourselves, count calories, or avoid delicious food. We&#8217;re wired to eat luxuriously and live well without getting fat.     </p>
<p>                    If you think that you&#8217;re stuck with the genes you inherited and there&#8217;s nothing you can do about it, read closely. The Wild Diet paints a different picture, one in which we have the power to influence our genetic expression by taking control of the quality of food we eat, the way we move, and the environment around us.     </p>
<p>                    We once had access to an immense variety of fresh seasonal foods from small, local sources. Now we have access to few varieties of processed foods from a massive industrial system often thousands of miles from where we live. The secret to great health simply getting back to our wild roots and enjoying real, Wild foods grown on a farm and not in a factory.     </p>
<p>                    By prioritizing foods found in the natural world, rich in fiber and nutrients, your body will burn fat instead of sugar for energy. When you reduce your consumption of processed grains, sugars and other simple carbohydrates in favor of healthy plants and animals, you will be shocked by how quickly you can reverse the damage of decades of poor eating.     </p>
<p>                    The Wild Diet proves that it&#8217;s possible to get in best shape of your life while eating delicious foods like chicken parmesan, bacon cheeseburgers, and even chocolate pudding. If you want to know how to burn more fat by indulging in incredible meals and exercising less, it&#8217;s time to treat yourself to The Wild Diet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wild-diet-go-beyond-paleo-to-burn-fat-and-drop-up-to-20-pounds-in-40-days-abel-james-abridged/">The Wild Diet : Go Beyond Paleo to Burn Fat and Drop Up to 20 Pounds in 40 Days &#8211; Abel James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Always Hungry? : Conquer Cravings, Retrain Your Fat Cells, and Lose Weight Permanently &#8211; David Ludwig, Read by Dawn Ludwig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/always-hungry-conquer-cravings-retrain-your-fat-cells-and-lose-weight-permanently-david-ludwig-read-by-dawn-ludwig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/always-hungry-conquer-cravings-retrain-your-fat-cells-and-lose-weight-permanently-david-ludwig-read-by-dawn-ludwig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leading Harvard Medical School expert and obesity warrior (Time magazine) Dr. David Ludwig rewrites the rules on weight loss, diet, and health in this guide to retraining your cells and reclaiming your health for life. Forget everything you&#8217;ve been taught about dieting. In Always Hungry?, renowned endocrinologist Dr. David Ludwig explains why traditional diets don&#8217;t [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/always-hungry-conquer-cravings-retrain-your-fat-cells-and-lose-weight-permanently-david-ludwig-read-by-dawn-ludwig-abridged/">Always Hungry? : Conquer Cravings, Retrain Your Fat Cells, and Lose Weight Permanently &#8211; David Ludwig, Read by Dawn Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading Harvard Medical School expert and obesity warrior (Time magazine) Dr. David Ludwig rewrites the rules on weight loss, diet, and health in this guide to retraining your cells and reclaiming your health for life.<br />
                    Forget everything you&#8217;ve been taught about dieting. In Always Hungry?, renowned endocrinologist Dr. David Ludwig explains why traditional diets don&#8217;t work and presents a radical new plan to help you lose weight without hunger, improve your health, and feel great.<br />
                    For over two decades, Dr. Ludwig has been at the forefront of research into weight control. His groundbreaking studies show that overeating doesn&#8217;t make you fat; the process of getting fat makes you overeat. That&#8217;s because fat cells play a key role in determining how much weight you gain or lose. Low-fat diets work against you by triggering fat cells to hoard more calories for themselves, leaving too few for the rest of the body. This hungry fat sets off a dangerous chain reaction that leaves you feeling ravenous as your metabolism slows down. Cutting calories only makes the situation worse by creating a battle between mind and metabolism that we&#8217;re destined to lose. You gain more weight even as you struggle to eat less food.<br />
                    Always Hungry? turns dieting on its head with a three-phase program that ignores calories and targets fat cells directly. The recipes and meal plan include luscious high-fat foods (like nuts and nut butters, full-fat dairy, avocados, and dark chocolate), savory proteins, and natural carbohydrates. The result? Fat cells release their excess calories, and you lose weight &#8211; and inches &#8211; without battling cravings and constant hunger. This is dieting without deprivation.<br />
                    Forget calories. Forget cravings. Forget dieting. Always hungry? reveals a liberating new way to tame hunger and lose weight for good.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/always-hungry-conquer-cravings-retrain-your-fat-cells-and-lose-weight-permanently-david-ludwig-read-by-dawn-ludwig-abridged/">Always Hungry? : Conquer Cravings, Retrain Your Fat Cells, and Lose Weight Permanently &#8211; David Ludwig, Read by Dawn Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exploring the World of Lucid Dreaming &#8211; Stephen LaBerge, Howard Rheingold (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/exploring-the-world-of-lucid-dreaming-stephen-laberge-howard-rheingold-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dreams & Their Interpretation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychoanalytical Theory (Freudian Psychology)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/exploring-the-world-of-lucid-dreaming-stephen-laberge-howard-rheingold-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;[A] solid how-to book . . . For amateur dream researchers, this is a must.&#8221;&#8211;Whole Earth Review Lucid Dreaming&#8211;conscious awareness during the dream state&#8211;is an exhilarating experience. Because the world you are experiencing is one of your own creation, you can do the impossible and consciously influence the outcome of your dreams. Exploring the World [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exploring-the-world-of-lucid-dreaming-stephen-laberge-howard-rheingold-abridged/">Exploring the World of Lucid Dreaming &#8211; Stephen LaBerge, Howard Rheingold (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;[A] solid how-to book . . . For amateur dream researchers, this is a must.&#8221;&#8211;Whole Earth Review    </p>
<p>                    Lucid Dreaming&#8211;conscious awareness during the dream state&#8211;is an exhilarating experience. Because the world you are experiencing is one of your own creation, you can do the impossible and consciously influence the outcome of your dreams.     </p>
<p>                    Exploring the World of Lucid Dreaming goes far beyond the confines of pop dream psychology, establishing a scientifically researched framework for using lucid dreaming. Based on Dr. Stephen LaBerge&#8217;s extensive laboratory work at Stanford University mapping mind/body relationships during the dream state, as well as the teachings of Tibetan dream yogis and the work of other scientists, including German psychologist Paul Tholey, this practical workbook will show you how to use your dreams to:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Solve problems<br />
                    &#8211; Gain greater confidence<br />
                    &#8211; Improve creativity<br />
                    &#8211; Face and overcome fears and inhibitions<br />
                    &#8211; Create a new sense of empowerment and liberation in your life     </p>
<p>                     The techniques you&#8217;ll learn in this exciting workbook will make your nightly dream journeys more enjoyable, increase your understanding of yourself, and make you realize that the possibilities of expanding consciousness are far greater than you might think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exploring-the-world-of-lucid-dreaming-stephen-laberge-howard-rheingold-abridged/">Exploring the World of Lucid Dreaming &#8211; Stephen LaBerge, Howard Rheingold (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and shines a bright light on the profound impact that diet&#8211;both good and bad&#8211;can have on our health and that of the planet.     </p>
<p>                     In A Bone to Pick, Mark&#8217;s most memorable and thought-provoking columns are compiled into a single volume for the first time. As abundant and safe as the American food supply appears to be, the state of our health reveals the presence of staggering deficiencies in both the system that produces food and the forces that regulate it. Bittman leaves no issue unexamined; agricultural practices, government legislation, fad diets, and corporate greed all come under scrutiny and show that the issues governing what ends up in our market basket and on our tables are both complex and often deliberately confusing. Unabashedly opinionated and invariably thought provoking, Bittman&#8217;s columns have helped readers decipher arcane policy, unpack scientific studies, and deflate affronts to common sense when it comes to determining what &#8220;eating well&#8221; truly means. As urgent as the situation is, Mark contends that we can be optimistic about the future of our food and its impact on our health, as slow-food movements, better school-lunch programs, and even &#8220;healthy fast food&#8221; become part of the norm.     </p>
<p>                     At once inspiring, enraging, and enlightening, A Bone to Pick is an essential resource for every reader eager to understand not only the complexities inherent in the American food system, but also the many opportunities that exist to improve it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book. Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book.     </p>
<p>                    Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. Why suffer from disease and ill health when the right food is proven to keep you healthy, and without the side effects of drugs? We can avoid heart disease, cancer and our other biggest killers if we use food as medicine, and the How Not To Die Cookbook offers a sustainable and delicious guide to preparing and eating the foods that will prevent and reverse fatal diseases.    </p>
<p>                    Featuring over 100 easy-to-follow, beautifully photographed plant-based recipes, with plenty of recipes suitable for vegetarians and vegans, the How Not To Die Cookbook merges cutting-edge science with everyday ingredients from the supermarket to help you and your family eat your way to better health and a longer life.    </p>
<p>                    All recipes in this cookbook have been fully anglicized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wheat Belly : Lose the Wheat, Lose the Weight, and Find Your Path Back to Health &#8211; William Davis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Endocrinology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every day, over 200 million Americans consume food products made of wheat. As a result, over 100 million of them experience some form of adverse health effect, ranging from minor rashes and high blood sugar to the unattractive stomach bulges that preventive cardiologist William Davis calls &#8220;wheat bellies.&#8221; According to Davis, that excess fat has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/">Wheat Belly : Lose the Wheat, Lose the Weight, and Find Your Path Back to Health &#8211; William Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every day, over 200 million Americans consume food products made of wheat. As a result, over 100 million of them experience some form of adverse health effect, ranging from minor rashes and high blood sugar to the unattractive stomach bulges that preventive cardiologist William Davis calls &#8220;wheat bellies.&#8221; According to Davis, that excess fat has nothing to do with gluttony, sloth, or too much butter: It&#8217;s due to the whole grain wraps we eat for lunch. After witnessing over 2,000 patients regain their health after giving up wheat, Davis reached the disturbing conclusion that wheat is the single largest contributor to the nationwide obesity epidemic &#8211; and its elimination is key to dramatic weight loss and optimal health. In &#8220;Wheat Belly&#8221;, Davis exposes the harmful effects of what is actually a product of genetic tinkering and agribusiness being sold to the public as &#8220;wheat&#8221; &#8211; and provides readers with a user-friendly, step-by-step plan to navigate a new, wheat-free lifestyle.<br />
                    Informed by cutting-edge science and nutrition, along with case studies from men and women who have experienced life-changing transformations in their health after waving goodbye to wheat, &#8220;Wheat Belly&#8221; is an illuminating look at what is truly making people sick and an action plan to clear our plates of this seemingly benign ingredient.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/">Wheat Belly : Lose the Wheat, Lose the Weight, and Find Your Path Back to Health &#8211; William Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dreams & Their Interpretation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now! __________________________________________________________________________________ FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now!<br />
                    __________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver    </p>
<p>                    Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in his Sunday Times bestselling book, The 4 Pillar Plan, BBC One&#8217;s Dr Rangan Chatterjee creates an easily accessible plan for taking control of your health and your life.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Chatterjee believes that everyday health revolves around the following four pillars: relaxation, food, movement and sleep. By making small, achievable changes in each of these key areas you can create and maintain good health &#8211; and avoid illness. Top tips in each area include:     </p>
<p>                    * an electronic &#8216;sabbath&#8217; once a week<br />
                     * 12 hours every day without food<br />
                     * exposure to sunlight first thing each morning<br />
                     * walking at least 10,000 steps a day    </p>
<p>                    Based on cutting edge research and his own two decades&#8217; worth of experience as a doctor, this book contains fascinating case studies from real patients and is an inspiring and easy-to-follow guide to better health and happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health    </p>
<p>                    Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, bacteria and human cells have co-existed in a relationship that has ensured the health and equilibrium of our body. But now, much like the natural world outside of us, our internal environment is being irrevocably destroyed. The culprit: some of our most revered medical advances &#8211; antibiotics &#8211; which appear to be linked to the epidemics of asthma, eczema, obesity, certain forms of cancer, and other diseases plaguing modern society.    </p>
<p>                    In a book that stands as the Silent Spring of its day, Blaser sounds a provocative alarm that we ignore at our peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle, from the bestselling author of How Not to Die. Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle,  from the bestselling author of How Not to Die.    </p>
<p>                    Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any happier or healthier. As obesity rates and associated disease and impairments continue to rise, it&#8217;s time for a different approach.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet is a treasure trove of buried data and cutting-edge dietary research that Dr Michael Greger has translated into accessible, actionable advice with exciting tools and tricks that will help you to safely lose weight and eliminate unwanted body fat &#8211; for good.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Greger, renowned nutrition expert, physician, and founder of the NutritionFacts website, explores the many causes of obesity &#8211; from our genes to the portions on our plate to other environmental factors &#8211; and the many consequences, from diabetes to cancer to mental health issues. From there, Dr Greger breaks down a variety of approaches to weight loss, honing in on the optimal criteria that enable success, including: a diet high in fibre and water, a diet low in fat, salt, and sugar, and diet full of anti-inflammatory foods.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet then goes beyond food to explore the many other weight-loss accelerators available to us in our body&#8217;s systems, revealing how plant-based meals can be eaten at specific times to maximize our bodies&#8217; natural fat-burning activities. Dr Greger provides a clear plan not only for the ultimate weight loss diet, but also the approach we must take to unlock its greatest efficacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
