<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Early Man Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/early-man/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/early-man/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Early Man Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/early-man/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</title>
		<link>/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Break the rules, not the fast with world-renowned biohacker and New York Times bestselling author Dave Asprey. For more than a decade, the Bulletproof founder Dave Asprey has shared his unique point of view and expertise to help fans become the best versions of themselves. From living longer to getting smarter, maximising performance to practising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/">Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Break the rules, not the fast with world-renowned biohacker and New York Times bestselling author Dave Asprey.</p>
<p>                              For more than a decade, the Bulletproof founder Dave Asprey has shared his unique point of view and expertise to help fans become the best versions of themselves. From living longer to getting smarter, maximising performance to practising mindfulness, Dave&#8217;s followers look to him for his take on the most effective techniques to become healthier and more powerful than most doctors think is possible.</p>
<p>                              Asprey has been fasting for years, long before it gained widespread popularity, and if you&#8217;re a fan of The Bulletproof Diet, you have been enjoying some of the benefits of Intermittent Fasting too.</p>
<p>                              In Fast This Way, Dave asks readers to forget everything they think they know about the ancient practice and takes them on a journey through cutting-edge science to examine the ways novice fasters and Intermittent Fasting loyalists can up-end their relationship with food and upgrade their fasting game beyond calorie restriction.  </p>
<p>                     What IF eating the right foods at the right time can actually enhance your fast?<br />
                     What IF how you work out and sleep could trick your body into thinking you are fasting?<br />
                     What IF it were easy to skip a meal, or two, or three?<br />
                     What IF fasting is different for women, can be personalised to your genes, and can impact your mental health?<br />
                     What IF all fasts could be created equal?</p>
<p>                              Fast This Way is a compelling read through the latest thinking on fasting and gives readers the manual and toolkit to make the most of their fasts and their personal biology.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/">Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sapiens : A Brief History of Humankind &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</title>
		<link>/sapiens-a-brief-history-of-humankind-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sapiens-a-brief-history-of-humankind-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**THE MULTI-MILLION COPY BESTSELLER** &#8216;Interesting and provocative&#8230; It gives you a sense of how briefly we&#8217;ve been on this Earth&#8217; Barack Obama What makes us brilliant? What makes us deadly? What makes us Sapiens? Yuval Noah Harari challenges everything we know about being human. Earth is 4.5 billion years old. In just a fraction of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sapiens-a-brief-history-of-humankind-yuval-noah-harari/">Sapiens : A Brief History of Humankind &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**THE MULTI-MILLION COPY BESTSELLER**</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Interesting and provocative&#8230; It gives you a sense of how briefly we&#8217;ve been on this Earth&#8217; Barack Obama</p>
<p>                    What makes us brilliant? What makes us deadly? What makes us Sapiens?</p>
<p>                    Yuval Noah Harari challenges everything we know about being human.</p>
<p>                    Earth is 4.5 billion years old. In just a fraction of that time, one species among countless others has conquered it: us.</p>
<p>                    In this bold and provocative book, Yuval Noah Harari explores who we are, how we got here and where we&#8217;re going. </p>
<p>                    ________________</p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR SAPIENS:</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jaw-dropping from the first word to the last&#8230; It may be the best book I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; Chris Evans</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Sweeps the cobwebs out of your brain&#8230; Radiates power and clarity&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It altered how I view our species and our world&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Startling&#8230; It changes the way you look at the world&#8217; Simon Mayo</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I would recommend Sapiens to anyone who&#8217;s interested in the history and future of our species&#8217; Bill Gates</p>
<p>                    **ONE OF THE GUARDIAN&#8217;S 100 BEST BOOKS OF THE 21st CENTURY**</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sapiens-a-brief-history-of-humankind-yuval-noah-harari/">Sapiens : A Brief History of Humankind &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeological Methodology & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, helped resolve long-existing controversies, challenged long-held views, and thrown up some remarkable surprises.    </p>
<p>                    The emerging picture is one of many waves of ancient human migrations, so that all populations existing today are mixes of ancient ones, as well as in many cases carrying a genetic component from Neanderthals, and, in some populations, Denisovans. David Reich, whose team has been at the forefront of these discoveries, explains what the genetics is telling us about ourselves and our complex and often surprising ancestry. Gone are old ideas of any kind of racial &#8216;purity&#8217;, or even deep and ancient<br />
                    divides between peoples. Instead, we are finding a rich variety of mixtures. Reich describes the cutting-edge findings from the past few years, and also considers the sensitivities involved in tracing ancestry, with science sometimes jostling with politics and tradition. He brings an important wider<br />
                    message: that we should celebrate our rich diversity, and recognize that every one of us is the result of a long history of migration and intermixing of ancient peoples, which we carry as ghosts in our DNA.    </p>
<p>                    What will we discover next?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Origin Story : A Big History of Everything &#8211; David Christian (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/origin-story-a-big-history-of-everything-david-christian-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Earliest Times To Present Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/origin-story-a-big-history-of-everything-david-christian-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>David Christian, creator of Big History (&#8216;My favourite course of all time&#8217; Bill Gates), brings us the epic story of the universe and our place in it, from 13.8 billion years ago to the remote future &#8216;Nails home the point: Life is a miracle &#8230; A compelling history of everything&#8217; Washington Post &#8216;Spectacular&#8217; Carlo Rovelli [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/origin-story-a-big-history-of-everything-david-christian-abridged/">Origin Story : A Big History of Everything &#8211; David Christian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>David Christian, creator of Big History (&#8216;My favourite course of all time&#8217; Bill Gates), brings us the epic story of the universe and our place in it, from 13.8 billion years ago to the remote future    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Nails home the point: Life is a  miracle &#8230; A compelling history of everything&#8217; Washington Post<br />
                     &#8216;Spectacular&#8217; Carlo Rovelli    </p>
<p>                    How  did we get from the Big Bang to today&#8217;s staggering complexity, in which  seven billion humans are connected into networks powerful enough to  transform the planet? And why, in comparison, are our closest primate  relatives reduced to near-extinction?     </p>
<p>                    Big History creator David  Christian gives the answers in a mind-expanding cosmological detective  story told on the grandest possible scale. He traces how, during eight  key thresholds, the right conditions have allowed new forms of  complexity to arise, from stars to galaxies, Earth to homo sapiens,  agriculture to fossil fuels. This last mega-innovation gave us an energy  bonanza that brought huge benefits to mankind, yet also threatens to  shake apart everything we have created.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rather like the Big Bang, the book is awe-inspiring &#8230; Superb&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;With   fascinating ideas on every page and the page-turning energy of a good   thriller, this is a landmark work&#8217; Sir Ken Robinson, author of The Element</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/origin-story-a-big-history-of-everything-david-christian-abridged/">Origin Story : A Big History of Everything &#8211; David Christian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals. In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals.     </p>
<p>                    In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind societies. He explores how the tension between identity and anonymity defines how societies develop, function, and fail. In the vein of Guns, Germs, and Steel and Sapiens, The Human Swarm reveals how mankind created sprawling civilizations of unrivalled complexity &#8211; and what it will take to sustain them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blueprint : The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society &#8211; Nicholas A. Christakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For too long, scientists have focused on the dark side of our biological heritage: our capacity for aggression, cruelty, prejudice, and self-interest. But natural selection has given us a suite of beneficial social features, including our capacity for love, friendship, cooperation, and learning. Beneath all our inventions &#8212; our tools, farms, machines, cities, nations &#8212; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/">Blueprint : The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society &#8211; Nicholas A. Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For too long, scientists have focused on the dark side of our biological heritage: our capacity for aggression, cruelty, prejudice, and self-interest. But natural selection has given us a suite of beneficial social features, including our capacity for love, friendship, cooperation, and learning. Beneath all our inventions &#8212; our tools, farms, machines, cities, nations &#8212; we carry with us innate proclivities to make a good society.     </p>
<p>                    In Blueprint, Nicholas A. Christakis introduces the compelling idea that our genes affect not only our bodies and behaviors, but also the ways in which we make societies, ones that are surprisingly similar worldwide. With many vivid examples &#8212; including diverse historical and contemporary cultures, communities formed in the wake of shipwrecks, commune dwellers seeking utopia, online groups thrown together by design or involving artificially intelligent bots, and even the tender and complex social arrangements of elephants and dolphins that so resemble our own &#8212; Christakis shows that, despite a human history replete with violence, we cannot escape our social blueprint for goodness.     </p>
<p>                    In a world of increasing political and economic polarization, it&#8217;s tempting to ignore the positive role of our evolutionary past. But by exploring the ancient roots of goodness in civilization, Blueprint shows that our genes have shaped societies for our welfare and that, in a feedback loop stretching back many thousands of years, societies have shaped, and are still shaping, our genes today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/">Blueprint : The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society &#8211; Nicholas A. Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
