<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Housing &amp; Property For The Individual - Buying/selling &amp; Legal Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/housing-property-for-the-individual-buying-selling-legal-aspects/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/housing-property-for-the-individual-buying-selling-legal-aspects/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Housing &amp; Property For The Individual - Buying/selling &amp; Legal Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/housing-property-for-the-individual-buying-selling-legal-aspects/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Clients First : The Two Word Miracle &#8211; Joseph Callaway, Joann Callaway (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/clients-first-the-two-word-miracle-joseph-callaway-joann-callaway-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Housing & Property For The Individual - Buying/selling & Legal Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/clients-first-the-two-word-miracle-joseph-callaway-joann-callaway-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How honesty, competency, and caring will make you rich Throw out the sales manual. Get off the motivation elevator. Clients First is a two word miracle that can change your life. This book outlines a powerful path to riches that authors Joseph and JoAnn Callaway used to sell a billion dollars in real estate in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clients-first-the-two-word-miracle-joseph-callaway-joann-callaway-abridged/">Clients First : The Two Word Miracle &#8211; Joseph Callaway, Joann Callaway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How honesty, competency, and caring will make you rich Throw out the sales manual. Get off the motivation elevator. Clients First is a two word miracle that can change your life. This book outlines a powerful path to riches that authors Joseph and JoAnn Callaway used to sell a billion dollars in real estate in just ten years a feat never before achieved. Here, they explain the three keys to putting your clients first that helped them create one of the most successful realty firms in the U.S. Each of the three keys is important and can stand on its own. However, the success you can achieve when following the Clients First program can only be reached when all three keys are used in coordination. * Explains how honesty ensures a strong client relationship * Details the ways in which competency pervades all aspects of a client&#8217;s perception of you * Shows how being a caring individual can win over a client on a personal level Unlock your potential by putting these to use in your life and your business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clients-first-the-two-word-miracle-joseph-callaway-joann-callaway-abridged/">Clients First : The Two Word Miracle &#8211; Joseph Callaway, Joann Callaway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zillow Talk : Rewriting the Rules of Real Estate &#8211; Spencer Rascoff, Stan Humphries (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zillow-talk-rewriting-the-rules-of-real-estate-spencer-rascoff-stan-humphries-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Housing & Property For The Individual - Buying/selling & Legal Aspects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zillow-talk-rewriting-the-rules-of-real-estate-spencer-rascoff-stan-humphries-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How do you spot an area poised for gentrification? Is spring or winter the best time to put your house on the market? Will a house on Swamp Road sell for less than one on Gingerbread Lane? The fact is that the rules of real estate have changed drastically over the past five years. To [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zillow-talk-rewriting-the-rules-of-real-estate-spencer-rascoff-stan-humphries-abridged/">Zillow Talk : Rewriting the Rules of Real Estate &#8211; Spencer Rascoff, Stan Humphries (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do you spot an area poised for gentrification? Is spring or winter the best time to put your house on the market? Will a house on Swamp Road sell for less than one on Gingerbread Lane? The fact is that the rules of real estate have changed drastically over the past five years. To understand real estate in our fast-paced, technology-driven world, we need to toss out all of the outdated truisms and embrace today&#8217;s brand new information. But how?    </p>
<p>                    Enter Zillow, the nation&#8217;s #1 real estate website and mobile app. Thanks to its treasure trove of proprietary data and army of statisticians and data scientists, led by chief economist Stan Humphries, Zillow has been able to spot the trends and truths of today&#8217;s housing market while acknowledging that a home is more than an economic asset. In Zillow Talk, Humphries and CEO Spencer Rascoff explain the science behind where and how we live now and reveal practical, data-driven insights about buying, selling, renting and financing real estate. Read this book to find out why:     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s better to remodel your bathroom than your kitchen<br />
                     Putting the word &#8220;cute&#8221; in your listing could cost you thousands of dollars<br />
                     You shouldn&#8217;t buy the worst house in the best neighborhood<br />
                     You should never list your house for $444,000<br />
                     You shouldn&#8217;t list your house for sale before March Madness or after the Masters    </p>
<p>                    Densely packed with entertaining anecdotes and invaluable how-to advice, Zillow Talk is poised to be the real estate almanac for the next generation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zillow-talk-rewriting-the-rules-of-real-estate-spencer-rascoff-stan-humphries-abridged/">Zillow Talk : Rewriting the Rules of Real Estate &#8211; Spencer Rascoff, Stan Humphries (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
