<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Welfare Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/welfare-economics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/welfare-economics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Welfare Economics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/welfare-economics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Portfolios of the Poor : How the World&#8217;s Poor Live on $2 a Day &#8211; Daryl Collins, Jonathan Morduch, Stuart Rutherford, Orlanda Ruthven (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nearly forty percent of humanity lives on an average of two dollars a day or less. If you&#8217;ve never had to survive on an income so small, it is hard to imagine. How would you put food on the table, afford a home, and educate your children? How would you handle emergencies and old age? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/">Portfolios of the Poor : How the World&#8217;s Poor Live on $2 a Day &#8211; Daryl Collins, Jonathan Morduch, Stuart Rutherford, Orlanda Ruthven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nearly forty percent of humanity lives on an average of two dollars a day or less. If you&#8217;ve never had to survive on an income so small, it is hard to imagine. How would you put food on the table, afford a home, and educate your children? How would you handle emergencies and old age? Every day, more than a billion people around the world must answer these questions. Portfolios of the Poor is the first book to systematically explain how the poor find solutions to their everyday financial problems. The authors conducted year-long interviews with impoverished villagers and slum dwellers in Bangladesh, India, and South Africa&#8211;records that track penny by penny how specific households manage their money. The stories of these families are often surprising and inspiring. Most poor households do not live hand to mouth, spending what they earn in a desperate bid to keep afloat. Instead, they employ financial tools, many linked to informal networks and family ties. They push money into savings for reserves, squeeze money out of creditors whenever possible, run sophisticated savings clubs, and use microfinancing wherever available.<br />
                    Their experiences reveal new methods to fight poverty and ways to envision the next generation of banks for the &#8220;bottom billion.&#8221; Indispensable for those in development studies, economics, and microfinance, Portfolios of the Poor will appeal to anyone interested in knowing more about poverty and what can be done about it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/">Portfolios of the Poor : How the World&#8217;s Poor Live on $2 a Day &#8211; Daryl Collins, Jonathan Morduch, Stuart Rutherford, Orlanda Ruthven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a rational explanation of the ways in which the AI revolution will affect us all. Tackling the implications of Artificial Intelligence on growth, productivity, inflation and the distribution of wealth and power, THE AI ECONOMY also examines coming changes to the the way we educate, work and spend our leisure time.    </p>
<p>                    A fundamentally optimistic view which will help you plan for changing times, this book explains AI and leads you towards a more certain future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart the crucial role of violent shocks in reducing inequality over the full sweep of human history around the world. The &#8220;Four Horsemen&#8221; of leveling-mass-mobilization warfare, transformative revolutions, state collapse, and catastrophic plagues-have repeatedly destroyed the fortunes of the rich. Today, the violence that reduced inequality in the past seems to have diminished, and that is a good thing. But it casts serious doubt on the prospects for a more equal future. An essential contribution to the debate about inequality, The Great Leveler provides important new insights about why inequality is so persistent-and why it is unlikely to decline anytime soon.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
