<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Banking Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/banking/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/banking/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Banking Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/banking/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</title>
		<link>/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Internet and smartphone are just the latest in a 250 year long cycle of disruption that has continuously changed the way we live, the way we work and the way we interact. The coming Augmented Age, however, promises a level of disruption, behavioral shifts and changes that are unparalleled. While consumers today are camping [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/">Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Internet and smartphone are just the latest in a 250 year long cycle of disruption that has continuously changed the way we live, the way we work and the way we interact. The coming Augmented Age, however, promises a level of disruption, behavioral shifts and changes that are unparalleled. While consumers today are camping outside of an Apple store waiting to be one of the first to score a new Apple Watch or iPhone, the next generation of wearables will be able to predict if we&#8217;re likely to have a heart attack and recommend a course of action. We watch news of Google&#8217;s self-driving cars, but don&#8217;t likely realize this means progressive cities will have to ban human drives in the next decade because us humans are too risky.  Following on from the Industrial or Machine Age, the Space Age and the Digital Age, the Augmented Age will be based on four key disruptive themes &#8211; Artificial Intelligence, Experience Design, Smart Infrastructure, and Health Tech. Historically the previous &#8216;ages&#8217; brought significant disruption and changes, but on a net basis jobs were created, wealth was enhanced, and the health and security of society improved. What will the Augmented Age bring?<br />
                    Will robots take our jobs, and AI&#8217;s subsume us as inferior intelligences, or will this usher in a new age of abundance?  Augmented is a book on future history, but more than that, it is a story about how you will live your life in a world that will change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 250 years. Are you ready to adapt? Because if history proves anything, you don&#8217;t have much of a choice.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/">Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review</p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.</p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.</p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.</p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year! &#8216;Will snare you in its web of deceit &#8230; A brilliant investigative expose&#8217; &#8211; Harlan Coben, bestselling thriller author &#8216;Reads like a fast-paced John le Carre thriller, and never lets up&#8217; &#8211; New York Times book review The Spider Network is the almost-unbelievable and darkly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/">The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year!    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Will snare you in its web of deceit &#8230; A brilliant investigative expose&#8217; &#8211; Harlan Coben, bestselling thriller author     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Reads like a fast-paced John le Carre thriller, and never lets up&#8217; &#8211; New York Times book review     </p>
<p>                    The Spider Network is the almost-unbelievable and darkly entertaining inside account of the Libor scandal &#8211; one of the biggest, farthest-reaching financial scams since the global financial crisis &#8211; written by the only journalist with access to Tom Hayes before he was sentenced to fourteen years in prison.   Full of exclusive details, and with ramifications that stretch right across the British establishment, this is a gripping, real-life story of outlandish characters and reckless greed in the City of London.     </p>
<p>                    By turns a rollicking account of the scandal and also a provocative examination of a financial system that was crooked throughout, The Spider Network is a perfect read for fans of The Wolf of Wall Street and The Big Short.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/">The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge    </p>
<p>                    With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. This clear, concise, and accessible guide from two industry insiders shows you how to navigate this brave new blockchain world-and how to invest in these emerging assets to secure your financial future.    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets gives you all the tools you need:    </p>
<p>                    * An actionable framework for investigating and valuing cryptoassets     </p>
<p>                    * Portfolio management techniques to maximize returns while managing risk    </p>
<p>                    * Historical context and tips to navigate inevitable bubbles and manias    </p>
<p>                    * Practical guides to exchanges, wallets, capital market vehicles, and ICOs    </p>
<p>                    * Predictions on how blockchain technology may disrupt current portfolios    </p>
<p>                    In addition to offering smart investment strategies, this authoritative resource will help you understand how these assets were created, how they work, and how they are evolving amid the blockchain revolution. The authors define a clear and original cryptoasset taxonomy, composed of cryptocurrencies, cryptocommodities, and cryptotokens, with insights into how each subset is blending technology and markets. You&#8217;ll find a variety of methods to invest in these assets, whether through global exchanges that trade 24/7 or initial cryptoasset offerings (ICOs). By sequentially building on the concepts of each prior chapter, the book will provide you with a full understanding of the cryptoasset economy and the opportunities that await the innovative investor .    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets represent the future of money and markets. This book is your guide to that future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millennial Money &#8211; Patrick O&#8217;Shaughnessy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We have witnessed one of the worst stock market beatings ever. As a result, abysmal returns are the new normal, financial experts are ringing the death knell of buy-and-hold, and investorsâ faith in equities has hit an all-time low. You have choices, you can abandon the stock market, or invest for tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/">Millennial Money &#8211; Patrick O&#8217;Shaughnessy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have witnessed one of the worst stock market beatings ever. As a result, abysmal returns are the new normal, financial experts are ringing the death knell of buy-and-hold, and investorsâ faith in equities has hit an all-time low. You have choices, you can abandon the stock market, or invest for tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/">Millennial Money &#8211; Patrick O&#8217;Shaughnessy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hoaxes & Deceptions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A BOOK OF THE YEAR FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND FORTUNE MAGAZINE. The epic story of how a young social climber from Malaysia pulled off one of the biggest financial heists in history. In 2015, rumours began circulating that billions of dollars had been stolen from a Malaysian investment fund. The mastermind of the heist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/">Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A BOOK OF THE YEAR FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND FORTUNE MAGAZINE.    </p>
<p>                    The epic story of how a young social climber from Malaysia pulled off one of the biggest financial heists in history.    </p>
<p>                    In 2015, rumours began circulating that billions of dollars had been stolen from a Malaysian investment fund. The mastermind of the heist was twenty-seven-year-old Jho Low, a serial fabulist from an upper-middle-class Malaysian family, who had carefully built his reputation as a member of the jet-setting elite by arranging and financing elaborate parties for Wall Street bankers, celebrities, and even royalty.    </p>
<p>                    With the aid of Goldman Sachs and others, Low stole billions of dollars, right under the nose of global financial industry watchdogs. He used the money to finance elections, purchase luxury real estate, throw champagne-drenched parties, and bankroll Hollywood films like The Wolf of Wall Street.     </p>
<p>                    Billion Dollar Whale reveals how this silver-tongued con man, a &#8216;modern Gatsby&#8217;, emerged from obscurity to pull off one of the most audacious financial heists the world has ever seen, and how the financial industry let him. It is a classic harrowing parable of hubris and greed in the financial world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/">Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Only Game in Town : Central Banks, Instability, and Recovering from Another Collapse &#8211; Mohamed A. El-Erian (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-only-game-in-town-central-banks-instability-and-recovering-from-another-collapse-mohamed-a-el-erian-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-only-game-in-town-central-banks-instability-and-recovering-from-another-collapse-mohamed-a-el-erian-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A roadmap to what lies ahead and the decisions we must make now to stave off the next global economic and financial crisis, from one of the world&#8217;s most influential economic thinkers and the author of When Markets Collide &#8211; Updated, with a new chapter and author&#8217;s note &#8220;The one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-only-game-in-town-central-banks-instability-and-recovering-from-another-collapse-mohamed-a-el-erian-abridged/">The Only Game in Town : Central Banks, Instability, and Recovering from Another Collapse &#8211; Mohamed A. El-Erian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A roadmap to what lies ahead and the decisions we must make now to stave off the next global economic and financial crisis, from one of the world&#8217;s most influential economic thinkers and the author of When Markets Collide &#8211; Updated, with a new chapter and author&#8217;s note     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The one economic book you must read now . . . If you want to understand [our] bifurcated world and where it&#8217;s headed, there is no better interpreter than Mohamed El-Erian.&#8221;&#8211;Time     </p>
<p>                    Our current economic path is coming to an end. The signposts are all around us: sluggish growth, rising inequality, stubbornly high pockets of unemployment, and jittery financial markets, to name a few. Soon we will reach a fork in the road: One path leads to renewed growth, prosperity, and financial stability, the other to recession and market disorder.     </p>
<p>                    In The Only Game in Town,  El-Erian casts his gaze toward the future of the global economy and markets, outlining the choices we face both individually and collectively in an era of economic uncertainty and financial insecurity. Beginning with their response to the 2008 global crisis, El-Erian explains how and why our central banks became the critical policy actors&#8211;and, most important, why they cannot continue is this role alone. They saved the financial system from collapse in 2008 and a multiyear economic depression, but lack the tools to enable a return to high inclusive growth and durable financial stability. The time has come for a policy handoff, from a prolonged period of monetary policy experimentation to a strategy that better targets what ails economies and distorts the financial sector&#8211;before we stumble into another crisis.     </p>
<p>                     The future, critically, is not predestined. It is up to us to decide where we will go from here as households, investors, companies, and governments. Using a mix of insights from economics, finance, and behavioral science, this book gives us the tools we need to properly understand this turning point, prepare for it, and come out of it stronger. A comprehensive, controversial look at the realities of our global economy and markets, The Only Game in Town is required reading for investors, policymakers, and anyone interested in the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-only-game-in-town-central-banks-instability-and-recovering-from-another-collapse-mohamed-a-el-erian-abridged/">The Only Game in Town : Central Banks, Instability, and Recovering from Another Collapse &#8211; Mohamed A. El-Erian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When a pseudonymous programmer introduced &#8220;a new electronic cash system that&#8217;s fully peer-to-peer, with no trusted third party&#8221; to a small online mailing list in 2008, very few paid attention. Ten years later, and against all odds, this upstart autonomous decentralized software offers an unstoppable and globally-accessible hard money alternative to modern central banks. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/">The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When a pseudonymous programmer introduced &#8220;a new electronic cash system that&#8217;s fully peer-to-peer, with no trusted third party&#8221; to a small online mailing list in 2008, very few paid attention. Ten years later, and against all odds, this upstart autonomous decentralized software offers an unstoppable and globally-accessible hard money alternative to modern central banks. The Bitcoin Standard analyzes the historical context to the rise of Bitcoin, the economic properties that have allowed it to grow quickly, and its likely economic, political, and social implications.    </p>
<p>                     While Bitcoin is a new invention of the digital age, the problem it purports to solve is as old as human society itself: transferring value across time and space. Ammous takes the reader on an engaging journey through the history of technologies performing the functions of money, from primitive systems of trading limestones and seashells, to metals, coins, the gold standard, and modern government debt. Exploring what gave these technologies their monetary role, and how most lost it, provides the reader with a good idea of what makes for sound money, and sets the stage for an economic discussion of its consequences for individual and societal future-orientation, capital accumulation, trade, peace, culture, and art. Compellingly, Ammous shows that it is no coincidence that the loftiest achievements of humanity have come in societies enjoying the benefits of sound monetary regimes, nor is it coincidental that monetary collapse has usually accompanied civilizational collapse.    </p>
<p>                     With this background in place, the book moves on to explain the operation of Bitcoin in a functional and intuitive way. Bitcoin is a decentralized, distributed piece of software that converts electricity and processing power into indisputably accurate records, thus allowing its users to utilize the Internet to perform the traditional functions of money without having to rely on, or trust, any authorities or infrastructure in the physical world. Bitcoin is thus best understood as the first successfully implemented form of digital cash and digital hard money. With an automated and perfectly predictable monetary policy, and the ability to perform final settlement of large sums across the world in a matter of minutes, Bitcoin&#8217;s real competitive edge might just be as a store of value and network for final settlement of large payments-a digital form of gold with a built-in settlement infrastructure.    </p>
<p>                     Ammous&#8217; firm grasp of the technological possibilities as well as the historical realities of monetary evolution provides for a fascinating exploration of the ramifications of voluntary free market money. As it challenges the most sacred of government monopolies, Bitcoin shifts the pendulum of sovereignty away from governments in favor of individuals, offering us the tantalizing possibility of a world where money is fully extricated from politics and unrestrained by borders.    </p>
<p>                     The final chapter of the book explores some of the most common questions surrounding Bitcoin: Is Bitcoin mining a waste of energy? Is Bitcoin for criminals? Who controls Bitcoin, and can they change it if they please? How can Bitcoin be killed? And what to make of all the thousands of Bitcoin knock-offs, and the many supposed applications of Bitcoin&#8217;s &#8216;blockchain technology&#8217;? The Bitcoin Standard is the essential resource for a clear understanding of the rise of the Internet&#8217;s decentralized, apolitical, free-market alternative to national central banks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/">The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019    </p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review    </p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.    </p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.    </p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his rich and nuanced portrait of the remarkable, elusive Rothschild family, Oxford scholar and bestselling author Niall Ferguson uncovers the secrets behind the family&#8217;s phenomenal economic success. He reveals for the first time the details of the family&#8217;s vast political network, which gave it access to and influence over many of the greatest statesmen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his rich and nuanced portrait of the remarkable, elusive Rothschild  family, Oxford scholar and bestselling author Niall Ferguson uncovers  the secrets behind the family&#8217;s phenomenal economic success. He reveals  for the first time the details of the family&#8217;s vast political network,  which gave it access to and influence over many of the greatest  statesmen of the age. And he tells a family saga, tracing the importance  of unity and the profound role of Judaism in the lives of a dynasty  that rose from the confines of the Frankfurt ghetto and later used its  influence to assist oppressed Jews throughout Europe. A definitive work  of impeccable scholarship with a thoroughly engaging narrative, &#8216;The  House of Rothschild&#8217; is a biography of the rarest kind, in which  mysterious and fascinating historical figures finally spring to life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Books, Manuscripts, Ephemera & Printed Matter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that a bank be established to issue paper money with the credit based on the value of land. But Queen Anne was not about to take advice from a gambler and felon. So, in exile in Paris, he convinced the bankrupt court of Louis XV of the value of his idea.<br />
                     Law soon engineered the revival of the French economy and found himself one of the most powerful men in Europe. In August 1717, he founded the Mississippi Company, and the Court granted him the right to trade in France&#8217;s vast territory in America. The shareholders in his new trading company made such enormous profits that the term millionaire was coined to describe them. Paris was soon in a frenzy of speculation, conspiracies, and insatiable consumption. Before this first boom-and-bust cycle was complete, markets throughout Europe crashed, the mob began calling for Law&#8217;s head, and his visionary ideas about what money could do were abandoned and forgotten.<br />
                     In Millionaire,  Janet Gleeson lucidly reconstructs this epic drama where fortunes were made and lost, paupers grew rich, and lords fell into penury &#8212; and a modern fiscal philosophy was born. Her enthralling tragicomic tale reveals two great characters: John Law, with his complex personality and inscrutable motives, and money itself, whose true nature even to this day remains elusive</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secrets of Sand Hill Road : Venture Capital-and How to Get It &#8211; Scott Kupor, Foreword by Eric Ries (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/secrets-of-sand-hill-road-venture-capital-and-how-to-get-it-scott-kupor-foreword-by-eric-ries-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/secrets-of-sand-hill-road-venture-capital-and-how-to-get-it-scott-kupor-foreword-by-eric-ries-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Worth far more than its cover price &#8230; I wish I&#8217;d had it available to me when I was first looking for startup funding&#8217; &#8212; Eric Ries Every startup needs capital, and ambitious startups seek it on Sand Hill Road &#8211; Silicon Valley&#8217;s dream street for entrepreneurs. That&#8217;s where you&#8217;ll find the biggest names in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-sand-hill-road-venture-capital-and-how-to-get-it-scott-kupor-foreword-by-eric-ries-abridged/">Secrets of Sand Hill Road : Venture Capital-and How to Get It &#8211; Scott Kupor, Foreword by Eric Ries (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Worth far more than its cover price &#8230; I wish I&#8217;d had it available to me when I was first looking for startup funding&#8217; &#8212; Eric Ries    </p>
<p>                    Every startup needs capital, and ambitious startups seek it on Sand Hill Road &#8211; Silicon Valley&#8217;s dream street for entrepreneurs. That&#8217;s where you&#8217;ll find the biggest names in venture capital, including the famed VC firm Andreessen Horowitz, where lawyer-turned-entrepreneur-turned-VC Scott Kupor serves as managing partner.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re trying to get a new company off the ground or scale an existing business to the next level, you need to understand how VCs think. Secrets of Sand Hill Road is the first book that shows you exactly how VCs decide where and how much to invest. It will help you get the best possible deal and make the most of your relationships with VCs. You&#8217;ll learn, for instance:    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why most VCs typically invest in only one startup in a given business category<br />
                    &#8212; Why the talent you need most when raising venture capital is your storytelling ability<br />
                    &#8212; How to handle a &#8216;down round&#8217;, when you have to raise funds at a lower valuation than in your previous round<br />
                    &#8212; Why bridge financing (reopening your last round to existing investors) is generally a bad idea<br />
                    &#8212; What to do when VCs get too entangled in the day-to-day operations of your business<br />
                    &#8212; Why you need to build relationships with potential acquirers long before you decide to sell    </p>
<p>                    Filled with Kupor&#8217;s firsthand experiences, insider advice, and practical takeaways, Secrets of Sand Hill Road is the guide you need to turn yourstartup into the next unicorn.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-sand-hill-road-venture-capital-and-how-to-get-it-scott-kupor-foreword-by-eric-ries-abridged/">Secrets of Sand Hill Road : Venture Capital-and How to Get It &#8211; Scott Kupor, Foreword by Eric Ries (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2019 Lionel Gelber Prize &#8216;Majestic, informative and often delightful &#8230; insights on every page&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis, Observer The definitive history of the Great Financial Crisis, from the acclaimed author of The Deluge and The Wages of Destruction. In September 2008 the Great Financial Crisis, triggered by the collapse of Lehman brothers, shook [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/">Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2019 Lionel Gelber Prize    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Majestic, informative and often delightful &#8230; insights on every page&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis, Observer    </p>
<p>                    The definitive history of the Great Financial Crisis, from the acclaimed author of The Deluge and The Wages of Destruction.     </p>
<p>                    In September 2008 the Great Financial Crisis, triggered by the collapse of Lehman brothers, shook the world. A decade later its spectre still haunts us. As the appalling scope and scale of the crash was revealed, the financial institutions that had symbolised the West&#8217;s triumph since the end of the Cold War, seemed &#8211; through greed, malice and incompetence &#8211; to be about to bring the entire system to its knees.    </p>
<p>                    Crashed is a brilliantly original and assured analysis of what happened and how we were rescued from something even worse &#8211; but at a price which continues to undermine democracy across Europe and the United States. Gnawing away at our institutions are the many billions of dollars which were conjured up to prevent complete collapse. Over and over again, the end of the crisis has been announced, but it continues to hound us &#8211; whether in Greece or Ukraine, whether through Brexit or Trump. Adam Tooze follows the trail like no previous writer and has written a book compelling as history, as economic analysis and as political horror story.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/">Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A tour de force of historical reportage, America&#8217;s Bank illuminates the tumultuous era and remarkable personalities that spurred the unlikely birth of America&#8217;s modern central bank, the Federal Reserve. Today, the Fed is the bedrock of the financial landscape, yet the fight to create it was so protracted and divisive that it seems a small [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A tour de force of historical reportage, America&#8217;s Bank illuminates the tumultuous era and remarkable personalities that spurred the unlikely birth of America&#8217;s modern central bank, the Federal Reserve. Today, the Fed is the bedrock of the financial landscape, yet the fight to create it was so protracted and divisive that it seems a small miracle that it was ever established.     </p>
<p>                    For nearly a century, America, alone among developed nations, refused to consider any central or organizing agency in its financial system. Americans&#8217; mistrust of big government and of big banks-a legacy of the country&#8217;s Jeffersonian, small-government traditions-was so widespread that modernizing reform was deemed impossible. Each bank was left to stand on its own, with no central reserve or lender of last resort. The real-world consequences of this chaotic and provincial system were frequent financial panics, bank runs, money shortages, and depressions. By the first decade of the twentieth century, it had become plain that the outmoded banking system was ill equipped to finance America&#8217;s burgeoning industry. But political will for reform was lacking. It took an economic meltdown, a high-level tour of Europe, and-improbably-a conspiratorial effort by vilified captains of Wall Street to overcome popular resistance. Finally, in 1913, Congress conceived a federalist and quintessentially American solution to the conflict that had divided bankers, farmers, populists, and ordinary Americans, and enacted the landmark Federal Reserve Act.    </p>
<p>                    Roger Lowenstein-acclaimed financial journalist and bestselling author of When Genius Failed and The End of Wall Street-tells the drama-laden story of how America created the Federal Reserve, thereby taking its first steps onto the world stage as a global financial power. America&#8217;s Bank showcases Lowenstein at his very finest: illuminating complex financial and political issues with striking clarity, infusing the debates of our past with all the gripping immediacy of today, and painting unforgettable portraits of Gilded Age bankers, presidents, and politicians.    </p>
<p>                    Lowenstein focuses on the four men at the heart of the struggle to create the Federal Reserve. These were Paul Warburg, a refined, German-born financier, recently relocated to New York, who was horrified by the primitive condition of America&#8217;s finances; Rhode Island&#8217;s Nelson W. Aldrich, the reigning power broker in the U.S. Senate and an archetypal Gilded Age legislator; Carter Glass, the ambitious, if then little-known, Virginia congressman who chaired the House Banking Committee at a crucial moment of political transition; and President Woodrow Wilson, the academician-turned-progressive-politician who forced Glass to reconcile his deep-seated differences with bankers and accept the principle (anathema to southern Democrats) of federal control. Weaving together a raucous era in American politics with a storied financial crisis and intrigue at the highest levels of Washington and Wall Street, Lowenstein brings the beginnings of one of the country&#8217;s most crucial institutions to vivid and unforgettable life. Readers of this gripping historical narrative will wonder whether they&#8217;re reading about one hundred years ago or the still-seething conflicts that mark our discussions of banking and politics today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Other People&#8217;s Money : Masters of the Universe or Servants of the People? &#8211; John Kay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/other-peoples-money-masters-of-the-universe-or-servants-of-the-people-john-kay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/other-peoples-money-masters-of-the-universe-or-servants-of-the-people-john-kay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Orwell Prize 2016 We all depend on the finance sector. We need it to store our money, manage our payments, finance housing stock, restore infrastructure, fund retirement and support new business. But these roles comprise only a tiny sliver of the sector&#8217;s activity: the vast majority of lending is within the finance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-peoples-money-masters-of-the-universe-or-servants-of-the-people-john-kay-abridged/">Other People&#8217;s Money : Masters of the Universe or Servants of the People? &#8211; John Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Orwell Prize 2016    </p>
<p>                    We all depend on the finance sector. We need it to store our money, manage our payments, finance housing stock, restore infrastructure, fund retirement and support new business. But these roles comprise only a tiny sliver of the sector&#8217;s activity: the vast majority of lending is within the finance sector. So what is it all for?  What is the purpose of this activity?  And why is it so profitable?    </p>
<p>                    John Kay, a distinguished economist with wide experience of the financial sector, argues that the industry&#8217;s perceived profitability is partly illusory, and partly an appropriation of wealth created elsewhere &#8211; of other people&#8217;s money. The financial sector, he shows, has grown too large, detached itself from ordinary business and everyday life, and has become an industry that mostly trades with itself, talks to itself, and judges itself by reference to standards which it has itself generated. And the outside world has itself adopted those standards, bailing out financial institutions that have failed all of us through greed and mismanagement.      </p>
<p>                    We need finance, but today we have far too much of a good thing. In Other People&#8217;s Money John Kay shows in his inimitable style what has gone wrong in the dark heart of finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-peoples-money-masters-of-the-universe-or-servants-of-the-people-john-kay-abridged/">Other People&#8217;s Money : Masters of the Universe or Servants of the People? &#8211; John Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
