<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Biotechnology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/biotechnology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/biotechnology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Biotechnology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/biotechnology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Ridley leaps from chromosome to chromosome in a handy summation of our ever increasing understanding of the roles that genes play in disease, behavior, sexual differences, and even intelligence. . . . . He addresses not only the ethical quandaries faced by contemporary scientists but the reductionist danger in equating inheritability with inevitability.&#8221; &#8212; The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/">Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Ridley leaps from chromosome to chromosome in a handy summation of our ever increasing understanding of the roles that genes play in disease, behavior, sexual differences, and even intelligence. . . . . He addresses not only the ethical quandaries faced by contemporary scientists but the reductionist danger in equating inheritability with inevitability.&#8221; &#8212; The New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    The genome&#8217;s been mapped. But what does it mean? Matt Ridley&#8217;s Genome is the book that explains it all: what it is, how it works, and what it portends for the future    </p>
<p>                    Arguably the most significant scientific discovery of the new century, the mapping of the twenty-three pairs of chromosomes that make up the human genome raises almost as many questions as it answers. Questions that will profoundly impact the way we think about disease, about longevity, and about free will. Questions that will affect the rest of your life.    </p>
<p>                    Genome offers extraordinary insight into the ramifications of this incredible breakthrough. By picking one newly discovered gene from each pair of chromosomes and telling its story, Matt Ridley recounts the history of our species and its ancestors from the dawn of life to the brink of future medicine. From Huntington&#8217;s disease to cancer, from the applications of gene therapy to the horrors of eugenics, Ridley probes the scientific, philosophical, and moral issues arising as a result of the mapping of the genome. It will help you understand what this scientific milestone means for you, for your children, and for humankind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/">Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Crack in Creation : Gene Editing and the Unthinkable Power to Control Evolution &#8211; Jennifer A Doudna, Samuel H Sternberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BY THE WINNER OF THE 2020 NOBEL PRIZE IN CHEMISTRY Finalist for the Los Angeles Times Book Prize &#8220;A powerful mix of science and ethics . . . This book is required reading for every concerned citizen&#8211;the material it covers should be discussed in schools, colleges, and universities throughout the country.&#8221;&#8211; New York Review of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/">A Crack in Creation : Gene Editing and the Unthinkable Power to Control Evolution &#8211; Jennifer A Doudna, Samuel H Sternberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BY THE WINNER OF THE 2020 NOBEL PRIZE IN CHEMISTRY Finalist for the Los Angeles Times Book Prize     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A powerful mix of science and ethics . . . This book is required reading for every concerned citizen&#8211;the material it covers should be discussed in schools, colleges, and universities throughout the country.&#8221;&#8211; New York Review of Books      </p>
<p>                     Not since the atomic bomb has a technology so alarmed its inventors that they warned the world about its use. That is, until 2015, when biologist Jennifer Doudna called for a worldwide moratorium on the use of the gene-editing tool CRISPR&#8211;a revolutionary new technology that she helped create&#8211;to make heritable changes in human embryos. The cheapest, simplest, most effective way of manipulating DNA ever known, CRISPR may well give us the cure to HIV, genetic diseases, and some cancers. Yet even the tiniest changes to DNA could have myriad, unforeseeable consequences, to say nothing of the ethical and societal repercussions of intentionally mutating embryos to create &#8220;better&#8221; humans. Writing with fellow researcher Sam Sternberg, Doudna&#8211;who has since won the Nobel Prize for her CRISPR research&#8211;shares the thrilling story of her discovery and describes the enormous responsibility that comes with the power to rewrite the code of life.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The future is in our hands as never before, and this book explains the stakes like no other.&#8221; &#8212; George Lucas     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An invaluable account . . . We owe Doudna several times over.&#8221; &#8212; Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-crack-in-creation-gene-editing-and-the-unthinkable-power-to-control-evolution-jennifer-a-doudna-samuel-h-sternberg-abridged/">A Crack in Creation : Gene Editing and the Unthinkable Power to Control Evolution &#8211; Jennifer A Doudna, Samuel H Sternberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a New Afterword Must We Age? Nearly all scientists who study the biology of aging agree that we will someday be able to substantially slow down the aging process, extending our productive, youthful lives. Dr. Aubrey de Grey is perhaps the most bullish of all such researchers. As has been reported in media outlets [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/">Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a New Afterword     </p>
<p>                    Must We Age?     </p>
<p>                    Nearly all scientists who study the biology of aging agree that we will someday be able to substantially slow down the aging process, extending our productive, youthful lives. Dr. Aubrey de Grey is perhaps the most bullish of all such researchers. As has been reported in media outlets ranging from 60 Minutes to The New York Times,  Dr. de Grey believes that the key biomedical technology required to eliminate aging-derived debilitation and death entirely&#8211;technology that would not only slow but periodically reverse age-related physiological decay, leaving us biologically young into an indefinite future&#8211;is now within reach.     </p>
<p>                    In Ending Aging,  Dr. de Grey and his research assistant Michael Rae describe the details of this biotechnology. They explain that the aging of the human body, just like the aging of man-made machines, results from an accumulation of various types of damage. As with man-made machines, this damage can periodically be repaired, leading to indefinite extension of the machine&#8217;s fully functional lifetime, just as is routinely done with classic cars. We already know what types of damage accumulate in the human body, and we are moving rapidly toward the comprehensive development of technologies to remove that -damage. By demystifying aging and its postponement for the nonspecialist reader, de Grey and Rae systematically dismantle the fatalist presumption that aging will forever defeat the efforts of medical science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/">Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
