<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700 Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/early-modern-history-c-1450-1500-to-c-1700/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/early-modern-history-c-1450-1500-to-c-1700/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700 Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/early-modern-history-c-1450-1500-to-c-1700/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable. We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now is humanity&#8217;s best moment. And our most fragile. Global health, wealth and education are booming. Scientific discovery is flourishing. But the same forces that make big gains possible for some of us deliver big losses to others-and tangle us together in ways that make everyone vulnerable.    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve been here before. The first Renaissance, the time of Columbus, Copernicus, Gutenberg and others, redrew all maps of the world, liberated information and shifted Western civilization from the medieval to the early modern era. Such change came at a price: social division, political extremism, economic shocks, pandemics and other unintended consequences of human endeavour.    </p>
<p>                    Now is our second Renaissance. In the face of terrorism, Brexit, refugee crises and the global impact of a Trump presidency, we can flourish-if we heed the urgent lessons of history. Age of Discovery, revised and updated for this paperback edition, shows us how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-discovery-navigating-the-storms-of-our-second-renaissance-revised-edition-ian-goldin-chris-kutarna-abridged/">Age of Discovery : Navigating the Storms of Our Second Renaissance (Revised Edition) &#8211; Ian Goldin, Chris Kutarna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Da Vinci&#8217;s Ghost : Genius, Obsession, and How Leonardo Created the World in His Own Image &#8211; Toby Lester (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/da-vincis-ghost-genius-obsession-and-how-leonardo-created-the-world-in-his-own-image-toby-lester-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History: Renaissance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Artists, Art Monographs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/da-vincis-ghost-genius-obsession-and-how-leonardo-created-the-world-in-his-own-image-toby-lester-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Da Vinci&#8217;s Ghost, critically acclaimed historian Toby Lester tells the story of the world&#8217;s most iconic image, the Vitruvian Man, and sheds surprising new light on the artistry and scholarship of Leonardo da Vinci, one of history&#8217;s most fascinating figures. Deftly weaving together art, architecture, history, theology, and much else, Da Vinci&#8217;s Ghost is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/da-vincis-ghost-genius-obsession-and-how-leonardo-created-the-world-in-his-own-image-toby-lester-abridged/">Da Vinci&#8217;s Ghost : Genius, Obsession, and How Leonardo Created the World in His Own Image &#8211; Toby Lester (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Da Vinci&#8217;s Ghost, critically acclaimed historian Toby Lester tells the story of the world&#8217;s most iconic image, the Vitruvian Man, and sheds surprising new light on the artistry and scholarship of Leonardo da Vinci, one of history&#8217;s most fascinating figures.     </p>
<p>                    Deftly weaving together art, architecture, history, theology, and much else, Da Vinci&#8217;s Ghost is a first-rate intellectual enchantment.&#8221;&#8211;Charles Mann, author of 1493     </p>
<p>                    Da Vinci didn&#8217;t summon Vitruvian Man out of thin air. He was inspired by the idea originally formulated by the Roman architect Vitruvius, who suggested that the human body could be made to fit inside a circle, long associated with the divine, and a square, related to the earthly and secular. To place a man inside those shapes was to imply that the human body could indeed be a blueprint for the workings of the universe. Da Vinci elevated Vitruvius&#8217; idea to exhilarating heights when he set out to do something unprecedented, if the human body truly reflected the cosmos, he reasoned, then studying its anatomy more thoroughly than had ever been attempted before&#8211;peering deep into body and soul&#8211;might grant him an almost godlike perspective on the makeup of the world.     </p>
<p>                    Written with the same narrative flair and intellectual sweep as Lester&#8217;s award-winning first book, the &#8220;almost unbearably thrilling&#8221; (Simon Winchester) Fourth Part of the World, and beautifully illustrated with Da Vinci&#8217;s drawings, Da Vinci&#8217;s Ghost follows Da Vinci on his journey to understanding the secrets of the Vitruvian man. It captures a pivotal time in Western history when the Middle Ages were giving way to the Renaissance, when art, science, and philosophy were rapidly converging, and when it seemed possible that a single human being might embody&#8211;and even understand&#8211;the nature of the universe.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/da-vincis-ghost-genius-obsession-and-how-leonardo-created-the-world-in-his-own-image-toby-lester-abridged/">Da Vinci&#8217;s Ghost : Genius, Obsession, and How Leonardo Created the World in His Own Image &#8211; Toby Lester (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Napoleonic Wars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions, Uprisings, Rebellions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217; Simon Sebag Montefiore &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon. Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the  momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217;   Simon Sebag Montefiore<br />
                    &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell    </p>
<p>                    From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon.    </p>
<p>                    Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of all human lives. In the space of just twenty years, from October 1795 when as a young artillery captain he cleared the streets of Paris of insurrectionists, to his final defeat at the (horribly mismanaged) battle of Waterloo in June 1815, Napoleon transformed France and Europe. After seizing power in a coup d&#8217;etat he ended the corruption and incompetence into which the Revolution had descended. In a series of dazzling battles he reinvented the art of warfare; in peace, he completely remade the laws of France, modernised her systems of education and administration, and presided over a flourishing of the beautiful &#8216;Empire style&#8217; in the arts. The impossibility of defeating his most persistent enemy, Great Britain, led him to make draining and ultimately fatal expeditions into Spain and Russia, where half a million Frenchmen died and his Empire began to unravel.    </p>
<p>                    More than any other modern biographer, Andrew Roberts conveys Napoleon&#8217;s tremendous energy, both physical and intellectual, and the attractiveness of his personality, even to his enemies. He has walked 53 of Napoleon&#8217;s 60 battlefields, and has absorbed the gigantic new French edition of Napoleon&#8217;s letters, which allows a complete re-evaluation of this exceptional man. He overturns many received opinions, including the myth of a great romance with Josephine: she took a lover immediately after their marriage, and, as Roberts shows, he had three times as many mistresses as he acknowledged.    </p>
<p>                    Of the climactic Battle of Leipzig in 1813, as the fighting closed around them, a French sergeant-major wrote, &#8216;No-one who has not experienced it can have any idea of the enthusiasm that burst forth among the half-starved, exhausted soldiers when the Emperor was there in person. If all were demoralised and he appeared, his presence was like an electric shock. All shouted &#8220;Vive l&#8217;Empereur!&#8221; and everyone charged blindly into the fire.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    The reader of this biography will understand why this was so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
