<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Television Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/television/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/television/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:08:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Television Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/television/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Stranger Things: Worlds Turned Upside Down : The Official Behind-The-Scenes Companion &#8211; Gina Mcintyre</title>
		<link>/stranger-things-worlds-turned-upside-down-the-official-behind-the-scenes-companion-gina-mcintyre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stranger-things-worlds-turned-upside-down-the-official-behind-the-scenes-companion-gina-mcintyre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER Welcome to Hawkins, Indiana. The official behind-the-scenes companion guide to the first two seasons of Stranger Things and beyond, brought to life with exclusive photos and stunning concept art. Stranger things have happened. . . . When the first season of Stranger Things debuted on Netflix in the summer of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stranger-things-worlds-turned-upside-down-the-official-behind-the-scenes-companion-gina-mcintyre/">Stranger Things: Worlds Turned Upside Down : The Official Behind-The-Scenes Companion &#8211; Gina Mcintyre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>Welcome to Hawkins, Indiana.</p>
<p>The official behind-the-scenes companion guide to the first two seasons of Stranger Things and beyond, brought to life with exclusive photos and stunning concept art.</p>
<p>Stranger things have happened. . . .</p>
<p>When the first season of Stranger Things  debuted on Netflix in the summer of 2016, the show struck a nerve with  millions of viewers worldwide and received broad critical acclaim. The  series has gone on to win six Emmy Awards, but its success was  driven more than anything by word of mouth, resonating across  generations. Viewers feel personal connections to the characters. Now  fans can immerse themselves in the world-or worlds-of Hawkins, Indiana,  like never before. Inside you&#8217;ll find</p>
<p>* original commentary and a foreword from creators Matt and Ross Duffer<br />
* exclusive interviews with the stars of the show, including Millie Bobby Brown, Finn Wolfhard, and David Harbour<br />
* the show&#8217;s earliest drafts, pitches to Netflix, and casting calls<br />
* insights into the Duffers&#8217; creative process from the entire crew-from  costume and set designers to composers and visual-effects specialists<br />
* deep dives into the cultural artifacts and references that inspired the look and feel of the show<br />
* a map of everyday Hawkins-with clues charting the network of the Upside Down<br />
* a digital copy of the Morse code disk Eleven uses, so you can decipher secret messages embedded throughout the text<br />
* a look into the future of the series-including a sneak preview of season three!</p>
<p>Adding whole new layers to enrich the viewing experience, this keepsake is essential reading for anyone and everyone who loves Stranger Things.</p>
<p>sn apisui si umop apisdn</p>
<p>Note: The ebook is best viewed on a colour device with a larger screen.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stranger-things-worlds-turned-upside-down-the-official-behind-the-scenes-companion-gina-mcintyre/">Stranger Things: Worlds Turned Upside Down : The Official Behind-The-Scenes Companion &#8211; Gina Mcintyre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</title>
		<link>/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR </p>
<p>                     When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch a cable news network in 1996, American politics and media changed forever. With a remarkable level of detail and insight, Vanity Fair magazine reporter Gabriel Sherman puts Ailes&#8217;s unique genius on display, along with the outsize personalities&#8211;Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Sean Hannity, Megyn Kelly, Sarah Palin, Karl Rove, Glenn Beck, Mike Huckabee, Gretchen Carlson, Bill Shine, and others&#8211;who have helped Fox News play a defining role in the great social and political controversies of the past two decades. From the Clinton-Lewinsky scandal to the Bush-Gore recount, from the war in Iraq to the Tea Party attack on the Obama presidency, Roger Ailes developed an unrivaled power to sway the national agenda. Even more, he became the indispensable figure in conservative America and the man any Republican politician with presidential aspirations had to court. </p>
<p>                     How did this man become the master strategist of our political landscape? In revelatory detail, Sherman chronicles the rise of Ailes, a frail kid from an Ohio factory town who, through sheer willpower, the flair of a showman, fierce corporate politicking, and a profound understanding of the priorities of middle America, built the most influential television news empire of our time. </p>
<p>                     Drawing on hundreds of interviews with Fox News insiders past and present, Sherman documents Ailes&#8217;s tactical acuity as he battled the press, business rivals, and countless real and perceived enemies inside and outside Fox. Sherman takes us inside the morning meetings in which Ailes and other high-level executives strategized Fox&#8217;s presentation of the news to advance Ailes&#8217;s political agenda; provides behind-the-scenes details of Ailes&#8217;s crucial role as finder and shaper of talent, including his sometimes rocky relationships with Fox News stars such as O&#8217;Reilly, Hannity, and Carlson; and probes Ailes&#8217;s fraught partnership with his equally brash and mercurial boss, Rupert Murdoch. </p>
<p>                     Roger Ailes&#8217;s life is a story worthy of Citizen Kane. Featuring an afterword about Ailes&#8217;s epic downfall during the extraordinary 2016 election, The Loudest Voice in the Room is an extraordinary feat of reportage with a compelling human drama at its heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Late Shift : Letterman, Leno, &#038; the Network Battle for the Night &#8211; Bill Carter</title>
		<link>/the-late-shift-letterman-leno-the-network-battle-for-the-night-bill-carter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Radio & Television Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-late-shift-letterman-leno-the-network-battle-for-the-night-bill-carter/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;gripping&#8221; New York Times bestseller from the host of CNN podcast Behind the Desk tells the true story-and backstage drama-of late-night comedy (Los Angeles Times). When beloved host Johnny Carson announced his retirement after thirty years on The Tonight Show, millions of Americans mourned. But inside the television industry, the news ignited a battle [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-late-shift-letterman-leno-the-network-battle-for-the-night-bill-carter/">The Late Shift : Letterman, Leno, &#038; the Network Battle for the Night &#8211; Bill Carter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;gripping&#8221; New York Times bestseller from the host of CNN podcast Behind the Desk tells the true story-and backstage drama-of late-night comedy (Los Angeles Times).</p>
<p>                     When beloved host Johnny Carson announced his retirement after thirty years on The Tonight Show, millions of Americans mourned. But inside the television industry, the news ignited a battle between two amazing talents-Jay Leno and David Letterman-who both yearned to occupy the departing legend&#8217;s chair. For NBC, it would be a decision with millions of dollars at stake. Soon these two comedians with strikingly different styles, who had once shared a friendship as they worked the clubs together, would be engaged in a fierce competition for the prize.</p>
<p>                     Based on in-depth reporting and interviews with those involved, and updated with a new introduction by the author-a producer of CNN series The Story of Late Night-The Late Shift is a &#8220;vivid, behind-the-scenes, blow-by-blow account&#8221; of the fight that ensued, as stars, agents, and executives maneuvered for control of the most profitable program in TV history (Chicago Tribune).</p>
<p>                     &#8220;Remarkably gripping . . . Takes us deep into the bizarre high-stakes world of broadcasting . . . A powerful story, and ultimately a sad one, filled with casualties as well as winners.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                     &#8220;Solid reporting, based on extensive interviews with the principals, lifts The Late Shift into a class of its own. . . . The insights into the people involved are what make [the book] a page-turner.&#8221; -Orange Country Register</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-late-shift-letterman-leno-the-network-battle-for-the-night-bill-carter/">The Late Shift : Letterman, Leno, &#038; the Network Battle for the Night &#8211; Bill Carter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Office &#8211; Andy Greene</title>
		<link>/the-office-andy-greene/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-office-andy-greene/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER The untold stories behind The Office, one of the most iconic television shows of the twenty-first century, told by its creators, writers, and actors When did you last hang out with Jim, Pam, Dwight, Michael, and the rest of Dunder Mifflin? It might have been back in 2013, when [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-office-andy-greene/">The Office &#8211; Andy Greene</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER </p>
<p>                    The untold stories behind The Office, one of the most iconic television shows of the twenty-first century, told by its creators, writers, and actors </p>
<p>                     When did you last hang out with Jim, Pam, Dwight, Michael, and the rest of Dunder Mifflin? It might have been back in 2013, when the series finale aired . . . or it might have been last night, when you watched three episodes in a row. But either way, long after the show first aired, it&#8217;s more popular than ever, and fans have only one problem&#8211;what to watch, or read, next. </p>
<p>                     Fortunately, Rolling Stone writer Andy Greene has that answer. In his brand-new oral history, The Office: The Untold Story of the Greatest Sitcom of the 2000s, Greene will take readers behind the scenes of their favorite moments and characters. Greene gives us the true inside story behind the entire show, from its origins on the BBC through its impressive nine-season run in America, with in-depth research and exclusive interviews. Fans will get the inside scoop on key episodes from The Dundies to Threat Level Midnight and Goodbye, Michael, including behind-the-scenes details like the battle to keep it on the air when NBC wanted to pull the plug after just six episodes and the failed attempt to bring in James Gandolfini as the new boss after Steve Carell left, spotlighting the incredible, genre-redefining show created by the family-like team, who together took a quirky British import with dicey prospects and turned it into a primetime giant with true historical and cultural significance. </p>
<p>                     Hilarious, heartwarming, and revelatory, The Office gives fans and pop culture buffs a front-row seat to the phenomenal sequence of events that launched The Office into wild popularity, changing the face of television and how we all see our office lives for decades to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-office-andy-greene/">The Office &#8211; Andy Greene</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing &#8211; Bob Mortimer</title>
		<link>/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Angling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fishing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV Tie-in Humour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller Two comedy greats talk life, friendship and the joys of fishing&#8230; Bob Mortimer and Paul Whitehouse have been friends for 30 years, but when life intervened, what was once a joyous and spontaneous friendship dwindled to the odd phone call or occasional catch up. Then, Glory Be! They were both diagnosed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/">Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing &#8211; Bob Mortimer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller</p>
<p>                    Two comedy greats talk life, friendship and the joys of fishing&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Bob Mortimer and Paul Whitehouse have been friends for 30 years, but when life intervened, what was once a joyous and spontaneous friendship dwindled to the odd phone call or occasional catch up. Then, Glory Be! They were both diagnosed with heart disease and realised that time is short. They&#8217;d better spend it fishing&#8230;</p>
<p>                    So they dusted off their kits, chucked on their waders and ventured into the achingly beautiful British countryside to fish, rediscover the joys of their friendship and ruminate on some of life&#8217;s most profound questions, such as: How did we get so old? Where are all the fish? What are your favourite pocket meats? What should we do if we find a corpse?   </p>
<p>                    Following the success of the BBC&#8217;s Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing series, this wonderful book by two lifelong friends is a love letter to the joys of angling, the thrill of the catch and the virtue of having a right daft laff with your mates. On the fish, the equipment, the food, and the locations, Gone Fishing is the perfect book for fans of Bob Mortimer, Paul Whitehouse and for anyone who wants to read a brilliantly written and endlessly funny joint memoir on life, friendship and joys of fishing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/">Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing &#8211; Bob Mortimer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Incomplete History of Secret Organizations : An Utterly Unreliable Account of Netflix&#8217;s a Series of Unfortunate Events &#8211; Joe Tracz</title>
		<link>/the-incomplete-history-of-secret-organizations-an-utterly-unreliable-account-of-netflixs-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-joe-tracz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History: From c 1960]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film: Styles & Genres]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-incomplete-history-of-secret-organizations-an-utterly-unreliable-account-of-netflixs-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-joe-tracz/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This mysterious illustrated tie-in to Netflix&#8217;s award-winning A Series of Unfortunate Events &#8212; featuring an introduction by Count Olaf&#8217;s legal representative, Neil Patrick Harris &#8212; shares insider secrets about the Baudelaire family and the making of the show. In every library there is a single book that can answer the question that burns like a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-incomplete-history-of-secret-organizations-an-utterly-unreliable-account-of-netflixs-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-joe-tracz/">The Incomplete History of Secret Organizations : An Utterly Unreliable Account of Netflix&#8217;s a Series of Unfortunate Events &#8211; Joe Tracz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This mysterious illustrated tie-in to Netflix&#8217;s award-winning A Series of Unfortunate Events &#8212; featuring an introduction by Count Olaf&#8217;s legal representative, Neil Patrick Harris &#8212; shares insider secrets about the Baudelaire family and the making of the show. </p>
<p>                     In every library there is a single book that can answer the question that burns like a fire in the mind&#8230; </p>
<p>                    In this collector&#8217;s companion you will discover never-before-seen photographs, never-before-told stories, and never-before, revealed secrets spanning all three seasons of the hilariously twisted, critically acclaimed hit series. You will encounter original concept art, annotated script excerpts, and interviews with the creative team and all-star cast, as well as glossaries, recipes, lyric sheets, hidden Easter eggs, shocking backstories, and suspicious pages from the titular tome, unredacted, and revealed here for the first time. </p>
<p>                     Featuring interviews with: </p>
<p>                    Tony HaleDaniel HandlerAasif MandviSara RueBarry SonnenfeldPatrick WarburtonBo WelchAlfre Woodardand more&#8230; </p>
<p>                     Perhaps you are wondering how a noble person such as yourself might become a member of a secret organization. Like so many things in life, it starts by picking up the right book. So go ahead, read at your own risk.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-incomplete-history-of-secret-organizations-an-utterly-unreliable-account-of-netflixs-a-series-of-unfortunate-events-joe-tracz/">The Incomplete History of Secret Organizations : An Utterly Unreliable Account of Netflix&#8217;s a Series of Unfortunate Events &#8211; Joe Tracz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secrets of My Life &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner</title>
		<link>/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Transsexuals & Hermaphroditism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nonfiction History Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER In this remarkable memoir &#8211; written with Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Buzz Bissinger during her pivotal first years of rebirth &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner reflects on her past as she looks to her future. With poignancy and humour, Caitlyn writes about her confusion growing up, the temporary triumph of the Olympics as Bruce [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/">The Secrets of My Life &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    In this remarkable memoir &#8211; written with Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Buzz Bissinger during her pivotal first years of rebirth &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner reflects on her past as she looks to her future.     </p>
<p>                    With poignancy and humour, Caitlyn writes about her confusion growing up, the temporary triumph of the Olympics as Bruce Jenner, and the noose of being endlessly described as the ultimate in manhood. She reveals her sense of shame and deceit she felt as she got older, as she went to great lengths to tell lies to conceal her true self. She also delves into her life in the public eye; her marriages and her troubled relationships with her children; what lead to her decision to becoming Caitlyn, and how the transgender community and the world has embraced her new life. Written with a searing honesty, this books shows you the real and true Caitlyn.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/">The Secrets of My Life &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thinking About It Only Makes It Worse : And Other Lessons from Modern Life &#8211; David Mitchell</title>
		<link>/thinking-about-it-only-makes-it-worse-and-other-lessons-from-modern-life-david-mitchell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thinking-about-it-only-makes-it-worse-and-other-lessons-from-modern-life-david-mitchell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES-BESTSELLING BOOK BY ONE OF BRITAIN&#8217;S BEST-LOVED COMIC WRITERS **Pre-order now: David Mitchell&#8217;s new book Dishonesty is the Second-best Policy** There are many aspects of modern life that trouble award-winning comedian David Mitchell, such as: Why is every film or TV programme a sequel or a remake? Why are people so f***ing hung [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-about-it-only-makes-it-worse-and-other-lessons-from-modern-life-david-mitchell/">Thinking About It Only Makes It Worse : And Other Lessons from Modern Life &#8211; David Mitchell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES-BESTSELLING BOOK BY ONE OF BRITAIN&#8217;S BEST-LOVED COMIC WRITERS</p>
<p>                    **Pre-order now: David Mitchell&#8217;s new book Dishonesty is the Second-best Policy**</p>
<p>                    There are many aspects of modern life that trouble award-winning comedian David Mitchell, such as: </p>
<p>                    Why is every film or TV programme a sequel or a remake? </p>
<p>                    Why are people so f***ing hung up about swearing? </p>
<p>                    Why do the asterisks in that sentence make it ok? </p>
<p>                    Why do so many people want to stop other people doing things, and how can they be stopped from stopping them?</p>
<p>                    Join Mitchell on a tour of the absurdities of our times &#8211; from Ryanair to Richard III, Downton Abbey to phone etiquette, UKIP to hotdogs made of cats. Funny, provocative and shot through with refreshing amounts of common sense, Thinking About It Only Makes It Worse celebrates and commiserates on the state of things in our not entirely glorious modern world.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Mitchell is an exceptionally clever, eloquent and spot-on commentator. We should be grateful for him.&#8217; Daily Mail, Books of the Year</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-about-it-only-makes-it-worse-and-other-lessons-from-modern-life-david-mitchell/">Thinking About It Only Makes It Worse : And Other Lessons from Modern Life &#8211; David Mitchell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amusing Ourselves to Death : Public Discourse in the Age of Show Business &#8211; Neil Postman, Introduction by Andrew Postman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when media and politics become forms of entertainment? As our world begins to look more and more like Orwell&#8217;s 1984, Neil&#8217;s Postman&#8217;s essential guide to the modern media is more relevant than ever. It&#8217;s unlikely that Trump has ever read Amusing Ourselves to Death, but his ascent would not have surprised Postman.&#8221; -CNN [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/">Amusing Ourselves to Death : Public Discourse in the Age of Show Business &#8211; Neil Postman, Introduction by Andrew Postman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when media and politics become forms of entertainment? As our world begins to look more and more like Orwell&#8217;s 1984, Neil&#8217;s Postman&#8217;s essential guide to the modern media is more relevant than ever.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s unlikely that Trump has ever read Amusing Ourselves to Death, but his ascent would not have surprised Postman.&#8221; -CNN     </p>
<p>                    Originally published in 1985, Neil Postman&#8217;s groundbreaking polemic about the corrosive effects of television on our politics and public discourse has been hailed as a twenty-first-century book published in the twentieth century. Now, with television joined by more sophisticated electronic media&#8211;from the Internet to cell phones to DVDs&#8211;it has taken on even greater significance. Amusing Ourselves to Death is a prophetic look at what happens when politics, journalism, education, and even religion become subject to the demands of entertainment. It is also a blueprint for regaining control of our media, so that they can serve our highest goals.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A brilliant, powerful, and important book. This is an indictment that Postman has laid down and, so far as I can see, an irrefutable one.&#8221; -Jonathan Yardley, The Washington Post Book World</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/">Amusing Ourselves to Death : Public Discourse in the Age of Show Business &#8211; Neil Postman, Introduction by Andrew Postman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Seinfeldia : How a Show About Nothing Changed Everything &#8211; Jennifer Keishin Armstrong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/seinfeldia-how-a-show-about-nothing-changed-everything-jennifer-keishin-armstrong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celebrity Biographies & Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/seinfeldia-how-a-show-about-nothing-changed-everything-jennifer-keishin-armstrong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller about two guys who went out for coffee and dreamed up Seinfeld-&#8220;A wildly entertaining must-read not only for Seinfeld fans but for anyone who wants a better understanding of how television series are made&#8221; (Booklist, starred review). Comedians Larry David and Jerry Seinfeld never thought anyone would watch their sitcom [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/seinfeldia-how-a-show-about-nothing-changed-everything-jennifer-keishin-armstrong-abridged/">Seinfeldia : How a Show About Nothing Changed Everything &#8211; Jennifer Keishin Armstrong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller about two guys who went out for coffee and dreamed up Seinfeld-&#8220;A wildly entertaining must-read not only for Seinfeld fans but for anyone who wants a better understanding of how television series are made&#8221; (Booklist, starred review).    </p>
<p>                    Comedians Larry David and Jerry Seinfeld never thought anyone would watch their sitcom about a New York comedian sitting around talking to his friends. But against all odds, viewers did watch-first a few and then many, until nine years later nearly forty million Americans were tuning in weekly. Fussy Jerry, neurotic George, eccentric Kramer, and imperious Elaine-people embraced them with love.    </p>
<p>                    Seinfeldia, Jennifer Keishin Armstrong&#8217;s intimate history is full of gossipy details, show trivia, and insights into how famous episodes came to be. Armstrong celebrates the creators and fans of this American television phenomenon, bringing readers into the writers&#8217; room and into a world of devotees for whom it never stopped being relevant. Seinfeld created a strange new reality, one where years after the show had ended the Soup Nazi still spends his days saying &#8220;No soup for you!&#8221;, Joe Davola gets questioned every day about his sanity, and Kenny Kramer makes his living giving tours of New York sites from the show.    </p>
<p>                    Seinfeldia is an outrageous cultural history. Dwight Garner of The New York Times Book Review wrote: &#8220;Armstrong has an eye for detail&#8230;.Perhaps the highest praise I can give Seinfeldia is that it made me want to buy a loaf of marbled rye and start watching again, from the beginning.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/seinfeldia-how-a-show-about-nothing-changed-everything-jennifer-keishin-armstrong-abridged/">Seinfeldia : How a Show About Nothing Changed Everything &#8211; Jennifer Keishin Armstrong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I&#8217;m Judging You : The Do-Better Manual &#8211; Luvvie Ajayi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/im-judging-you-the-do-better-manual-luvvie-ajayi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction, Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/im-judging-you-the-do-better-manual-luvvie-ajayi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With over 500,000 readers a month at her enormously popular blog, AwesomelyLuvvie.com, Luvvie Ajayi has become a go-to source for smart takes on pop culture. I&#8217;m Judging You is her debut book of humorous essays that dissects our cultural obsessions and calls out bad behavior in our increasingly digital, connected lives-from the cultural importance of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/im-judging-you-the-do-better-manual-luvvie-ajayi-abridged/">I&#8217;m Judging You : The Do-Better Manual &#8211; Luvvie Ajayi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With over 500,000 readers a month at her enormously popular blog, AwesomelyLuvvie.com, Luvvie Ajayi has become a go-to source for smart takes on pop culture. I&#8217;m Judging You is her debut book of humorous essays that dissects our cultural obsessions and calls out bad behavior in our increasingly digital, connected lives-from the cultural importance of the newest Shonda Rhimes television drama to serious discussions of race and media representation to what to do about your fool cousin sharing casket pictures from Grandma&#8217;s wake on Facebook. With a lighthearted, rapier wit and a unique perspective, I&#8217;m Judging You is the handbook the world needs, doling out the hard truths and a road map for bringing some &#8220;act right&#8221; into our lives, social media, and popular culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/im-judging-you-the-do-better-manual-luvvie-ajayi-abridged/">I&#8217;m Judging You : The Do-Better Manual &#8211; Luvvie Ajayi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Opinion & Polls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans. &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate. You have nowhere to go. You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221; &#8211;From the Introduction In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate.<br />
                     You have nowhere to go.<br />
                     You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;From the Introduction     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools: How a Selfish Ruling Class is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution, Tucker Carlson tells the truth about the new American elites, a group whose power and wealth has grown beyond imagination even as the rest of the country has withered. The people who run America now barely interact with it. They fly on their own planes, ski on their own mountains, watch sporting events far from the stands in sky boxes. They have total contempt for you.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;They view America the way a private equity firm sizes up an aging conglomerate,&#8221; Carlson writes, &#8220;as something outdated they can profit from. When it fails, they&#8217;re gone.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools,  Tucker Carlson offers a blistering critique of our new overlords. Traditional liberals are gone, he writes. The patchouli-scented hand-wringers who worried about whales and defended free speech have been replaced by globalists who hide their hard-edged economic agenda behind the smokescreen of identity politics. They&#8217;ll outsource your job while lecturing you about transgender bathrooms. Left and right, Carlson says, are no longer meaningful categories in America. &#8220;The rift is between those who benefit from the status quo, and those who don&#8217;t.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     Our leaders are fools, Carlson concludes, &#8220;unaware that they are captains of a sinking ship.&#8221; But in the signature and witty style that viewers of Tucker Carlson Tonight have come to enjoy, his book answers the all-important question: How do we put the country back on course?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>And the Good News Is&#8230; : Lessons and Advice from the Bright Side &#8211; Dana Perino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thoughtful, inspiring and often surprising, AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230; traces Dana&#8217;s unlikely journey through politics, the White House, and television. She has an uncanny ability for knowing what to say and how best to say it. A recurring theme in AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230;is that planning has never worked for Dana; every time [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/">And the Good News Is&#8230; : Lessons and Advice from the Bright Side &#8211; Dana Perino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thoughtful, inspiring and often surprising, AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230; traces Dana&#8217;s unlikely journey through politics, the White House, and television. She has an uncanny ability for knowing what to say and how best to say it. A recurring theme in AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230;is that planning has never worked for Dana; every time she has made a plan, something unexpected-and often better-has happened.<br />
                    AND THE GOOD NEWS IS&#8230; blends a candid self-portrait with advice for allowing one&#8217;s very best personality traits to shine through, emphasizing that dignity and civility are choices we make for ourselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/and-the-good-news-is-lessons-and-advice-from-the-bright-side-dana-perino-abridged/">And the Good News Is&#8230; : Lessons and Advice from the Bright Side &#8211; Dana Perino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
