<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Marine Biology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/marine-biology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/marine-biology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Marine Biology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/marine-biology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic In the two years after the 1939 publication of Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful The Grapes of Wrath, Steinbeck and his novel increasingly became the center of intense controversy and censorship. In search of a respite from the national stage, Steinbeck and his close friend, biologist Ed Ricketts, embarked on a month long marine specimen-collecting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/">The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic     </p>
<p>                    In the two years after the 1939 publication of Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful The Grapes of Wrath, Steinbeck and his novel increasingly became the center of intense controversy and censorship. In search of a respite from the national stage, Steinbeck and his close friend, biologist Ed Ricketts, embarked on a month long marine specimen-collecting expedition in the Gulf of California, which resulted in their collaboration on the Sea of Cortez. In 1951, after Ricketts&#8217; death, Steinbeck reissued his narrative portion of the work in memory of his friend and the inspiration for Cannery Row&#8217;s &#8220;Doc&#8221;. This exciting day-by-day account of their journey together is a rare blend of science, philosophy, and high-spirited adventure. This edition features an introduction by Richard Astro.     </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/">The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oceanography (seas)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter? In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week<br />
                              &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian<br />
                              &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                                What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter?    </p>
<p>                              In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science and a skilled scuba diver, tells a bold new story of how nature became aware of itself &#8211; a story that largely occurs in the ocean, where animals first appeared.    </p>
<p>                              Tracking the mind&#8217;s fitful development from unruly clumps of seaborne cells to the first evolved nervous systems in ancient relatives of jellyfish, he explores the incredible evolutionary journey of the cephalopods, which began as inconspicuous molluscs who would later abandon their shells to rise above the ocean floor, searching for prey and acquiring the greater intelligence needed to do so &#8211; a journey completely independent from the route that mammals and birds would later take.    </p>
<p>                              But what kind of intelligence do cephalopods possess? How did the octopus, a solitary creature with little social life, become so smart? What is it like to have eight tentacles that are so packed with neurons that they virtually &#8216;think for themselves&#8217;? By tracing the question of inner life back to its roots and comparing human beings with our most remarkable animal relatives, Godfrey-Smith casts crucial new light on the octopus mind &#8211; and on our own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
