<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Customer Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/customer-services/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/customer-services/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Customer Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/customer-services/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Thank You Economy &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</title>
		<link>/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Thank You Economy isn&#8217;t some abstract concept or wacky business strategy. It&#8217;s the way we buy and sell, the way we&#8217;re interacting as consumers, as employees, as entrepreneurs on all levels, right now. The way our marketplace functions has been evolving right before our eyes. Top-down, one-way exchanges are gone, replaced by relationships based [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/">The Thank You Economy &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Thank You Economy isn&#8217;t some abstract concept or wacky business strategy. It&#8217;s the way we buy and sell, the way we&#8217;re interacting as consumers, as employees, as entrepreneurs on all levels, right now. The way our marketplace functions has been evolving right before our eyes. Top-down, one-way exchanges are gone, replaced by relationships based on open, honest, and constant communication between customers and business. Today, individuals and brands that out-care and out-love their competition &#8211; those emphasising quality, value, responsiveness, and attention to detail, among other essentials &#8211; see the biggest returns. Gary Vaynerchuk contends that the people and companies harnessing the word-of-mouth power provided by multiplatform media &#8211; those that can shift their outlook and operations to be more customer-aware and fan-friendly &#8211; will pull away from the pack and profit in today&#8217;s markets. In &#8220;The Thank You Economy&#8221;, he dissects the companies on the leading edge, showing how they are succeeding &#8211; and sometimes failing.<br />
                    Laying out the ideas and insight that support this enormous change, Vaynerchuk explores these emerging connections &#8211; from consumer to consumer and business to business and everything in between. Passionate and persuasive, he reminds us that, surviving and thriving today it takes more than just hard work-it takes a heartfelt thanks to those who make it possible.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/">The Thank You Economy &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising. For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising.     </p>
<p>                     For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup founder, a small business owner, or part of a large corporation.     </p>
<p>                     No matter what your product or service, this book will help you reframe how it&#8217;s presented to the world, in order to meaningfully connect with people who want it. Seth employs his signature blend of insight, observation, and memorable examples to teach you:    </p>
<p>                     * How to build trust and permission with your target market.<br />
                     * The art of positioning&#8211;deciding not only who it&#8217;s for, but who it&#8217;s not for.<br />
                     * Why the best way to achieve your goals is to help others become who they want to be.<br />
                     * Why the old approaches to advertising and branding no longer work.<br />
                     * The surprising role of tension in any decision to buy (or not).<br />
                     * How marketing is at its core about the stories we tell ourselves about our social status.    </p>
<p>                     You can do work that matters for people who care. This book shows you the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This Is Marketing is a very accessible way into Godin&#8217;s thinking&#8230;. Godin writes in pacy, jargon-free prose and this book is interesting and useful for anyone who wants an insight into how, and why, we buy things or change our habits in any way.&#8221; &#8211; The Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s Purple Cow, a true business classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hug Your Haters &#8211; Jay Baer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Haters are not your problem. . . . Ignoring them is. Eighty percent of companies say they deliver out­standing customer service, but only 8 percent of their customers agree. This book will help you close that gap by reconfiguring your customer service to deliver knockout experiences. The near-universal adoption of smartphones and social media has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/">Hug Your Haters &#8211; Jay Baer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Haters are not your problem. . . .<br />
                    Ignoring them is.     </p>
<p>                    Eighty percent of companies say they deliver out­standing customer service, but only 8 percent of their customers agree. This book will help you close that gap by reconfiguring your customer service to deliver knockout experiences.     </p>
<p>                    The near-universal adoption of smartphones and social media has fundamentally altered the science of complaints. Critics (&#8220;haters&#8221;) can now express their displeasure faster and more pub­licly than ever. These trends have resulted in an overall increase in complaints and a belief by many businesses that they have to &#8220;pick their spots&#8221; when choosing to answer criticisms.     </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author Jay Baer shows why that approach is a major mistake. Based on an exten­sive proprietary study of how, where, and why we complain, Hug Your Haters proves that there are two types of complainers, each with very differ­ent motivations:     </p>
<p>                    -Offstage haters. These people simply want solutions to their problems. They complain via legacy channels where the likelihood of a response is highest&#8211;phone, e-mail, and com­pany websites. Offstage haters don&#8217;t care if any­one else finds out, as long as they get answers.<br />
                    -Onstage haters. These people are often disap­pointed by a substandard interaction via tradi­tional channels, so they turn to indirect venues, such as social media, online review sites, and discussion boards. Onstage haters want more than solutions&#8211;they want an audience to share their righteous indignation.     </p>
<p>                    Hug Your Haters shows exactly how to deal with both groups, drawing on meticulously researched case studies from businesses of all types and sizes from around the world. It includes specific play­books and formulas as well as a fold-out poster of &#8220;the Hatrix,&#8221; which summarizes the best strate­gies for different situations. The book is also filled with poignant and hilarious examples of haters gone wild, and companies gone crazy, as well as inspirational stories of companies responding with speed, compassion, and humanity.     </p>
<p>                    Whether you work for a mom-and-pop store or a global brand, you will have haters&#8211;and you can&#8217;t afford to ignore them. Baer&#8217;s insights and tactics will teach you how to embrace complaints, put haters to work for you, and turn bad news into good outcomes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/">Hug Your Haters &#8211; Jay Baer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Service Design Thinking : Basics, Tools, Cases &#8211; Marc Stickdorn, Jakob Schneider (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to design and market services to create outstanding customer experiences Service design thinking is the designing and marketing of services that improve the customer experience, and the interactions between the service providers and the customers. If you have two coffee shops right next to each other, and each sell the exact same coffee at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/">This is Service Design Thinking : Basics, Tools, Cases &#8211; Marc Stickdorn, Jakob Schneider (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to design and market services to create outstanding customer experiences Service design thinking is the designing and marketing of services that improve the customer experience, and the interactions between the service providers and the customers. If you have two coffee shops right next to each other, and each sell the exact same coffee at the exact same price, service design is what makes you walk into one and not the other. Maybe one plays music and the other doesn&#8217;t. Maybe one takes credit cards and the other is cash only. Maybe you like the layout of one over the other, or one has more comfortable seating. Maybe the staff at one is friendlier, or draws fun shapes on the top of their lattes. All of these nuances relate to service design.<br />
                    This Is Service Design Thinking combines the knowledge of twenty-three international authors and even more online contributors from the global service design community and is divided into three sections: * Basics: outlines service design thinking along five basic principles * Tools: describing a variety of tools and methods used in Service Design Thinking * Cases: vivid examples for the introduced fundamentals with real-life case studies from 5 companies that did inspiring projects within the field of Service Design At the end, a one-page &#8220;Customer Journey Canvas&#8221; is included, which can be used to quickly sketch any service on a single sheet of paper capturing different stakeholder concerns: e.g. customers, front-line staff and management.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/">This is Service Design Thinking : Basics, Tools, Cases &#8211; Marc Stickdorn, Jakob Schneider (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the international bestseller Business Model Generation explain how to create value propositions customers can&#8217;t resist Value Proposition Design helps you tackle the core challenge of every business &#8211; creating compelling products and services customers want to buy. This highly practical book, paired with its online companion, will teach you the processes and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/">Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the international bestseller Business Model Generation explain how to create value propositions customers can&#8217;t resist    </p>
<p>                     Value Proposition Design helps you tackle the core challenge of every business &#8211; creating compelling products and services customers want to buy. This highly practical book, paired with its online companion, will teach you the processes and tools you need to create products that sell.    </p>
<p>                    Using the same stunning visual format as the authors&#8217; global bestseller, Business Model Generation, this sequel explains how to use the &#8220;Value Proposition Canvas&#8221; to design, test, create, and manage products and services customers actually want.    </p>
<p>                    Value Proposition Design is for anyone who has been frustrated by new product meetings based on hunches and intuitions; it&#8217;s for anyone who has watched an expensive new product launch fail in the market. The book will help you understand the patterns of great value propositions, get closer to customers, and avoid wasting time with ideas that won&#8217;t work. You&#8217;ll learn the simple process of designing and testing value propositions, that perfectly match customers&#8217; needs and desires.    </p>
<p>                    In addition the book gives you exclusive access to an online companion on Strategyzer.com. You will be able to assess your work, learn from peers, and download pdfs, checklists, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Value Proposition Design is an essential companion to the &#8220;Business Model Canvas&#8221; from Business Model Generation, a tool embraced globally by startups and large corporations such as MasterCard, 3M, Coca Cola, GE, Fujitsu, LEGO, Colgate-Palmolive, and many more.<br />
                    Value Proposition Design gives you a proven methodology for success, with value propositions that sell, embedded in profitable business models.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/">Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212; Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International    </p>
<p>                      &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! There, I learned the fundamentals of guest service that consistently gave Disney a tremendous advantage in the marketplace. Now, anyone can know these secrets of success thanks to Doug Lipp&#8217;s informative book. No matter what your business, the lessons taught at DisneyUniversity will prove invaluable.&#8221; &#8212; Michael Eisner, Former CEO and Chairman, The Walt Disney Company    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to world-class employees, few organizations rival Disney. Famous for their friendliness, knowledge, passion, and superior customer service, Disney&#8217;s employees have been fueling the iconic brand&#8217;s wild success for more than 50 years.    </p>
<p>                    How has Disney succeeded in maintaining such a powerful workforce for so many years? Why are so many corporations and executives drawn to study how Disney continues to exemplify service and leadership standards?    </p>
<p>                    The Disney University, founded by Van France, trains the supporting cast that helps create the world-famous Disney Magic. Now, for the first time, the secrets of this exemplary institution are revealed. In Disney U, Doug Lipp examines how Van perpetuated Walt Disney&#8217;s timeless company values and leadership lessons, creating a training and development dynasty. It contains never-before-told stories from numerous Disney legends. These pioneers share behind-the-scenes success stories of how they helped bring Walt Disney&#8217;s dream to life.    </p>
<p>                    Disney U reveals the heart of the Disney culture and describes the company&#8217;s values and operational philosophies that support the iconic brand. Doug Lipp lays out 13 timeless lessons Disney has used to drive profits and growth worldwide for more than half a century.    </p>
<p>                    To this day, the Disney University continues to turn out some of the most engaged, loyal, and customer-centered employees the business world has ever seen. Using the lessons outlined in Disney U will set your organization on a path of sustained success.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR Disney U:    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I highly recommend Disney U to anyone interested in building an enduring market presence and brand.&#8221; &#8212; Stephen Cannon, President and Chief Executive Officer, Mercedes-Benz USA    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lipp&#8217;s narratives reveal how Van and other Disney visionaries set the stage for a world-class organization by skillfully balancing both &#8216;people&#8217; and &#8216;technology.'&#8221; &#8212; Debi Aubee, Vice President of Sales, Bose Corporation    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every leader should have the equivalent of a Van France at his or her side. Thanks to Doug Lipp, we can now tap into the brilliance of a man who helped Walt createThe Happiest Place on Earth.&#8221; &#8212; David Overton, Founder and Chief Executive Officer, The Cheesecake Factory    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;How does Disney University create such enthusiastic, loyal, and customer-centered employees, year after year? Now, for the first time, Doug Lipp takes us on a journey backstage to answer this pivotal question.&#8221; &#8212; John G. Veres III, Ph.D., Chancellor, Auburn University at Montgomery    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Doug Lipp shares terrific stories about Disney that underscore the importance of creating an organizational culture with an unwavering dedication to superlativeservice and exceptional quality, both for employees and customers. He then takes it a step further by explaining how to bring these values to life for your organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Christine A. Morena, Executive Vice President of Human Resources, Saks Incorporated</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s business world, it takes more than a website to stay competitive. The smartest, most successful companies are using radically new membership models, subscription-based formats, and freemium pricing structures to grow their customer base-and explode their market valuation-in the most disruptive shift in business since the Industrial Revolution. This is The Membership Economy. Written [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/">The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s business world, it takes more than a website to stay competitive. The smartest, most successful companies are using radically new membership models, subscription-based formats, and freemium pricing structures to grow their customer base-and explode their market valuation-in the most disruptive shift in business since the Industrial Revolution.    </p>
<p>                    This is The Membership Economy.    </p>
<p>                     Written by an expertconsultant, this groundbreaking book will show you how to turn ordinary customers into members for life. Learn how to:    </p>
<p>                     Turn digital subscriptions into forever sales Build an online community your customers will loveDevelop new loyalty programs that really pay offTransform freemium users into superusers Create a self-generating revenue stream Keep memberships and profits growing for years to come<br />
                    Whether you&#8217;re a small business with limited resources, an established company using a traditional business model, or a hungry start-up who wants a bigger bang for your buck, this comprehensive guide provides a wealth of membership-building options to suit every need.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll learn the best-kept secrets of top industry leaders, from global giants like Am Ex and Weight Watchers to smaller dot-com successes like SurveyMonkey and Pandora. You&#8217;ll find proven strategies for creating membership programs for everything from vacation timeshares and car rentals to video streaming and Software-as-a-Service.    </p>
<p>                     Most importantly, you&#8217;ll discover what works, and what doesn&#8217;t, from some of the key players in the new membership economy. It&#8217;s not about ownership; it&#8217;s about access, options, and freedom.    </p>
<p>                    When you join forces with your customers, membership has its rewards-for you, your company, and your continued success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/">The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Connected CRM : Implementing a Data-Driven, Customer-Centric Business Strategy &#8211; David S. Williams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/connected-crm-implementing-a-data-driven-customer-centric-business-strategy-david-s-williams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/connected-crm-implementing-a-data-driven-customer-centric-business-strategy-david-s-williams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Connected CRM Many books explore the subject of CRM. In this book the m is for Marketing and David s seasoned perspective indeed makes it a capital M. Taking core direct response marketing techniques and moving beyond the simple use of data and analytics, he explores how today s marketers can leverage advances [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/connected-crm-implementing-a-data-driven-customer-centric-business-strategy-david-s-williams-abridged/">Connected CRM : Implementing a Data-Driven, Customer-Centric Business Strategy &#8211; David S. Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Connected CRM Many books explore the subject of CRM. In this book the m is for Marketing and David s seasoned perspective indeed makes it a capital M. Taking core direct response marketing techniques and moving beyond the simple use of data and analytics, he explores how today s marketers can leverage advances in technology to create successful customer-centric business strategies. Ted Ward, VP of Marketing, GEICO A must-read for CMOs, and more importantly CEOs, to simplify all the buzzwords around big data and dimensionalize the organizational change necessary to become truly customer centric. Theresa McLaughlin, Chief Marketing and Communications Officer, Citizens Financial Group Big Data, Social, and Cloud have become overused buzzwords with ambiguous meaning, but David brings to bear his years of industry leadership and experiences to break down today s trends and opportunities in a practical, actionable fashion. A must-read for anyone who prefers profit over PowerPoint.<br />
                    Manish Bhatt, SVP and Chief Digital Officer, MetLife In a data-rich world, consumers demand that marketers turn data into highly relevant and personal experiences Don t talk with me as a member of a segment, talk with me about how you will meet my unique expectations and solve my unique problems. For those of us who grew up in the marketing world of mass and broadcast, this is a tall order. Connected CRM helps marketers unpack customer centricity for their organizations, providing real insight into the development of a framework for enterprise customer centricity; a framework that promises true sustainable advantage. Tom Lamb, CMO, Lowe s Never before has customer data been more available, more necessary to build sales and loyalty, and more confusing to act on. David shows exactly what needs to be done. It s about time. And we should all thank him. A lot! Steve Cone, EVP of Integrated Value and Strategy, AARP The marketers who truly learn to harness the power of customer analytics and big data will take the spoils in an increasingly digital age. Those who don t will quickly find themselves on a growing heap of failed marketing plans.<br />
                    Paul Guyardo, Chief Revenue and Marketing Officer, DIRECTV</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/connected-crm-implementing-a-data-driven-customer-centric-business-strategy-david-s-williams-abridged/">Connected CRM : Implementing a Data-Driven, Customer-Centric Business Strategy &#8211; David S. Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zombie Loyalists : Using Great Service to Create Rabid Fans &#8211; Jason Huggins, Peter Shankman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zombie-loyalists-using-great-service-to-create-rabid-fans-jason-huggins-peter-shankman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zombie-loyalists-using-great-service-to-create-rabid-fans-jason-huggins-peter-shankman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Marketing and PR expert Peter Shankman has been working with the biggest companies in the world to create what he calls &#8220;Zombie Loyalists,&#8221; fervent fans that help companies massively increase their customer base, brand awareness, and most importantly, revenue. Imagine an army of customers who will do your public relations, marketing and advertising, without being [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zombie-loyalists-using-great-service-to-create-rabid-fans-jason-huggins-peter-shankman-abridged/">Zombie Loyalists : Using Great Service to Create Rabid Fans &#8211; Jason Huggins, Peter Shankman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Marketing and PR expert Peter Shankman has been working with the biggest companies in the world to create what he calls &#8220;Zombie Loyalists,&#8221; fervent fans that help companies massively increase their customer base, brand awareness, and most importantly, revenue. Imagine an army of customers who will do your public relations, marketing and advertising, without being asked, each and every time they give you their money. These are Zombie Loyalists. They are ready to buy what you sell, respond to your email offers and demand that their friends to do the same. Looking at exceptional companies like the Ritz Carlton, Commerce Bank, and Starwood Hotels, as well as smaller businesses to turn their customers into Zombie Loyalists, he shows how you can create your own customer army.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zombie-loyalists-using-great-service-to-create-rabid-fans-jason-huggins-peter-shankman-abridged/">Zombie Loyalists : Using Great Service to Create Rabid Fans &#8211; Jason Huggins, Peter Shankman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company     </p>
<p>                    What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and delivering value consistently, day in and day out.    </p>
<p>                    In Top of Mind, the cofounder of a leading content marketing company shows you how to create business opportunities by occupying the space at the top of your audience&#8217;s minds-and keeping it there. This groundbreaking book explains how consumer needs and expectations have changed and what this shift means for readers interested in building a brand-whether you&#8217;re a leader in marketing engaging potential customers, a VP of sales bringing in new business, or a director of HR who&#8217;s recruiting the best talent in the industry. It provides effective ways to establish trust and foster connections; maintain transparency and consistency; identify and clearly communicate the &#8220;why&#8221; behind the message; and create processes to make that message part of a brand&#8217;s DNA.     </p>
<p>                    Maintaining a prominent spot in your audience&#8217;s minds will increase the likelihood that the moment they need to make a choice, you&#8217;ll be the first one they call.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hug Your Customers : The Proven Way to Personalize Sales and Achieve Astounding Results &#8211; Jack Mitchell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hug-your-customers-the-proven-way-to-personalize-sales-and-achieve-astounding-results-jack-mitchell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hug-your-customers-the-proven-way-to-personalize-sales-and-achieve-astounding-results-jack-mitchell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Revised and updated for the first time since original publication! Here is the 200,000-copy staple, praised by Warren Buffett as a gem &#8230; I wish everyone at Berkshire would follow [Jack Mitchell&#8217;s] advice&#8211;we would own the world. If you want to put your arms around your business and bottom line, you&#8217;ll want all the updated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-customers-the-proven-way-to-personalize-sales-and-achieve-astounding-results-jack-mitchell-abridged/">Hug Your Customers : The Proven Way to Personalize Sales and Achieve Astounding Results &#8211; Jack Mitchell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Revised and updated for the first time since original publication!     </p>
<p>                     Here is the 200,000-copy staple, praised by Warren Buffett as a gem &#8230; I wish everyone at Berkshire would follow [Jack Mitchell&#8217;s] advice&#8211;we would own the world.     </p>
<p>                     If you want to put your arms around your business and bottom line, you&#8217;ll want all the updated information and practices found in the landmark business bestseller, Hug Your Customers. The only way to stay in business is to have customers; the only way to increase your profit is to attract more customer visits by providing exceptional customer service. It&#8217;s that simple says Jack Mitchell. Hug Your Customers shares the hands-on practical philosophy that has allowed Mitchell and his Family of Stores to thrive and excel in today&#8217;s challenging retail marketplace. Filled with accessible advice, personal case studies and tips any businessperson can use, Hug Your Customers is an energizing blueprint for customer and employee retention, increased per capita spending, and groundbreaking success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-customers-the-proven-way-to-personalize-sales-and-achieve-astounding-results-jack-mitchell-abridged/">Hug Your Customers : The Proven Way to Personalize Sales and Achieve Astounding Results &#8211; Jack Mitchell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pricing for Profit : How to Develop a Powerful Pricing Strategy for Your Business &#8211; Peter Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Price is the most significant factor affecting the profitability of every business, profit centre or department. When the pressure is on to perform or grow, your instinct may be to discount, undercut your competitors, cut costs and promote through price. Yet these are often the last things you should do. Pricing for Profit is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/">Pricing for Profit : How to Develop a Powerful Pricing Strategy for Your Business &#8211; Peter Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Price is the most significant factor affecting the profitability of every business, profit centre or department. When the pressure is on to perform or grow, your instinct may be to discount, undercut your competitors, cut costs and promote through price. Yet these are often the last things you should do. Pricing for Profit is the most practical guide on pricing available. Using a firm, profit-focused framework developed running real projects for real businesses, this book shows you how by getting your pricing structures right you can make a huge difference to your bottom line. It gives business owners, managers and leaders simple, achievable pricing strategies that will deliver sustainable business growth. Can you afford to leave money on the table? If not, Pricing for Profit is the guide for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/">Pricing for Profit : How to Develop a Powerful Pricing Strategy for Your Business &#8211; Peter Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Referral Engine &#8211; John Jantsch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The small business guru behind Duct Tape Marketing shares his most valuable lesson: how to get your customers to do your best marketing for you. The power of glitzy advertising and elaborate marketing campaigns is on the wane; word- of-mouth referrals are what drive business today. People trust the recommendation of a friend, family member, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/">The Referral Engine &#8211; John Jantsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The small business guru behind Duct Tape Marketing shares his most valuable lesson: how to get your customers to do your best marketing for you.   The power of glitzy advertising and elaborate marketing campaigns is on the wane; word- of-mouth referrals are what drive business today. People trust the recommendation of a friend, family member, colleague, or even stranger with similar tastes over anything thrust at them by a faceless company.  Most business owners believe that whether customers refer them is entirely out of their hands. But science shows that people can&#8217;t help recommending products and services to their friends-it&#8217;s an instinct wired deep in the brain. And smart businesses can tap into that hardwired desire.  Marketing expert John Jantsch offers practical techniques for harnessing the power of referrals to ensure a steady flow of new customers. Keep those customers happy, and they will refer your business to even more customers. Some of Jantsch&#8217;s strategies include:  -Talk with your customers, not at them. Thanks to social networking sites, companies of any size have the opportunity to engage with their customers on their home turf as never before-but the key is listening.  -The sales team is the most important part of your marketing team. Salespeople are the company&#8217;s main link to customers, who are the main source of referrals. Getting them on board with your referral strategy is critical.  -Educate your customers. Referrals are only helpful if they&#8217;re given to the right people. Educate your customers about whom they should be talking to.  The secret to generating referrals lies in understanding the Customer Referral Cycle-the way customers refer others to your company who, in turn, generate even more referrals. Businesses can ensure a healthy referral cycle by moving customers and prospects along the path of Know, Like, Trust, Try, Buy, Repeat, and Refer. If everyone in an organization keeps this sequence in mind, Jantsch argues, your business will generate referrals like a well-oiled machine.  This practical, smart, and original guide is essential reading for any company looking to grow without a fat marketing budget.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-referral-engine-john-jantsch-abridged/">The Referral Engine &#8211; John Jantsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Getting Naked : A Business Fable About Shedding The Three Fears That Sabotage Client Loyalty &#8211; Patrick M. Lencioni (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/getting-naked-a-business-fable-about-shedding-the-three-fears-that-sabotage-client-loyalty-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/getting-naked-a-business-fable-about-shedding-the-three-fears-that-sabotage-client-loyalty-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Another extraordinary business fable from the New York Times bestselling author Patrick LencioniWritten in the same dynamic style as his previous bestsellers including The Five Dysfunctions of a Team, Lencioni illustrates the principles of inspiring client loyalty through a fascinating business fable. He explains the theory of vulnerability in depth and presents concrete steps for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-naked-a-business-fable-about-shedding-the-three-fears-that-sabotage-client-loyalty-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/">Getting Naked : A Business Fable About Shedding The Three Fears That Sabotage Client Loyalty &#8211; Patrick M. Lencioni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Another extraordinary business fable from the New York Times bestselling author Patrick LencioniWritten in the same dynamic style as his previous bestsellers including The Five Dysfunctions of a Team, Lencioni illustrates the principles of inspiring client loyalty through a fascinating business fable. He explains the theory of vulnerability in depth and presents concrete steps for putting it to work in any organization. The story follows a small consulting firm, Lighthouse Partners, which often beats out big-name competitors for top clients. One such competitor buys out Lighthouse and learns important lessons about what it means to provide value to its clients. * Offers a key resource for gaining competitive advantage in tough times * Shows why the quality of vulnerability is so important in business * Includes ideas for inspiring customer and client loyalty * Written by the highly successful consultant and business writer Patrick LencioniThis new book in the popular Lencioni series shows what it takes to gain a real and lasting competitive edge.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/getting-naked-a-business-fable-about-shedding-the-three-fears-that-sabotage-client-loyalty-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/">Getting Naked : A Business Fable About Shedding The Three Fears That Sabotage Client Loyalty &#8211; Patrick M. Lencioni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clients First : The Two Word Miracle &#8211; Joseph Callaway, Joann Callaway (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/clients-first-the-two-word-miracle-joseph-callaway-joann-callaway-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Housing & Property For The Individual - Buying/selling & Legal Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/clients-first-the-two-word-miracle-joseph-callaway-joann-callaway-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How honesty, competency, and caring will make you rich Throw out the sales manual. Get off the motivation elevator. Clients First is a two word miracle that can change your life. This book outlines a powerful path to riches that authors Joseph and JoAnn Callaway used to sell a billion dollars in real estate in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clients-first-the-two-word-miracle-joseph-callaway-joann-callaway-abridged/">Clients First : The Two Word Miracle &#8211; Joseph Callaway, Joann Callaway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How honesty, competency, and caring will make you rich Throw out the sales manual. Get off the motivation elevator. Clients First is a two word miracle that can change your life. This book outlines a powerful path to riches that authors Joseph and JoAnn Callaway used to sell a billion dollars in real estate in just ten years a feat never before achieved. Here, they explain the three keys to putting your clients first that helped them create one of the most successful realty firms in the U.S. Each of the three keys is important and can stand on its own. However, the success you can achieve when following the Clients First program can only be reached when all three keys are used in coordination. * Explains how honesty ensures a strong client relationship * Details the ways in which competency pervades all aspects of a client&#8217;s perception of you * Shows how being a caring individual can win over a client on a personal level Unlock your potential by putting these to use in your life and your business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clients-first-the-two-word-miracle-joseph-callaway-joann-callaway-abridged/">Clients First : The Two Word Miracle &#8211; Joseph Callaway, Joann Callaway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Mathematics & Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Engineering: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How do today&#8217;s most successful tech companies-Amazon, Google, Facebook, Netflix, Tesla-design, develop, and deploy the products that have earned the love of literally billions of people around the world? Perhaps surprisingly, they do it very differently than most tech companies. In INSPIRED, technology product management thought leader Marty Cagan provides readers with a master class [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/">Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How do today&#8217;s most successful tech companies-Amazon, Google, Facebook, Netflix, Tesla-design, develop, and deploy the products that have earned the love of literally billions of people around the world?    </p>
<p>                     Perhaps surprisingly, they do it very differently than most tech companies.    </p>
<p>                     In INSPIRED, technology product management thought leader Marty Cagan provides readers with a master class in how to structure and staff a vibrant and successful product organization, and how to discover and deliver technology products that your customers will love-and that will work for your business.    </p>
<p>                     With sections on assembling the right people and skillsets, discovering the right product, embracing an effective yet lightweight process, and creating a strong product culture, readers can take the information they learn and immediately leverage it within their own organizations-dramatically improving their own product efforts.    </p>
<p>                     Whether you&#8217;re an early stage startup working to get to product/market fit, or a growth-stage company working to scale your product organization, or a large, long-established company trying to regain your ability to consistently deliver new value for your customers, INSPIRED will take you and your product organization to a new level of customer engagement, consistent innovation, and business success.    </p>
<p>                     Filled with the author&#8217;s own personal stories-and profiles of some of today&#8217;s most-successful product managers and technology-powered product companies, including Adobe, Apple, BBC, Google, Microsoft, and Netflix-INSPIRED will show you how to turn up the dial of your own product efforts, creating technology products your customers love.    </p>
<p>                     The first edition of INSPIRED, published ten years ago, established itself as the primary reference for technology product managers, and can be found on the shelves of nearly every successful technology product company worldwide. This thoroughly updated second edition shares the same objective of being the most valuable resource for technology product managers, yet it is completely new-sharing the latest practices and techniques of today&#8217;s most-successful tech product companies, and the men and women behind every great product.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inspired-how-to-create-tech-products-customers-love-marty-cagan-abridged/">Inspired : How to Create Tech Products Customers Love &#8211; Marty Cagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>User Research : Improve Product and Service Design and Enhance Your UX Research &#8211; Stephanie Marsh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many businesses are based on creating desirable experiences, products and services for users. However, companies often fail to consider the end user &#8211; the consumer &#8211; in their planning and development processes. How can marketing practitioners effectively understand their customers and create products and services that work for them? This book has the answers. User [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/">User Research : Improve Product and Service Design and Enhance Your UX Research &#8211; Stephanie Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many businesses are based on creating desirable experiences, products and services for users. However, companies often fail to consider the end user &#8211; the consumer &#8211; in their planning and development processes. How can marketing practitioners effectively understand their customers and create products and services that work for them? This book has the answers.    </p>
<p>                    User experience research, also known as UX research, focuses on understanding user behaviours, needs and motivations through a range of observational techniques, task analysis and other methodologies. User Research is a practical guide that shows readers how to use the vast array of user research methods available. Written by one of the UK&#8217;s leading UX research professionals, readers can benefit from in-depth knowledge that explores the fundamentals of user research.    </p>
<p>                    Covering all the key research methods including face-to-face user testing, card sorting, surveys, A/B testing and many more, the book gives expert insight into the nuances, advantages and disadvantages of each, while also providing guidance on how to interpret, analyze and share the data once it has been obtained. Now in its second edition, User Research provides a new chapter on research operations and infrastructure as well as new material on combining user research methodologies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/user-research-improve-product-and-service-design-and-enhance-your-ux-research-stephanie-marsh-abridged/">User Research : Improve Product and Service Design and Enhance Your UX Research &#8211; Stephanie Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walmart : Key Insights and Practical Lessons from the World&#8217;s Largest Retailer &#8211; Bryan Roberts, Natalie Berg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multinationals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Purchasing & Supply Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Walmart provides a detailed assessment of the world&#8217;s largest retailer that forever changed the face of retailing. The book examines Walmart&#8217;s successes, failures, and whether it can stay ahead for the next 50 years. Despite being a source for best practice in procurement, logistics, systems and store format innovation, the retail giant is now facing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/">Walmart : Key Insights and Practical Lessons from the World&#8217;s Largest Retailer &#8211; Bryan Roberts, Natalie Berg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Walmart provides a detailed assessment of the world&#8217;s largest retailer that forever changed the face of retailing. The book examines Walmart&#8217;s successes, failures, and whether it can stay ahead for the next 50 years. Despite being a source for best practice in procurement, logistics, systems and store format innovation, the retail giant is now facing several issues that affect its future development. Starting from its inception in rural Arkansas in 1962, this objective analysis of Walmart&#8217;s history addresses the rapid change of retail, including the rise of e-commerce and multi-channel retailing; Walmart International and its &#8216;everyday low prices&#8217; philosophy; the saturation of the superstore format, and much more.     </p>
<p>                    In a time of rapid change, will the world&#8217;s largest retailer be able to reconfigure? Walmart provides the necessary insights for retailers, advertisers, other business professionals and students to understand how Walmart became a retail giant, the lessons that can be learned, and what is in store for the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walmart-key-insights-and-practical-lessons-from-the-worlds-largest-retailer-bryan-roberts-natalie-berg-abridged/">Walmart : Key Insights and Practical Lessons from the World&#8217;s Largest Retailer &#8211; Bryan Roberts, Natalie Berg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Customer Service Quotes Ever Said &#8211; John R DiJulius, III (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-best-customer-service-quotes-ever-said-john-r-dijulius-iii-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-best-customer-service-quotes-ever-said-john-r-dijulius-iii-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Become a Customer Service Revolutionary! John R. DiJulius III has raised the bar for what it means to deliver world-class customer service. Now, with this indispensable book, you can too! DiJulius has combined the most inspiring quotes on how to best connect with customers and employees with a user-friendly journal to create the ultimate customer-service [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-best-customer-service-quotes-ever-said-john-r-dijulius-iii-abridged/">The Best Customer Service Quotes Ever Said &#8211; John R DiJulius, III (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Become a Customer Service Revolutionary!     </p>
<p>                    John R. DiJulius III has raised the bar for what it means to deliver world-class customer service. Now, with this indispensable book, you can too! DiJulius has combined the most inspiring quotes on how to best connect with customers and employees with a user-friendly journal to create the ultimate customer-service handbook. The Best Customer Service Quotes Ever Said uses the powerful and motivational words from world-renowned experts to inspire greatness and revolutionize how you interact with customers. This book is the perfect guide to taking customer interactions to the next level, and it provides expert wisdom to bring the customer service revolution to you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-best-customer-service-quotes-ever-said-john-r-dijulius-iii-abridged/">The Best Customer Service Quotes Ever Said &#8211; John R DiJulius, III (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Be Our Guest (10th Anniversary Updated Edition) : Perfecting the Art of Customer Service &#8211; Ted Kinni, Edited by Wendy Lefkon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exceeding expectations rather than simply satisfying them is the cornerstone of the Disney approach to customer service. Disney Institute specializes in helping professionals see new possibilities through concepts not found in the typical workplace, is revealing even more of the business behind the magic of quality service. During the last twenty-five years, thousands of professionals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/">Be Our Guest (10th Anniversary Updated Edition) : Perfecting the Art of Customer Service &#8211; Ted Kinni, Edited by Wendy Lefkon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exceeding expectations rather than simply satisfying them is the cornerstone of the Disney approach to customer service.<br />
                    Disney Institute specializes in helping professionals see new possibilities through concepts not found in the typical workplace, is revealing even more of the business behind the magic of quality service. During the last twenty-five years, thousands of professionals from more than thirty-five countries and more than forty industries have attended business programs at Disney Institute and learned how to adapt the Disney approach for their own organizations.Be Our Guest highlights the successes many of these companies have achieved, plus the key processes and best practices that have made Disney a trusted and revered brand around the world for more than eighty-five years.<br />
                    Want more insight on The Walt Disney Company, its founder, and its driving creative forces? Explore these behind-the-scenes stories from Disney Editions: Travels with Figment: On the Road in Search of Disney Dreams (By Disney Legend Marty Sklar)<br />
                    One Little Spark! Mickey&#8217;s Ten Commandments and The Road to Imagineering (By Disney Legend Marty Sklar)<br />
                    Magic Journey: My Fantastical Walt Disney Imagineering Career (By Kevin Rafferty)<br />
                    Travels with Walt Disney: A Photographic Voyage Around the World (By Jeff Kurtti)<br />
                    Eat Like Walt: The Wonderful World of Disney Food (By Marcy Carriker Smothers)<br />
                    Walt Disney: An American Original (By Bob Thomas)<br />
                    Disney A to Z: The Official Encyclopedia, Fifth Edition (By Disney Legend Dave Smith)<br />
                    Disney Facts Revealed: Answers to Fans&#8217; Curious Questions (By Disney Legend Dave Smith)<br />
                    Disney Trivia from the Vault: Secrets Revealed and Questions Answered (By Disney Legend Dave Smith)<br />
                    My Pride: Mastering Life&#8217;s Daily Performance from Broadway&#8217;s Record-Breaking Lion King (By Alton Fitzgerald White)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/be-our-guest-10th-anniversary-updated-edition-perfecting-the-art-of-customer-service-ted-kinni-edited-by-wendy-lefkon-abridged/">Be Our Guest (10th Anniversary Updated Edition) : Perfecting the Art of Customer Service &#8211; Ted Kinni, Edited by Wendy Lefkon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startupland : How Three Guys Risked Everything to Turn an Idea into a Global Business &#8211; Mikkel Svane, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/startupland-how-three-guys-risked-everything-to-turn-an-idea-into-a-global-business-mikkel-svane-carlye-adler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Programming / Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/startupland-how-three-guys-risked-everything-to-turn-an-idea-into-a-global-business-mikkel-svane-carlye-adler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The real story of what it takes to risk it all and go for broke. Conventional wisdom says most startups need to be in Silicon Valley, started by young engineers around a sexy new idea, and backed by VC funding. But as Mikkel Svane reveals in Startupland, the story of founding Zendesk was anything but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startupland-how-three-guys-risked-everything-to-turn-an-idea-into-a-global-business-mikkel-svane-carlye-adler-abridged/">Startupland : How Three Guys Risked Everything to Turn an Idea into a Global Business &#8211; Mikkel Svane, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The real story of what it takes to risk it all and go for broke. Conventional wisdom says most startups need to be in Silicon Valley, started by young engineers around a sexy new idea, and backed by VC funding. But as Mikkel Svane reveals in Startupland, the story of founding Zendesk was anything but conventional. Founded in a Copenhagen loft by three thirty-something friends looking to break free from corporate doldrums, Zendesk Inc. is now one of the hottest enterprise software companies, still rapidly growing with customers in 150 countries. But its success was anything but predestined. With revealing stories both funny and frank, Mikkel shares how he and his friends bravely left secure jobs to start something on their own, how he almost went broke several times, how they picked up themselves and their families to travel across the world to California and the unknown, and how the three friends were miraculously still together for Zendesk&#8217;s IPO and (still growing) success.<br />
                    Much like Zendesk&#8217;s mission itself to remove friction, barriers, and mystery in order to make customer service easier and more approachable Startupland removes some of the myths about startups and startup founders. Mikkel&#8217;s advice, hard-won through experience, often bucks conventional wisdom and entrepreneurial tropes. He shares why failure (whether fast or slow) is awful, why a seemingly boring product or idea can be the most exciting, why giving back to the community is as important as the bottom line. From how to hire right (look for people who are not offended by swearing) to which personas generate the highest response rates, Mikkel answers the most pressing questions from the perspective of someone still in the trenches and willing to share the hard truth, warts and all. While there are books by consultants who tell you how to build businesses, or by entrepreneurs now running billion-dollar businesses, there are few books from people still in the trenches who acutely remember the difficult daily decisions, the thrill (and fears) of the early days, the problems that scale with growing a business, and the reason why they all went on the adventure in the first place.<br />
                    Startupland is indispensable reading for all entrepreneurs who want to make their ideas the next big thing. The book will inspire and empower you to follow your own dream and create your own story.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startupland-how-three-guys-risked-everything-to-turn-an-idea-into-a-global-business-mikkel-svane-carlye-adler-abridged/">Startupland : How Three Guys Risked Everything to Turn an Idea into a Global Business &#8211; Mikkel Svane, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?) The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect. Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?)    </p>
<p>                    The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect.    </p>
<p>                    Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover exactly what people want to buy, and how to give it to them &#8211; and in a way that makes people fall in love with you and your company.     </p>
<p>                    The proven, repeatable (yet slightly counterintuitive) Ask Method has quietly generated over $100 million in online sales across 23 different industries, and counting. In this tell-all book, Ryan Levesque reveals this exact method step-by-step, as well as the unusual story behind its discovery.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re an aspiring Internet entrepreneur, advanced online marketer, or established business owner, this book will both inspire you and show you how to skyrocket your online income-while creating a mass of raving fans in the process-simply by asking the right questions in a surprisingly different way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ryan has uncovered some enormous misunderstandings about human buying behavior and then utilized his neuroscience background to create this game-changing marketing and survey strategy. Before you finish the first third of the book, you&#8217;ll be eager to jump ahead and implement his process immediately &#8211; it&#8217;s that powerful!&#8217; &#8211; Annie Hyman Pratt, former CEO of The Coffee Bean and Tea Leaf and CEO of IMPAQ Entrepreneur Business Execution Systems    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ask may be the most important book written for anyone who sells products or services directly to consumers since Breakthrough Advertising was published in 1966. Like that masterpiece, Ask gives us a new paradigm for understanding human behavior at the deepest level, which gives rise to a more intelligent and profitable way to sell almost anything. Ryan Levsque will go down in history as the marketer who used his background to change the way products and services are sold online.&#8217; &#8211; Brian Kurtz, business builder of Boardroom Inc. and serial direct marketer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Storytelling Edge : How to Transform Your Business, Stop Screaming into the Void, and Make People Love You &#8211; Shane Snow, Joe Lazauskas, Contently, Inc. (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-storytelling-edge-how-to-transform-your-business-stop-screaming-into-the-void-and-make-people-love-you-shane-snow-joe-lazauskas-contently-inc-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-storytelling-edge-how-to-transform-your-business-stop-screaming-into-the-void-and-make-people-love-you-shane-snow-joe-lazauskas-contently-inc-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A terrific and timely book that makes a compelling case for fundamentally rethinking how your business communicates. Recommended!&#8221; -Jay Baer, founder of Convince &#038; Convert and author of Hug Your Haters &#8220;Once upon a time, storytelling was confused with talking at people. Not anymore. Shane and Joe are your narrators in a journey that will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storytelling-edge-how-to-transform-your-business-stop-screaming-into-the-void-and-make-people-love-you-shane-snow-joe-lazauskas-contently-inc-abridged/">The Storytelling Edge : How to Transform Your Business, Stop Screaming into the Void, and Make People Love You &#8211; Shane Snow, Joe Lazauskas, Contently, Inc. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A terrific and timely book that makes a compelling case for fundamentally rethinking how your business communicates. Recommended!&#8221;<br />
                    -Jay Baer, founder of Convince &#038; Convert and author of Hug Your Haters    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Once upon a time, storytelling was confused with talking at people. Not anymore. Shane and Joe are your narrators in a journey that will transform how you talk to other human beings to be more believable, relevant, compelling and unforgettable.&#8221;<br />
                    -Brian Solis, experience architect, digital anthropologist, best-selling author    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Shane Snow and Joe Lazauskas spend the overwhelming majority of their time thinking, writing, and theorizing about brand storytelling &#8211; so you don&#8217;t have to. They&#8217;re smart and they know this topic inside out (and sideways). Read their book. While I can&#8217;t guarantee you&#8217;ll rise to Shane and Joe&#8217;s ridiculously obsessive level, you will be infinitely better prepared to tell your own brand&#8217;s story. Promise!&#8221;<br />
                    -Rebecca Lieb, Analyst, Author &#038; Advisor    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Contently team understands the power of story, and how to craft and spread a great narrative, like no other. In an era where brand, design, and mission are a competitive advantage for every business, Contently underscores the importance of stories and how they transform companies and industries.&#8221;<br />
                    -Scott Belsky, Entrepreneur, Investor, &#038; Author (Founder of Behance, bestselling author of Making Ideas Happen)    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I can&#8217;t think of a better way to illustrate the power of story telling than by telling great stories. This book should be required reading not just by those with content in their titles, but by anyone in Marketing AND Sales. Then, when you&#8217;re done, give it to your CEO to read&#8230; but make sure you get it back, because I guarantee you&#8217;ll refer to it more than once.&#8221;<br />
                    -Shawna Dennis, Senior Marketing Leader    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Neuroscience, algorithms, illustrations, personal anecdotes and good, old-fashioned empathy: This entertaining and informative tome journeys to the core of how we communicate and pushes us, as marketers and humans, to do it better, &#8220;speeding the reader through and leaving us wanting more.&#8221;<br />
                    -Ann Hynek, VP of global content marketing at Morgan Stanley    </p>
<p>                     Transform your business through the power of storytelling.    </p>
<p>                     Content strategists Joe Lazauskas and Shane Snow offer an insider&#8217;s guide to transforming your business-and all the relationships that matter to it-through the art and science of telling great stories.    </p>
<p>                     Smart businesses today understand the need to use stories to better connect with the people they care about. But few know how to do it well. In The Storytelling Edge, the strategy minds behind Contently, the world renowned content marketing technology company, reveal their secrets that have helped award-winning brands to build relationships with millions of advocates and customers.    </p>
<p>                     Join as they dive into the neuroscience of storytelling, the elements of powerful stories, and methodologies to grow businesses through engaging and accountable content.    </p>
<p>                     With The Storytelling Edge you will discover how leaders and workers can craft the powerful stories that not only build brands and engage customers, but also build relationships and make people care-in work and in life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storytelling-edge-how-to-transform-your-business-stop-screaming-into-the-void-and-make-people-love-you-shane-snow-joe-lazauskas-contently-inc-abridged/">The Storytelling Edge : How to Transform Your Business, Stop Screaming into the Void, and Make People Love You &#8211; Shane Snow, Joe Lazauskas, Contently, Inc. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Evergreen: Cultivate the Enduring Customer Loyalty That Keeps Your Business Thriving &#8211; Noah Fleming (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/evergreen-cultivate-the-enduring-customer-loyalty-that-keeps-your-business-thriving-noah-fleming-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/evergreen-cultivate-the-enduring-customer-loyalty-that-keeps-your-business-thriving-noah-fleming-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Loyal customers are the beating heart of every great business. So why do so many companies act like adrenalin junkies, chasing after new customers at the expense of creating deeper, more profitable relationships with the ones they already have?Evergreen exposes the mad pursuit for what it is: a brief spike in metrics and an ongoing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/evergreen-cultivate-the-enduring-customer-loyalty-that-keeps-your-business-thriving-noah-fleming-abridged/">Evergreen: Cultivate the Enduring Customer Loyalty That Keeps Your Business Thriving &#8211; Noah Fleming (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Loyal customers are the beating heart of every great business. So why do so many companies act like adrenalin junkies, chasing after new customers at the expense of creating deeper, more profitable relationships with the ones they already have?Evergreen exposes the mad pursuit for what it is: a brief spike in metrics and an ongoing revenue drain, as one-time customers fail to return. A better solution is to shift resources from attracting new customers to engaging the base &#8211; the path to stable growth, season after season. The book&#8217;s entertaining stories and action steps reveal how anyone can:    </p>
<p>                    Cultivate the 3Cs of evergreen companies: character, community, and contentBuild loyalty programs that turn satisfied customers into enthusiastic advocatesNurture profitable customers while pruning those who sap time and moneyInject authenticity into social media communicationsInvert the expectations gap that can drive customers away<br />
                    From Internet startups and mom-and-pop businesses to multinational giants, strong companies are rooted in customer retention. Evergreen helps anyone merge high-tech tools with the personal touch to forge lasting bonds and steady profits.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/evergreen-cultivate-the-enduring-customer-loyalty-that-keeps-your-business-thriving-noah-fleming-abridged/">Evergreen: Cultivate the Enduring Customer Loyalty That Keeps Your Business Thriving &#8211; Noah Fleming (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Customer Winback : How to Recapture Lost Customers&#8211;And Keep Them Loyal &#8211; Jill Griffin, Michael W. Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/customer-winback-how-to-recapture-lost-customers-and-keep-them-loyal-jill-griffin-michael-w-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/customer-winback-how-to-recapture-lost-customers-and-keep-them-loyal-jill-griffin-michael-w-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most firms consider the lost customer a lost cause. But in this ground breaking book, Jill Griffin and Michael Lowenstein provide you with step-by-step solutions for winning back lost customers, saving customers on the brink of defection, and making your firm defection proof. Whether your business is small or large, product- or service-based, retail or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/customer-winback-how-to-recapture-lost-customers-and-keep-them-loyal-jill-griffin-michael-w-lowenstein-abridged/">Customer Winback : How to Recapture Lost Customers&#8211;And Keep Them Loyal &#8211; Jill Griffin, Michael W. Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most firms consider the lost customer a lost cause. But in this ground breaking book, Jill Griffin and Michael Lowenstein provide you with step-by-step solutions for winning back lost customers, saving customers on the brink of defection, and making your firm defection proof. Whether your business is small or large, product- or service-based, retail or wholesale, this book offers proven strategies for recognizing which lost customers have the highest win-back value and implementing a sure-fire plan to recover them. It includes the techniques of hundreds of innovative companies who are already working to recapture lost customers and keep them loyal. In today&#8217;s hyper-competitive marketplace, no customer retention program can be entirely foolproof, but with this guide gives you today&#8217;s best methods for winning back those customers you simply can&#8217;t afford to let go.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/customer-winback-how-to-recapture-lost-customers-and-keep-them-loyal-jill-griffin-michael-w-lowenstein-abridged/">Customer Winback : How to Recapture Lost Customers&#8211;And Keep Them Loyal &#8211; Jill Griffin, Michael W. Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Lose A Customer Again &#8211; Joey Coleman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Award-winning speaker and business consultant Joey Coleman teaches audiences and companies all over the world how to turn a one-time purchaser into a lifelong customer. Coleman&#8217;s theory of building customer loyalty isn&#8217;t about focusing on marketing or closing the sale: It&#8217;s about the First 100 Days(R) after the sale and the interactions the customer experiences. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/">Never Lose A Customer Again &#8211; Joey Coleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Award-winning speaker and business consultant Joey Coleman teaches audiences and companies all over the world how to turn a one-time purchaser into a lifelong customer.     </p>
<p>                    Coleman&#8217;s theory of building customer loyalty isn&#8217;t about focusing on marketing or closing the sale: It&#8217;s about the First 100 Days(R) after the sale and the interactions the customer experiences.     </p>
<p>                    While new customers experience joy, euphoria, and excitement, these feelings quickly shift to fear, doubt, and uncertainty as buyer&#8217;s remorse sets in. Across all industries, somewhere between 20%-70% of newly acquired customers will stop doing business with a company with the first 100 days of being a new customer because they feel neglected in the early stages of customer onboarding.     </p>
<p>                    In Never Lose a Customer Again, Coleman offers a philosophy and methodology for dramatically increasing customer retention and as a result, the bottom line. He identifies eight distinct emotional phases customers go through in the 100 days following a purchase. From an impulse buy at Starbucks to the thoughtful purchase of a first house, all customers have the potential to experience the eight phases of the customer journey. If you can understand and anticipate the customers&#8217; emotions, you can apply a myriad of tools and techniques &#8212; in-person, email, phone, mail, video, and presents &#8212; to cement a long and valuable relationship.     </p>
<p>                    Coleman&#8217;s system is presented through research and case studies showing how best-in-class companies create remarkable customer experiences at each step in the customer lifecycle.     </p>
<p>                     In the Acclimate stage, customers need you to hold their hand and over-explain how to use your product or service. They&#8217;re often too embarrassed to admit they&#8217;re confused. Take a cue from Canadian software company PolicyMedical and their challenge of getting non-technical users to undergo a complex installation and implementation process. They turned a series of project spreadsheets and installation manuals into a beautiful puzzle customers could assemble after completing each milestone.     </p>
<p>                     In the Adopt stage, customers should be welcomed to the highest tier of tribal membership with both public and private recognitions. For instance, Sephora&#8217;s VIB Rogue member welcome gift provides a metallic membership card (private recognition) and a members-only shade of lipstick (for public display).     </p>
<p>                     In the final stage, Advocate, loyal customers and raving fans are primed to provide powerful referrals. That&#8217;s how elite entrepreneurial event MastermindTalks continues to sell-out their conference year after year &#8211; with zero dollars spent on marketing. By surprising their loyal fans with amazing referral bonuses (an all-expenses paid safari?!) they guarantee their community will keep providing perfect referrals.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly two decades of consulting and keynoting, Coleman provides strategies and systems to increase customer loyalty. Applicable to companies in any industry and of any size (whether measured in employee count, revenue, or total number of customers), implementing his methods regularly leads to an increase in profits of 25-100%.     </p>
<p>                    Working with well-known clients like Hyatt Hotels, Zappos, and NASA, as well as mom-and-pop shops and solo entrepreneurs around the world, Coleman&#8217;s customer retention system has produced incredible results in dozens of industries.     </p>
<p>                    His approach to creating remarkable customer experiences requires minimal financial investment and will be fun for owners, employees, and teams to implement. This book is required reading for business owners, CEOs, and managers &#8211; as well as sales and marketing teams, account managers, and customer service representatives looking for easy to implement action steps that result in lasting change, increased profits, and lifelong customer retention.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/">Never Lose A Customer Again &#8211; Joey Coleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related to the way managers treat employees.    </p>
<p>                    Kelsey Young is an optimistic but disillusioned sales associate working her way through college. Her world opens up when one of her professors challenges her to create a culture of service at her workplace by putting the five components of Legendary Service into practice. AlthoughFerguson&#8217;s, the store where Kelsey works, certainly isn&#8217;t known for service excellence, Kelsey believes she can make a positive difference. She quickly learns that culture change isn&#8217;t easy&#8211;and that her role as a frontline employee is more significant than she ever could have imagined.    </p>
<p>                    In characteristic Blanchard style, Legendary Service: The Key Is to Care is a quick and entertainingread for people at all organizational levels in every industry. When applied, its lessons will have a profound impact on the service experience your customers will receive. Whether a CEO or a part-time employee, every person can make a difference&#8211;and customer service iseveryone&#8217;s job.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR LEGENDARY SERVICE:&#8221;Read this book and establish a service culture in your organization.&#8221; &#8212; Horst Schulze, Chairman/CEO, Capella Hotel Group    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Legendary Service has great learnings for people at all organizational levels: for executives and managers, the value of a service culture; and for frontlinestaff, the reality that they are the face of the company and can make a difference. Legendary service&#8211;it&#8217;s everyone, always.&#8221; &#8212; Mark King, CEO and President, TaylorMade Golf    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Everything I know about service I learned from my career at Hilton Hotels, Marriott International, The Walt Disney Company, and Ken Blanchard. The One Minute Manager dramatically changed my thinking 32 years ago. LegendaryService will teach the next generation how to deliver sensational service. Buy it, study it, implement it.&#8221; &#8212; Lee Cockerell, Executive Vice President, Walt Disney World (Retired &#038; Inspired), and author of Creating Magic and The Customer Rules    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Kathy Cuff and Vicki Halsey have created a fantastic customer service model called ICARE. When you add their voices to that of the master storyteller KenBlanchard, you have a masterpiece entitled Legendary Service. It is a must-read for everyone who, like me, has a passion for service.&#8221; &#8212; Colleen Barrett, President Emeritus, Southwest Airlines, and coauthor of Lead with LUV    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken Blanchard has done it again and delivered the right book at the right time. Legendary Service provides the essentials of hospitality and servant leadership in a way that everyone can adopt&#8211;right now&#8211;today!&#8221; &#8212; John Caparella, President and COO,The Venetian, The Palazzo, and Sands Expo    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken, Kathy, and Vicki show us how to change everyday service events into memorable experiences. Their book is a must-read for anyone unwilling to acceptmediocrity.&#8221; &#8212; Leonardo Inghilleri, coauthor ofExceptional Service, Exceptional Profit</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just Listen : Discover the Secret to Getting Through to Absolutely Anyone &#8211; Mark Goulston (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/just-listen-discover-the-secret-to-getting-through-to-absolutely-anyone-mark-goulston-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/just-listen-discover-the-secret-to-getting-through-to-absolutely-anyone-mark-goulston-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Getting through to someone is a critical, fine art. Whether you are dealing with a harried colleague, a stressed-out client, or an insecure spouse, things will go from bad to worse if you can&#8217;t break through emotional barricades and get your message thoroughly communicated and registered. Drawing on his experience as a psychiatrist, business consultant, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-listen-discover-the-secret-to-getting-through-to-absolutely-anyone-mark-goulston-abridged/">Just Listen : Discover the Secret to Getting Through to Absolutely Anyone &#8211; Mark Goulston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Getting through to someone is a critical, fine art. Whether you are dealing with a harried colleague, a stressed-out client, or an insecure spouse, things will go from bad to worse if you can&#8217;t break through emotional barricades and get your message thoroughly communicated and registered.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his experience as a psychiatrist, business consultant, and coach, author Mark Goulston combines his background with the latest scientific research to help you turn the &#8220;impossible&#8221; and &#8220;unreachable&#8221; people in their lives into allies, devoted customers, loyal colleagues, and lifetime friends.    </p>
<p>                    In Just Listen, Goulston provides simple yet powerful techniques you can use to really get through to people including how to:    </p>
<p>                    make a powerful and positive first impression;<br />
                    listen effectively;<br />
                    make even a total stranger (potential client) feel understood;<br />
                    talk an angry or aggressive person away from an instinctual, unproductive reaction and toward a more rational mindset;<br />
                    and achieve buy-in&#8211;the linchpin of all persuasion, negotiation, and sales.    </p>
<p>                    Whether they&#8217;re coworkers, friends, strangers, or enemies, the first make-or-break step in persuading anyone to do anything is getting them to hear you out. The invaluable principles in Just Listen will get you through that first tough step with anyone.    </p>
<p>                    With this groundbreaking book, you will be able to master the fine but critical art of effective communication.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-listen-discover-the-secret-to-getting-through-to-absolutely-anyone-mark-goulston-abridged/">Just Listen : Discover the Secret to Getting Through to Absolutely Anyone &#8211; Mark Goulston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
