<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mental Health Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/mental-health-services/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/mental-health-services/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Mental Health Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/mental-health-services/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hidden Valley Road &#8211; Robert Kolker</title>
		<link>/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unforgettable&#8217; The Times &#8216;Grippingly told and brilliantly reported&#8217; Mail on Sunday &#8216;Startlingly intimate&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Groundbreaking&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Exceptional and moving&#8217; Spectator &#8216;Hidden Valley Road contains everything: scientific intrigue, meticulous reporting, startling revelations, and, most of all, a profound sense of humanity. It is that rare book that can be read again [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/">Hidden Valley Road &#8211; Robert Kolker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unforgettable&#8217; The Times &#8216;Grippingly told and brilliantly reported&#8217; Mail on Sunday &#8216;Startlingly intimate&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Groundbreaking&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Exceptional and moving&#8217; Spectator &#8216;Hidden Valley Road contains everything: scientific intrigue, meticulous reporting, startling revelations, and, most of all, a profound sense of humanity. It is that rare book that can be read again and again.&#8217; -David Grann, author of Killers of the Flower Moon One of the New York Times&#8217; &#8217;20 most anticipated books of 2020&#8242;: the heartrending story of a mid-century American family with twelve children, six of them diagnosed with schizophrenia, that became science&#8217;s great hope in the quest to understand the disease. &#8216;An extraordinary case study and tour de force of reporting.&#8217; -Sylvia Nasar, author of A Beautiful Mind Don and Mimi Galvin seemed to be living the American dream. After World War II, Don&#8217;s work with the Air Force brought them to Colorado, where their twelve children perfectly spanned the baby boom: the oldest born in 1945, the youngest in 1965. In those years, there was an established script for a family like the Galvins &#8211; aspiration, hard work, upward mobility, domestic harmony &#8211; and they worked hard to play their parts. But behind the scenes was a different story: psychological breakdown, sudden shocking violence, hidden abuse. By the mid-1970s, six of the ten Galvin boys, one after the other, were diagnosed as schizophrenic. How could all this happen to one family? What took place inside the house on Hidden Valley Road was so extraordinary that the Galvins became one of the first families to be studied by the National Institutes of Mental Health. Their story offers a shadow history of the science of schizophrenia, from the era of institutionalization, lobotomy, and the schizophrenogenic mother, to the search for genetic markers for the disease, always amidst profound disagreements about the nature of the illness itself. And unbeknownst to the Galvins, samples of their DNA informed decades of genetic research that continues today, offering paths to treatment, prediction, and even eradication of the disease for future generations. With clarity and compassion, bestselling and award-winning author Robert Kolker uncovers one family&#8217;s unforgettable legacy of suffering, love and hope. &#8216;This book tore my heart out. It is a revelation-about the history of mental health treatment, about trauma, foremost about family-and a more-than-worthy follow-up to Robert Kolker&#8217;s brilliant Lost Girls.&#8217; -Megan Abbott, Edgar Award-winning author of Dare Me and Give Me Your Hand</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/">Hidden Valley Road &#8211; Robert Kolker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Client Centered Therapy (New Ed) &#8211; Carl Rogers</title>
		<link>/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Counselling & Advice Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Presenting the non-directive and related points of view in counselling and therapy, this book defines the progress recently made in the development of the techniques and basic philosophy of counselling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/">Client Centered Therapy (New Ed) &#8211; Carl Rogers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Presenting the non-directive and related points of view in counselling  and therapy, this book defines the progress recently made in the  development of the techniques and basic philosophy of counselling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/client-centered-therapy-new-ed-carl-rogers/">Client Centered Therapy (New Ed) &#8211; Carl Rogers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fight back against a modern culture that is rewiring our brains and damaging our health with this practical, doctor-approved plan for healing that includes a ten-day boot camp and forty delicious recipes. Contemporary life provides us with infinite opportunities, along with endless temptations. We can eat whatever we want, whenever we want. We can immerse [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fight back against a modern culture that is rewiring our brains and damaging our health with this practical, doctor-approved plan for healing that includes a ten-day boot camp and forty delicious recipes.<br />
                    Contemporary life provides us with infinite opportunities, along with endless temptations. We can eat whatever we want, whenever we want. We can immerse ourselves in the vast, enticing world of digital media. We can buy goods and services for rapid delivery with our fingertips or voice commands. But living in this 24/7 hyper-reality poses serious risks to our physical and mental states, our connections to others, and even to the world at large.<br />
                    Brain Wash builds from a simple premise: Our brains are being gravely manipulated, resulting in behaviors that leave us more lonely, anxious, depressed, distrustful, illness-prone, and overweight than ever before.<br />
                    Based on the latest science, the book identifies the mental hijacking that undermines each and every one of us, and presents the tools necessary to think more clearly, make better decisions, strengthen bonds with others, and develop healthier habits. Featuring a 10-day bootcamp program, including a meal plan and 40 delicious original recipes, Brain Wash is the key to cultivating a more purposeful and fulfilling life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spark &#8211; Dr John J. Ratey, Eric Hagerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exercise is not only good for the body: it can transform your mind too. This new scientific revolution will teach you how to boost brain cells, protect yourself against mental illness and dementia, and ensure success in exams and the workplace. We all know that exercise is good for the body. But did you know [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/">Spark &#8211; Dr John J. Ratey, Eric Hagerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exercise is not only good for the body: it can transform your mind  too. This new scientific revolution will teach you how to boost brain  cells, protect yourself against mental illness and dementia, and ensure  success in exams and the workplace.    </p>
<p>                    We all know that exercise is good for the body. But did you know that it can transform your mind? This new scientific revolution will teach you how to boost brain cells, protect yourself against mental illness and dementia, and ensure success in exams and the workplace.     </p>
<p>                    Follow the SPARK! training regimen and build your brain to its peak performance. This book will change the way you think about exercise &#8211; and, for that matter, the way you think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/">Spark &#8211; Dr John J. Ratey, Eric Hagerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rethinking Narcissism : The Secret to Recognizing and Coping with Narcissists &#8211; Craig Malkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rethinking-narcissism-the-secret-to-recognizing-and-coping-with-narcissists-craig-malkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rethinking-narcissism-the-secret-to-recognizing-and-coping-with-narcissists-craig-malkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;[Dr. Malkin&#8217;s] reassuring tone and plethora of case histories offer considered advice and generous encouragement.&#8221; &#8212; Kirkus Reviews When most of us hear the word narcissism or narcissist, we envision vain, preening, braggarts who can&#8217;t stop talking about themselves. But most of the time, we&#8217;ve got it wrong; many narcissists aren&#8217;t driven by looks, fame, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rethinking-narcissism-the-secret-to-recognizing-and-coping-with-narcissists-craig-malkin-abridged/">Rethinking Narcissism : The Secret to Recognizing and Coping with Narcissists &#8211; Craig Malkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;[Dr. Malkin&#8217;s] reassuring tone and plethora of case histories offer considered advice and generous encouragement.&#8221; &#8212; Kirkus Reviews    </p>
<p>                    When most of us hear the word narcissism or narcissist, we envision vain, preening, braggarts who can&#8217;t stop talking about themselves. But most of the time, we&#8217;ve got it wrong; many narcissists aren&#8217;t driven by looks, fame, or money&#8211;some may even be shy or soft spoken. The startling truth is we&#8217;ve been distracted by an empty stereotype that blinds us to far more reliable signs of danger&#8211;and an entire generation is suffering because of it.     </p>
<p>                    In Rethinking Narcissism Harvard Medical School psychologist Craig Malkin addresses the narcissism epidemic by illuminating the spectrum of narcissism, identifying ways to control the trait, and explaining how too little of it may be a bad thing. Readers will learn that there&#8217;s far more to narcissism than its reductive invective would imply. The reality is that we all fall somewhere between utter selflessness and grandiosity. A healthy middle&#8211;a healthy degree of narcissism&#8211;is essential for a strong sense of self. Malkin deconstructs our misconceptions of narcissism and offers clear, step-by-step guidance on how to protect ourselves and how to promote healthy narcissism in our partners, our children, and ourselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rethinking-narcissism-the-secret-to-recognizing-and-coping-with-narcissists-craig-malkin-abridged/">Rethinking Narcissism : The Secret to Recognizing and Coping with Narcissists &#8211; Craig Malkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm : The One Stop Guide: Practical Advice for Anybody Affected by Self-Harm &#8211; Allan House (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Self-harm is increasingly prevalent in our society. But few of us understand why, or know what to do to help ourselves, friends or family in such situations. It can be very isolating. Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm aims to fill this gap, providing practical information and advice for anyone who has an experience of self-harm. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/">Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm : The One Stop Guide: Practical Advice for Anybody Affected by Self-Harm &#8211; Allan House (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Self-harm is increasingly prevalent in our society. But few of us understand why, or know what to do to help ourselves, friends or family in such situations. It can be very isolating.    </p>
<p>                    Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm aims to fill this gap, providing practical information and advice for anyone who has an experience of self-harm.    </p>
<p>                    Showing the various forms self-harm can take, this book explores the reasons behind it, and offers advice on self-management, support to others, and what services are available. Full of clear, thoughtful advice for those who may be thinking of harming themselves, or have already done so, as well as guidance for families and friends on helpful strategies and responses &#8211; and ones to avoid &#8211; it uses evidence from research and direct experience to provide an essential resource.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/">Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm : The One Stop Guide: Practical Advice for Anybody Affected by Self-Harm &#8211; Allan House (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fear Factor : How One Emotion Connects Altruists, Psychopaths and Everyone In-Between &#8211; Abigail Marsh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fear-factor-how-one-emotion-connects-altruists-psychopaths-and-everyone-in-between-abigail-marsh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fear-factor-how-one-emotion-connects-altruists-psychopaths-and-everyone-in-between-abigail-marsh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A riveting ride through your own brain&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals WINNER of the Society for Personality and Social Psychology&#8217;s book prize for &#8216;The Promotion of Social and Personality Science&#8217; If humans are fundamentally good, why do we engage in acts of great cruelty? If we are evil, why [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fear-factor-how-one-emotion-connects-altruists-psychopaths-and-everyone-in-between-abigail-marsh-abridged/">The Fear Factor : How One Emotion Connects Altruists, Psychopaths and Everyone In-Between &#8211; Abigail Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A riveting ride through your own brain&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    WINNER of the Society for Personality and Social Psychology&#8217;s book prize for &#8216;The Promotion of Social and Personality Science&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    If humans are fundamentally good, why do we engage in acts of great cruelty? If we are evil, why do we sometimes help others at a cost to ourselves?     </p>
<p>                    Whether humans are good or evil is a question that has plagued philosophers and scientists for as long as there have been philosophers and scientists.    </p>
<p>                    Many argue that we are fundamentally selfish, and only the rules and laws of our societies and our own relentless efforts of will can save us from ourselves. But is this really true?     </p>
<p>                    Abigail Marsh is a social neuroscientist who has closely studied the brains of both the worst and the best among us-from children with psychopathic traits whose families live in fear of them, to adult altruists who have given their own kidneys to strangers. Her groundbreaking findings suggest a possibility that is more optimistic than the dominant view. Humans are not good or evil, but are equally (and fundamentally) capable of good and evil.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fear Factor Marsh explores the human capacity for caring, drawing on cutting edge research findings from clinical, translational and brain imaging investigations on the nature of empathy, altruism, and aggression and brings us closer to understanding the basis of humans&#8217; social nature.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You won&#8217;t be able to put it down&#8217; &#8211; Daniel Gilbert, New York Times bestselling author of Stumbling on Happiness    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;[It] reads like a thriller&#8230; One of the most mind-opening books I have read in years&#8217; &#8211; Matthieu Ricard, author of Altruism</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fear-factor-how-one-emotion-connects-altruists-psychopaths-and-everyone-in-between-abigail-marsh-abridged/">The Fear Factor : How One Emotion Connects Altruists, Psychopaths and Everyone In-Between &#8211; Abigail Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news. In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news.     </p>
<p>                    In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled mentally ill in the United States tripled over the past two decades?     </p>
<p>                    Interwoven with Whitaker&#8217;s groundbreaking analysis of the merits of psychiatric medications are the personal stories of children and adults swept up in this epidemic. As Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, other societies have begun to alter their use of psychiatric medications and are now reporting much improved outcomes . . . so why can&#8217;t such change happen here in the United States? Why have the results from these long-term studies&#8211;all of which point to the same startling conclusion&#8211;been kept from the public?     </p>
<p>                    Our nation has been hit by an epidemic of disabling mental illness, and yet, as Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, the medical blueprints for curbing that epidemic have already been drawn up.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Anatomy of an Epidemic     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The timing of Robert Whitaker&#8217;s Anatomy of an Epidemic, a comprehensive and highly readable history of psychiatry in the United States, couldn&#8217;t be better.&#8221;&#8211;Salon     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Anatomy of an Epidemic offers some answers, charting controversial ground with mystery-novel pacing.&#8221;&#8211;TIME     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lucid, pointed and important, Anatomy of an Epidemic should be required reading for anyone considering extended use of psychiatric medicine. Whitaker is at the height of his powers.&#8221; &#8211;Greg Critser, author of Generation Rx</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Where You Belong : Finding Home Wherever You Are &#8211; Melody Warnick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-where-you-belong-finding-home-wherever-you-are-melody-warnick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-where-you-belong-finding-home-wherever-you-are-melody-warnick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Gretchen Rubin&#8217;s megaseller The Happiness Project and Eric Weiner&#8217;s The Geography of Bliss, a journalist embarks on a project to discover what it takes to love where you live The average restless American will move 11.7 times in a lifetime. For Melody Warnick, it was move #6, from Austin, Texas, to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-where-you-belong-finding-home-wherever-you-are-melody-warnick-abridged/">This Is Where You Belong : Finding Home Wherever You Are &#8211; Melody Warnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Gretchen Rubin&#8217;s megaseller The Happiness Project and Eric Weiner&#8217;s The Geography of Bliss, a journalist embarks on a project to discover what it takes to love where you live    </p>
<p>                    The average restless American will move 11.7 times in a lifetime. For Melody Warnick, it was move #6, from Austin, Texas, to Blacksburg, Virginia, that threatened to unhinge her. In the lonely aftermath of unpacking, she wondered: Aren&#8217;t we supposed to put down roots at some point? How does the place we live become the place we want to stay? This time, she had an epiphany. Rather than hold her breath and hope this new town would be her family&#8217;s perfect fit, she would figure out how to fall in love with it-no matter what.<br />
                         How we come to feel at home in our towns and cities is what Warnick sets out to discover in This Is Where You Belong. She dives into the body of research around place attachment-the deep sense of connection that binds some of us to our cities and increases our physical and emotional well-being-then travels to towns across America to see it in action. Inspired by a growing movement of placemaking, she examines what its practitioners are doing to create likeable locales. She also speaks with frequent movers and loyal stayers around the country to learn what draws highly mobile Americans to a new city, and what makes us stay. The best ideas she imports to her adopted hometown of Blacksburg for a series of Love Where You Live experiments designed to make her feel more locally connected. Dining with her neighbors. Shopping Small Business Saturday. Marching in the town Christmas parade.<br />
                         Can these efforts make a halfhearted resident happier? Will Blacksburg be the place she finally stays? What Warnick learns will inspire you to embrace your own community-and perhaps discover that the place where you live right now . . . is home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-where-you-belong-finding-home-wherever-you-are-melody-warnick-abridged/">This Is Where You Belong : Finding Home Wherever You Are &#8211; Melody Warnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reclaim Your Brain : How to Calm Your Thoughts, Heal Your Mind, and Bring Your Life Back Under Control &#8211; Joseph A. Annibali, Foreword by Daniel G. Amen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reclaim-your-brain-how-to-calm-your-thoughts-heal-your-mind-and-bring-your-life-back-under-control-joseph-a-annibali-foreword-by-daniel-g-amen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reclaim-your-brain-how-to-calm-your-thoughts-heal-your-mind-and-bring-your-life-back-under-control-joseph-a-annibali-foreword-by-daniel-g-amen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A prescriptive guide to restoring cognitive calm, based on Amen Clinics chief psychiatrist Dr. Joseph Annibali&#8217;s three decades of treating patients who suffer from overloaded, overstimulated brains. Dr. Joseph Annibali has treated thousands of people with overloaded, overstimulated brains. Some people describe their brain as being &#8220;in chaos&#8221;; others feel that their brain is &#8220;on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaim-your-brain-how-to-calm-your-thoughts-heal-your-mind-and-bring-your-life-back-under-control-joseph-a-annibali-foreword-by-daniel-g-amen-abridged/">Reclaim Your Brain : How to Calm Your Thoughts, Heal Your Mind, and Bring Your Life Back Under Control &#8211; Joseph A. Annibali, Foreword by Daniel G. Amen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A prescriptive guide to restoring cognitive calm, based on Amen Clinics chief psychiatrist Dr. Joseph Annibali&#8217;s three decades of treating patients who suffer from overloaded, overstimulated brains.    </p>
<p>                     Dr. Joseph Annibali has treated thousands of people with overloaded, overstimulated brains. Some people describe their brain as being &#8220;in chaos&#8221;; others feel that their brain is &#8220;on fire.&#8221; But whether they are ultimately diagnosed with anxiety, disabling OCD, depression, bipolar disorder, or even substance abuse, the underlying problem is a Too-Busy Brain, a great irritant that interferes with attention, concentration, focus, mood, and often much more. It may even be a sign of undetected damage to either the brain or the body itself. But through practical strategies, understandable explanations, and prescriptive mind-management techniques, Dr. Annibali will help readers finally reclaim their brains and get back in control of their lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaim-your-brain-how-to-calm-your-thoughts-heal-your-mind-and-bring-your-life-back-under-control-joseph-a-annibali-foreword-by-daniel-g-amen-abridged/">Reclaim Your Brain : How to Calm Your Thoughts, Heal Your Mind, and Bring Your Life Back Under Control &#8211; Joseph A. Annibali, Foreword by Daniel G. Amen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Change Your Mind : What the New Science of Psychedelics Teaches Us About Consciousness, Dying, Addiction, Depression, and Transcendence &#8211; Michael Pollan</title>
		<link>/how-to-change-your-mind-what-the-new-science-of-psychedelics-teaches-us-about-consciousness-dying-addiction-depression-and-transcendence-michael-pollan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Body]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pain & Pain Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-change-your-mind-what-the-new-science-of-psychedelics-teaches-us-about-consciousness-dying-addiction-depression-and-transcendence-michael-pollan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Pollan keeps you turning the pages . . . cleareyed and assured.&#8221; -New York Times A #1 New York Times Bestseller, New York Times Book Review 10 Best Books of 2018, and New York Times Notable Book A brilliant and brave investigation into the medical and scientific revolution taking place around psychedelic drugs&#8211;and the spellbinding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-change-your-mind-what-the-new-science-of-psychedelics-teaches-us-about-consciousness-dying-addiction-depression-and-transcendence-michael-pollan/">How to Change Your Mind : What the New Science of Psychedelics Teaches Us About Consciousness, Dying, Addiction, Depression, and Transcendence &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Pollan keeps you turning the pages . . . cleareyed and assured.&#8221; -New York Times</p>
<p>A #1 New York Times Bestseller, New York Times Book Review 10 Best Books of 2018, and New York Times Notable Book</p>
<p>A brilliant and brave investigation into the medical and scientific revolution taking place around psychedelic drugs&#8211;and the spellbinding story of his own life-changing psychedelic experiences</p>
<p>When Michael Pollan set out to research how LSD and psilocybin (the active ingredient in magic mushrooms) are being used to provide relief to people suffering from difficult-to-treat conditions such as depression, addiction and anxiety, he did not intend to write what is undoubtedly his most personal book. But upon discovering how these remarkable substances are improving the lives not only of the mentally ill but also of healthy people coming to grips with the challenges of everyday life, he decided to explore the landscape of the mind in the first person as well as the third. Thus began a singular adventure into various altered states of consciousness, along with a dive deep into both the latest brain science and the thriving underground community of psychedelic therapists.  Pollan sifts the historical record to separate the truth about these mysterious drugs from the myths that have surrounded them since the 1960s, when a handful of psychedelic evangelists inadvertently catalyzed a powerful backlash against what was then a promising field of research.</p>
<p>A unique and elegant blend of science, memoir, travel writing, history, and medicine, How to Change Your Mind is a triumph of participatory journalism. By turns dazzling and edifying, it is the gripping account of a journey to an exciting and unexpected new frontier in our understanding of the mind, the self, and our place in the world. The true subject of Pollan&#8217;s &#8220;mental travelogue&#8221; is not just psychedelic drugs but also the eternal puzzle of human consciousness and how, in a world that offers us both suffering and joy, we can do our best to be fully present and find meaning in our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-change-your-mind-what-the-new-science-of-psychedelics-teaches-us-about-consciousness-dying-addiction-depression-and-transcendence-michael-pollan/">How to Change Your Mind : What the New Science of Psychedelics Teaches Us About Consciousness, Dying, Addiction, Depression, and Transcendence &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
