<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Popular Medicine &amp; Health Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/popular-medicine-health/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/popular-medicine-health/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Popular Medicine &amp; Health Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/popular-medicine-health/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Wuhan Diary : Dispatches from a Quarantined City &#8211; Fang Fang</title>
		<link>/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aid & Relief Programmes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Disasters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From one of China&#8217;s most acclaimed and decorated writers comes a powerful first-person account of life in Wuhan during the COVID-19 outbreak. On January 25, 2020, after the central government imposed a lockdown in Wuhan, acclaimed Chinese writer Fang Fang began publishing an online diary. In the days and weeks that followed, Fang Fang&#8217;s nightly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/">Wuhan Diary : Dispatches from a Quarantined City &#8211; Fang Fang</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From one of China&#8217;s most acclaimed and decorated writers comes a powerful first-person account of life in Wuhan during the COVID-19 outbreak.</p>
<p>                    On January 25, 2020, after the central government imposed a lockdown in Wuhan, acclaimed Chinese writer Fang Fang began publishing an online diary. In the days and weeks that followed, Fang Fang&#8217;s nightly postings gave voice to the fears, frustrations, anger, and hope of millions of her fellow citizens, reflecting on the psychological impact of forced isolation, the role of the internet as both community lifeline and source of misinformation, and most tragically, the lives of neighbors and friends taken by the deadly virus. </p>
<p>                    A fascinating eyewitness account of events as they unfold, Wuhan Diary captures the challenges of daily life and the changing moods and emotions of being quarantined without reliable information. Fang Fang finds solace in small domestic comforts and is inspired by the courage of friends, health professionals and volunteers, as well as the resilience and perseverance of Wuhan&#8217;s nine million residents. But, by claiming the writer´s duty to record she also speaks out against social injustice, abuse of power, and other problems which impeded the response to the epidemic and gets herself embroiled in online controversies because of it.</p>
<p>                    As Fang Fang documents the beginning of the global health crisis in real time, we are able to identify patterns and mistakes that many of the countries dealing with the novel coronavirus have later repeated. She reminds us that, in the face of the new virus, the plight of the citizens of Wuhan is also that of citizens everywhere. As Fang Fang writes: &#8220;The virus is the common enemy of humankind; that is a lesson for all humanity. The only way we can conquer this virus and free ourselves from its grip is for all members of humankind to work together.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    Blending the intimate and the epic, the profound and the quotidian, Wuhan Diary is a remarkable record of an extraordinary time. </p>
<p>                    Translated from the Chinese by Michael Berry</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/">Wuhan Diary : Dispatches from a Quarantined City &#8211; Fang Fang</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wild Embers : Poems of rebellion, fire and beauty &#8211; Nikita Gill</title>
		<link>/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry By Individual Poets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A stunning collection of poetry on feminism, trauma, survival and empowerment. You cannot burn away What has always been aflame WILD EMBERS explores the fire that lies within every soul, weaving words around ideas of feeling at home in your own skin, allowing yourself to heal and learning to embrace your uniqueness with love from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/">Wild Embers : Poems of rebellion, fire and beauty &#8211; Nikita Gill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A stunning collection of poetry on feminism, trauma, survival and empowerment.    </p>
<p>                    You cannot burn away<br />
                    What has always been aflame    </p>
<p>                    WILD EMBERS explores the fire that lies within every soul, weaving words around ideas of feeling at home in your own skin, allowing yourself to heal and learning to embrace your uniqueness with love from the universe.     </p>
<p>                    Featuring rewritten fairytale heroines, goddess wisdom and poetry that burns with revolution, this collection is an explosion of femininity, empowerment and personal growth.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wild-embers-poems-of-rebellion-fire-and-beauty-nikita-gill/">Wild Embers : Poems of rebellion, fire and beauty &#8211; Nikita Gill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</title>
		<link>/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8211; Over five million copies sold worldwide! From renowned psychiatrist Dr. David D. Burns, the revolutionary volume that popularized Dr. Aaron T. Beck&#8217;s cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) and has helped millions combat feelings of depression and develop greater self-esteem. Anxiety and depression are the most common mental illnesses in the world, affecting 18% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/">Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8211; Over five million copies sold worldwide!</p>
<p>                    From renowned psychiatrist Dr. David D. Burns, the revolutionary volume that popularized Dr. Aaron T. Beck&#8217;s cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) and has helped millions combat feelings of depression and develop greater self-esteem.</p>
<p>                    Anxiety and depression are the most common mental illnesses in the world, affecting 18% of the U.S. population every year. But for many, the path to recovery seems daunting, endless, or completely out of reach.</p>
<p>                    The good news is that anxiety, guilt, pessimism, procrastination, low self-esteem, and other black holes of depression can be alleviated. In Feeling Good, eminent psychiatrist, David D. Burns, M.D., outlines the remarkable, scientifically proven techniques that will immediately lift your spirits and help you develop a positive outlook on life, enabling you to: Nip negative feelings in the budRecognize what causes your mood swingsDeal with guiltHandle hostility and criticismOvercome addiction to love and approvalBuild self-esteemFeel good everyday</p>
<p>                    This groundbreaking, life-changing book has helped millions overcome negative thoughts and discover joy in their daily lives. You owe it to yourself to FEEL GOOD!</p>
<p>                    I would personally evaluate David Burns&#8217; Feeling Good as one of the most significant books to come out of the last third of the Twentieth Century. ?- Dr. David F. Maas, Professor of English, Ambassador University</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/">Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The UltraMind Solution : The Simple Way to Defeat Depression, Overcome Anxiety, and Sharpen Your Mind &#8211; Mark Hyman</title>
		<link>/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Ultramind Solutionspeaks directly to the massive generation of boomers who, for the first time, are encountering diminishing memory and focus, among other affects of life on earth and the human brain. Like all of Dr. Hyman&#8217;s work, this latest instalment in the &#8220;Ultra&#8221; series teaches the reader how to use the body to heal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/">The UltraMind Solution : The Simple Way to Defeat Depression, Overcome Anxiety, and Sharpen Your Mind &#8211; Mark Hyman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ultramind Solutionspeaks directly to the massive generation of boomers who, for the first time, are encountering diminishing memory and focus, among other affects of life on earth and the human brain. Like all of Dr. Hyman&#8217;s work, this latest instalment in the &#8220;Ultra&#8221; series teaches the reader how to use the body to heal the body, this time making lifestyle changes that will foster brain function, including memory, mood, and attention span as well as battle everything from brain fatigue to depression.     </p>
<p>                    Like all of Dr. Hyman&#8217;s books, Ultramindincludes the 7 Keys to Brain Health and a simple 6 week program that will cleanse, heal and strengthen the brain. Each section has a quiz for the reader to access the affect of each particular key on their brain function, provides a list of diagnostic tests for clinical treatments as well as a how to implement healing solutions from changes in nutrition to supplements, hormones, detoxification, and fighting brain &#8220;allergies.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    The Ultramind Solutionincludes a brain workout and recipes for &#8220;brain&#8221; foods that stimulate performance.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultramind-solution-the-simple-way-to-defeat-depression-overcome-anxiety-and-sharpen-your-mind-mark-hyman/">The UltraMind Solution : The Simple Way to Defeat Depression, Overcome Anxiety, and Sharpen Your Mind &#8211; Mark Hyman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</title>
		<link>/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Giving Up Smoking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Respiratory Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Funding & Policy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19. Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19.    </p>
<p>                    Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns and border closings causing widespread business closures, economic collapse, and massive unemployment; and an unprecedented curtailment of civil liberties and freedoms in the name of keeping people safe by locking them up in their homes.    </p>
<p>                    We are now living in a world that is increasingly ruled, not by our democratic systems and institutions, but by public health fiat, carried out by politicians who rule by instilling fear and panic.    </p>
<p>                    In The Truth About COVID-19, Dr. Mercola and Cummins reveal new and emerging evidence that:    </p>
<p>                    The SARS-CoV-2 virus was, indeed, lab-engineered and emerged from a negligently managed bioweapons lab in Wuhan, China<br />
                    The global pandemic was long anticipated by global elites who have used it to facilitate and hide the largest upward transfer of wealth in human history<br />
                    PCR testing, case counts, morbidity, and vaccine safety and efficacy data have been widely manipulated and misrepresented<br />
                    Obesity, diabetes, and heart disease are known to worsen COVID-19 outcomes, but the junk food industry continues to push its agenda at the expense of public health<br />
                    Safe, simple, and inexpensive treatment and prevention for COVID-19 have been censored and suppressed to create a clear path for vaccine acceptance<br />
                    Effectiveness of the vaccines has been wildly exaggerated and major safety questions have gone unanswered    </p>
<p>                    The good news in all of this is that we can take control of our health and that, together, we have the power to unite and fight back for our health, democracy, and freedom. The time is now for a global awakening. As Dr. Mercola and Cummins remind us, this is the fight of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Night School : The Life-Changing Science of Sleep &#8211; Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/night-school-the-life-changing-science-of-sleep-richard-wiseman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/night-school-the-life-changing-science-of-sleep-richard-wiseman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Almost a third of your whole life is spent asleep. Every night you close your eyes, become oblivious to your surroundings and waste hours flying, being chased or watching all your teeth fall out &#8211; and then you wake up. What on earth is going on? Based on exciting new peer-reviewed research, mass-participation experiments and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/night-school-the-life-changing-science-of-sleep-richard-wiseman-abridged/">Night School : The Life-Changing Science of Sleep &#8211; Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Almost a third of your whole life is spent asleep. Every night you close your eyes, become oblivious to your surroundings and waste hours flying, being chased or watching all your teeth fall out &#8211; and then you wake up. What on earth is going on?    </p>
<p>                     Based on exciting new peer-reviewed research, mass-participation experiments and the world&#8217;s largest archive of dream reports, Night School uncovers the truth about the sleeping brain &#8211; and gives powerful tips on how you can use those hours of apparently &#8216;dead&#8217; time to change your waking life. Along the way you will discover how to learn information while you sleep, the creative potential of a six-minute nap, and what your dreams really mean.    </p>
<p>                     Studies show that even a small lack of sleep can have a detrimental effect on health and happiness. It&#8217;s time to banish nightmares, make the most of the missing third of your days, and get the best night&#8217;s sleep of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/night-school-the-life-changing-science-of-sleep-richard-wiseman-abridged/">Night School : The Life-Changing Science of Sleep &#8211; Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Lucky Years : How to Thrive in the Brave New World of Health &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-lucky-years-how-to-thrive-in-the-brave-new-world-of-health-david-b-agus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-lucky-years-how-to-thrive-in-the-brave-new-world-of-health-david-b-agus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bestselling author David Agus unveils the brave new world of medicine, one in which we can take control of our health like never before and doctors can fine-tune strategies and weapons to prevent illness. In his first bestseller, The End of Illness, David Agus revealed how to add vibrant years to your life by knowing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-lucky-years-how-to-thrive-in-the-brave-new-world-of-health-david-b-agus-abridged/">The Lucky Years : How to Thrive in the Brave New World of Health &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bestselling author David Agus unveils the brave new world of medicine, one in which we can take control of our health like never before and doctors can fine-tune strategies and weapons to prevent illness.    </p>
<p>                    In his first bestseller, The End of Illness, David Agus revealed how to add vibrant years to your life by knowing the real facts of health. In this book, he builds on that theme by showing why this is the luckiest time yet to be alive, giving you the keys to the new kingdom of wellness.     </p>
<p>                    Medicine is undergoing rapid change. In the old world, you followed general principles and doctors treated you based on broad, one-size-fits-all solutions. In this new golden age, you&#8217;ll be able to take full advantage of the latest scientific findings and leverage the power of technology to customize your care. Only those who know how to access and adapt to these breakthroughs &#8211; without being distracted by hyped ideas and bad medicine &#8211; will benefit. Imagine being able to get fit and lose weight without dieting, train your immune system to fight cancer, edit your DNA to avoid a certain fate, erase the risk of a heart attack, reverse aging, and know exactly which drugs to take to optimize health with zero side effects.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-lucky-years-how-to-thrive-in-the-brave-new-world-of-health-david-b-agus-abridged/">The Lucky Years : How to Thrive in the Brave New World of Health &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone struggles with sleep from time to time, but when sleepless nights and overtired days become the norm, your well-being is compromised, and frustration and worry increase-including concerns about what&#8217;s stopping you from getting the sleep you need, and what can be done about it. So, how do you stop the cycle of relentless worries [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/">End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone struggles with sleep from time to time, but when sleepless nights and overtired days become the norm, your well-being is compromised, and frustration and worry increase-including concerns about what&#8217;s stopping you from getting the sleep you need, and what can be done about it. So, how do you stop the cycle of relentless worries and restless nights?    </p>
<p>                    End the Insomnia Struggle offers a comprehensive, medication-free program that can be individually tailored for anyone who struggles with insomnia. Integrating the physiology of sleep, and proven-effective approaches from cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I) and acceptance and commitment therapy (ACT), this book provides step-by-step guidance for developing your own treatment plan according to your particular challenges with insomnia.    </p>
<p>                    With this book, you&#8217;ll have everything you need to overcome the relentless thoughts, ruminations, and stress of insomnia. Utilizing these evidence-based strategies and easy-to-use tools, you&#8217;ll finally get to sleep, stay asleep, and wake up rested and ready to face the world as your best self, day after day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/">End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fight back against a modern culture that is rewiring our brains and damaging our health with this practical, doctor-approved plan for healing that includes a ten-day boot camp and forty delicious recipes. Contemporary life provides us with infinite opportunities, along with endless temptations. We can eat whatever we want, whenever we want. We can immerse [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fight back against a modern culture that is rewiring our brains and damaging our health with this practical, doctor-approved plan for healing that includes a ten-day boot camp and forty delicious recipes.<br />
                    Contemporary life provides us with infinite opportunities, along with endless temptations. We can eat whatever we want, whenever we want. We can immerse ourselves in the vast, enticing world of digital media. We can buy goods and services for rapid delivery with our fingertips or voice commands. But living in this 24/7 hyper-reality poses serious risks to our physical and mental states, our connections to others, and even to the world at large.<br />
                    Brain Wash builds from a simple premise: Our brains are being gravely manipulated, resulting in behaviors that leave us more lonely, anxious, depressed, distrustful, illness-prone, and overweight than ever before.<br />
                    Based on the latest science, the book identifies the mental hijacking that undermines each and every one of us, and presents the tools necessary to think more clearly, make better decisions, strengthen bonds with others, and develop healthier habits. Featuring a 10-day bootcamp program, including a meal plan and 40 delicious original recipes, Brain Wash is the key to cultivating a more purposeful and fulfilling life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ultimate Introduction to NLP: How to build a successful life &#8211; Richard Bandler, Alessio Roberti, Owen Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ultimate-introduction-to-nlp-how-to-build-a-successful-life-richard-bandler-alessio-roberti-owen-fitzpatrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neuro Linguistic Programming (NLP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ultimate-introduction-to-nlp-how-to-build-a-successful-life-richard-bandler-alessio-roberti-owen-fitzpatrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Bandler, co-creator of NLP and the man who inspired Paul McKenna to greatness, collaborates with Alessio Roberti and Owen Fitzpatrick to reveal how to unleash your true potential and transform your life. Richard Bandler &#8211; the world-renowned co-creator of NLP who has helped millions around the world change their lives for the better &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultimate-introduction-to-nlp-how-to-build-a-successful-life-richard-bandler-alessio-roberti-owen-fitzpatrick-abridged/">The Ultimate Introduction to NLP: How to build a successful life &#8211; Richard Bandler, Alessio Roberti, Owen Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Richard Bandler, co-creator of NLP and the man who inspired Paul McKenna to greatness, collaborates with Alessio Roberti and Owen Fitzpatrick to reveal how to unleash your true potential and transform your life.    </p>
<p>                              Richard Bandler &#8211; the world-renowned co-creator of NLP who has helped millions around the world change their lives for the better &#8211; has teamed up with Italian NLP Master Trainer Alessio and co-founder of the Irish Institute of NLP Owen, to craft a simple yet engaging story of one man&#8217;s personal change and discovery, to help readers understand the remarkable principles of NLP.    </p>
<p>                              Inspiring and easy-to-read, this fable recreates the experience of being at a workshop with Bandler. Rather than explaining the theories, An Introduction to NLP illustrates the principles and simple techniques that Bandler has developed over the past 35 years in action.    </p>
<p>                              This inspirational book gives you the tools to change your life, overcoming the things that are holding you back: your phobias, depression, habits, psychosomatic illnesses or learning disorders.    </p>
<p>                              Through the simple techniques of NLP, you too can become a strong, happy, successful person and achieve your goals.    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;The must have self-help book!&#8217; Paul McKenna</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultimate-introduction-to-nlp-how-to-build-a-successful-life-richard-bandler-alessio-roberti-owen-fitzpatrick-abridged/">The Ultimate Introduction to NLP: How to build a successful life &#8211; Richard Bandler, Alessio Roberti, Owen Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners : Your Essential Guide to Living the Keto Lifestyle &#8211; Amy Ramos, Rockridge Press, Foreword by Amanda C Hughes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The simple, friendly way to start the ketogenic diet and lifestyle Starting the ketogenic diet can be overwhelming―so much to learn, so many resources to choose from. So why doesn&#8217;t somebody make it easy? We did with this must-have cookbook. The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners makes it easy to start, and stick with, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/">The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners : Your Essential Guide to Living the Keto Lifestyle &#8211; Amy Ramos, Rockridge Press, Foreword by Amanda C Hughes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The simple, friendly way to start the ketogenic diet and lifestyle    </p>
<p>                    Starting the ketogenic diet can be overwhelming―so much to learn, so many resources to choose from. So why doesn&#8217;t somebody make it easy? We did with this must-have cookbook. The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners makes it easy to start, and stick with, the ketogenic diet. You get exactly what you need for surprisingly simple keto: meal plans, shopping lists, support, and lots of keto-licious recipes.    </p>
<p>                    What sets this ketogenic cookbook apart from other keto books for beginners:<br />
                    75 scrumptious recipes―From Bacon-Artichoke Omelets to Pesto Zucchini Noodles, these easy-to-follow recipes can be prepared in 30 minutes or less.14-day meal plan―With breakfast, lunch, dinner, and snack suggestions, this book takes the guesswork out of starting your ketogenic diet.The big picture―An overview explaining the fundamentals of the ketogenic diet and handy charts illustrating nutritional information help you master keto in no time.    </p>
<p>                    Easy meets delicious meets healthy in this ketogenic diet and healthy lifestyle guide and cookbook. Start eating keto today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-complete-ketogenic-diet-for-beginners-your-essential-guide-to-living-the-keto-lifestyle-amy-ramos-rockridge-press-foreword-by-amanda-c-hughes-abridged/">The Complete Ketogenic Diet for Beginners : Your Essential Guide to Living the Keto Lifestyle &#8211; Amy Ramos, Rockridge Press, Foreword by Amanda C Hughes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Breathe : Calm Your Mind. Find Focus. Get Stuff Done &#8211; Michael Townsend Williams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-breathe-calm-your-mind-find-focus-get-stuff-done-michael-townsend-williams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-breathe-calm-your-mind-find-focus-get-stuff-done-michael-townsend-williams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When you get the right balance in life you can do amazing things: create, perform, lead a team, build a great company, raise a family. But so often the scales tip and we feel overwhelmed and stressed. Michael Townsend Williams, an adman turned yoga teacher and mindfulness coach, is an advocate of welldoing leading a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-breathe-calm-your-mind-find-focus-get-stuff-done-michael-townsend-williams-abridged/">Do Breathe : Calm Your Mind. Find Focus. Get Stuff Done &#8211; Michael Townsend Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When you get the right balance in life you can do amazing things: create, perform, lead a team, build a great company, raise a family. But so often the scales tip and we feel overwhelmed and stressed.  Michael Townsend Williams, an adman turned yoga teacher and mindfulness coach, is an advocate of  welldoing    leading a busy and productive life, but not at the expense of our health and wellbeing. And key to this? Our breath.  The crucial link between mind and body, our breath reflects what we re dealing with at any given moment. It tells us when we re out of our depth.  With simple breathing exercises and elements from yoga, meditation and mindfulness, Do Breathe will help you to: -Reduce stress and increase productivity -Improve focus and work flow -Cultivate new good habits and drop the bad -Build courage and resilience.  Why not breathe yourself better?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-breathe-calm-your-mind-find-focus-get-stuff-done-michael-townsend-williams-abridged/">Do Breathe : Calm Your Mind. Find Focus. Get Stuff Done &#8211; Michael Townsend Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Twenty-four Hour Mind : The Role of Sleep and Dreaming in Our Emotional Lives &#8211; Rosalind D. Cartwright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-twenty-four-hour-mind-the-role-of-sleep-and-dreaming-in-our-emotional-lives-rosalind-d-cartwright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Respiratory Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep & Dreams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-twenty-four-hour-mind-the-role-of-sleep-and-dreaming-in-our-emotional-lives-rosalind-d-cartwright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In January of 1999, an otherwise nonviolent man under great stress at work brutally murdered his wife in their backyard. He then went back to bed, awakening only when police entered his home. He claimed to have no memory of the event because, while his body was awake at the time, his mind was not. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-twenty-four-hour-mind-the-role-of-sleep-and-dreaming-in-our-emotional-lives-rosalind-d-cartwright-abridged/">The Twenty-four Hour Mind : The Role of Sleep and Dreaming in Our Emotional Lives &#8211; Rosalind D. Cartwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In January of 1999, an otherwise nonviolent man under great stress at work brutally murdered his wife in their backyard. He then went back to bed, awakening only when police entered his home. He claimed to have no memory of the event because, while his body was awake at the time, his mind was not. He had been sleepwalking.    </p>
<p>                    In The Twenty-four Hour Mind, sleep scientist Rosalind Cartwright brings together decades of research into the bizarre sleep disorders known as parasomnias to propose a new theory of how the human mind works consistently throughout waking and sleeping hours. Thanks to increasingly sophisticated EEG and brain imaging technologies, we now know that our minds do not simply &#8220;turn off&#8221; during sleep. Rather, they continue to be active, and research has indicated that one of the primary<br />
                    purposes of sleep is to aid in regulating emotions and processing experiences that occur during preceding waking hours. As such, when sleep is neurologically or genetically impaired or just too short, the processes that good sleep facilitates-those that usually have a positive effect on our mood and<br />
                    performance-can short circuit, with negative results that occasionally reach tragic proportions. Examining the interactions between conscious and unconscious forms of thinking as they proceed throughout the cycles of sleeping, dreaming, and waking, Cartwright demystifies the inner workings of the human mind that trigger sleep problems, how researchers are working to control them, and how they can apply what they learn to further our understanding of the brain. Along the way, she provides a<br />
                    lively account of the history of sleep research and the birth of sleep medicine that will initiate readers into this fascinating field of inquiry and the far-reaching implications it will have on the future of neuroscience. The Twenty-four Hour Mind offers a unique look at a relatively new area of study<br />
                    that will be of interest to those with and without sleep problems, as well as anyone captivated by the mysteries of the brain-and what sleep continues to teach us about the waking mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-twenty-four-hour-mind-the-role-of-sleep-and-dreaming-in-our-emotional-lives-rosalind-d-cartwright-abridged/">The Twenty-four Hour Mind : The Role of Sleep and Dreaming in Our Emotional Lives &#8211; Rosalind D. Cartwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers -Revised Edition &#8211; M. Sapolsky, M. Sapolsky, Robert, Robert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmetics, Hair & Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now in a third edition, Robert M. Sapolsky&#8217;s acclaimed and successful Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers features new chapters on how stress affects sleep and addiction, as well as new insights into anxiety and personality disorder and the impact of spirituality on managing stress. As Sapolsky explains, most of us do not lie awake at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/">Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers -Revised Edition &#8211; M. Sapolsky, M. Sapolsky, Robert, Robert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now in a third edition, Robert M. Sapolsky&#8217;s acclaimed and successful Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers features new chapters on how stress affects sleep and addiction, as well as new insights into anxiety and personality disorder and the impact of spirituality on managing stress. As Sapolsky explains, most of us do not lie awake at night worrying about whether we have leprosy or malaria. Instead, the diseases we fear &#8211; and the ones that plague us now &#8211; are illnesses brought on by the slow accumulation of damage, such as heart disease and cancer. When we worry or experience stress, our body turns on the same physiological responses that an animal&#8217;s does, but we do not resolve conflict in the same way &#8211; through fighting or fleeing. Over time, this activation of a stress response makes us literally sick. Combining cutting-edge research with a healthy dose of good humour and practical advice, Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers explains how prolonged stress causes or intensifies a range of physical and mental afflictions, including depression, ulcers, colitis, heart disease, and more. It also provides essential guidance to controlling our stress responses.<br />
                    This new edition promises to be the most comprehensive and engaging one yet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/">Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers -Revised Edition &#8211; M. Sapolsky, M. Sapolsky, Robert, Robert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oncology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases. Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases.      </p>
<p>                    Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to identify the strategies and dosages for using food to transform your resilience and health in Eat to Beat Disease.     </p>
<p>                    We have radically underestimated our body&#8217;s power to transform and restore our health. Pioneering physician scientist, Dr. William Li, empowers readers by showing them the evidence behind over 200 health-boosting foods that can starve cancer, reduce your risk of dementia, and beat dozens of avoidable diseases. Eat to Beat Disease isn&#8217;t about what foods to avoid, but rather is a life-changing guide to the hundreds of healing foods to add to your meals that support the body&#8217;s defense systems, including: PlumsCinnamonJasmine teaRed wine and beerBlack BeansSan Marzano tomatoesOlive oilPacific oystersCheeses like Jarlsberg, Camembert and cheddarSourdough bread<br />
                    The book&#8217;s plan shows you how to integrate the foods you already love into any diet or health plan to activate your body&#8217;s health defense systems-Angiogenesis, Regeneration, Microbiome, DNA Protection, and Immunity-to fight cancer, diabetes, cardiovascular, neurodegenerative autoimmune diseases, and other debilitating conditions.     </p>
<p>                    Both informative and practical, Eat to Beat Disease explains the science of healing and prevention, the strategies for using food to actively transform health, and points the science of wellbeing and disease prevention in an exhilarating new direction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beat Sugar Addiction Now! : The Cutting-Edge Program That Cures Your Type of Sugar Addiction and Puts You on the Road to Feeling Great &#8211; and Losing Weight! &#8211; Jacob Teitelbaum, Chrystle Fiedler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Normal0MicrosoftInternetExplorer4 The No-Fail Plan to Beating Sugar Addiction! With one-third of our calories coming from sugar and white flour added to processed foods, sugar addiction is a rapidly growing epidemic. However, unlike other addictions, going &#8220;cold turkey&#8221; won&#8217;t fix it. In this groundbreaking book, nationally recognized physician Dr. Jacob Teitelbaum uncovers four types of sugar [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/">Beat Sugar Addiction Now! : The Cutting-Edge Program That Cures Your Type of Sugar Addiction and Puts You on the Road to Feeling Great &#8211; and Losing Weight! &#8211; Jacob Teitelbaum, Chrystle Fiedler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Normal0MicrosoftInternetExplorer4    </p>
<p>                    The No-Fail Plan to Beating Sugar Addiction!    </p>
<p>                    With one-third of our calories coming from sugar and white flour added to processed foods, sugar addiction is a rapidly growing epidemic. However, unlike other addictions, going &#8220;cold turkey&#8221; won&#8217;t fix it. In this groundbreaking book, nationally recognized physician Dr. Jacob Teitelbaum uncovers four types of sugar addiction and gives a step-by-step plan for resolving their underlying causes, breaking sugar cravings forever, and achieving dramatically improved health and energy levels&#8211;while also making it easier to lose weight!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beat-sugar-addiction-now-the-cutting-edge-program-that-cures-your-type-of-sugar-addiction-and-puts-you-on-the-road-to-feeling-great-and-losing-weight-jacob-teitelbaum-chrystle-fiedler-abridg/">Beat Sugar Addiction Now! : The Cutting-Edge Program That Cures Your Type of Sugar Addiction and Puts You on the Road to Feeling Great &#8211; and Losing Weight! &#8211; Jacob Teitelbaum, Chrystle Fiedler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Revolutionise your life one day at a time with this empowering handbook designed for men and women which provides simple strategies for each element of your day. Marcus Aubrey, author of the book is CEO of Onnit, a human performance company that he has built into one of the fastest growing companies in the world. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/">Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Revolutionise your life one day at a time with this empowering handbook designed for men and women which provides simple strategies for each element of your day. Marcus Aubrey, author of the book is CEO of Onnit, a human performance company that he has built into one of the fastest growing companies in the world.    </p>
<p>                              How can we get the most out of our body and mind on a daily basis? Want to change your life for the better?    </p>
<p>                              Aubrey Marcus answers these questions in this handbook that guides the reader to optimise each moment of the day. With small, actionable changes implemented throughout the course of one day we can feel better, perform more efficiently and live happier. And these habits turn into weekly routines, ultimately becoming part of a lifelong healthy choice.    </p>
<p>                              From workouts and diet to inbox triage, mindfulness, shower temperature and sex this groundbreaking manual provides strategies for each element of your day. Drawing on the latest studies and traditional practices from around the world, this book delivers cutting-edge life hacks, nutritional expertise, brain upgrades and fitness regimes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/">Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clean : The Revolutionary Program to Restore the Body&#8217;s Natural Ability to Heal Itself &#8211; Alejandro Junger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Life-Changing Medical Breakthrough Clean is an M.D.&#8217;s program designed to be easily incorporated into our busy schedule while providing all the practical tools necessary to support and rejuvenate our bodies. The effect is transformative: nagging health problems will suddenly disappear, extra weight will drop away, and for the first time in our lives, we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/">Clean : The Revolutionary Program to Restore the Body&#8217;s Natural Ability to Heal Itself &#8211; Alejandro Junger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Life-Changing Medical Breakthrough Clean is an M.D.&#8217;s program designed to be easily incorporated into our busy schedule while providing all the practical tools necessary to support and rejuvenate our bodies. The effect is transformative: nagging health problems will suddenly disappear, extra weight will drop away, and for the first time in our lives, we will experience what it truly means to feel healthy.  Expanded Edition Includes: New Introduction * New Recipes * How to Become Clean for Life</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clean-the-revolutionary-program-to-restore-the-bodys-natural-ability-to-heal-itself-alejandro-junger-abridged/">Clean : The Revolutionary Program to Restore the Body&#8217;s Natural Ability to Heal Itself &#8211; Alejandro Junger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What to Eat When : A Strategic Plan to Improve Your Health and Life Through Food &#8211; Michael F. Roizen, Michael Crupain, With Ted Spiker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-to-eat-when-a-strategic-plan-to-improve-your-health-and-life-through-food-michael-f-roizen-michael-crupain-with-ted-spiker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celebrity Chefs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-to-eat-when-a-strategic-plan-to-improve-your-health-and-life-through-food-michael-f-roizen-michael-crupain-with-ted-spiker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now in paperback, NY Times best-selling author Dr. Michael Roizen&#8217;s groundbreaking book reveals how the food choices you make each day&#8211;and when you make them&#8211;can affect your health, your energy, your sex life, your waistline, your attitude, and how you age. What if eating two cups of blueberries a day could prevent cancer? If drinking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-eat-when-a-strategic-plan-to-improve-your-health-and-life-through-food-michael-f-roizen-michael-crupain-with-ted-spiker-abridged/">What to Eat When : A Strategic Plan to Improve Your Health and Life Through Food &#8211; Michael F. Roizen, Michael Crupain, With Ted Spiker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now in paperback, NY Times best-selling author Dr. Michael Roizen&#8217;s groundbreaking book reveals how the food choices you make each day&#8211;and when you make them&#8211;can affect your health, your energy, your sex life, your waistline, your attitude, and how you age.    </p>
<p>                     What if eating two cups of blueberries a day could prevent cancer? If drinking a kale-infused smoothie could counteract missing an hour&#8217;s worth of sleep? When is the right time of day to eat that chocolate chip cookies? And would you actually drink that glass of water if it meant skipping the gym? This revolutionary guide&#8211;Dr. Mehmet Oz&#8217;s 2019 Diet of the Year&#8211;reveals how to use food to enhance our personal and professional lives, and increase our longevity to boot.     </p>
<p>                     What to Eat When is not a diet book. Instead, acclaimed Cleveland Clinic internist Michael Roizen and certified physician Michael Crupain offer reader the choices that will benefit them the most&#8211;whether it&#8217;s meals to help them look younger or snacks that prevent diseases&#8211;based on the science that governs them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-eat-when-a-strategic-plan-to-improve-your-health-and-life-through-food-michael-f-roizen-michael-crupain-with-ted-spiker-abridged/">What to Eat When : A Strategic Plan to Improve Your Health and Life Through Food &#8211; Michael F. Roizen, Michael Crupain, With Ted Spiker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal & Public Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it. Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it.    </p>
<p>                    Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer understanding of how we live and how we die. While it is one of the largest scientific projects ever attempted&#8211;as breathtaking as the first moon landing or the Human Genome Project&#8211;the questions it answers are meaningful for every one of us: What are the world&#8217;s health problems? Who do they hurt? How much? Where? Why?    </p>
<p>                    Murray argues that the ideal existence isn&#8217;t simply the longest but the one lived well and with the least illness. Until we can accurately measure how people live and die, we cannot understand what makes us sick or do much to improve it. Challenging the accepted wisdom of the WHO and the UN, the charismatic and controversial health maverick has made enemies&#8211;and some influential friends, including Bill Gates who gave Murray a $100 million grant.    </p>
<p>                    In Epic Measures, journalist Jeremy N. Smith offers an intimate look at Murray and his groundbreaking work. From ranking countries&#8217; healthcare systems (the U.S. is 37th) to unearthing the shocking reality that world governments are funding developing countries at only 30% of the potential maximum efficiency when it comes to health, Epic Measures introduces a visionary leader whose unwavering determination to improve global health standards has already changed the way the world addresses issues of health and wellness, sets policy, and distributes funding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent wake-up call about the future of emerging viruses and a gripping account of the doctors and scientists fighting to protect us, told through the story of the deadly 2013-2014 Ebola epidemic &#8220;Crisis in the Red Zone reads like a thriller. That the story it tells is all true [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/">Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent wake-up call about the future of emerging viruses and a gripping account of the doctors and scientists fighting to protect us, told through the story of the deadly 2013-2014 Ebola epidemic &#8220;Crisis in the Red Zone reads like a thriller. That the story it tells is all true makes it all more terrifying.&#8221;&#8211;Elizabeth Kolbert, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Sixth Extinction From the #1 bestselling author of The Hot Zone, now a National Geographic original miniseries . . . This time, Ebola started with a two-year-old child who likely had contact with a wild creature and whose entire family quickly fell ill and died. The ensuing global drama activated health professionals in North America, Europe, and Africa in a desperate race against time to contain the viral wildfire. By the end&#8211;as the virus mutated into its deadliest form, and spread farther and faster than ever before&#8211;30,000 people would be infected, and the dead would be spread across eight countries on three continents. In this taut and suspenseful medical drama, Richard Preston deeply chronicles the pandemic, in which we saw for the first time the specter of Ebola jumping continents, crossing the Atlantic, and infecting people in America. Rich in characters and conflict&#8211;physical, emotional, and ethical&#8211;Crisis in the Red Zone is an immersion in one of the great public health calamities of our time. Preston writes of doctors and nurses in the field putting their own lives on the line, of government bureaucrats and NGO administrators moving, often fitfully, to try to contain the outbreak, and of pharmaceutical companies racing to develop drugs to combat the virus. He also explores the charged ethical dilemma over who should and did receive the rare doses of an experimental treatment when they became available at the peak of the disaster. Crisis in the Red Zone makes clear that the outbreak of 2013-2014 is a harbinger of further, more severe outbreaks, and of emerging viruses heretofore unimagined&#8211;in any country, on any continent. In our ever more interconnected world, with roads and towns cut deep into the jungles of equatorial Africa, viruses both familiar and undiscovered are being unleashed into more densely populated areas than ever before. The more we discover about the virosphere, the more we realize its deadly potential. Crisis in the Red Zone is an exquisitely timely book, a stark warning of viral outbreaks to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/">Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Equipment & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nursing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Telemedicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy & Therapeutics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they indicate further (and more invasive) tests, most of which will probably prove unnecessary (much like physicals themselves). And your bill will be astronomical.In  The Patient Will See You Now , Eric Topol, one of the nation&#8217;s top physicians, shows why medicine does not have to be that way. Instead, you could use your smartphone to get rapid test results from one drop of blood, monitor your vital signs both day and night, and use an artificially intelligent algorithm to receive a diagnosis without having to see a doctor, all at a small fraction of the cost imposed by our modern healthcare system. The change is powered by what Topol calls medicine&#8217;s &#8220;Gutenberg moment.&#8221; Much as the printing press took learning out of the hands of a priestly class, the mobile internet is doing the same for medicine, giving us unprecedented control over our healthcare. With smartphones in hand, we are no longer beholden to an impersonal and paternalistic system in which &#8220;doctor knows best.&#8221; Medicine has been digitized, Topol argues now it will be democratized. Computers will replace physicians for many diagnostic tasks, citizen science will give rise to citizen medicine, and enormous data sets will give us new means to attack conditions that have long been incurable. Massive, open, online medicine, where diagnostics are done by Facebook-like comparisons of medical profiles, will enable real-time, real-world research on massive populations. There&#8217;s no doubt the path forward will be complicated: the medical establishment will resist these changes, and digitized medicine inevitably raises serious issues surrounding privacy. Nevertheless, the result,better, cheaper, and more human health care,will be worth it.Provocative and engrossing,  The Patient Will See You Now  is essential reading for anyone who thinks they deserve better health care. That is, for all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report, Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report,  Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by Medicare when offered virtually at home.     </p>
<p>                     Dean Ornish, M.D., has directed revolutionary research proving, for the first time, that lifestyle changes can often reverse&#8211;undo!&#8211;the progression of many of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level.     </p>
<p>                     Medicare and many insurance companies now cover Dr. Ornish&#8217;s lifestyle medicine program for reversing chronic disease because it consistently achieves bigger changes in lifestyle, better clinical outcomes, larger cost savings, and greater adherence than have ever been reported&#8211;based on forty years of research published in the leading peer-reviewed medical and scientific journals.     </p>
<p>                     Now, in this landmark book, he and Anne Ornish present a simple yet powerful new unifying theory explaining why these same lifestyle changes can reverse so many different chronic diseases and how quickly these benefits occur. They describe what it is, why it works, and how you can do it:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Eat well a whole foods, plant-based diet naturally low in fat and sugar and high in flavor. The &#8220;Ornish diet&#8221; has been rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report for eleven years since 2011.<br />
                     &#8211; Move more moderate exercise such as walking<br />
                     &#8211; Stress less including meditation and gentle yoga practices<br />
                     &#8211; Love more how love and intimacy transform loneliness into healing     </p>
<p>                    With seventy recipes, easy-to-follow meal plans, tips for stocking your kitchen and eating out, recommended exercises, stress-reduction advice, and inspiring patient stories of life-transforming benefits&#8211;for example, several people improved so much after only nine weeks they were able to avoid a heart transplant&#8211;Undo It! empowers readers with new hope and new choices.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Undo It!     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Ornishes&#8217; work is elegant and simple and deserving of a Nobel Prize, since it can change the world!&#8221;&#8211;Richard Carmona, M.D., MPH, FACS, seventeenth Surgeon General of the United States     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;If you want to see what medicine will be like ten years from now, read this book today.&#8221;&#8211;Rita F. Redberg, M.D., editor in chief, JAMA Internal Medicine     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This is one of the most important books on health ever written.&#8221;&#8211;John Mackey, CEO, Whole Foods Market</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiest Baby on the Block; Fully Revised and Updated Second Edition : The New Way to Calm Crying and Help Your Newborn Baby Sleep Longer &#8211; Harvey Karp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Never again will you have to stand by helplessly while your little baby cries and cries. There is a way to calm most crying babies . . . usually in minutes! Thousands of parents, from regular moms and dads to Hollywood superstars, have come to baby expert Dr. Harvey Karp to learn his remarkable techniques [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/">The Happiest Baby on the Block; Fully Revised and Updated Second Edition : The New Way to Calm Crying and Help Your Newborn Baby Sleep Longer &#8211; Harvey Karp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Never again will you have to stand by helplessly while your little baby cries and cries. There is a way to calm most crying babies . . . usually in minutes!      </p>
<p>                     Thousands of parents, from regular moms and dads to Hollywood superstars, have come to baby expert Dr. Harvey Karp to learn his remarkable techniques for soothing babies and increasing sleep. Now his landmark book&#8211;fully revised and updated with the latest insights into infant sleep, bedsharing, breastfeeding, swaddling, and SIDS risk&#8211;can teach you too! Dr. Karp&#8217;s highly successful method is based on four revolutionary concepts:     </p>
<p>                     1. The Fourth Trimester: Why babies still yearn for a womblike atmosphere . . . even after birth<br />
                     2. The Calming Reflex: An &#8220;off switch&#8221; all babies are born with<br />
                     3. The 5 S&#8217;s: Five easy steps to turn on your baby&#8217;s amazing calming reflex<br />
                     4. The Cuddle Cure:  How to combine the 5 S&#8217;s to calm even colicky babies     </p>
<p>                     With Dr. Karp&#8217;s sensible advice, parents and grandparents, nurses and nannies, will be able to transform even the fussiest infant into the happiest baby on the block!     </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Happiest Baby on the Block     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Dr. Karp&#8217;s book is fascinating and will guide new parents for years to come.&#8221;&#8211;Julius Richmond, M.D., Harvard Medical School, former Surgeon General of the United States     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Happiest Baby on the Block is fun and convincing. I highly recommend it.&#8221;&#8211;Elisabeth Bing, co-founder of Lamaze International     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Will fascinate anyone who wants to know how babies experience the world, and wants to answer their cries lovingly and effectively.&#8221;&#8211;The San Diego Union-Tribune</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiest-baby-on-the-block-fully-revised-and-updated-second-edition-the-new-way-to-calm-crying-and-help-your-newborn-baby-sleep-longer-harvey-karp-abridged/">The Happiest Baby on the Block; Fully Revised and Updated Second Edition : The New Way to Calm Crying and Help Your Newborn Baby Sleep Longer &#8211; Harvey Karp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dr. Gundry is a true trailblazer, always at the forefront of scientific knowledge. The Plant Paradox shows the world what pioneer thinking is about and is a must-read book for anyone interested in being as healthy as nature has designed them to be.&#8221; -Alejandro Junger MD, New York Times bestselling author of Clean, Clean Gut [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dr. Gundry is a true trailblazer, always at the forefront of scientific knowledge. The Plant Paradox shows the world what pioneer thinking is about and is a must-read book for anyone interested in being as healthy as nature has designed them to be.&#8221; -Alejandro Junger MD, New York Times bestselling author of Clean, Clean Gut and Clean Eats  &#8220;The Plant Paradox elegantly explains how plants defend themselves from being consumed by humans, and how eating the wrong ones at the wrong times immeasurably hurts our health. An eye-opening read.&#8221; -Mehmet Oz, MD, Professor of Surgery, New York Presbyterian/Columbia University  Most of us have heard of gluten-a protein found in wheat that causes widespread inflammation in the body. Americans spend billions of dollars on gluten-free diets in an effort to protect their health. But what if we&#8217;ve been missing the root of the problem? In The Plant Paradox, renowned cardiologist Dr. Steven Gundry reveals that gluten is just one variety of a common, and highly toxic, plant-based protein called lectin.<br />
                    Lectins are found not only in grains like wheat but also in the &#8220;gluten-free&#8221; foods most of us commonly regard as healthy, including many fruits, vegetables, nuts, beans, and conventional dairy products. These proteins, which are found in the seeds, grains, skins, rinds, and leaves of plants, are designed by nature to protect them from predators (including humans). Once ingested, they incite a kind of chemical warfare in our bodies, causing inflammatory reactions that can lead to weight gain and serious health conditions.  At his waitlist-only clinics in California, Dr. Gundry has successfully treated tens of thousands of patients suffering from autoimmune disorders, diabetes, leaky gut syndrome, heart disease, and neurodegenerative diseases with a protocol that detoxes the cells, repairs the gut, and nourishes the body. Now, in The Plant Paradox, he shares this clinically proven program with readers around the world.  The simple (and daunting) fact is, lectins are everywhere. Thankfully, Dr. Gundry offers simple hacks we easily can employ to avoid them, including: * Peel your veggies.<br />
                    Most of the lectins are contained in the skin and seeds of plants; simply peeling and de-seeding vegetables (like tomatoes and peppers) reduces their lectin content.* Shop for fruit in season. Fruit contain fewer lectins when ripe, so eating apples, berries, and other lectin-containing fruits at the peak of ripeness helps minimize your lectin consumption.* Swap your brown rice for white. Whole grains and seeds with hard outer coatings are designed by nature to cause digestive distress-and are full of lectins. With a full list of lectin-containing foods and simple substitutes for each, a step-by-step detox and eating plan, and delicious lectin-free recipes, The Plant Paradox illuminates the hidden dangers lurking in your salad bowl-and shows you how to eat whole foods in a whole new way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8220;A valuable read that will help you understand what it takes to stop COVID-19. &#8230; A super interesting look at the science of immunity.&#8221; -Bill Gates, Gates Notes Summer Reading List The Pulitzer Prize-winning New York Times journalist &#8220;explicates for the lay reader the intricate biology of our immune system&#8221; (Jerome Groopman, MD, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/">Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable read that will help you understand what it takes to stop COVID-19. &#8230; A super interesting look at the science of immunity.&#8221; -Bill Gates, Gates Notes Summer Reading List    </p>
<p>                    The Pulitzer Prize-winning New York Times journalist &#8220;explicates for the lay reader the intricate biology of our immune system&#8221; (Jerome Groopman, MD, New York Review of Books)    </p>
<p>                    From New York Times science journalist Matt Richtel, An Elegant Defense is an acclaimed and definitive exploration of the immune system and the secrets of health. Interweaving cutting-edge science with the intimate stories of four individual patients, this epic, first-of-its-kind book &#8220;give[s] lay readers a means of understanding what&#8217;s known so far about the intricate biology of our immune systems&#8221; (The Week).    </p>
<p>                    The immune system is our body&#8217;s essential defense network, a guardian vigilantly fighting illness, healing wounds, maintaining order and balance, and keeping us alive. It has been honed by evolution over millennia to face an almost infinite array of threats. For all its astonishing complexity, however, the immune system can be easily compromised by fatigue, stress, toxins, advanced age, and poor nutrition-hallmarks of modern life-and even by excessive hygiene. Paradoxically, it is a fragile wonder weapon that can turn on our own bodies with startling results, leading today to epidemic levels of autoimmune disorders.    </p>
<p>                    An Elegant Defense effortlessly guides readers on a scientific detective tale winding from the Black Plague to twentieth-century breakthroughs in vaccination and antibiotics, to today&#8217;s laboratories that are revolutionizing immunology-perhaps the most extraordinary and consequential medical story of our time. Drawing on extensive new interviews with dozens of world-renowned scientists, Richtel has produced a landmark book, equally an investigation into the deepest riddles of survival and a profoundly human tale that is movingly brought to life through the eyes of his four main characters, each of whom illuminates an essential facet of our &#8220;elegant defense.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/">Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cribsheet : A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting, from Birth to Preschool &#8211; Emily Oster (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Emily Oster is the non-judgemental girlfriend holding our hand and guiding us through pregnancy and motherhood. She has done the work to get us the hard facts in a soft, understandable way&#8217; Amy Schumer Parenting is full of decisions, nearly all of which can be agonized over. There is an abundance of often-conflicting advice hurled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/">Cribsheet : A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting, from Birth to Preschool &#8211; Emily Oster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Emily Oster is the non-judgemental girlfriend holding our hand and guiding us through pregnancy and motherhood. She has done the work to get us the hard facts in a soft, understandable way&#8217; Amy Schumer    </p>
<p>                    Parenting is full of decisions, nearly all of which can be agonized over. There is an abundance of often-conflicting advice hurled at you from doctors, family, friends, and strangers on the internet. But the benefits of these choices can be overstated, and the trade-offs can be profound. How do you make your own best decision?     </p>
<p>                     Armed with the data, Oster finds that the conventional wisdom doesn&#8217;t always hold up. She debunks myths and offers non-judgemental ways to consider our options in light of the facts. Cribsheet is a thinking parent&#8217;s guide that empowers us to make better, less fraught decisions &#8211; and stay sane in the years before preschool.    </p>
<p>                    *Now you can navigate the primary school years with Emily Oster too, in her new book The Family Firm, out now*</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cribsheet-a-data-driven-guide-to-better-more-relaxed-parenting-from-birth-to-preschool-emily-oster-abridged/">Cribsheet : A Data-Driven Guide to Better, More Relaxed Parenting, from Birth to Preschool &#8211; Emily Oster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon : The New Science and Stories of the Brain &#8211; Dr Rahul Jandial (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosurgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rehabilitation: Brain & Spinal Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER *As heard on Chris Evans&#8217; Virgin Radio* &#8216;You&#8217;re amazing I could talk to you (Rahul) all day&#8217; Chris Evans &#8216;This is a gripping new book&#8217; The Times World-leading neuroscientist and neurosurgeon Dr Rahul Jandial draws on his years of work with patients suffering from the most extreme cases of brain damage, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/">Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon : The New Science and Stories of the Brain &#8211; Dr Rahul Jandial (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    *As heard on Chris Evans&#8217; Virgin Radio*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You&#8217;re amazing I could talk to you (Rahul) all day&#8217; Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is a gripping new book&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    World-leading neuroscientist and neurosurgeon Dr Rahul Jandial draws on his years of work with patients suffering from the most extreme cases of brain damage, disorders and illnesses to reveal what they can tell us about the science of the mind.    </p>
<p>                    From a languages teacher who has to choose whether to lose her ability to speak Spanish or English after brain surgery, to a former TV exec, now homeless, who discovers that his life-altering despondency is the result of a tumour, to a fainting teen who learns that deep breathing can mean the difference between life or death, these stories uncover the secret workings of the brain.    </p>
<p>                    Blending cutting-edge research and beautiful storytelling, Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon is a vital resource on the best ways to boost your memory, control stress and emotions, minimize pain, unleash your creativity, raise smart kids and reduce the risk of Alzheimer&#8217;s. This is a deeply practical and readable book, which will take you on an expedition through the anatomy of the most fascinating &#8211; and mysterious &#8211; of organs.    </p>
<p>                    Rahul&#8217;s new book Life on a Knife&#8217;s Edge is out now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/">Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon : The New Science and Stories of the Brain &#8211; Dr Rahul Jandial (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Take a break and read Rest: you&#8217;ll make smarter decisions, have better relationships, and be happier and more creative&#8221; James Wallman, author of Stuffocation Do you regularly find yourself too tired after a long day at your desk to do anything other than binge TV, or scroll mindlessly through social media? Do you go on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/">Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Take a break and read Rest: you&#8217;ll make smarter decisions, have better relationships, and be happier and more creative&#8221; James Wallman, author of Stuffocation    </p>
<p>                     Do you regularly find yourself too tired after a long day at your desk to do anything other than binge TV, or scroll mindlessly through social media? Do you go on holiday and still compulsively check your email? Do you work through your lunch-break, often not even leaving your desk to get some fresh air?    </p>
<p>                     For most of us, overwork is the new norm, and we never truly take the time to rest and recharge. But as Silicon Valley consultant Alex Soojung-Kim Pang explains in this groundbreaking book, rest needs to be taken seriously and to be done properly, because when you rest better you work better.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on emerging neuroscience, Rest is packed with easy practical tips for incorporating rest into our everyday:    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Go for a long walk to stimulate and sustain creativity<br />
                     &#8211; Schedule deliberate active rest periods into your diary to try out new activities like painting or learning a language<br />
                     &#8211; Stop working on a task when you know what the next step will be, this will make it easier to get started the next day<br />
                    &#8211; Establish clear boundaries between work and rest time<br />
                     &#8211; Take a nap during the day to increase alertness, boost your concentration and decrease fatigue<br />
                     &#8211; Get good quality sleep at night to stay healthy, solidify memories and generate new ideas    </p>
<p>                     When you rest better you&#8217;ll find that it won&#8217;t just be your work which improves &#8211; you&#8217;ll have more time for hobbies, stronger relationships and you&#8217;ll sleep better, too.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;An incredibly timely read for my own increasingly rest-starved life. This might be the book to finally persuade us that downtime isn&#8217;t in conflict with good work; rather, it&#8217;s an essential ingredient of it&#8221; Oliver Burkeman, Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/">Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book. Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book.     </p>
<p>                    Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. Why suffer from disease and ill health when the right food is proven to keep you healthy, and without the side effects of drugs? We can avoid heart disease, cancer and our other biggest killers if we use food as medicine, and the How Not To Die Cookbook offers a sustainable and delicious guide to preparing and eating the foods that will prevent and reverse fatal diseases.    </p>
<p>                    Featuring over 100 easy-to-follow, beautifully photographed plant-based recipes, with plenty of recipes suitable for vegetarians and vegans, the How Not To Die Cookbook merges cutting-edge science with everyday ingredients from the supermarket to help you and your family eat your way to better health and a longer life.    </p>
<p>                    All recipes in this cookbook have been fully anglicized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whole : Rethinking the Science of Nutrition &#8211; T. Colin Campbell, Howard Jacobson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller What happens when you eat an apple? The answer is vastly more complex than you imagine. Every apple contains thousands of antioxidants whose names, beyond a few like vitamin C, are unfamiliar to us, and each of these powerful chemicals has the potential to play an important role in supporting our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/">Whole : Rethinking the Science of Nutrition &#8211; T. Colin Campbell, Howard Jacobson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller  What happens when you eat an apple? The answer is vastly more complex than you imagine.  Every apple contains thousands of antioxidants whose names, beyond a few like vitamin C, are unfamiliar to us, and each of these powerful chemicals has the potential to play an important role in supporting our health. They impact thousands upon thousands of metabolic reactions inside the human body. But calculating the specific influence of each of these chemicals isn&#8217;t nearly sufficient to explain the effect of the apple as a whole. Because almost every chemical can affect every other chemical, there is an almost infinite number of possible biological consequences.  And that&#8217;s just from an apple.  Nutritional science, long stuck in a reductionist mindset, is at the cusp of a revolution. The traditional &#8220;gold standard&#8221; of nutrition research has been to study one chemical at a time in an attempt to determine its particular impact on the human body.<br />
                    These sorts of studies are helpful to food companies trying to prove there is a chemical in milk or pre-packaged dinners that is &#8220;good&#8221; for us, but they provide little insight into the complexity of what actually happens in our bodies or how those chemicals contribute to our health.  In The China Study, T. Colin Campbell (alongside his son, Thomas M. Campbell) revolutionized the way we think about our food with the evidence that a whole food, plant-based diet is the healthiest way to eat. Now, in Whole, he explains the science behind that evidence, the ways our current scientific paradigm ignores the fascinating complexity of the human body, and why, if we have such overwhelming evidence that everything we think we know about nutrition is wrong, our eating habits haven&#8217;t changed.  Whole is an eye-opening, paradigm-changing journey through cutting-edge thinking on nutrition, a scientific tour de force with powerful implications for our health and for our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whole-rethinking-the-science-of-nutrition-t-colin-campbell-howard-jacobson-abridged/">Whole : Rethinking the Science of Nutrition &#8211; T. Colin Campbell, Howard Jacobson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pollution & Threats To The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When the U.S. Public Health Service endorsed water fluoridation in 1950, there was little evidence of its safety. Now, six decades later and after most countries have rejected the practice, more than 70 percent of Americans, as well as 200 million people worldwide, are drinking fluoridated water. The Center for Disease Control and the American [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/">The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When the U.S. Public Health Service endorsed water fluoridation in 1950, there was little evidence of its safety. Now, six decades later and after most countries have rejected the practice, more than 70 percent of Americans, as well as 200 million people worldwide, are drinking fluoridated water. The Center for Disease Control and the American Dental Association continue to promote it&#8211;and even mandatory statewide water fluoridation&#8211;despite increasing evidence that it is not only unnecessary, but potentially hazardous to human health.    </p>
<p>                    In this timely and important book, Dr. Paul Connett, Dr. James Beck, and Dr. H. Spedding Micklem take a new look at the science behind water fluoridation and argue that just because the dental and medical establishments endorse a public health measure doesn&#8217;t mean it&#8217;s safe. In the case of water fluoridation, the chemicals that go into the drinking water that more than 180 million people drink each day are not even pharmaceutical grade, but rather a hazardous waste product of the phosphate fertilizer industry. It is illegal to dump this waste into the sea or local surface water, and yet it is allowed in our drinking water. To make matters worse, this program receives no oversight from the Food and Drug Administration, and the Environmental Protection Agency takes no responsibility for the practice. And from an ethical standpoint, say the authors, water fluoridation is a bad medical practice: individuals are being forced to take medication without their informed consent, there is no control over the dose, and no monitoring of possible side effects.    </p>
<p>                    At once painstakingly documented and also highly readable, The Case Against Fluoride brings new research to light, including links between fluoride and harm to the brain, bones, and endocrine system, and argues that the evidence that fluoridation reduces tooth decay is surprisingly weak.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/">The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nine Pints : A Journey Through the Mysterious, Miraculous World of Blood &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most humans contain between nine and twelve pints of blood. Here Rose George, who probably contains nine pints, tells nine different stories about the liquid that sustains us, discovering what it reveals about who we are. In Nepal, she meets girls challenging the taboos surrounding menstruation; in the Canadian prairies, she visits a controversial plasma [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/">Nine Pints : A Journey Through the Mysterious, Miraculous World of Blood &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most humans contain between nine and twelve pints of blood. Here Rose George, who probably contains nine pints, tells nine different stories about the liquid that sustains us, discovering what it reveals about who we are. In Nepal, she meets girls challenging the taboos surrounding menstruation; in the Canadian prairies, she visits a controversial plasma clinic; in Wales she gets a tour of the UK&#8217;s only leech farm to learn about the vital role the creatures still play in modern surgery; and in a London hospital she accompanies a medical team revolutionising the way we treat trauma.    </p>
<p>                     Nine Pints reveals the richness and wonder of the potent red fluid that courses around our bodies, unseen but miraculous.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nine-pints-a-journey-through-the-mysterious-miraculous-world-of-blood-rose-george-abridged/">Nine Pints : A Journey Through the Mysterious, Miraculous World of Blood &#8211; Rose George (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Can&#8217;t Sleep : Generation X Women&#8217;s New Midlife Crisis &#8211; Ada Calhoun (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-cant-sleep-generation-x-womens-new-midlife-crisis-ada-calhoun-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-cant-sleep-generation-x-womens-new-midlife-crisis-ada-calhoun-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Ada Calhoun found herself in the throes of a midlife crisis, she thought that she had no right to complain. She was married with children and a good career. So why did she feel miserable? And why did it seem that the women around her were miserable, too? Calhoun decided to find some answers. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-cant-sleep-generation-x-womens-new-midlife-crisis-ada-calhoun-abridged/">Why We Can&#8217;t Sleep : Generation X Women&#8217;s New Midlife Crisis &#8211; Ada Calhoun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Ada Calhoun found herself in the throes of a midlife crisis, she thought that she had no right to complain. She was married with children and a good career. So why did she feel miserable? And why did it seem that the women around her were miserable, too?    </p>
<p>                    Calhoun decided to find some answers. She looked into housing costs, HR trends, credit card debt averages and divorce data. At every turn, she saw a pattern: sandwiched between the Boomers and the Millennials, Gen X women were facing new problems as they entered middle age, problems that were largely overlooked. Speaking with women across America about their experiences as the generation raised to &#8216;have it all,&#8217; Calhoun found that most were exhausted, terrified about money, under-employed, and overwhelmed. Instead of being heard, they were told instead to lean in, take &#8216;me-time&#8217;, or make a chore chart to get their lives and homes in order.    </p>
<p>                    In Why We Can&#8217;t Sleep, Calhoun opens up the cultural and political contexts of this predicament and offers solutions for how to pull oneself out of the abyss-and keep the next generation of women from falling in. The result is reassuring, empowering and essential reading for all middle-aged women, and anyone who hopes to understand them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-cant-sleep-generation-x-womens-new-midlife-crisis-ada-calhoun-abridged/">Why We Can&#8217;t Sleep : Generation X Women&#8217;s New Midlife Crisis &#8211; Ada Calhoun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do You Believe in Magic? : Vitamins, Supplements, and All Things Natural: A Look Behind the Curtain &#8211; Dr Paul A Offit (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Medical expert Paul A. Offit, M.D., offers a scathing exposé of the alternative medicine industry, revealing how even though some popular therapies are remarkably helpful due to the placebo response, many of them are ineffective, expensive, and even deadly. Dr. Offit reveals how alternative medicine&#8211;an unregulated industry under no legal obligation to prove its claims [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/">Do You Believe in Magic? : Vitamins, Supplements, and All Things Natural: A Look Behind the Curtain &#8211; Dr Paul A Offit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Medical expert Paul A. Offit, M.D., offers a scathing exposé of the alternative medicine industry, revealing how even though some popular therapies are remarkably helpful due to the placebo response, many of them are ineffective, expensive, and even deadly.    </p>
<p>                    Dr. Offit reveals how alternative medicine&#8211;an unregulated industry under no legal obligation to prove its claims or admit its risks&#8211;can actually be harmful to our health.    </p>
<p>                    Using dramatic real-life stories, Offit separates the sense from the nonsense, showing why any therapy&#8211;alternative or traditional&#8211;should be scrutinized. He also shows how some nontraditional methods can do a great deal of good, in some cases exceeding therapies offered by conventional practitioners.    </p>
<p>                    An outspoken advocate for science-based health advocacy who is not afraid to take on media celebrities who promote alternative practices, Dr. Offit advises, &#8220;There&#8217;s no such thing as alternative medicine. There&#8217;s only medicine that works and medicine that doesn&#8217;t.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/">Do You Believe in Magic? : Vitamins, Supplements, and All Things Natural: A Look Behind the Curtain &#8211; Dr Paul A Offit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Joy of Work : The No.1 Sunday Times Business Bestseller &#8211; 30 Ways to Fix Your Work Culture and Fall in Love with Your Job Again &#8211; Bruce Daisley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>__________________________ &#8216;Bruce Daisley is on a mission to change the world of work.&#8217; The Times __________________________ From the creator of hit podcast Eat Sleep Work Repeat comes a revolutionary re-envisioning of how to enjoy your job. Do you want to get more done, feel less stressed and love your job again? Sometimes having a job [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/">The Joy of Work : The No.1 Sunday Times Business Bestseller &#8211; 30 Ways to Fix Your Work Culture and Fall in Love with Your Job Again &#8211; Bruce Daisley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>__________________________<br />
                    &#8216;Bruce Daisley is on a mission to change the world of work.&#8217; The Times<br />
                    __________________________    </p>
<p>                    From the creator of hit podcast Eat Sleep Work Repeat comes a revolutionary re-envisioning of how to enjoy your job.    </p>
<p>                    Do you want to get more done, feel less stressed and love your job again?    </p>
<p>                    Sometimes having a job can feel like hard work. But between Monk Mode mornings, silent meetings and crisp Thursdays, the solutions are at your fingertips.    </p>
<p>                    Bruce Daisley knows a thing or two about the workplace. In the course of a career that has taken him from some of the world&#8217;s biggest media companies to Twitter, via Google and YouTube, he has become a leading expert on how we work now. And in his hugely popular podcast Eat Sleep Work Repeat, he has explored ways to fix it. Now he shares 30 brilliant &#8211; and refreshingly simple &#8211; tips on how to make your job more productive, more rewarding &#8211; and much, much more enjoyable.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;With just 30 changes, you can transform your work experience from bland and boring (or worse) to fulfilling, fun, and even joyful.&#8217; Daniel Pink, author of When and Drive    </p>
<p>                    __________________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is a warm, wise and funny book which provides a terrific summary of some of the science &#8211; and stories &#8211; behind what makes work a positive part of people&#8217;s lives. From the importance of lunch to the value of laughter, this book gives witty and practical advice. I loved it and I&#8217;ve already started changing some of the things I do at work, as a result!&#8221; &#8211; Professor Sophie Scott    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Don&#8217;t quit yet! In this book, Bruce shares remarkable advice that may well have you laughing while you work and truly loving your job.&#8221; &#8211; Biz Stone, Twitter co-founder    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Bruce Daisley&#8217;s The Joy of Work is a joy to read. It translates the best of workplace psychology research into practical ways of establishing creative and liveable cultures at work-a must read for all of us 9-5ers!&#8221; &#8211; Professor Sir Cary Cooper, ALLIANCE Manchester Business School, University of Manchester    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Bruce&#8217;s The Joy of Work is an important reminder of simple everyday practices to improve how we all work together, which will lead to greater team and individual happiness and performance. Great results will follow.&#8221; &#8211; Jack Dorsey, CEO of Twitter and Square    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;With just 30 changes, you can transform your work experience from bland and boring (or worse) to fulfilling, fun, and even joyful. Bruce Daisley has pulled together threads of research and woven them into a tapestry of strategies that actually work, and that don&#8217;t depend on the CEO&#8217;s sign-off for implementation. You can begin changing your work culture today at the individual, team, and organisational levels with these tactics that increase creativity, productivity, and satisfaction.&#8221; &#8211; Daniel Pink, author of WHEN and DRIVE</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/">The Joy of Work : The No.1 Sunday Times Business Bestseller &#8211; 30 Ways to Fix Your Work Culture and Fall in Love with Your Job Again &#8211; Bruce Daisley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mortality &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mortality-christopher-hitchens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Death & Dying]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mortality-christopher-hitchens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On June 8, 2010, while on a book tour for his bestselling memoir, Hitch-22, Christopher Hitchens was stricken in his New York hotel room with excruciating pain in his chest and thorax. As he would later write in the first of a series of award-winning columns for Vanity Fair, he suddenly found himself being deported [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortality-christopher-hitchens-abridged/">Mortality &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On June 8, 2010, while on a book tour for his bestselling memoir, Hitch-22, Christopher Hitchens was stricken in his New York hotel room with excruciating pain in his chest and thorax. As he would later write in the first of a series of award-winning columns for Vanity Fair, he suddenly found himself being deported from the country of the well across the stark frontier that marks off the land of malady. Over the next eighteen months, until his death in Houston on December 15, 2011, he wrote constantly and brilliantly on politics and culture, astonishing readers with his capacity for superior work even in extremis.     </p>
<p>                     Throughout the course of his ordeal battling esophageal cancer, Hitchens adamantly and bravely refused the solace of religion, preferring to confront death with both eyes open. In this riveting account of his affliction, Hitchens poignantly describes the torments of illness, discusses its taboos, and explores how disease transforms experience and changes our relationship to the world around us. By turns personal and philosophical, Hitchens embraces the full panoply of human emotions as cancer invades his body and compels him to grapple with the enigma of death.     </p>
<p>                    Mortality is the exemplary story of one man&#8217;s refusal to cower in the face of the unknown, as well as a searching look at the human predicament. Crisp and vivid, veined throughout with penetrating intelligence, Hitchens&#8217;s testament is a courageous and lucid work of literature, an affirmation of the dignity and worth of man.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortality-christopher-hitchens-abridged/">Mortality &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Planet of Viruses : Second Edition &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Virology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The past year has been one of viral panic-panic about viruses, that is. Through headlines, public health warnings, and at least one homemade hazmat suit, we were reminded of the powerful force of viruses. They are the smallest living things known to science, yet they can hold the entire planet in their sway. A Planet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/">A Planet of Viruses : Second Edition &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past year has been one of viral panic-panic about viruses, that is. Through headlines, public health warnings, and at least one homemade hazmat suit, we were reminded of the powerful force of viruses. They are the smallest living things known to science, yet they can hold the entire planet in their sway. A Planet of Viruses is Carl Zimmer&#8217;s eye-opening look at the hidden world of viruses. Zimmer, the popular science writer and author of National Geographic&#8217;s award-winning blog The Loom, has updated this edition to include the stories of new outbreaks, such as Ebola, MERS, and chikungunya virus; new scientific discoveries, such as a hundred-million-year-old virus that infected the common ancestor of armadillos, elephants, and humans; and new findings that show why climate change may lead to even deadlier outbreaks. Zimmer&#8217;s lucid explanations and fascinating stories demonstrate how deeply humans and viruses are intertwined. Viruses helped give rise to the first life-forms, are responsible for many of our most devastating diseases, and will continue to control our fate for centuries.<br />
                    Thoroughly readable, and as reassuring as it is frightening, A Planet of Viruses is a fascinating tour of a formidable hidden world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-planet-of-viruses-second-edition-carl-zimmer-abridged/">A Planet of Viruses : Second Edition &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep & Dreams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all. Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all.    </p>
<p>                    Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising solutions for insomnia and other sleep disturbances, empowering readers to stop taking sleeping pills and enjoy the best sleep of their lives.    </p>
<p>                    Written in a clear and entertaining way, The Sleep Solution contains tips, tricks, exercises, and illustrations throughout. Dr Winter is an international expert on sleep and has helped thousands of patients &#8211; including professional athletes &#8211; rest better at night. Now, he&#8217;s ready to help you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Longevity Project : Surprising Discoveries for Health and Long Life from the Landmark Eight Decade Study &#8211; Howard S. Friedman, Leslie R. Martin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-longevity-project-surprising-discoveries-for-health-and-long-life-from-the-landmark-eight-decade-study-howard-s-friedman-leslie-r-martin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-longevity-project-surprising-discoveries-for-health-and-long-life-from-the-landmark-eight-decade-study-howard-s-friedman-leslie-r-martin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We have been told that the key to longevity involves obsessing over what we eat, how much we stress, and how fast we run. Based on the most extensive study of longevity ever conducted, The Longevity Project exposes what really impacts our lifespan-including friends, family, personality and work. Gathering new information and using modern statistics [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-project-surprising-discoveries-for-health-and-long-life-from-the-landmark-eight-decade-study-howard-s-friedman-leslie-r-martin-abridged/">The Longevity Project : Surprising Discoveries for Health and Long Life from the Landmark Eight Decade Study &#8211; Howard S. Friedman, Leslie R. Martin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have been told that the key to longevity involves obsessing over what we eat, how much we stress, and how fast we run. Based on the most extensive study of longevity ever conducted, The Longevity Project exposes what really impacts our lifespan-including friends, family, personality and work.     </p>
<p>                    Gathering new information and using modern statistics to study participants across eight decades, Dr Howard Friedman and Dr Leslie Martin bust myths about achieving health and long life. For example, people do not die from working long hours at a challenging job &#8211; many who worked the hardest lived the longest. Getting and staying married is not the magic ticket to long life, especially if you&#8217;re a woman. And it&#8217;s not the happy-go-lucky ones who thrive &#8211; it&#8217;s the prudent and persistent who flourish through the years.     </p>
<p>                    With questionnaires that help you determine where you are heading on the longevity spectrum and advice about how to stay healthy, this book changes the conversation about living a long, healthy life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-project-surprising-discoveries-for-health-and-long-life-from-the-landmark-eight-decade-study-howard-s-friedman-leslie-r-martin-abridged/">The Longevity Project : Surprising Discoveries for Health and Long Life from the Landmark Eight Decade Study &#8211; Howard S. Friedman, Leslie R. Martin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 5 AM Club : Own Your Morning. Elevate Your Life. &#8211; Robin Sharma (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-5-am-club-own-your-morning-elevate-your-life-robin-sharma-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations & Safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-5-am-club-own-your-morning-elevate-your-life-robin-sharma-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Legendary leadership and elite performance expert Robin Sharma introduced The 5am Club concept over twenty years ago, based on a revolutionary morning routine that has helped his clients maximize their productivity, activate their best health and bulletproof their serenity in this age of overwhelming complexity. Now, in this life-changing book, handcrafted by the author over [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-am-club-own-your-morning-elevate-your-life-robin-sharma-abridged/">The 5 AM Club : Own Your Morning. Elevate Your Life. &#8211; Robin Sharma (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Legendary leadership and elite performance expert Robin Sharma introduced The 5am Club concept over twenty years ago, based on a revolutionary morning routine that has helped his clients maximize their productivity, activate their best health and bulletproof their serenity in this age of overwhelming complexity.    </p>
<p>                              Now, in this life-changing book, handcrafted by the author over a rigorous four-year period, you will discover the early-rising habit that has helped so many accomplish epic results while upgrading their happiness, helpfulness and feelings of aliveness.    </p>
<p>                              Through an enchanting-and often amusing-story about two struggling strangers who meet an eccentric tycoon who becomes their secret mentor, The 5am Club will walk you through:    </p>
<p>                    How great geniuses, business titans and the world&#8217;s wisest people start their mornings to produce astonishing achievements<br />
                    A little-known formula you can use instantly to wake up early feeling inspired, focused and flooded with a fiery drive to get the most out of each day<br />
                    A step-by-step method to protect the quietest hours of daybreak so you have time for exercise, self-renewal and personal growth<br />
                    A neuroscience-based practice proven to help make it easy to rise while most people are sleeping, giving you precious time for yourself to think, express your creativity and begin the day peacefully instead of being rushed<br />
                    &#8216;Insider-only&#8217; tactics to defend your gifts, talents and dreams against digital distraction and trivial diversions so you enjoy fortune, influence and a magnificent impact on the world    </p>
<p>                              Part manifesto for mastery, part playbook for genius-grade productivity and part companion for a life lived beautifully, The 5am Club is a work that will transform your life. Forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-am-club-own-your-morning-elevate-your-life-robin-sharma-abridged/">The 5 AM Club : Own Your Morning. Elevate Your Life. &#8211; Robin Sharma (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What the Fork are You Eating? : An Action Plan for Your Pantry and Plate &#8211; Stefanie Sacks, Foreword by Kathie Madonna Swift (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s labeled natural, grass-fed, or free-roaming; yet it might be anything but. It&#8217;s time to find out what you&#8217;re actually eating&#8230; When your groceries are labeled &#8220;low-fat,&#8221; &#8220;sugar-free,&#8221; and even &#8220;natural&#8221; and antibiotic-free, it&#8217;s easy to assume that you&#8217;re making healthy choices. Yet even some of those seemingly wholesome offerings contain chemical preservatives, pesticides, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/">What the Fork are You Eating? : An Action Plan for Your Pantry and Plate &#8211; Stefanie Sacks, Foreword by Kathie Madonna Swift (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s labeled natural, grass-fed, or free-roaming; yet it might be anything but. It&#8217;s time to find out what you&#8217;re actually eating&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    When your groceries are labeled &#8220;low-fat,&#8221; &#8220;sugar-free,&#8221; and even &#8220;natural&#8221; and antibiotic-free, it&#8217;s easy to assume that you&#8217;re making healthy choices. Yet even some of those seemingly wholesome offerings contain chemical preservatives, pesticides, and artificial flavors and coloring that negatively affect your health. In What the Fork Are You Eating?, a practical guide written by certified chef and nutritionist Stefanie Sacks, MS, CNS, CDN, we learn exactly what the most offensive ingredients in our food are and how we can remove (or at least minimize) them in our diets. Sacks gives us an aisle-by-aisle rundown of how to shop for healthier items and create simple, nutritious, and delicious meals, including fifty original recipes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-the-fork-are-you-eating-an-action-plan-for-your-pantry-and-plate-stefanie-sacks-foreword-by-kathie-madonna-swift-abridged/">What the Fork are You Eating? : An Action Plan for Your Pantry and Plate &#8211; Stefanie Sacks, Foreword by Kathie Madonna Swift (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diaries, Letters & Journals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geographical Discovery & Exploration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transplant Surgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories: Discovery / Historical / Scientific]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jauhar weaves his own personal and family story into his history of the heart&#8230;very effectively&#8230; This gives a certain dramatic tension to the book, as it tells the fascinating and rather wonderful history of cardiology.&#8217; -Henry Marsh, New Statesman A Mail on Sunday Book of the Year The heart lies at the centre of life. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/">Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jauhar weaves his own personal and family story into his history of the heart&#8230;very effectively&#8230; This gives a certain dramatic tension to the book, as it tells the fascinating and rather wonderful history of cardiology.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    -Henry Marsh, New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    A Mail on Sunday Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    The heart lies at the centre of life. For cardiologist Sandeep Jauhar it is an obsession.    </p>
<p>                    In this fascinating history he interweaves gripping scenes from the operating theatre with the moving tale of his family&#8217;s history of heart problems &#8211; from the death of his grandfather to the ominous signs of how he himself might die.    </p>
<p>                    Jauhar looks at the pioneers who risked patients&#8217; lives and their own careers, and confronts the limits of medical technology, arguing that how we live is more important than any device or drug we may invent. Heart is the all-encompassing story of the engine of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/">Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller from the author of How to Change Your Mind, The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, and Food Rules Food. There&#8217;s plenty of it around, and we all love to eat it. So why should anyone need to defend it? Because in the so-called Western diet, food has been replaced by nutrients, and common [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/">In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times Bestseller from the author of How to Change Your Mind, The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, and Food Rules      </p>
<p>                     Food. There&#8217;s plenty of it around, and we all love to eat it. So why should anyone need to defend it?     </p>
<p>                     Because in the so-called Western diet, food has been replaced by nutrients, and common sense by confusion&#8211;most of what we&#8217;re consuming today is longer the product of nature but of food science. The result is what Michael Pollan calls the American Paradox: The more we worry about nutrition, the less healthy we see to become. With In Defense of Food, Pollan proposes a new (and very old) answer to the question of what we should eat that comes down to seven simple but liberating words: Eat food. Not too much. Mostly plants. Pollan&#8217;s bracing and eloquent manifesto shows us how we can start making thoughtful food choices that will enrich our lives, enlarge our sense of what it means to be healthy, and bring pleasure back to eating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defense-of-food-an-eaters-manifesto-michael-pollan-abridged/">In Defense of Food : An Eater&#8217;s Manifesto &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news. In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news.     </p>
<p>                    In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled mentally ill in the United States tripled over the past two decades?     </p>
<p>                    Interwoven with Whitaker&#8217;s groundbreaking analysis of the merits of psychiatric medications are the personal stories of children and adults swept up in this epidemic. As Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, other societies have begun to alter their use of psychiatric medications and are now reporting much improved outcomes . . . so why can&#8217;t such change happen here in the United States? Why have the results from these long-term studies&#8211;all of which point to the same startling conclusion&#8211;been kept from the public?     </p>
<p>                    Our nation has been hit by an epidemic of disabling mental illness, and yet, as Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, the medical blueprints for curbing that epidemic have already been drawn up.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Anatomy of an Epidemic     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The timing of Robert Whitaker&#8217;s Anatomy of an Epidemic, a comprehensive and highly readable history of psychiatry in the United States, couldn&#8217;t be better.&#8221;&#8211;Salon     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Anatomy of an Epidemic offers some answers, charting controversial ground with mystery-novel pacing.&#8221;&#8211;TIME     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lucid, pointed and important, Anatomy of an Epidemic should be required reading for anyone considering extended use of psychiatric medicine. Whitaker is at the height of his powers.&#8221; &#8211;Greg Critser, author of Generation Rx</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4-Hour Body : An Uncommon Guide to Rapid Fat-loss, Incredible Sex and Becoming Superhuman &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to lose fat, double testosterone, get the perfect posterior or give your partner a fifteen-minute female orgasm? Whatever your physical goal, The 4-Hour Body eclipses every other health manual by sharing the best kept secrets in the latest science and research to provide new strategies for redesigning the human body. And you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">The 4-Hour Body : An Uncommon Guide to Rapid Fat-loss, Incredible Sex and Becoming Superhuman &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to lose fat, double testosterone, get the perfect posterior or give your partner a fifteen-minute female orgasm? Whatever your physical goal, The 4-Hour Body eclipses every other health manual by sharing the best kept secrets in the latest science and research to provide new strategies for redesigning the human body.     </p>
<p>                    And you don&#8217;t need to exhaust yourself. International bestselling author, Timothy Ferriss, helps you reach your true genetic potential in 3-6 months with a commitment of less than four hours per week. You can pick and choose from a menu of options, from simple to extreme, for dramatic body changes.     </p>
<p>                    Based on over 15 years of research and with personal stories, amazing before and after photos, recipes and sidebars, The 4-Hour Body will give unbelievable results and change the way you look forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-hour-body-an-uncommon-guide-to-rapid-fat-loss-incredible-sex-and-becoming-superhuman-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">The 4-Hour Body : An Uncommon Guide to Rapid Fat-loss, Incredible Sex and Becoming Superhuman &#8211; Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sleep Smarter : 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to a Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success &#8211; Shawn Stevenson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your body&#8217;s natural ability to sleep soundly and learn how to boost your energy, lose weight, and improve your overall health and wellbeing. When it comes to health, there is one criminally overlooked element: sleep. Good sleep helps you shed fat for good, stave off disease, stay productive and improve virtually every function of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/">Sleep Smarter : 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to a Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success &#8211; Shawn Stevenson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your body&#8217;s natural ability to sleep soundly and learn how to boost your energy, lose weight, and improve your overall health and wellbeing.    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to health, there is one criminally overlooked element: sleep. Good sleep helps you shed fat for good, stave off disease, stay productive and improve virtually every function of your mind and body. When a degenerative bone disease crushed Shawn Stevenson&#8217;s dream of becoming a professional athlete and restricted his ability to function normally in daily life, Shawn took his health into his own hands. Through better sleep and optimized nutrition, he not only healed his body but also achieved fitness and business goals he never thought possible.    </p>
<p>                    Now in Sleep Smarter, Shawn shares easy tips and tricks to discover the best sleep and best health of your life. With a 14-Day Sleep Makeover, you&#8217;ll learn:<br />
                    &#8211; How to create the ideal sleep sanctuary<br />
                    &#8211; How to hack sunlight to regulate your circadian rhythms<br />
                    &#8211; Which clinically proven sleep nutrients and supplements you need and why<br />
                    &#8211; Stress-reduction exercises and fitness tips to keep you mentally and physically sharp&#8230; and more!    </p>
<p>                    Sleep Smarter is the much-needed guide for achieving the rest, energy and life you truly deserve.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleep-smarter-21-essential-strategies-to-sleep-your-way-to-a-better-body-better-health-and-bigger-success-shawn-stevenson-abridged/">Sleep Smarter : 21 Essential Strategies to Sleep Your Way to a Better Body, Better Health, and Bigger Success &#8211; Shawn Stevenson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Immunity : An Inoculation &#8211; Eula Biss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-immunity-an-inoculation-eula-biss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-immunity-an-inoculation-eula-biss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;On Immunity is a book I&#8217;ve recommended too many times to count&#8211;a searching, empathetic, ultimately unassailable argument, not just for vaccination but for thoroughly acknowledging our interdependence, and for all that becomes necessary and possible once we do. Written before COVID, it nonetheless speaks directly to the concerns of the pandemic era&#8211;to the fact that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-immunity-an-inoculation-eula-biss-abridged/">On Immunity : An Inoculation &#8211; Eula Biss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;On Immunity is a book I&#8217;ve recommended too many times to count&#8211;a searching, empathetic, ultimately unassailable argument, not just for vaccination but for thoroughly acknowledging our interdependence, and for all that becomes necessary and possible once we do. Written before COVID, it nonetheless speaks directly to the concerns of the pandemic era&#8211;to the fact that we are dangerous as well as vulnerable, to the way collective well-being and individual self-interest are configured at odds to one another when they are fundamentally intertwined.&#8221;&#8211;Jia Tolentino     </p>
<p>                    In this bold, fascinating book, Eula Biss addresses our fear of the government, the medical establishment, and what may be in our children&#8217;s air, food, mattresses, medicines, and vaccines. Reflecting on her own experience as a new mother, she suggests that we cannot immunize our children, or ourselves, against the world. As she explores the metaphors surrounding immunity, Biss extends her conversations with other mothers to meditations on the myth of Achilles, Voltaire&#8217;s Candide, Bram Stoker&#8217;s Dracula, Rachel Carson&#8217;s Silent Spring, Susan Sontag&#8217;s AIDS and Its Metaphors, and beyond. On Immunity is an inoculation against our fear and a moving account of how we are all interconnected-our bodies and our fates.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-immunity-an-inoculation-eula-biss-abridged/">On Immunity : An Inoculation &#8211; Eula Biss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dreams & Their Interpretation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now! __________________________________________________________________________________ FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now!<br />
                    __________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver    </p>
<p>                    Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in his Sunday Times bestselling book, The 4 Pillar Plan, BBC One&#8217;s Dr Rangan Chatterjee creates an easily accessible plan for taking control of your health and your life.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Chatterjee believes that everyday health revolves around the following four pillars: relaxation, food, movement and sleep. By making small, achievable changes in each of these key areas you can create and maintain good health &#8211; and avoid illness. Top tips in each area include:     </p>
<p>                    * an electronic &#8216;sabbath&#8217; once a week<br />
                     * 12 hours every day without food<br />
                     * exposure to sunlight first thing each morning<br />
                     * walking at least 10,000 steps a day    </p>
<p>                    Based on cutting edge research and his own two decades&#8217; worth of experience as a doctor, this book contains fascinating case studies from real patients and is an inspiring and easy-to-follow guide to better health and happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a New Afterword Must We Age? Nearly all scientists who study the biology of aging agree that we will someday be able to substantially slow down the aging process, extending our productive, youthful lives. Dr. Aubrey de Grey is perhaps the most bullish of all such researchers. As has been reported in media outlets [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/">Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a New Afterword     </p>
<p>                    Must We Age?     </p>
<p>                    Nearly all scientists who study the biology of aging agree that we will someday be able to substantially slow down the aging process, extending our productive, youthful lives. Dr. Aubrey de Grey is perhaps the most bullish of all such researchers. As has been reported in media outlets ranging from 60 Minutes to The New York Times,  Dr. de Grey believes that the key biomedical technology required to eliminate aging-derived debilitation and death entirely&#8211;technology that would not only slow but periodically reverse age-related physiological decay, leaving us biologically young into an indefinite future&#8211;is now within reach.     </p>
<p>                    In Ending Aging,  Dr. de Grey and his research assistant Michael Rae describe the details of this biotechnology. They explain that the aging of the human body, just like the aging of man-made machines, results from an accumulation of various types of damage. As with man-made machines, this damage can periodically be repaired, leading to indefinite extension of the machine&#8217;s fully functional lifetime, just as is routinely done with classic cars. We already know what types of damage accumulate in the human body, and we are moving rapidly toward the comprehensive development of technologies to remove that -damage. By demystifying aging and its postponement for the nonspecialist reader, de Grey and Rae systematically dismantle the fatalist presumption that aging will forever defeat the efforts of medical science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/">Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paediatric Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;courageous, compassionate, and rigorous every-person&#8217;s guide&#8221; (Christina Bethell, PhD, Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health) that shows the link between Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs) and diseases, and how to cope and heal from these emotional traumas. Your biography becomes your biology. The emotional trauma we suffer as children not only shapes our emotional [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/">Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;courageous, compassionate, and rigorous every-person&#8217;s guide&#8221; (Christina Bethell, PhD, Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health) that shows the link between Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs)  and diseases, and how to cope and heal from these emotional traumas.    </p>
<p>                    Your biography becomes your biology. The emotional trauma we suffer as children not only shapes our emotional lives as adults, but it also affects our physical health, longevity, and overall well-being. Scientists now know on a bio-chemical level exactly how parents&#8217; chronic fights, divorce, death in the family, being bullied or hazed, and growing up with a hypercritical, alcoholic, or mentally ill parent can leave permanent, physical &#8220;fingerprints&#8221; on our brains.    </p>
<p>                    When children encounter sudden or chronic adversity, stress hormones cause powerful changes in the body, altering the body&#8217;s chemistry. The developing immune system and brain react to this chemical barrage by permanently resetting children&#8217;s stress response to &#8220;high,&#8221; which in turn can have a devastating impact on their mental and physical health as they grow up.    </p>
<p>                    Donna Jackson Nakazawa shares stories from people who have recognized and overcome their adverse experiences, shows why some children are more immune to stress than others, and explains why women are at particular risk. &#8220;Groundbreaking&#8221; (Tara Brach, PhD, author of Radical Acceptance) in its research, inspiring in its clarity, Childhood Disrupted explains how you can reset your biology-and help your loved ones find ways to heal. &#8220;A truly important gift of understanding-illuminates the heartbreaking costs of childhood trauma and like good medicine offers the promising science of healing and prevention&#8221; (Jack Kornfield, author of A Path With Heart).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/">Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insurance & Actuarial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicolegal Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017 &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene At a moment of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene      </p>
<p>                    At a moment of drastic political upheaval, An American Sickness is a shocking investigation into our dysfunctional healthcare system &#8211; and offers practical solutions to its myriad problems.    </p>
<p>                     In these troubled times, perhaps no institution has unraveled more quickly and more completely than American medicine. In only a few decades, the medical system has been overrun by organizations seeking to exploit for profit the trust that vulnerable and sick Americans place in their healthcare. Our politicians have proven themselves either unwilling or incapable of reining in the increasingly outrageous costs faced by patients, and market-based solutions only seem to funnel larger and larger sums of our money into the hands of corporations. Impossibly high insurance premiums and inexplicably large bills have become facts of life; fatalism has set in. Very quickly Americans have been made to accept paying more for less. How did things get so bad so fast?     </p>
<p>                     Breaking down this monolithic business into the individual industries-the hospitals, doctors, insurance companies, and drug manufacturers-that together constitute our healthcare system, Rosenthal exposes the recent evolution of American medicine as never before. How did healthcare, the caring endeavor, become healthcare, the highly profitable industry? Hospital systems, which are managed by business executives, behave like predatory lenders, hounding patients and seizing their homes. Research charities are in bed with big pharmaceutical companies, which surreptitiously profit from the donations made by working people. Patients receive bills in code, from entrepreneurial doctors they never even saw.     </p>
<p>                     The system is in tatters, but we can fight back. Dr. Elisabeth Rosenthal doesn&#8217;t just explain the symptoms, she diagnoses and treats the disease itself. In clear and practical terms, she spells out exactly how to decode medical doublespeak, avoid the pitfalls of the pharmaceuticals racket, and get the care you and your family deserve. She takes you inside the doctor-patient relationship and to hospital C-suites, explaining step-by-step the workings of a system badly lacking transparency. This is about what we can do, as individual patients, both to navigate the maze that is American healthcare and also to demand far-reaching reform. An American Sickness is the frontline defense against a healthcare system that no longer has our well-being at heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health    </p>
<p>                    Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, bacteria and human cells have co-existed in a relationship that has ensured the health and equilibrium of our body. But now, much like the natural world outside of us, our internal environment is being irrevocably destroyed. The culprit: some of our most revered medical advances &#8211; antibiotics &#8211; which appear to be linked to the epidemics of asthma, eczema, obesity, certain forms of cancer, and other diseases plaguing modern society.    </p>
<p>                    In a book that stands as the Silent Spring of its day, Blaser sounds a provocative alarm that we ignore at our peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Life of Sleep &#8211; Kat Duff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-life-of-sleep-kat-duff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-life-of-sleep-kat-duff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Embark on an exploration of what lies behind our eyelids when we surrender to the secret life of sleep. What makes us cross the line from waking to slumber? According to Harvard scientists it&#8217;s our &#8216;sleep switch&#8217; &#8211; a cluster of neurons in the hypothalamus. For the ancient Greeks it was the god Hypnos, caressing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-sleep-kat-duff-abridged/">The Secret Life of Sleep &#8211; Kat Duff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Embark on an exploration of what lies behind our eyelids when we surrender to the secret life of sleep.    </p>
<p>                    What makes us cross the line from waking to slumber? According to Harvard scientists it&#8217;s our &#8216;sleep switch&#8217; &#8211; a cluster of neurons in the hypothalamus. For the ancient Greeks it was the god Hypnos, caressing you with his wings. For the Blackfeet Indians, a butterfly.    </p>
<p>                    From the meaning of dreams to the dangers of sleeping pills, Kat Duff brings insights from the latest in sleep science, the paintings of Salvador Dali, the musings of Michel de Montaigne, and rituals from around the world to paint a portrait of an activity that we all cherish but know little about. Why do we sleep? What happens in our brains when we sleep? Why are sleep patterns in Western industrialised countries so unhealthy? Is the boundary between sleep and wakefulness as clear cut as we might have supposed?    </p>
<p>                    Tackling the full breadth of what sleep means to us, The Secret Life of Sleep blends cutting-edge research with captivating narrative to explore a hidden world that is both intimate and mysterious.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-sleep-kat-duff-abridged/">The Secret Life of Sleep &#8211; Kat Duff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, With Brendan Buhler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more. In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, With Brendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more.     </p>
<p>                    In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly within our intestines&#8211;has an astonishing impact on our lives. Your health, mood, sleep patterns, eating preferences&#8211;even your likelihood of getting bitten by mosquitoes&#8211;can be traced in part to the tiny creatures that live on and inside of us.     </p>
<p>                    In Follow Your Gut,  pioneering scientist Rob Knight pairs with award-winning science journalist Brendan Buhler to explain&#8211;with good humor and easy-to-grasp examples&#8211;why these new findings matter to everyone. They lead a detailed tour of the previously unseen world inside our bodies, calling out the diseases and conditions believed to be most directly impacted by them.     </p>
<p>                    With a practical eye toward deeper knowledge and better decisions, they also explore the known effects of antibiotics, probiotics, diet choice and even birth method on our children&#8217;s lifelong health. Ultimately, this pioneering book explains how to learn about your own microbiome and take steps toward understanding and improving your health, using the latest research as a guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, With Brendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax    </p>
<p>                    Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world has become a word-of-mouth bestseller and global phenomenon. It reveals a set of simple yet powerful practices that you can incorporate into daily life to break the cycle of anxiety, stress unhappiness and exhaustion. It promotes the kind of happiness that gets into your bones and allows you to meet the worst that life throws at you with new courage.     </p>
<p>                    Mindfulness is based on mindfulness-based cognitive therapy (MBCT). Co-developed by Professor Mark Williams of Oxford University, MBCT is recommended by the UK&#8217;s National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and is as effective as drugs for preventing depression. But, equally, it works for the rest of us who aren&#8217;t depressed but who are struggling to keep up with the relentless demands of the modern world.     </p>
<p>                    By investing just a few minutes each day, this classic guide to mindfulness will put you back in control of your life once again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trauma & Shock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;An astonishing and important book. The trauma Bible. I cannot recommend it enough for anyone struggling with&#8230;well&#8230;anything&#8217; Tara Westover The effects of trauma can be devastating for sufferers, their families and future generations. Here one of the world&#8217;s experts on traumatic stress offers a bold new paradigm for treatment, moving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/">The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An astonishing and important book. The trauma Bible. I  cannot recommend it enough for anyone struggling with&#8230;well&#8230;anything&#8217; Tara Westover    </p>
<p>                    The effects of trauma can be devastating for sufferers, their families and future generations. Here one of the world&#8217;s experts on traumatic stress offers a bold new paradigm for treatment, moving away from standard talking and drug therapies and towards an alternative approach that heals mind, brain and body.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Dr. van der Kolk&#8217;s masterpiece combines the boundless curiosity of the scientist, the erudition of the scholar, and the passion of the truth teller&#8217; Judith Herman, author of Trauma and Recovery</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/">The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking prescription for health care reform&#8211;from a legendaryleader in innovation . . . Our health care system is in critical condition. Each year, fewer Americans can afford it, fewer businesses can provide it, and fewer government programs can promise it for future generations. We need a cure, and we need it now. Harvard Business [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking prescription for health care reform&#8211;from a legendaryleader in innovation . . .    </p>
<p>                    Our health care system is in critical condition. Each year, fewer Americans can afford it, fewer businesses can provide it, and fewer government programs can promise it for future generations.    </p>
<p>                    We need a cure, and we need it now.    </p>
<p>                    Harvard Business School&#8217;s Clayton M. Christensen-whose bestselling The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma revolutionized the business world-presents The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription, a comprehensive analysis of the strategies that will improvehealth care and make it affordable.    </p>
<p>                    Christensen applies the principles of disruptive innovation to the broken health care system with two pioneers in the field-Dr. Jerome Grossman and Dr. Jason Hwang. Together, they examine arange of symptoms and offer proven solutions.    </p>
<p>                    YOU&#8217;LL DISCOVER HOW    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Precision medicine&#8221; reduces costs and makes good on the promise of personalized careDisruptive business models improve quality, accessibility, and affordability by changing the way hospitals and doctors workPatient networks enable better treatment of chronic diseasesEmployers can change the roles they play in health care to compete effectively in the era of globalizationInsurance and regulatory reforms stimulate disruption in health care</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking study that reveals how decades of misleading science and policy unjustly demonized the high-fat diet, which might actually be our healthiest option. For the past 60 years we have been told that a low-fat diet can protect against obesity, diabetes, and heart disease. Yet despite many of us taking this advice in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking study that reveals how decades of misleading science and policy unjustly demonized the high-fat diet, which<br />
                    might actually be our healthiest option.    </p>
<p>                    For the past 60 years we have been told that a low-fat diet can protect against obesity, diabetes, and heart disease. Yet despite<br />
                    many of us taking this advice in the developed West, we are now in the midst of an obesity epidemic that is breeding serious<br />
                    health problems.    </p>
<p>                    Recent more rigorous scientific work has overturned some of the shoddier theories of earlier decades to demonstrate conclusively that we have been needlessly avoiding red meat, cheese, whole milk, and eggs for decades, and that we can now, guilt-free, welcome these delicious foods back into our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of The Willpower Instinct introduces a surprising science-based book that doesn&#8217;t tell us why we should exercise but instead shows us how to fall in love with movement. Exercise is health-enhancing and life-extending, yet many of us feel it&#8217;s a chore. But, as Kelly McGonigal reveals, it doesn&#8217;t have to be. Movement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of The Willpower Instinct introduces a surprising science-based book that doesn&#8217;t tell us why we should exercise but instead shows us how to fall in love with movement.    </p>
<p>                    Exercise is health-enhancing and life-extending, yet many of us feel it&#8217;s a chore. But, as Kelly McGonigal reveals, it doesn&#8217;t have to be. Movement can and should be a source of joy.    </p>
<p>                    Through her trademark blend of science and storytelling, McGonigal draws on insights from neuroscience, psychology, anthropology, and evolutionary biology, as well as memoirs, ethnographies, and philosophers. She shows how movement is intertwined with some of the most basic human joys, including self-expression, social connection, and mastery&#8211;and why it is a powerful antidote to the modern epidemics of depression, anxiety, and loneliness.    </p>
<p>                    McGonigal tells the stories of people who have found fulfillment and belonging through running, walking, dancing, swimming, weightlifting, and more, with examples that span the globe, from Tanzania, where one of the last hunter-gatherer tribes on the planet live, to a dance class at Juilliard for people with Parkinson&#8217;s disease, to the streets of London, where volunteers combine fitness and community service, to races in the remote wilderness, where athletes push the limits of what a human can endure. Along the way, McGonigal paints a portrait of human nature that highlights our capacity for hope, cooperation, and self-transcendence.    </p>
<p>                    The result is a revolutionary narrative that goes beyond familiar arguments in favor of exercise, to illustrate why movement is integral to both our happiness and our humanity. Readers will learn what they can do in their own lives and communities to harness the power of movement to create happiness, meaning, and connection.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ask Me About My Uterus : A Quest to Make Doctors Believe in Women&#8217;s Pain &#8211; Abby Norman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ask-me-about-my-uterus-a-quest-to-make-doctors-believe-in-womens-pain-abby-norman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Study & Revision Guides & Reference Material]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ask-me-about-my-uterus-a-quest-to-make-doctors-believe-in-womens-pain-abby-norman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the fall of 2010, Abby Norman&#8217;s strong dancer&#8217;s body dropped forty pounds and gray hairs began to sprout from her temples. She was repeatedly hospitalized in excruciating pain, but the doctors insisted it was a urinary tract infection and sent her home with antibiotics. Unable to get out of bed, much less attend class, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-me-about-my-uterus-a-quest-to-make-doctors-believe-in-womens-pain-abby-norman-abridged/">Ask Me About My Uterus : A Quest to Make Doctors Believe in Women&#8217;s Pain &#8211; Abby Norman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the fall of 2010, Abby Norman&#8217;s strong dancer&#8217;s body dropped forty pounds and gray hairs began to sprout from her temples. She was repeatedly hospitalized in excruciating pain, but the doctors insisted it was a urinary tract infection and sent her home with antibiotics. Unable to get out of bed, much less attend class, Norman dropped out of college and embarked on what would become a years-long journey to discover what was wrong with her. It wasn&#8217;t until she took matters into her own hands&#8211;securing a job in a hospital and educating herself over lunchtime reading in the medical library&#8211;that she found an accurate diagnosis of endometriosis.    </p>
<p>                    In Ask Me About My Uterus, Norman describes what it was like to have her pain dismissed, to be told it was all in her head, only to be taken seriously when she was accompanied by a boyfriend who confirmed that her sexual performance was, indeed, compromised. Putting her own trials into a broader historical, sociocultural, and political context, Norman shows that women&#8217;s bodies have long been the battleground of a never-ending war for power, control, medical knowledge, and truth. It&#8217;s time to refute the belief that being a woman is a preexisting condition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-me-about-my-uterus-a-quest-to-make-doctors-believe-in-womens-pain-abby-norman-abridged/">Ask Me About My Uterus : A Quest to Make Doctors Believe in Women&#8217;s Pain &#8211; Abby Norman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grain Brain : The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar&#8211;Your Brain&#8217;s Silent Killers &#8211; David Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Allergies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The devastating truth about the effects of wheat, sugar, and carbs on the brain, with a 4-week plan to achieve optimum health. In Grain Brain, renowned neurologist David Perlmutter, MD, exposes a finding that&#8217;s been buried in the medical literature for far too long: carbs are destroying your brain. Even so-called healthy carbs like whole [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Grain Brain : The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar&#8211;Your Brain&#8217;s Silent Killers &#8211; David Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The devastating truth about the effects of wheat, sugar, and carbs on the brain, with a 4-week plan to achieve optimum health.     </p>
<p>                     In Grain Brain, renowned neurologist David Perlmutter, MD, exposes a finding that&#8217;s been buried in the medical literature for far too long: carbs are destroying your brain. Even so-called healthy carbs like whole grains can cause dementia, ADHD, epilepsy, anxiety, chronic headaches, depression, decreased libido, and much more.     </p>
<p>                     Groundbreaking and timely, Grain Brain shows that the fate of your brain is not in your genes. It&#8217;s in the food you eat. The cornerstone of all degenerative conditions, including brain disorders, is inflammation, which can be triggered by carbs, especially containing gluten or high in sugar. Dr. Perlmutter explains what happens when the brain encounters common ingredients in your daily bread and fruit bowls, how statin drugs may be erasing your memory, why a diet high in good fats is ideal, and how to spur the growth of new brain cells at any age.     </p>
<p>                     Dr. Perlmutter&#8217;s revolutionary 4-week plan shows you how to keep your brain healthy, vibrant, and sharp while dramatically reducing your risk for debilitating neurological diseases as well as relieving more common, everyday conditions &#8212; without drugs. Easy-to-follow strategies, delicious recipes, and weekly goals help you to put the plan into action. With a blend of anecdotes, cutting-edge research, and accessible, practical advice, Grain Brain teaches you how to take control of your smart genes, regain wellness, and enjoy lifelong health and vitality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Grain Brain : The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar&#8211;Your Brain&#8217;s Silent Killers &#8211; David Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice we receive from public health bodies is muddled, out of date, and frequently contradictory, and in many quarters still promotes the unproven hypothesis that fats are the greatest evil.    </p>
<p>                    With expert science and compelling storytelling, Gary Taubes investigates the history of nutritional science which, shaped by a handful of charismatic and misguided individuals, has for a hundred years denied the impact of sugar on our health. He exposes the powerful influence of the food industry which has lobbied for sugar&#8217;s ubiquity &#8211; the Sugar Association even today promoting &#8216;sugar&#8217;s goodness&#8217; &#8211;  and the extent that the industry has corrupted essential scientific research. He delves into the science of sugar, exposes conventional thinking that sugar is &#8217;empty calories&#8217; as a myth, and finds that its addictive pleasures are resulting in worldwide consumption as never experienced before, to devastating effect.     </p>
<p>                    The Case Against Sugar is a revelatory read, which will fundamentally change the way we eat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat to Live : The Amazing Nutrient-Rich Program for Fast and Sustained Weight Loss &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hailed a &#8220;medical breakthrough&#8221; by Dr. Mehmet Oz, Eat to Live offers a highly effective, scientifically proven way to lose weight quickly. The key to Dr. Joel Fuhrman&#8217;s revolutionary six-week plan is simple: health = nutrients / calories. When the ratio of nutrients to calories in the food you eat is high, you lose weight. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Eat to Live : The Amazing Nutrient-Rich Program for Fast and Sustained Weight Loss &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hailed a &#8220;medical breakthrough&#8221; by Dr. Mehmet Oz, Eat to Live offers a highly effective, scientifically proven way to lose weight quickly.     </p>
<p>                     The key to Dr. Joel Fuhrman&#8217;s revolutionary six-week plan is simple: health = nutrients / calories. When the ratio of nutrients to calories in the food you eat is high, you lose weight. The more nutrient-dense food you eat, the less you crave fat, sweets, and high-caloric foods.     </p>
<p>                    Eat to Live has been revised to include inspiring success stories from people who have used the program to lose shockingly large amounts of weight and recover from life-threatening illnesses; Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s nutrient density index; up-to-date scientific research supporting the principles behind Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s plan; new recipes and meal ideas; and much more. This easy-to-follow, nutritionally sound diet can help anyone shed pounds quickly-and keep them off.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Furhman&#8217;s formula is simple, safe, and solid.&#8221; &#8211;Body and Soul</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-live-the-amazing-nutrient-rich-program-for-fast-and-sustained-weight-loss-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Eat to Live : The Amazing Nutrient-Rich Program for Fast and Sustained Weight Loss &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle, from the bestselling author of How Not to Die. Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle,  from the bestselling author of How Not to Die.    </p>
<p>                    Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any happier or healthier. As obesity rates and associated disease and impairments continue to rise, it&#8217;s time for a different approach.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet is a treasure trove of buried data and cutting-edge dietary research that Dr Michael Greger has translated into accessible, actionable advice with exciting tools and tricks that will help you to safely lose weight and eliminate unwanted body fat &#8211; for good.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Greger, renowned nutrition expert, physician, and founder of the NutritionFacts website, explores the many causes of obesity &#8211; from our genes to the portions on our plate to other environmental factors &#8211; and the many consequences, from diabetes to cancer to mental health issues. From there, Dr Greger breaks down a variety of approaches to weight loss, honing in on the optimal criteria that enable success, including: a diet high in fibre and water, a diet low in fat, salt, and sugar, and diet full of anti-inflammatory foods.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet then goes beyond food to explore the many other weight-loss accelerators available to us in our body&#8217;s systems, revealing how plant-based meals can be eaten at specific times to maximize our bodies&#8217; natural fat-burning activities. Dr Greger provides a clear plan not only for the ultimate weight loss diet, but also the approach we must take to unlock its greatest efficacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diabetes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FROM NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR DR. JASON FUNG * &#8220;The doctor who invented intermittent fasting.&#8221;-The Daily Mail &#8220;Dr. Fung reveals how [type 2 diabetes] can be prevented and also reversed using natural dietary methods instead of medications &#8230; This is an important and timely book. Highly recommended.&#8221;-Dr. Mark Hyman, author of The Pegan Diet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FROM NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR DR. JASON FUNG * &#8220;The doctor who invented intermittent fasting.&#8221;-The Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Fung reveals how [type 2 diabetes] can be prevented and also reversed using natural dietary methods instead of medications &#8230; This is an important and timely book. Highly recommended.&#8221;-Dr. Mark Hyman, author of The Pegan Diet    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Jason Fung has done it again. &#8230; Get this book!&#8221;-Dr. Steven R. Gundry, author of The Plant Paradox    </p>
<p>                    Everything you believe about treating type 2 diabetes is wrong. Today, most doctors, dietitians, and even diabetes specialists consider type 2 diabetes to be a chronic and progressive disease-a life sentence with no possibility of parole. But the truth, as Dr. Fung reveals in this groundbreaking book, is that type 2 diabetes is reversible.     </p>
<p>                    Writing with clear, persuasive language, Dr. Fung explains why conventional treatments that rely on insulin or other blood-glucose-lowering drugs can actually exacerbate the problem, leading to significant weight gain and even heart disease. The only way to treat type 2 diabetes effectively, he argues, is proper dieting and intermittent fasting-not medication.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Diabetes Code is unabashedly provocative yet practical &#8230; a clear blueprint for everyone to take control of their blood sugar, their health, and their lives.&#8221;- Dr. Will Cole, author of Intuitive Fasting</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From world-renowned health expert and New York Times bestselling author of Eat to Live and Eat for Life Dr. Joel Fuhrman comes a practical nutritional plan to prevent and reverse disease&#8211;no shots, drugs or sick days required. Why do some of us get sick with greater frequency than others? What makes us more susceptible to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From world-renowned health expert and New York Times bestselling author of Eat to Live and Eat for Life Dr. Joel Fuhrman comes a practical nutritional plan to prevent and reverse disease&#8211;no shots, drugs or sick days required.    </p>
<p>                     Why do some of us get sick with greater frequency than others? What makes us more susceptible to illness? Is there a secret to staying healthy? Dr. Fuhrman doesn&#8217;t believe the secret to staying healthy lies in medical care&#8211;rather, the solution is to change the way we eat.    </p>
<p>                     With more than 85 plant-based recipes, a two-week menu plan, and lists of super foods that boost immunity, Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s proven strategies in Super Immunity combine the latest data from clinical tests, nutritional research, and results from thousands of patients .    </p>
<p>                    Inside Super Immunity, you&#8217;ll find: The big picture&#8211;Learn everything you need to know about healthy eating for a healthy life.A 2-week meal plan&#8211;Take the guesswork out of changing your diet with planned meals for breakfast, lunch, and dinner every day of the week.85 immunity-boosting recipes&#8211;These delicious plant based recipes make eating healthy easy and crave-worthy.    </p>
<p>                     Live longer, stronger, and disease free with this proven plan to change your diet and change your life.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Super Immunity is a much needed book that contains the key to ending the cycle of sickness that plagues many of our lives. This is enlightened medicine, at last!&#8221; (Dr. Alejandro Junger, New York Times bestselling author of CLEAN)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
