<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Internet Guides &amp; Online Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/internet-guides-online-services/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/internet-guides-online-services/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Internet Guides &amp; Online Services Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/internet-guides-online-services/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>121 First Dates : How to Succeed at Online Dating, Fall in Love, and Live Happily Ever After (Really!) &#8211; Wendy Newman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/121-first-dates-how-to-succeed-at-online-dating-fall-in-love-and-live-happily-ever-after-really-wendy-newman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/121-first-dates-how-to-succeed-at-online-dating-fall-in-love-and-live-happily-ever-after-really-wendy-newman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Based on years of research and 121 real-life first dates, relationship expert Wendy Newman dishes up practical wisdom for navigating the online dating trenches with grace, efficiency, and a strong dose of humour. Wendy Newman has made every imaginable dating mistake so you don&#8217;t have to. Part guidebook, part personal tell-all, 121 First Dates chronicles [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/121-first-dates-how-to-succeed-at-online-dating-fall-in-love-and-live-happily-ever-after-really-wendy-newman-abridged/">121 First Dates : How to Succeed at Online Dating, Fall in Love, and Live Happily Ever After (Really!) &#8211; Wendy Newman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Based on years of research and 121 real-life first dates, relationship expert Wendy Newman dishes up practical wisdom for navigating the online dating trenches with grace, efficiency, and a strong dose of humour.     </p>
<p>                    Wendy Newman has made every imaginable dating mistake so you don&#8217;t have to. Part guidebook, part personal tell-all, 121 First Dates chronicles Wendy&#8217;s funny, real-life misadventures and the practical wisdom she gained from them. Her dating tales will find you laughing, commiserating, and nodding your head as you learn how to stay in the dating game until you find the right man, just like Wendy did.     </p>
<p>                    This book busts myths, answers age-old questions, and examines pitfalls that make you want to give up on dating altogether. Just when you&#8217;re about to submit to a lifetime at home with a pint of Haagen-Dazs and sitcom reruns, 121 First Dates will inspire you to keep stepping out. Wendy discusses how to date successfully and efficiently, avoid the most common dating pitfalls, have an amazing first date with anyone, end uncomfortable situations with grace, and much, much more. She offers up realistic Dos and Don&#8217;ts as well as tips for making the most of any situation you find yourself in-whether you want to run or you think he&#8217;s the one.     </p>
<p>                    Brimming with humour, hope, and authenticity, 121 First Dates will give every woman the tools, confidence, and determination to be and stay real when dating. How else will you find the best match for you?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/121-first-dates-how-to-succeed-at-online-dating-fall-in-love-and-live-happily-ever-after-really-wendy-newman-abridged/">121 First Dates : How to Succeed at Online Dating, Fall in Love, and Live Happily Ever After (Really!) &#8211; Wendy Newman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Power : Why outsiders are winning, institutions are failing, and how the rest of us can keep up in the age of mass participation &#8211; Jeremy Heimans, Henry Timms (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For most of human history the rules of power were clear: power was something to be seized, and then jealously guarded. Under this &#8216;Old Power&#8217; we lived in a world of rulers and subjects. Now, we all sense that something has changed. From #MeToo to Harvey Weinstein; Corbyn to Trump; from YouTube sensations to darker [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/">New Power : Why outsiders are winning, institutions are failing, and how the rest of us can keep up in the age of mass participation &#8211; Jeremy Heimans, Henry Timms (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For most of human history the rules of power were clear: power was something to be seized, and then jealously guarded. Under this &#8216;Old Power&#8217; we lived in a world of rulers and subjects.    </p>
<p>                    Now, we all sense that something has changed. From #MeToo to Harvey Weinstein; Corbyn to Trump; from YouTube sensations to darker phenomena such as the emergence of ISIS &#8211; in our new hyper-connected world, ideas and movements can spread and flourish with astonishing force and speed.    </p>
<p>                    In New Power, Jeremy Heimans and Henry Timms confront the biggest story of our age and trace how New Power is the key to understanding where we are and will prosper in the 21st Century.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on examples from business, politics, popular culture and social justice, as well as case studies of organisations like LEGO and TED, they explain the forces that are changing the course of our age.    </p>
<p>                    In a world increasingly shaped by New Power, this book will show you how to shape your future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/">New Power : Why outsiders are winning, institutions are failing, and how the rest of us can keep up in the age of mass participation &#8211; Jeremy Heimans, Henry Timms (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gen Z Effect : The Six Forces Shaping the Future of Business &#8211; Tom Koulopoulos, Dan Keldsen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/gen-z-effect-the-six-forces-shaping-the-future-of-business-tom-koulopoulos-dan-keldsen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/gen-z-effect-the-six-forces-shaping-the-future-of-business-tom-koulopoulos-dan-keldsen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the most profound changes in business and society is the emergence of the post-Millennial generation, Gen Z. While every new generation has faced its share of disruption in technology, economics, politics and society, no other generation in the history of mankind has had the ability to connect every human being on the planet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gen-z-effect-the-six-forces-shaping-the-future-of-business-tom-koulopoulos-dan-keldsen-abridged/">Gen Z Effect : The Six Forces Shaping the Future of Business &#8211; Tom Koulopoulos, Dan Keldsen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the most profound changes in business and society is the emergence of the post-Millennial generation, Gen Z.  While every new generation has faced its share of disruption in technology, economics, politics and society, no other generation in the history of mankind has had the ability to connect every human being on the planet to each other and in the process to provide the opportunity for each person to be fully educated, socially and economically engaged.  What might this mean for business, markets, and educational institutions in the future? In this revolutionary new book, The Gen Z Effect: The Six Forces Shaping the Future of Business, authors Tom Koulopoulos and Dan Keldsen delve into a vision of the future where disruptive invention and reinvention is the acknowledged norm, touching almost every aspect of how we work, live and play. From radical new approaches to marketing and manufacturing to the potential obliteration of intellectual property and the shift to mass innovation, to the decimation of our oldest learning institutions through open source and adaptive learning, The Gen Z Effect provides a mind-bending view of why we will need to embrace Gen Z as the last, best hope for taking on the world&#8217;s biggest challenges and opportunities, and how you can prepare yourself and your business for the greatest era of disruption, prosperity, and progress the world has ever experienced.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gen-z-effect-the-six-forces-shaping-the-future-of-business-tom-koulopoulos-dan-keldsen-abridged/">Gen Z Effect : The Six Forces Shaping the Future of Business &#8211; Tom Koulopoulos, Dan Keldsen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dragonfly Effect : Quick, Effective, and Powerful Ways To Use Social Media to Drive Social Change &#8211; Jennifer Aaker, Andy Smith, Carlye Adler, Dan Ariely, Foreword by Chip Heath (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dragonfly-effect-quick-effective-and-powerful-ways-to-use-social-media-to-drive-social-change-jennifer-aaker-andy-smith-carlye-adler-dan-ariely-foreword-by-chip-heath-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dragonfly-effect-quick-effective-and-powerful-ways-to-use-social-media-to-drive-social-change-jennifer-aaker-andy-smith-carlye-adler-dan-ariely-foreword-by-chip-heath-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for harnessing the power of social media to drive social change Many books teach the mechanics of using Facebook, Twitter, and YouTube to compete in business. But no book addresses how to harness the incredible power of social media to make a difference. The Dragonfly Effect shows you how to tap social media [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dragonfly-effect-quick-effective-and-powerful-ways-to-use-social-media-to-drive-social-change-jennifer-aaker-andy-smith-carlye-adler-dan-ariely-foreword-by-chip-heath-abridged/">The Dragonfly Effect : Quick, Effective, and Powerful Ways To Use Social Media to Drive Social Change &#8211; Jennifer Aaker, Andy Smith, Carlye Adler, Dan Ariely, Foreword by Chip Heath (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for harnessing the power of social media to drive social change Many books teach the mechanics of using Facebook, Twitter, and YouTube to compete in business. But no book addresses how to harness the incredible power of social media to make a difference. The Dragonfly Effect shows you how to tap social media and consumer psychological insights to achieve a single, concrete goal.<br />
                    Named for the only insect that is able to move in any direction when its four wings are working in concert, this book * Reveals the four &#8220;wings&#8221; of the Dragonfly Effect-and how they work together to produce colossal results * Features original case studies of global organizations like the Gap, Starbucks, Kiva, Nike, eBay, Facebook; and start-ups like Groupon and COOKPAD, showing how they achieve social good and customer loyalty * Leverage the power of design thinking and psychological research with practical strategies * Reveals how everyday people achieve unprecedented results-whether finding an almost impossible bone marrow match for a friend, raising millions for cancer research, or electing the current president of the United States The Dragonfly Effect shows that you don&#8217;t need money or power to inspire seismic change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dragonfly-effect-quick-effective-and-powerful-ways-to-use-social-media-to-drive-social-change-jennifer-aaker-andy-smith-carlye-adler-dan-ariely-foreword-by-chip-heath-abridged/">The Dragonfly Effect : Quick, Effective, and Powerful Ways To Use Social Media to Drive Social Change &#8211; Jennifer Aaker, Andy Smith, Carlye Adler, Dan Ariely, Foreword by Chip Heath (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trust Me, I&#8217;m Lying : Confessions of a Media Manipulator &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ve seen it all before. A malicious online rumor costs a company millions. A political sideshow derails the national news cycle and destroys a candidate. Some product or celebrity zooms from total obscurity to viral sensation. What you don&#8217;t know is that someone is responsible for all this. Usually, someone like me. I&#8217;m a media [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Trust Me, I&#8217;m Lying : Confessions of a Media Manipulator &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ve seen it all before. A malicious online rumor costs a company millions. A  political sideshow derails the national news cycle and destroys a candidate.  Some product or celebrity zooms from total obscurity to viral sensation. What  you don&#8217;t know is that someone is responsible for all this. Usually, someone  like me.    </p>
<p>                    I&#8217;m a media manipulator. In a world where blogs control and  distort the news, my job is to control blogs-as much as any one person  can.    </p>
<p>                    IN TODAY&#8217;S CULTURE&#8230;  Blogs like Gawker, BuzzFeed, and The Huffington Post drive the media agenda.   Bloggers are slaves to money, technology, and deadlines.  Manipulators wield these levers to shape everything you read, see, and hear-  online and off.Why am I giving away these secrets? Because I&#8217;m tired  of a world where blogs take indirect bribes, marketers help write the news,  reckless journalists spread lies, and no one is accountable for any of it. I&#8217;m  going to explain exactly how the media really works. What you choose to do with  this information is up to you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Trust Me, I&#8217;m Lying : Confessions of a Media Manipulator &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want. Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want.    </p>
<p>                    Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, product managers, entrepreneurs, and aspiring strategists simple to advanced methods that can be applied right away. You&#8217;ll gain valuable perspective through business cases and historical context. This second edition includes new real-world examples, updated techniques, and a chapter on conducting qualitative online user research.    </p>
<p>                    Define value propositions and validate target users through provisional personas and customer discovery techniques<br />
                    Explore marketplace opportunities by conducting competitive research and analysis<br />
                    Design experiments using rapid prototypes that are focused on the business model<br />
                    Conduct online user research to gain valuable insights quickly on any budget<br />
                    Test business ideas and validate marketing channels by running online advertising and landing page campaigns</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curate This : The Hands-On, How-To Guide To Content Curation &#8211; Steven Rosenbaum (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/curate-this-the-hands-on-how-to-guide-to-content-curation-steven-rosenbaum-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Library & Information Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Library, Archive & Information Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/curate-this-the-hands-on-how-to-guide-to-content-curation-steven-rosenbaum-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The concept of &#8220;Curation&#8221; has rapidly moved from museums to mainstream media. As the sheer volume of Tweets, Likes, Blogs, YouTube videos, and emails overwhelm the web, publishers and brands are increasingly being asked to provide a human face to content organization and editorial curation. With the right framework, curation can be a powerful tool [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/curate-this-the-hands-on-how-to-guide-to-content-curation-steven-rosenbaum-abridged/">Curate This : The Hands-On, How-To Guide To Content Curation &#8211; Steven Rosenbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The concept of &#8220;Curation&#8221; has rapidly moved from museums to mainstream media. As the sheer volume of Tweets, Likes, Blogs, YouTube videos, and emails overwhelm the web, publishers and brands are increasingly being asked to provide a human face to content organization and editorial curation. With the right framework, curation can be a powerful tool to help editorial meet new challenges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/curate-this-the-hands-on-how-to-guide-to-content-curation-steven-rosenbaum-abridged/">Curate This : The Hands-On, How-To Guide To Content Curation &#8211; Steven Rosenbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With roughly 95,000 blogs launched worldwide every 24 hours (BlogPulse), making a fledgling site stand out isn&#8217;t easy. This authoritative handbook gives creative hopefuls a leg up. Joy Cho, of the award-winning Oh Joy!, offers expert advice on starting and growing a blog, from design and finance to overcoming blogger&#8217;s block, attracting readers, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/">Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With roughly 95,000 blogs launched worldwide every 24 hours (BlogPulse), making a fledgling site stand out isn&#8217;t easy. This authoritative handbook gives creative hopefuls a leg up. Joy Cho, of the award-winning Oh Joy!, offers expert advice on starting and growing a blog, from design and finance to overcoming blogger&#8217;s block, attracting readers, and more. With a foreword from Grace Bonney of Design*Sponge plus expert interviews, this book will fine-tune what the next generation of bloggers shares with the world. Learn how to design your site, choose the right platform, attract a fan base, finance your blog, maintain work/life balance, manage comments, find content inspiration, overcome blogger&#8217;s block, choose the right ads, develop a voice, protect your work, create a media kit, leverage your social network, take better photographs, set up an affiliate program, partner with sponsors, build community, go full-time with your blog, and more!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/">Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose. This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose.    </p>
<p>                    This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is among mankind&#8217;s great masterpieces-a massive work of art. As an idea, it rivals monotheism. But its cultural potential and its societal impact often elude us. In this deep and thoughtful book, Virginia Heffernan reveals the logic and aesthetics behind the Internet, just as Susan Sontag did for photography and Marshall McLuhan did for television.    </p>
<p>                    Life online, in the highly visual, social, portable, and global incarnation rewards certain virtues. The new medium favors speed, accuracy, wit, prolificacy, and versatility, and its form and functions are changing how we perceive, experience, and understand the world. In &#8220;sumptuous writing, saturated with observations that are simultaneously personal, cultural, and strikingly original&#8221; (The New Republic), Heffernan presents &#8220;a revealing look at how the Internet continues to reshape our lives emotionally, visually, and culturally&#8221; (The Smithsonian Magazine). &#8220;Magic and Loss is an illuminating guide to the Internet&#8230;it is impossible to come away from this book without sharing some of Heffernan&#8217;s awe for this brave new world&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wikipedia @ 20 &#8211; Joseph M. Jr Reagle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wikipedia-20-joseph-m-jr-reagle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automation Of Library & Information Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Encyclopaedias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wikipedia-20-joseph-m-jr-reagle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wikipedia&#8217;s first twenty years: how what began as an experiment in collaboration became the world&#8217;s most popular reference work. We have been looking things up in Wikipedia for twenty years. What began almost by accident&#8211;a wiki attached to an nascent online encyclopedia&#8211;has become the world&#8217;s most popular reference work. Regarded at first as the scholarly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wikipedia-20-joseph-m-jr-reagle-abridged/">Wikipedia @ 20 &#8211; Joseph M. Jr Reagle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wikipedia&#8217;s first twenty years: how what began as an experiment in collaboration became the world&#8217;s most popular reference work.    </p>
<p>                    We have been looking things up in Wikipedia for twenty years. What began almost by accident&#8211;a wiki attached to an nascent online encyclopedia&#8211;has become the world&#8217;s most popular reference work. Regarded at first as the scholarly equivalent of a Big Mac, Wikipedia is now known for its reliable sourcing and as a bastion of (mostly) reasoned interaction. How has Wikipedia, built on a model of radical collaboration, remained true to its original mission of &#8220;free access to the sum of all human knowledge&#8221; when other tech phenomena have devolved into advertising platforms? In this book, scholars, activists, and volunteers reflect on Wikipedia&#8217;s first twenty years, revealing connections across disciplines and borders, languages and data, the professional and personal.    </p>
<p>                    The contributors consider Wikipedia&#8217;s history, the richness of the connections that underpin it, and its founding vision. Their essays look at, among other things, the shift from bewilderment to respect in press coverage of Wikipedia; Wikipedia as &#8220;the most important laboratory for social scientific and computing research in history&#8221;; and the acknowledgment that &#8220;free access&#8221; includes not just access to the material but freedom to contribute&#8211;that the summation of all human knowledge is biased by who documents it.    </p>
<p>                    Contributors    </p>
<p>                    Phoebe Ayers, Omer Benjakob, Yochai Benkler, William Beutler, Siko Bouterse, Rebecca Thorndike-Breeze, Amy Carleton, Robert Cummings, LiAnna L. Davis, Siân Evans, Heather Ford, Stephen Harrison, Heather Hart, Benjamin Mako Hill, Dariusz Jemielniak, Brian Keegan, Jackie Koerner, Alexandria Lockett, Jacqueline Mabey, Katherine Maher, Michael Mandiberg, Stephane Coillet-Matillon, Cecelia A. Musselman, Eliza Myrie, Jake Orlowitz, Ian A. Ramjohn, Joseph Reagle, Anasuya Sengupta, Aaron Shaw, Melissa Tamani, Jina Valentine, Matthew Vetter, Adele Vrana, Denny Vrandečic</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wikipedia-20-joseph-m-jr-reagle-abridged/">Wikipedia @ 20 &#8211; Joseph M. Jr Reagle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times &#8216;Best Thing I Read This Year&#8217; LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD Google. Amazon. Facebook. The modern world is defined by vast digital monopolies turning ever-larger profits. Those of us who consume the content that feeds them are farmed for the purposes of being sold ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/">Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times &#8216;Best Thing I Read This Year&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD    </p>
<p>                    Google. Amazon. Facebook. The modern world is defined by vast digital monopolies turning ever-larger profits. Those of us who consume the content that feeds them are farmed for the purposes of being sold ever more products and advertising. Those that create the content &#8211; the artists, writers and musicians &#8211; are finding they can no longer survive in this unforgiving economic landscape.     </p>
<p>                     But it didn&#8217;t have to be this way.     </p>
<p>                     In Move Fast and Break Things, Jonathan Taplin offers a succinct and powerful history of how online life began to be shaped around the values of the entrepreneurs like Peter Thiel and Larry Page who founded these all-powerful companies. Their unprecedented growth came at the heavy cost of tolerating piracy of books, music and film, while at the same time promoting opaque business practices and subordinating the privacy of individual users to create the surveillance marketing monoculture in which we now live.    </p>
<p>                    It is the story of a massive reallocation of revenue in which $50 billion a year has moved from the creators and owners of content to the monopoly platforms. With this reallocation of money comes a shift in power. Google, Facebook and Amazon now enjoy political power on par with Big Oil and Big Pharma, which in part explains how such a tremendous shift in revenues from creators to platforms could have been achieved and why it has gone unchallenged for so long.    </p>
<p>                    And if you think that&#8217;s got nothing to do with you, their next move is to come after your jobs.     </p>
<p>                    Move Fast and Break Things is a call to arms, to say that is enough is enough and to demand that we do everything in our power to create a different future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/">Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award! There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life. In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award!<br />
                    There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life.<br />
                    In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest spam and hacker operations targeting Americans and their bank accounts. Tracing the rise, fall, and alarming resurrection of the digital mafia behind the two largest spam pharmacies-and countless viruses, phishing, and spyware attacks-he delivers the first definitive narrative of the global spam problem and its threat to consumers everywhere.<br />
                    Blending cutting-edge research, investigative reporting, and firsthand interviews, this terrifying true story reveals how we unwittingly invite these digital thieves into our lives every day. From unassuming computer programmers right next door to digital mobsters like &#8220;Cosma&#8221;-who unleashed a massive malware attack that has stolen thousands of Americans&#8217; logins and passwords-Krebs uncovers the shocking lengths to which these people will go to profit from our data and our wallets.<br />
                    Not only are hundreds of thousands of Americans exposing themselves to fraud and dangerously toxic products from rogue online pharmacies, but even those who never open junk messages are at risk. As Krebs notes, spammers can-and do-hack into accounts through these emails, harvest personal information like usernames and passwords, and sell them on the digital black market. The fallout from this global epidemic doesn&#8217;t just cost consumers and companies billions, it costs lives too.<br />
                    Fast-paced and utterly gripping, Spam Nation ultimately proposes concrete solutions for protecting ourselves online and stemming this tidal wave of cybercrime-before it&#8217;s too late.<br />
                    &#8220;Krebs&#8217;s talent for exposing the weaknesses in online security has earned him respect in the IT business and loathing among cybercriminals&#8230; His track record of scoops&#8230;has helped him become the rare blogger who supports himself on the strength of his reputation for hard-nosed reporting.&#8221; -Bloomberg Businessweek</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breakpoint : Why the Web Will Implode, Search Will be Obsolete, and Everything Else You Need to Know About Technology is in Your Brain &#8211; Robert David Grant, Jeff Stibel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller USA Today Bestseller We are living in a world in which cows send texts to farmers when they&#8217;re in heat, where the most valuable real estate in New York City houses computers, not people, and some of humanity&#8217;s greatest works are created by crowds, not individuals. We are in the midst [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/">Breakpoint : Why the Web Will Implode, Search Will be Obsolete, and Everything Else You Need to Know About Technology is in Your Brain &#8211; Robert David Grant, Jeff Stibel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    USA Today Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    We are living in a world in which cows send texts to farmers when they&#8217;re in heat, where the most valuable real estate in New York City houses computers, not people, and some of humanity&#8217;s greatest works are created by crowds, not individuals.     </p>
<p>                    We are in the midst of a networking revolution&#8211;set to transform the way we access the world&#8217;s information and the way we connect with one another. Studying biological systems is perhaps the best way to understand such networks, and nature has a lesson for us if we care to listen: bigger is rarely better in the long run. The deadliest creature is the mosquito, not the lion. It is the quality of a network that is important for survival, not the size, and all networks&#8211;the human brain, Facebook, Google, even the internet itself&#8211;eventually reach a breakpoint and collapse. That&#8217;s the bad news. The good news is that reaching a breakpoint can be a step forward, allowing a network to substitute quality for quantity.     </p>
<p>                    In Breakpoint, brain scientist and entrepreneur Jeff Stibel takes readers to the intersection of the brain, biology, and technology. He shows how exceptional companies are using their understanding of the internet&#8217;s brain-like powers to create a competitive advantage by building more effective websites, utilizing cloud computing, engaging social media, monetizing effectively, and leveraging a collective consciousness. Indeed, the result of these technologies is a more tightly connected world with capabilities far beyond the sum of our individual minds. Breakpoint offers a fresh and exciting perspective about the future of technology and its effects on all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/">Breakpoint : Why the Web Will Implode, Search Will be Obsolete, and Everything Else You Need to Know About Technology is in Your Brain &#8211; Robert David Grant, Jeff Stibel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fanatical Prospecting : The Ultimate Guide to Opening Sales Conversations and Filling the Pipeline by Leveraging Social Selling, Telephone, Email, Text, and Cold Calling &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword by Mike Weinberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ditch the failed sales tactics, fill your pipeline, and crush your number Fanatical Prospecting gives salespeople, sales leaders, entrepreneurs, and executives a practical, eye-opening guide that clearly explains the why and how behind the most important activity in sales and business development prospecting. The brutal fact is the number one reason for failure in sales [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/">Fanatical Prospecting : The Ultimate Guide to Opening Sales Conversations and Filling the Pipeline by Leveraging Social Selling, Telephone, Email, Text, and Cold Calling &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword by Mike Weinberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ditch the failed sales tactics, fill your pipeline, and crush your number  Fanatical Prospecting gives salespeople, sales leaders, entrepreneurs, and executives a practical, eye-opening guide that clearly explains the why and how behind the most important activity in sales and business development prospecting.  The brutal fact is the number one reason for failure in sales is an empty pipe and the root cause of an empty pipeline is the failure to consistently prospect. By ignoring the muscle of prospecting, many otherwise competent salespeople and sales organizations consistently underperform. Step by step, Jeb Blount outlines his innovative approach to prospecting that works for real people, in the real world, with real prospects. Learn how to keep the pipeline full of qualified opportunities and avoid debilitating sales slumps by leveraging a balanced prospecting methodology across multiple prospecting channels. This book reveals the secrets, techniques, and tips of top earners.<br />
                    You ll learn: * Why the 30-Day Rule is critical for keeping the pipeline full * Why understanding the Law of Replacement is the key to avoiding sales slumps * How to leverage the Law of Familiarity to reduce prospecting friction and avoid rejection * The 5 C s of Social Selling and how to use them to get prospects to call you * How to use the simple 5 Step Telephone Framework to get more appointments fast * How to double call backs with a powerful voice mail technique * How to leverage the powerful 4 Step Email Prospecting Framework to create emails that compel prospects to respond * How to get text working for you with the 7 Step Text Message Prospecting Framework * And there is so much more! Fanatical Prospecting is filled with the high-powered strategies, techniques, and tools you need to fill your pipeline with high quality opportunities. In the most comprehensive book ever written about sales prospecting, Jeb Blount reveals the real secret to improving sales productivity and growing your income fast. You ll gain the power to blow through resistance and objections, gain more appointments, start more sales conversations, and close more sales.<br />
                    Break free from the fear and frustration that is holding you and your team back from effective and consistent prospecting. It&#8217;s time to get off the feast or famine sales roller-coaster for good!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/">Fanatical Prospecting : The Ultimate Guide to Opening Sales Conversations and Filling the Pipeline by Leveraging Social Selling, Telephone, Email, Text, and Cold Calling &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword by Mike Weinberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing, insider&#8217;s account of how a teacher built one of the world&#8217;s most valuable companies-rivaling Walmart and Amazon-and forever reshaped the global economy In just a decade and a half, Jack Ma, a man from modest beginnings who started out as an English teacher, founded Alibaba and built it into one of the world&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/">Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing, insider&#8217;s account of how a teacher built one of the world&#8217;s most valuable companies-rivaling Walmart and Amazon-and forever reshaped the global economy  In just a decade and a half, Jack Ma, a man from modest beginnings who started out as an English teacher, founded Alibaba and built it into one of the world&#8217;s largest companies, an e-commerce empire on which hundreds of millions of Chinese consumers depend. In 2014, Alibaba&#8217;s $25 billion IPO was the largest global IPO in history. A Rockefeller of his time, who is courted by CEOs and presidents around the world, Jack is an icon for China&#8217;s booming private sector and the gatekeeper to hundreds of millions of middle-class consumers. Duncan Clark first met Jack in 1999 in the small apartment where Jack founded Alibaba. Granted unprecedented access to a wealth of new material, including exclusive interviews, Clark draws on his own experience as an early adviser to Alibaba as well as his two decades in China chronicling the Internet&#8217;s impact on the country to create an authoritative, compelling narrative account of Alibaba&#8217;s rise.<br />
                    How did Jack overcome his humble origins and early failures to achieve massive success with Alibaba? How did he outsmart rival entrepreneurs from both China and Silicon Valley? Can Alibaba maintain its 80 percent market share? As it forges ahead into finance and entertainment, are there limits to Alibaba&#8217;s ambitions? How does the Chinese government view its rise? Will Alibaba expand farther overseas, including into the United States?  Clark tells Alibaba&#8217;s tale in the context of China&#8217;s momentous economic and social changes, illuminating an unlikely corporate titan as never before.  Advance Praise For Alibaba  &#8220;Anybody who thinks the Chinese just copy or steal technology from the West should read this book and think again. Jack Ma is part Bill Gates, part Steve Jobs, part Larry Page, part Sergey Brin, and part Mark Zuckerberg, all rolled into one.&#8221;-Sir Martin Sorrell, CEO of WPP &#8220;Duncan Clark gets into the heart and soul of Alibaba and its founder, Jack Ma, who deftly maneuvered through the discontinuities and barriers in China to create one of the greatest companies in the world. China has thrived under the leadership of Jack Ma.<br />
                    This book is a must-read for anyone who wants to understand the present China and the heartbeat of a great entrepreneur.&#8221;-Tim Draper, founder of Draper Associates, DFJ, and Draper University  &#8220;This book provides excellent insight into the world of Jack Ma, perhaps the most famous of the leaders of the new economy in China. Duncan Clark is a real China &#8216;Old Hand,&#8217; unique in his knowledge of the Jack Ma generation. This book is definitely on the short list for those who wish to understand the Chinese economy today.&#8221;-Ken Wilcox, Chairman Emeritus, Silicon Valley Bank</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/">Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disrupted : Ludicrous Misadventures in the Tech Start-up Bubble &#8211; Dan Lyons (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dan Lyons was Technology Editor at Newsweek Magazine for years, a magazine writer at the top of his profession. One Friday morning he received a phone call: his job no longer existed. Fifty years old and with a wife and two young kids, Dan was unemployed and facing financial oblivion. Then an idea hit. Dan [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/">Disrupted : Ludicrous Misadventures in the Tech Start-up Bubble &#8211; Dan Lyons (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dan Lyons was Technology Editor at Newsweek Magazine for years, a magazine writer at the top of his profession. One Friday morning he received a phone call: his job no longer existed. Fifty years old and with a wife and two young kids, Dan was unemployed and facing financial oblivion. Then an idea hit. Dan had long reported on Silicon Valley and the tech explosion. Why not join it? HubSpot, a Boston start-up, was flush with $100 million in venture capital. They offered Dan a pile of stock options for the nebulous role of &#8220;marketing fellow.&#8221; What could possibly go wrong?     </p>
<p>                     What follows is a hilarious and excoriating account of Dan&#8217;s time at the start-up and a revealing window onto the dysfunctional culture that prevails in a world flush with cash and devoid of experience. Filled with stories of meaningless jargon, teddy bears at meetings, push-up competitions and all-night parties, this uproarious tale is also a trenchant analysis of the dysfunctional start-up world, a de facto conspiracy between those who start companies and those who fund them. It is a world where bad ideas are rewarded with hefty investments, where companies blow money lavishing perks on their post-collegiate workforces, and where everybody is trying to hang on just long enough to cash out with a fortune.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/">Disrupted : Ludicrous Misadventures in the Tech Start-up Bubble &#8211; Dan Lyons (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trust Agents : Using the Web to Build Influence, Improve Reputation, and Earn Trust &#8211; Chris Brogan, Julien Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trust-agents-using-the-web-to-build-influence-improve-reputation-and-earn-trust-chris-brogan-julien-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trust-agents-using-the-web-to-build-influence-improve-reputation-and-earn-trust-chris-brogan-julien-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times and Wall Street Journal bestseller-now in a new, updated paperback edition Today&#8217;s online influencers are Web natives who trade in trust, reputation, and relationships, using social media to accrue the influence that builds up or brings down businesses online. In Trust Agents, two social media veterans show you how to tap [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-agents-using-the-web-to-build-influence-improve-reputation-and-earn-trust-chris-brogan-julien-smith-abridged/">Trust Agents : Using the Web to Build Influence, Improve Reputation, and Earn Trust &#8211; Chris Brogan, Julien Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times and Wall Street Journal bestseller-now in a new, updated paperback edition  Today&#8217;s online influencers are Web natives who trade in trust, reputation, and relationships, using social media to accrue the influence that builds up or brings down businesses online. In Trust Agents, two social media veterans show you how to tap into the power of social networks to build your brand&#8217;s influence, reputation, and, of course, profits.  In this revised paperback version, learn how businesses are using the latest online social tools to build networks of influence and how you can use those networks to positively impact your business. Combining high-level theory and practical actions, this guide delivers actionable steps and case studies that show how social media can positively impact your business.<br />
                    * New edition features specific first moves for entering social media for small businesses, educators, travel and hospitality enterprises, nonprofit organizations, and corporations * Authors both have a major presence on the social Web as well as years of online marketing and new media experience If you want your business to succeed, don&#8217;t sit on the sidelines while new markets and channels grow. Instead, use the Web to build trust with your consumers using  Trust Agents.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-agents-using-the-web-to-build-influence-improve-reputation-and-earn-trust-chris-brogan-julien-smith-abridged/">Trust Agents : Using the Web to Build Influence, Improve Reputation, and Earn Trust &#8211; Chris Brogan, Julien Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets. Welcome to 2011. Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to 2011.    </p>
<p>                    Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers are following your every click. Your computer monitor is becoming a one-way mirror, reflecting your interests and reinforcing your prejudices.    </p>
<p>                    The internet is no longer a free, independent space. It is commercially controlled and ever more personalised. The Filter Bubble reveals how this hidden web is starting to control our lives &#8211; and shows what we can do about it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A gripping read&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Originals Reddit hails itself as &#8216;the front page of the Internet&#8217;. It&#8217;s the sixth most-visited website in the world &#8211; and yet, millions have no idea what it is. They should be paying attention. This definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit is perfect for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/">We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A gripping read&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    Reddit hails itself as &#8216;the front page of the Internet&#8217;. It&#8217;s the sixth most-visited website in the world &#8211; and yet, millions have no idea what it is. They should be paying attention.    </p>
<p>                    This definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit is perfect for readers of The Everything Store, Googled and The Facebook Effect.    </p>
<p>                    We Are the Nerds takes readers inside this captivating, maddening enterprise, whose army of obsessed users have been credited with everything from solving crimes and spurring millions in charitable donations to seeding alt-right fury and even landing Donald Trump in the White House. Reddit has become a mirror of the Internet itself: It has dark trenches, shiny memes, malicious trolls, and a heart-warming ability to connect people across cultures, oceans, and ideological divides.    </p>
<p>                    This is the gripping story of how Reddit&#8217;s founders, Steve Huffman and Alexis Ohanian, transformed themselves from student video-gamers into Silicon Valley millionaires as they turned their creation into an icon of the digital age. But the journey was often fraught. Reporting on Reddit for more than six years, conducting hundreds of interviews and gaining exclusive access to its founders, Christine Lagorio-Chafkin has written the definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit. Packed with revelatory details about its biggest triumphs and controversies, this inside look at Reddit includes fresh insights on the relationship between Huffman and Ohanian, staff turmoil, the tragic life of Aaron Swartz, and Reddit&#8217;s struggle to become profitable.    </p>
<p>                    In a time when we are increasingly concerned about privacy and manipulation on social platforms, We Are the Nerds reveals Reddit&#8217;s central role in the dissemination of culture and information in history&#8217;s first fully digital century. Rigorously reported and highly entertaining, We Are the Nerds explores how this unique platform has changed the way we all communicate today.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR THE BOOK:    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Incisive, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Emily Chang, bestselling author of Brotopia    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A triumph &#8211; a business book that reads like a page-turning novel&#8217; &#8211; James Ledbetter, author of One Nation Under Gold    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The best, grittiest, most accurate book yet about what it&#8217;s like to build a startup and a community from scratch&#8217; &#8211; John Zeratsky, bestselling author of Sprint and Make Time    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A gripping, entertaining book that is a must-read for every entrepreneur&#8217; &#8211; Daymond John, bestselling author of Rise and Grind    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Too many books on tech feel like they have been Googled together; Lagorio-Chafkin&#8217;s is rich in original reportage&#8217; &#8211; TLS</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/">We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why the troll problem is actually a culture problem: how online trolling fits comfortably within today&#8217;s media landscape. Internet trolls live to upset as many people as possible, using all the technical and psychological tools at their disposal. They gleefully whip the media into a frenzy over a fake teen drug crisis; they post offensive [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/">This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why the troll problem is actually a culture problem: how online trolling fits comfortably within today&#8217;s media landscape.    </p>
<p>                    Internet trolls live to upset as many people as possible, using all the technical and psychological tools at their disposal. They gleefully whip the media into a frenzy over a fake teen drug crisis; they post offensive messages on Facebook memorial pages, traumatizing grief-stricken friends and family; they use unabashedly racist language and images. They take pleasure in ruining a complete stranger&#8217;s day and find amusement in their victim&#8217;s anguish. In short, trolling is the obstacle to a kinder, gentler Internet. To quote a famous Internet meme, trolling is why we can&#8217;t have nice things online. Or at least that&#8217;s what we have been led to believe. In this provocative book, Whitney Phillips argues that trolling, widely condemned as obscene and deviant, actually fits comfortably within the contemporary media landscape. Trolling may be obscene, but, Phillips argues, it isn&#8217;t all that deviant. Trolls&#8217; actions are born of and fueled by culturally sanctioned impulses&#8211;which are just as damaging as the trolls&#8217; most disruptive behaviors.     </p>
<p>                    Phillips describes, for example, the relationship between trolling and sensationalist corporate media&#8211;pointing out that for trolls, exploitation is a leisure activity; for media, it&#8217;s a business strategy. She shows how trolls, &#8220;the grimacing poster children for a socially networked world,&#8221; align with social media. And she documents how trolls, in addition to parroting media tropes, also offer a grotesque pantomime of dominant cultural tropes, including gendered notions of dominance and success and an ideology of entitlement. We don&#8217;t just have a trolling problem, Phillips argues; we have a culture problem. This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things isn&#8217;t only about trolls; it&#8217;s about a culture in which trolls thrive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/">This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Copyright Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Filled with wisdom and thought experiments and things that will mess with your mind.&#8221; &#8212; Neil Gaiman, author of The Graveyard Book and American Gods In sharply argued, fast-moving chapters, Cory Doctorow&#8217;s Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free takes on the state of copyright and creative success in the digital age. Can small artists still [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/">Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Filled with wisdom and thought experiments and things that will mess with your mind.&#8221; &#8212; Neil Gaiman, author of The Graveyard Book and American Gods     </p>
<p>                    In sharply argued, fast-moving chapters, Cory Doctorow&#8217;s Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free takes on the state of copyright and creative success in the digital age. Can small artists still thrive in the Internet era? Can giant record labels avoid alienating their audiences? This is a book about the pitfalls, and the opportunities, creative industries (and individuals) are confronting today&#8211;about how the old models have failed or found new footing, and about what might soon replace them. An essential read for anyone with a stake in the future of the arts, Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free offers a vivid guide to the ways creativity and the Internet interact today, and to what might be coming next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/">Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Success Secrets of Social Media Marketing Superstars &#8211; Entrepreneur Press, Mitch Meyerson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/success-secrets-of-social-media-marketing-superstars-entrepreneur-press-mitch-meyerson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/success-secrets-of-social-media-marketing-superstars-entrepreneur-press-mitch-meyerson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;An amazing book &#8211; top social media professionals provide the &#8216;inside&#8217; tips on how they stay on top and stay organized. Filled with specific tricks, tips and strategies to cut the clutter and build your business, you really want to read this one.&#8221; &#8211;Dave Evans, Author of Social Media Marketing: An Hour a DayRevelations from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-secrets-of-social-media-marketing-superstars-entrepreneur-press-mitch-meyerson-abridged/">Success Secrets of Social Media Marketing Superstars &#8211; Entrepreneur Press, Mitch Meyerson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;An amazing book &#8211; top social media professionals provide the &#8216;inside&#8217; tips on how they stay on top and stay organized.  Filled with specific tricks, tips and strategies to cut the clutter and build your business, you really want to read this one.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Dave Evans, Author of Social Media Marketing: An Hour a DayRevelations from Top Social Media Revolution Leaders<br />
                    Online marketing expert Mitch Meyerson presents you with an unmatched advantage into the world of social media &#8211; the priceless secrets, strategies, tactics and insights of more than 20 of today&#8217;s social media elite. Handpicked to cover almost every aspect of social media marketing, Meyerson and this distinguished team of experts open their playbooks and teach you how to create effective social media campaigns to cut through the clutter, reach out to millions and grow your business.Features:    </p>
<p>                    Proven tips and tactics from 20+ top social media marketersThe biggest mistakes businesses make with social media and how to fix themActionable plans for all areas including social networks, blogs, web TV and mobile marketingReal-world case studies, best practices and proven techniques from the expertsDetailed list of resources<br />
                    Contributions from World-Class Social Media Experts:    </p>
<p>                    Keith Ferrazi &#038; Tahl Raz: Relationship StrategyBrian Clark: Psychology of Social MediaMitch Meyerson: Online MarketingAnn Handley: Creating ContentGary Vaynerchuk: Building Mega-FollowingsAndy Willbes: PersonalityChris Brogan: Building CommunitiesJoel Comm: Success QualitiesCraig Valentine: Communicate with ImpactStarr Hall: Building ProfitsDan Janal: PR StrategiesMichael Stelzner: Go ViralDenise Wakeman: Business BlogsMari Smith: FacebookDeborah Cole Micek: TwitterBarbara Rozgonyi: LinkedInJulie Perry: YouTubePaul Colligan: PodcastingChris Garrett: Social BookmarkingKim Dushinski: Mobile MarketingShama Kabani: Online VideoDave Evans: One Hour a Day</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-secrets-of-social-media-marketing-superstars-entrepreneur-press-mitch-meyerson-abridged/">Success Secrets of Social Media Marketing Superstars &#8211; Entrepreneur Press, Mitch Meyerson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
