<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Judaism: Life &amp; Practice Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/judaism-life-practice/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/judaism-life-practice/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Judaism: Life &amp; Practice Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/judaism-life-practice/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Thou Shall Prosper : Ten Commandments for Making Money &#8211; Rabbi Daniel Lapin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Judaism: Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to creating wealth-based on the established principles of ancient Jewish wisdom-made accessible to people of all backgrounds The ups and downs of the economy prove Rabbi Daniel Lapin&#8217;s famous principle that the more things change, the more we need to depend upon the things that never change. There&#8217;s no better source for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/">Thou Shall Prosper : Ten Commandments for Making Money &#8211; Rabbi Daniel Lapin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to creating wealth-based on the established principles of ancient Jewish wisdom-made accessible to people of all backgrounds  The ups and downs of the economy prove Rabbi Daniel Lapin&#8217;s famous principle that the more things change, the more we need to depend upon the things that never change. There&#8217;s no better source for both practical and spiritual financial wisdom than the time-tested knowledge found in the ancient Jewish faith and its culture. In the  Second Edition  of  Thou Shall Prosper,  Lapin offers a practical approach to creating wealth based on the established principles of ancient Jewish wisdom. This book details the ten permanent principles that never change, the ten commandments of making money if you will, and explores the economic and philosophic vision of business that has been part of Jewish culture for centuries. The book&#8217;s focus is on making accessible to individuals of all backgrounds, the timeless truths that Jews have used for centuries to excel in business.<br />
                    Outlines ten fundamental &#8220;commandments&#8221; relating to business and money  Includes insights that will increase your potential for creating wealth, no matter what your faith or background may be  Blends contemporary business stories and Lapin&#8217;s own business experiences with the wisdom of the Torah and Talmudic prescriptions This  Second Edition  provides new examples, especially of Internet related business opportunities. In addition, each chapter highlights specific action steps that can lead to wealth opportunities in both difficult economic times and periods of prosperity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/">Thou Shall Prosper : Ten Commandments for Making Money &#8211; Rabbi Daniel Lapin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
