<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Business Competition Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/business-competition/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/business-competition/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Business Competition Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/business-competition/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Growth IQ : Master the 10 Paths to Grow Your Business &#8211; Tiffani Bova (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/growth-iq-master-the-10-paths-to-grow-your-business-tiffani-bova-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/growth-iq-master-the-10-paths-to-grow-your-business-tiffani-bova-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A worthy successor to Michael Porter, Bova&#8217;s book is that rare gift: it opens doors for new ideas and new actions. No glib answers here, simply hard-won wisdom that will provoke big changes for organizations large and small.&#8217; &#8211; Seth Godin, author of Linchpin The Wall Street Journal Top Ten Bestseller: The 10 strategies to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/growth-iq-master-the-10-paths-to-grow-your-business-tiffani-bova-abridged/">Growth IQ : Master the 10 Paths to Grow Your Business &#8211; Tiffani Bova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A worthy successor to Michael Porter, Bova&#8217;s book is that rare gift: it opens doors for new ideas and new actions. No glib answers here, simply hard-won wisdom that will provoke big changes for organizations large and small.&#8217; &#8211; Seth Godin, author of Linchpin    </p>
<p>                    The Wall Street Journal Top Ten Bestseller: The 10 strategies to sustainable growth, based on a purpose-led culture for organizations large and small.    </p>
<p>                    Tiffani Bova, the Growth and Innovation Evangelist at Salesforce, draws on her expertise as a consultant and practitioner to devise a new framework for business leaders looking to pursue growth. We&#8217;re witnessing an age of endless customization, and growth strategy is no exception. There&#8217;s no one size fits all strategy; a winning strategy for one business may spell doom for another.    </p>
<p>                    In Growth IQ, Bova determines that there are ten simple &#8211; but easily misunderstood &#8211; growth paths, and explains how companies can get a handle on their particular business context, and use it to determine the right combination and sequence of growth paths to take them into the future.     </p>
<p>                    Bova breaks down the strategies deployed by a wide range of companies to show you how:    </p>
<p>                      *  GE and John Deere have lasted over a century and continue to thrive by combining their strategy of innovative product development with a renewed focus on R&#038;D and customer experience.<br />
                      *  Marvel transformed from a struggling comic book publisher to a global entertainment behemoth by realigning their market penetration strategy to focus on comic book characters, instead of just comic books.<br />
                      *  Gateway&#8217;s attempt at market expansion into brick-and-mortar retail led to its failure, while the same move by Apple has accelerated its growth.    </p>
<p>                    Whether your company is on a growth spurt, in a worrying stall, or showing signs of decline, Growth IQ is your map to charting the course of your company&#8217;s future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/growth-iq-master-the-10-paths-to-grow-your-business-tiffani-bova-abridged/">Growth IQ : Master the 10 Paths to Grow Your Business &#8211; Tiffani Bova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gamification for Business : Why Innovators and Changemakers use Games to break down Silos, Drive Engagement and Build Trust &#8211; Sune Gudiksen, Jake Inlove (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/gamification-for-business-why-innovators-and-changemakers-use-games-to-break-down-silos-drive-engagement-and-build-trust-sune-gudiksen-jake-inlove-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/gamification-for-business-why-innovators-and-changemakers-use-games-to-break-down-silos-drive-engagement-and-build-trust-sune-gudiksen-jake-inlove-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gamification for Business shows how games and game-based design can be used to effectively tackle business challenges and improve organizational performance. From siloed working and information overload to the clash between ongoing operations and innovation, this book shows how to identify what type of game is best suited to each business issue. With guidance on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gamification-for-business-why-innovators-and-changemakers-use-games-to-break-down-silos-drive-engagement-and-build-trust-sune-gudiksen-jake-inlove-abridged/">Gamification for Business : Why Innovators and Changemakers use Games to break down Silos, Drive Engagement and Build Trust &#8211; Sune Gudiksen, Jake Inlove (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gamification for Business shows how games and game-based design can be used to effectively tackle business challenges and improve organizational performance. From siloed working and information overload to the clash between ongoing operations and innovation, this book shows how to identify what type of game is best suited to each business issue. With guidance on online games, simulations, event-based games and gamified training, this book ensures that business leaders and senior decision makers feel confident in their ability to assess the opportunities of each type of gamification for their business.     </p>
<p>                    Including case studies from more than 20 organizations who have implemented a game-based solution, this book outlines the business issue in each company and the aim of the game, the impact the game had and key learning points to help readers implement a similar type of game in their own business. Based on extensive research into the effectiveness of games and real-world examples from companies who have experienced the benefits of serious games and design thinking, Gamification for Business is essential reading for all business professionals looking to improve employee motivation, boost engagement, create a cohesive team environment and facilitate innovation in their company for improved business performance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gamification-for-business-why-innovators-and-changemakers-use-games-to-break-down-silos-drive-engagement-and-build-trust-sune-gudiksen-jake-inlove-abridged/">Gamification for Business : Why Innovators and Changemakers use Games to break down Silos, Drive Engagement and Build Trust &#8211; Sune Gudiksen, Jake Inlove (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pricing for Profit : How to Develop a Powerful Pricing Strategy for Your Business &#8211; Peter Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Price is the most significant factor affecting the profitability of every business, profit centre or department. When the pressure is on to perform or grow, your instinct may be to discount, undercut your competitors, cut costs and promote through price. Yet these are often the last things you should do. Pricing for Profit is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/">Pricing for Profit : How to Develop a Powerful Pricing Strategy for Your Business &#8211; Peter Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Price is the most significant factor affecting the profitability of every business, profit centre or department. When the pressure is on to perform or grow, your instinct may be to discount, undercut your competitors, cut costs and promote through price. Yet these are often the last things you should do. Pricing for Profit is the most practical guide on pricing available. Using a firm, profit-focused framework developed running real projects for real businesses, this book shows you how by getting your pricing structures right you can make a huge difference to your bottom line. It gives business owners, managers and leaders simple, achievable pricing strategies that will deliver sustainable business growth. Can you afford to leave money on the table? If not, Pricing for Profit is the guide for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/">Pricing for Profit : How to Develop a Powerful Pricing Strategy for Your Business &#8211; Peter Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In September 2014, a Chinese company that most Westerners had never heard of held the largest IPO in history &#8211; bigger than Google, Facebook and Twitter combined. Alibaba, now the world&#8217;s largest e-commerce company, mostly escaped Western notice for over ten years, while building a customer base larger than Amazon&#8217;s, and handling the bulk of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/">Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In September 2014, a Chinese company that most Westerners had never heard of held the largest IPO in history &#8211; bigger than Google, Facebook and Twitter combined. Alibaba, now the world&#8217;s largest e-commerce company, mostly escaped Western notice for over ten years, while building a customer base larger than Amazon&#8217;s, and handling the bulk of e-commerce transactions in China. How did it happen? And what was it like to be along for such a revolutionary ride?    </p>
<p>                    In Alibaba&#8217;s World, author Porter Erisman, one of Alibaba&#8217;s first Western employees, who helped spearhead its international expansion, shows how Jack Ma, a Chinese schoolteacher who twice failed his college entrance exams, rose from obscurity to found Alibaba and lead it from struggling startup to the world&#8217;s most dominant e-commerce player.     </p>
<p>                    Now, in the first English language account of Alibaba&#8217;s extraordinary success, Erisman shares stories of weathering the dotcom crash, facing down eBay and Google, negotiating with the unpredictable Chinese government, and enduring the misguided advice of foreign experts, all to build the behemoth that&#8217;s poised to sweep the ecommerce world today. And he analyzes Alibaba&#8217;s role as a harbinger of the new global business landscape &#8211; with its focus on the East rather than the West, emerging markets over developed ones, and the nimble entrepreneur over the industry titan. As we face this near future, the story of Alibaba &#8211; and its inevitable descendants &#8211; is both essential and instructive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/">Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Co-Opetition &#8211; Adam M. Brandenburger, Barry J. Nalebuff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/co-opetition-adam-m-brandenburger-barry-j-nalebuff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/co-opetition-adam-m-brandenburger-barry-j-nalebuff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now available in paperback, with an all new Reader&#8217;s guide, The New York Times and Business Week bestseller Co-opetition revolutionized the game of business. With over 40,000 copies sold and now in its 9th printing, Co-opetition is a business strategy that goes beyond the old rules of competition and cooperation to combine the advantages of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/co-opetition-adam-m-brandenburger-barry-j-nalebuff-abridged/">Co-Opetition &#8211; Adam M. Brandenburger, Barry J. Nalebuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now available in paperback, with an all new Reader&#8217;s guide, The New York Times and Business Week bestseller Co-opetition revolutionized the game of business. With over 40,000 copies sold and now in its 9th printing, Co-opetition is a business strategy that goes beyond the old rules of competition and cooperation to combine the advantages of both. Co-opetition is a pioneering, high profit means of leveraging business relationships.<br />
                    Intel, Nintendo, American Express, NutraSweet, American Airlines, and dozens of other companies have been using the strategies of co-opetition to change the game of business to their benefit. Formulating strategies based on game theory, authors Brandenburger and Nalebuff created a book that&#8217;s insightful and instructive for managers eager to move their companies into a new mind set.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/co-opetition-adam-m-brandenburger-barry-j-nalebuff-abridged/">Co-Opetition &#8211; Adam M. Brandenburger, Barry J. Nalebuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Bang Disruption : Business Survival in the Age of Constant Innovation &#8211; Larry Downes, Paul Nunes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/big-bang-disruption-business-survival-in-the-age-of-constant-innovation-larry-downes-paul-nunes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/big-bang-disruption-business-survival-in-the-age-of-constant-innovation-larry-downes-paul-nunes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A stimulating read&#8230;carefully researched and accessibly written&#8230;the case studies on disruption alone are worth the cover price&#8217; -Financial Times &#8216;Everything you need from business school in one very direct book&#8217; -Dick Costolo, CEO, Twitter It used to take years for new products and services to dethrone industry leaders. Now any busi ness can be instantly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-bang-disruption-business-survival-in-the-age-of-constant-innovation-larry-downes-paul-nunes-abridged/">Big Bang Disruption : Business Survival in the Age of Constant Innovation &#8211; Larry Downes, Paul Nunes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A stimulating read&#8230;carefully researched and accessibly written&#8230;the case studies on disruption alone are worth the cover price&#8217; -Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Everything you need from business school in one very direct book&#8217; -Dick Costolo, CEO, Twitter    </p>
<p>                    It used to take years for new products and services to dethrone industry leaders. Now any busi ness can be instantly devastated by something better and cheaper. How can you protect yourself, and harness the power of Big Bang Disruption?    </p>
<p>                    No matter what your industry, start-ups can change the market before you even begin to grasp what&#8217;s happening. The good news is that any business can mas ter the strategy of the start-ups.    </p>
<p>                    In Big Bang Disruption, Larry Downes and Paul Nunes show you how to spot the next big thing &#8211; before the next start-up does. Based on extensive research by the Accenture Institute for High Performance and interviews from over 30 industries, this essential bookwill give you with the tools to take control of your future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-bang-disruption-business-survival-in-the-age-of-constant-innovation-larry-downes-paul-nunes-abridged/">Big Bang Disruption : Business Survival in the Age of Constant Innovation &#8211; Larry Downes, Paul Nunes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
