<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Corporate Governance &amp; Responsibilities Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/corporate-governance-responsibilities/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/corporate-governance-responsibilities/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Corporate Governance &amp; Responsibilities Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/corporate-governance-responsibilities/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Curse of Bigness : Antitrust in the New Gilded Age &#8211; Tim Wu (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Company, Commercial & Competition Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Competition Law / Antitrust Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law As It Applies To Other Professions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the man who coined the term net neutrality, comes a warning about the dangers of excessive corporate and industrial concentration for our economic and political future. We live in an age of extreme corporate concentration, in which global industries are controlled by just a few giant firms&#8211;big banks, big pharma, and big tech, just [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/">The Curse of Bigness : Antitrust in the New Gilded Age &#8211; Tim Wu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the man who coined the term net neutrality, comes a warning about the dangers of excessive corporate and industrial concentration for our economic and political future.     </p>
<p>                    We live in an age of extreme corporate concentration, in which global industries are controlled by just a few giant firms&#8211;big banks, big pharma, and big tech, just to name a few. But concern over what Louis Brandeis called the curse of bigness can no longer remain the province of specialist lawyers and economists, for it has spilled over into policy and politics, even threatening democracy itself. History suggests that tolerance of inequality and failing to control excessive corporate power may prompt the rise of populism, nationalism, extremist politicians, and fascist regimes. In short, as Wu warns, we are in grave danger of repeating the signature errors of the twentieth century.     </p>
<p>                    In The Curse of Bigness, Tim Wu, special assistant to President Biden for technology and competition policy, explains how figures like Brandeis and Theodore Roosevelt first confronted the democratic threats posed by the great trusts of the Gilded Age&#8211;but the lessons of the Progressive Era were forgotten in the last 40 years. He calls for recovering the lost tenets of the trustbusting age as part of a broader revival of American progressive ideas as we confront the fallout of persistent and extreme economic inequality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/">The Curse of Bigness : Antitrust in the New Gilded Age &#8211; Tim Wu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Difference Makers &#8211; Dr Nicky Howe, Alicia Curtis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/difference-makers-dr-nicky-howe-alicia-curtis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Boards & Directors: Role & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/difference-makers-dr-nicky-howe-alicia-curtis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Outstanding insight into how to effectively embrace diversity &#8230; a roadmap for creating better organisations, better companies and a better society.&#8217; &#8211; Rhys Williams, 2015 Young West Australian of the Year &#8216;&#8230;includes practical tools, checklists and activities for both the aspiring and experienced director.&#8217; &#8211; Angie Paskevicius, CEO, Holyoake &#8216;If you seriously want to make [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/difference-makers-dr-nicky-howe-alicia-curtis-abridged/">Difference Makers &#8211; Dr Nicky Howe, Alicia Curtis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Outstanding insight into how to effectively embrace diversity &#8230; a roadmap for creating better organisations, better companies and a better society.&#8217; &#8211; Rhys Williams, 2015 Young West Australian of the Year &#8216;&#8230;includes practical tools, checklists and activities for both the aspiring and experienced director.&#8217; &#8211; Angie Paskevicius, CEO, Holyoake &#8216;If you seriously want to make a difference &#8211; you must read Difference Makers.&#8217; &#8211; David Koutsoukis, founder of the Exceptional Teams Academy &#8216;I recommend this book to all those who believe we deserve better organisations.&#8217; &#8211; Rabia Siddique, international humanitarian, author and advocate &#8216;&#8230;a sound rationale highlighting the importance of diversity in achieving good governance &#8230; a nuanced and thoughtful resource designed to help meet the challenge.&#8217; &#8211; Professor David Gilchrist, director, Curtin University Dr Nicky Howe is a CEO and leadership and management expert, with a doctorate of business administration from the University of Western Australia, and postgraduate qualification in management from Flinders University. Nicky has a passion for building the capacity of individuals, organisations and communities. She is author of Better Relationships with Those You Lead, a handbook of practical skills and strategies for leaders and managers. Alicia Curtis is one of Western Australia&#8217;s most inspiring young social and business entrepreneurs, an award-winning speaker and leadership facilitator. Alicia established Alyceum in 2002 developing innovative transformational leadership programs. Alicia has a master&#8217;s degree in business leadership and was named one of the Australian Financial Review&#8217;s 100 Women of Influence in 2014. Together Nicky and Alicia founded the Engaging Young Leaders on Aged Care and Community Boards governance program, and as a consequence they were driven to share their findings and experiences in this fascinating book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/difference-makers-dr-nicky-howe-alicia-curtis-abridged/">Difference Makers &#8211; Dr Nicky Howe, Alicia Curtis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Broadcasting Happinesss : The Science of Igniting and Sustaining Positive Change &#8211; Michelle Gielan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/broadcasting-happinesss-the-science-of-igniting-and-sustaining-positive-change-michelle-gielan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/broadcasting-happinesss-the-science-of-igniting-and-sustaining-positive-change-michelle-gielan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Broadcasting Happiness will &#8220;inspire you and change your life.&#8221; &#8211;Parade Magazine We are all broadcasters. As managers, colleagues, parents and friends, we are constantly transmitting information to the people around us, and the messages we choose to broadcast create success or hold us back. What&#8217;s your broadcast? New research from the fields of positive psychology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/broadcasting-happinesss-the-science-of-igniting-and-sustaining-positive-change-michelle-gielan-abridged/">Broadcasting Happinesss : The Science of Igniting and Sustaining Positive Change &#8211; Michelle Gielan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Broadcasting Happiness will &#8220;inspire you and change your life.&#8221; &#8211;Parade Magazine  We are all broadcasters. As managers, colleagues, parents and friends, we are constantly transmitting information to the people around us, and the messages we choose to broadcast create success or hold us back.  What&#8217;s your broadcast?  New research from the fields of positive psychology and neuroscience shows that small shifts in the way we communicate can create big ripple effects on business and educational outcomes, including 31 percent higher productivity, 25 percent better performance ratings, 37 percent higher sales, and 23 percent lower levels of stress.  In Broadcasting Happiness, Michelle Gielan, former national CBS News anchor turned positive psychology researcher, shows you how changing your broadcast changes your power by sharing jaw-dropping stories and incredible research.  Learn Michelle&#8217;s simple research-based communication habits that have been featured in her PBS program Inspire Happiness and Oprah&#8217;s 21 Days to Happiness class.<br />
                    Broadcasting Happiness will help you:  &#8211; Inoculate your brain against stress and negativity by fact-checking challenges &#8211; Drive success by leading a conversation or communication with positivity &#8211; Rewrite debilitating thought patterns and turn them into fuel for resilience and growth &#8211; Deal with negative people in a way that lessens their power &#8211; Share bad news more effectively to increase future social capital &#8211; Create and sustain a positive culture at work or home by creating contagious optimism &#8211; Help the people you care about most move from negative to positive in seconds  Broadcasting Happiness showcases how real individuals and organizations have used these techniques to achieve results that include increasing revenues by hundreds of millions of dollars, raising a school district&#8217;s graduation rate by 45 percent, and shifting family gatherings from toxic to thriving.  Changing your broadcast can change your life, your success, and the lives of others around you. Broadcasting Happiness will show you how!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/broadcasting-happinesss-the-science-of-igniting-and-sustaining-positive-change-michelle-gielan-abridged/">Broadcasting Happinesss : The Science of Igniting and Sustaining Positive Change &#8211; Michelle Gielan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Berkshire Hathaway, the $300 billion conglomerate that Warren Buffett built, is among the world&#8217;s largest and most famous corporations. Yet, for all its power and celebrity, few people understand Berkshire, and many assume it cannot survive without Buffett. This book proves them wrong. In a comprehensive portrait of the corporate culture that unites Berkshire&#8217;s subsidiaries, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/">Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Berkshire Hathaway, the $300 billion conglomerate that Warren Buffett built, is among the world&#8217;s largest and most famous corporations. Yet, for all its power and celebrity, few people understand Berkshire, and many assume it cannot survive without Buffett. This book proves them wrong. In a comprehensive portrait of the corporate culture that unites Berkshire&#8217;s subsidiaries, Lawrence A. Cunningham unearths the traits that assure the conglomerate&#8217;s continued prosperity. Riveting stories of each subsidiary&#8217;s origins, triumphs, and journey to Berkshire reveal how managers generate economic value from intangibles like thrift, integrity, entrepreneurship, autonomy, and a sense of permanence. Rich with lessons for those wishing to profit from the Berkshire model, this engaging book is a valuable read for entrepreneurs, business owners, managers, family business members, and investors, and it is an important resource for scholars of corporate stewardship. General readers will enjoy learning how an iconoclastic businessman transformed a struggling textile company into a corporate legacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/">Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
