<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Films, Cinema Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/films-cinema/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/films-cinema/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Films, Cinema Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/films-cinema/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Princess Diarist &#8211; Carrie Fisher</title>
		<link>/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Carrie Fisher discovered the journals she kept during the filming of the first Star Wars movie, she was astonished to see what they had preserved &#8211; plaintive love poems, unbridled musings with youthful naivete, and a vulnerability that she barely recognized. Now her fame as an author, actress, and pop-culture icon is indisputable, but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/">The Princess Diarist &#8211; Carrie Fisher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Carrie Fisher discovered the journals she kept during the filming of the first Star Wars movie, she was astonished to see what they had preserved &#8211; plaintive love poems, unbridled musings with youthful naivete, and a vulnerability that she barely recognized. Now her fame as an author, actress, and pop-culture icon is indisputable, but in 1977, Carrie Fisher was just a teenager with an all-consuming crush on her co-star, Harrison Ford.<br />
                     With these excerpts from her handwritten notebooks, The Princess Diarist is Fisher&#8217;s intimate and revealing recollection of what happened on one of the most famous film sets of all time &#8211; and what developed behind the scenes.  Fisher also ponders the joys and insanity of celebrity, and the absurdity of a life spawned by Hollywood royalty, only to be surpassed by her own outer-space royalty. Laugh-out-loud hilarious and endlessly quotable, The Princess Diarist brims with the candour and introspection of a diary while offering shrewd insight into the type of stardom that few will ever experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/">The Princess Diarist &#8211; Carrie Fisher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN* A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood<br />
                    &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson<br />
                    &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson    </p>
<p>                    *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN*    </p>
<p>                    A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey that helped change the world.    </p>
<p>                    Hollywood was talking as never before. Kantor and Twohey outmanoeuvred Harvey Weinstein, his team of defenders and private investigators, convincing some of the most famous women in the world &#8211; and some unknown ones &#8211; to go on the record. Three years later, it helped lead to his conviction.    </p>
<p>                    This is how they did it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year. Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir. For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year.    </p>
<p>                                Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir.    </p>
<p>                              For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore has never been far from the spotlight &#8211; or the headlines.    </p>
<p>                              Even as Demi was becoming the highest paid actress in Hollywood, however, she was always outrunning her past, just one step ahead of the doubts and insecurities that defined her childhood. Throughout her rise to fame and during some of the most pivotal moments of her life, Demi battled addiction, body image issues, and childhood trauma that would follow her for years &#8211; all while juggling a skyrocketing career and at times negative public perception.  As her success grew, Demi found herself questioning if she belonged in Hollywood, if she was a good mother, a good actress &#8211; and, always, if she was simply good enough.    </p>
<p>                              As much as her story is about adversity, it is also about tremendous resilience. In this deeply candid and reflective memoir, Demi pulls back the curtain and opens up about her career and personal life &#8211; laying bare her tumultuous relationship with her mother, her marriages, her struggles balancing stardom with raising a family, and her journey toward open heartedness. Inside Outis a story of survival, success, and surrender &#8211; a wrenchingly honest portrayal of one woman&#8217;s at once ordinary and iconic life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life. Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life.    </p>
<p>                     Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a movie star. By the age of 21, he was living in Los Angeles and had been crowned Mr Universe. Within five years, he had learned English and become the greatest bodybuilder in the world. Within ten years, he had earned his college degree and was a millionaire from his business enterprises in real estate, landscaping and bodybuilding. He was also the winner of a Golden Globe Award for his debut as a dramatic actor in Stay Hungry.    </p>
<p>                     But that was only the beginning. The Terminator spawned numerous sequels and made him one of Hollywood&#8217;s biggest stars, as he had a series of hit films including Predator, Total Recall, True Lies and Twins. He married Maria Shriver, becoming part of the Kennedy clan, while going on to become the Republican governor of California, where he led the state through a budget crisis, natural disasters and political turmoil.     </p>
<p>                    It is the greatest immigrant success story of our time. His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. Until now, he has never told the full story of his life, in his own voice. Here is Arnold, with total recall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
