<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Geopolitics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/geopolitics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/geopolitics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Geopolitics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/geopolitics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond</title>
		<link>/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS </p>
<p>                    ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** </p>
<p>                    Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding of what makes civilizations rise and fall. Now, at a time when crises are erupting around the world, heexplores what makes certain nations resilient, and reveals the factors that influence how nations and individuals can respond to enormous challenges. </p>
<p>                    In a riveting journey into the recent past, he traces how six distinctive modern nations &#8211; Finland, Chile, Indonesia, Japan, Germany and Australia &#8211; have survived defining catastrophes, and identifies patterns in their recovery. Looking ahead, he investigates the risk that the United States and other countries, faced by grave threat, are set on a course towards catastrophe. </p>
<p>                    Adding a rich psychological dimension to the in-depth history, geography, biology and anthropology that underpin all of Diamond&#8217;s writing, Upheaval is epic in scope, but also his most personal book yet.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating &#8230; I finished the book even more optimistic about our ability to solve problems than I started&#8217; BILL GATES</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jared Diamond does it again: another rich, original and fascinating chapter in the human saga &#8211; with vital lessons for our difficult times&#8217; STEVEN PINKER</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU & European Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller** &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian What happens when you take on the European establishment? Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis. Varoufakis sparked one of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    What happens when you take on the European establishment?     </p>
<p>                    Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis.     </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              Varoufakis sparked one of the most spectacular and controversial battles in recent political history with his attempt to renegotiate Greece&#8217;s relationship with the European Union. Yet despite the mass support of the Greek people, and simple logic of his arguments, he succeeded only in provoking the fury of Europe&#8217;s political, financial and media elite.<br />
                                                                                                                                                                                          Exposing the real business taking place behind the EU&#8217;s closed doors, Varoufakis reveals all in this fearless, personal account. Adults In The Room is an extraordinary tale of brinkmanship, hypocrisy, collusion and betrayal that will shake the European and economic establishment to its foundations.     </p>
<p>                    Varoufakis is sending out an urgent wake-up call to renew European democracy before it is too late.    </p>
<p>                    **ONE OF THE GUARDIAN&#8217;S 100 BEST BOOKS OF THE 21st CENTURY**</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late    </p>
<p>                    A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and living standards. The bottom line of this outrage is the same; people are demanding their governments do more to improve their lives faster, something which policymakers are unable to deliver under conditions of anaemic growth. Rising income inequality and a stagnant economy are threats to both the developed and the developing world, and leaders can no longer afford to ignore this gathering storm.    </p>
<p>                    In Edge of Chaos, Dambisa Moyo sets out the new political and economic challenges facing the world, and the specific, radical solutions needed to resolve these issues and reignite global growth. Dambisa enumerates the four headwinds of demographics, inequality, commodity scarcity and technological innovation that are driving social and economic unrest, and argues for a fundamental retooling of democratic capitalism to address current problems and deliver better outcomes in the future. In the twenty-first century, a crisis in one country can quickly become our own, and fragile economies produce a fragile international community. Edge of Chaos is a warning for advanced and emerging nations alike: we must reverse the dramatic erosion in growth, or face the consequences of a fragmented and unstable global future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the acclaim for The End of the Free Market, Ian Bremmer is back with Every Nation for Itself, now in paperback, where he addresses the next big issue for the shifting world economy. &#8216;Smart and snappy &#8230; provides the most cogent prediction of how the politics of a post-America world will play out&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following the acclaim for The End of the Free Market, Ian Bremmer is back with Every Nation for Itself, now in paperback, where he addresses the next big issue for the shifting world economy.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Smart and snappy &#8230; provides the most cogent prediction of how the politics of a post-America world will play out&#8217;  New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    What happens when nobody&#8217;s running the world?    </p>
<p>                    The United States is in financial crisis and can&#8217;t hold onto the reins of the G-20. But China has no interest in international leadership, Europe is trying to save the euro, and emerging powers like Brazil and India are focused on domestic development. No government has the time, resources or political capital needed to take an international lead. The world power structure is about to have a vacancy&#8230;at the top.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the G-Zero world, in which no single country has the power to shape a truly global agenda. That means we are about to see 20 years of conflict over economics, finance and climate change.    </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author and strategist Ian Bremmer reveals how world powers are rapidly turning into gated communities, locked in competition. Who will prevail?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prodigy in the US global commentariat. Mr Bremmer&#8217;s rehearsal of the consequences should make us all wise up&#8217; Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An author who is always full of insights&#8217; George Osborne    </p>
<p>                    Ian Bremmer is the president of the world&#8217;s leading global political risk research and consulting firm, Eurasia Group. He has written for the Wall Street Journal, Washington Post, Newsweek, and Harvard Business Review. His six books include The J Curve and The End Of The Free Market.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Political Order and Political Decay : From the Industrial Revolution to the Globalisation of Democracy &#8211; Francis Fukuyama (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Origins of Political Order, Francis Fukuyama took us from the dawn of mankind to the French and American Revolutions. Here, he picks up the thread again in the second instalment of his definitive account of mankind&#8217;s emergence as a political animal. This is the story of how state, law and democracy developed after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/">Political Order and Political Decay : From the Industrial Revolution to the Globalisation of Democracy &#8211; Francis Fukuyama (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Origins of Political Order, Francis Fukuyama took us from the dawn of mankind to the French and American Revolutions.  Here, he picks up the thread again in the second instalment of his definitive account of mankind&#8217;s emergence as a political animal.    </p>
<p>                    This is the story of how state, law and democracy developed after these cataclysmic events, how the modern landscape &#8211; with its uneasy tension between dictatorships and liberal democracies &#8211; evolved and how in the United States and in other developed democracies, unmistakable signs of decay have emerged.     </p>
<p>                    If we want to understand the political systems that dominate and order our lives, we must first address their origins &#8211; in our own recent past as well as in the earliest systems of human government. Fukuyama argues that the key to successful government can be reduced to three key elements: a strong state, the rule of law and institutions of democratic accountability.    </p>
<p>                    This magisterial account is required reading for anyone wishing to know more about mankind&#8217;s greatest achievements.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/">Political Order and Political Decay : From the Industrial Revolution to the Globalisation of Democracy &#8211; Francis Fukuyama (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017 &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217; &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217; &#8211; Christine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Christine Lagarde, Managing Director of the International Monetary Fund     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    From Brexit, to Donald Trump, to extremist parties in Europe and the developing world, populism has dominated recent headlines.     </p>
<p>                    But what explains the rise of leaders who stoke nationalist anger in their countries, from Le Pen to Erdogan? How long will the populist wave last? Who will be the winners and losers in this climate, and how can we defend the values of democracy, free trade and international cooperation?     </p>
<p>                    No one is better suited to explore these questions than Ian Bremmer, the CEO of the Eurasia Group and acclaimed Time magazine columnist. Analysing the social, economic and technological forces fuelling this new wave of populism, Bremmer explains why we&#8217;re witnessing a rejection of the democratic, global, cosmopolitan trends of the late 20th century. Us vs. Them is a definitive guide to navigating the shifting political landscape, for businesses looking to weather and survive the populist storm.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Global politics is a jungle today. Thank goodness Ian Bremmer can be your guide&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; David Miliband, president and CEO of the International Rescue Committee    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A masterful analysis of why global crashed and populism soared&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Adam Grant, author of Give and Take, and Originals and Option B with Sheryl Sandberg</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Flags : The Rise of ISIS &#8211; Joby Warrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Fundamentalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**WINNER of the PULITZER PRIZE for NON-FICTION 2016** In a thrilling dramatic narrative, Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter Joby Warrick traces how the strain of militant Islam behind ISIS first arose in a remote Jordanian prison and spread to become the world&#8217;s greatest threat. When the government of Jordan granted amnesty to a group of political prisoners [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/">Black Flags : The Rise of ISIS &#8211; Joby Warrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**WINNER of the PULITZER PRIZE for NON-FICTION 2016**    </p>
<p>                    In a thrilling dramatic narrative, Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter  Joby Warrick traces how the strain of militant Islam behind ISIS first  arose in a remote Jordanian prison and spread to become the world&#8217;s greatest threat.    </p>
<p>                                   When the government of Jordan granted amnesty to a group of political prisoners in 1999, it little realized that among them was Abu Musab al-Zarqawi, a terrorist mastermind and soon the architect of an Islamist movement bent on dominating the Middle East. In Black Flags, an unprecedented character-driven account of the rise of ISIS, Joby Warrick shows how the zeal of this one man and the strategic mistakes of Western governments led to the banner of ISIS being raised over huge swathes of Syria and Iraq.    </p>
<p>                     Zarqawi began by directing terror attacks from a base in northern Iraq, but it was the allied invasion in 2003 that catapulted him to the head of a vast insurgency. By falsely identifying him as the link between Saddam Hussein and Osama bin Laden, Western officials inadvertently spurred like-minded radicals to rally to his cause. Their wave of brutal beheadings and suicide bombings persisted until American and Jordanian intelligence discovered clues that led to a lethal airstrike on Zarqawi&#8217;s hideout in 2006.    </p>
<p>                     His movement, however, endured. First calling themselves al-Qaeda in Iraq, then Islamic State of Iraq and Syria, or ISIS, his followers sought refuge in unstable, ungoverned pockets on the Iraq-Syria border. When the Syrian civil war broke out in 2011, and the rest of the world largely stood by, ISIS seized its chance to pursue Zarqawi&#8217;s dream of an ultra-conservative Islamic caliphate.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on unique high-level access to global intelligence sources, Warrick weaves gripping, moment-by-moment operational details with the perspectives of diplomats and spies, generals and heads of state, many of whom foresaw a menace worse than al Qaeda and tried desperately to stop it. Black Flags is a brilliant and definitive history that reveals the long arc of today&#8217;s most dangerous extremist threat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/">Black Flags : The Rise of ISIS &#8211; Joby Warrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re entitled to your own opinion but not your own facts Fantasy is the USA&#8217;s primary product. From the Pilgrim Fathers onward America has been a place where renegades and freaks came in search of freedom to create their own realities with little objectively regulated truth standing in their way. The freedom to invent and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/">Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re entitled to your own opinion but not your own facts    </p>
<p>                    Fantasy is the USA&#8217;s primary product. From the Pilgrim Fathers onward America has been a place where renegades and freaks came in search of freedom to create their own realities with little objectively regulated truth standing in their way. The freedom to invent and believe whatever the hell you like is, in some ways, an unwritten constitutional right. But, this do-your-own-thing freedom also is the driving credo of America&#8217;s current transformation where the difference between opinion and fact is rapidly crumbling.     </p>
<p>                    So how did we get to this weird pseudo-reality, where science and objective facts are dismissed in favour of opinions and wild speculation, or indeed, fantasies? The post truth, fake news, free-for-all mentality isn&#8217;t exactly a new phenomenon. If you want to understand Trump&#8217;s America, how the lines between reality and illusion have become dangerously blurred, you have to go back to the very beginning and take a dizzying road trip across five centuries of crackpot delusion and make-believe from Salem to Scientology.    </p>
<p>                    Fantasyland is a journey that connects the dots between crazed franchises of true believers &#8211; a rich freak show tapestry from Mormons to Flat-Earthers and satanic panic, new age quacks to anti-vaxxers, conspiracy theorists of every stripe, creationists to climate change deniers, UFO-obsessives to gun-toting libertarians, showmen hucksters from P T Barnum to Trump himself, all topped off with a dangerous dose of anti-government paranoia and pseudoscience. Along the way, New York Times bestselling author Kurt Andersen has created a unique and raucous history of America and a new paradigm for understanding our post-factual world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/">Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller The Next 100 Years now focuses his geopolitical forecasting acumen on the next decade and the imminent events and challenges that will test America and the world, specifically addressing the skills that will be required by the decade&#8217;s leaders. In the long view, history is seen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/">The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller The Next 100 Years now focuses his geopolitical forecasting acumen on the next decade and the imminent events and challenges that will test America and the world, specifically addressing the skills that will be required by the decade&#8217;s leaders.     </p>
<p>                    In the long view, history is seen as a series of events&#8211;but the course of those events is determined by individuals and their actions. During the next ten years, individual leaders will face significant transitions for their nations: the United States&#8217; relationships with Iran and Israel will be undergoing changes, China will likely confront a major crisis, and the wars in the Islamic world will subside. Unexpected energy and technology developments will emerge, and labor shortages will begin to matter more than financial crises. Distinguished geopolitical forecaster George Friedman analyzes these events from the perspectives of the men and women leading these global changes, focusing in particular on the American president, who will require extraordinary skills to shepherd the United States through this transitional period. The Next Decade is a provocative and fascinating look at the conflicts and opportunities that lie ahead.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/">The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ukraine Crisis : What It Means for the West &#8211; Andrew Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ukraine-crisis-what-it-means-for-the-west-andrew-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Armed Conflict]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ukraine-crisis-what-it-means-for-the-west-andrew-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A leading Ukraine specialist and firsthand witness to the 2014 Kiev Uprising analyzes the world&#8217;s newest flashpoint The aftereffects of the February 2014 Uprising in Ukraine are still reverberating around the world. The consequences of the popular rebellion and Russian President Putin&#8217;s attempt to strangle it remain uncertain. In this book, Andrew Wilson combines a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ukraine-crisis-what-it-means-for-the-west-andrew-wilson-abridged/">Ukraine Crisis : What It Means for the West &#8211; Andrew Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A leading Ukraine specialist and firsthand witness to the 2014 Kiev Uprising analyzes the world&#8217;s newest flashpoint    </p>
<p>                     The aftereffects of the February 2014 Uprising in Ukraine are still reverberating around the world. The consequences of the popular rebellion and Russian President Putin&#8217;s attempt to strangle it remain uncertain. In this book, Andrew Wilson combines a spellbinding, on-the-scene account of the Kiev Uprising with a deeply informed analysis of what precipitated the events, what has developed in subsequent months, and why the story is far from over.    </p>
<p>                     Wilson situates Ukraine&#8217;s February insurgence within Russia&#8217;s expansionist ambitions throughout the previous decade. He reveals how President Putin&#8217;s extravagant spending to develop soft power in all parts of Europe was aided by wishful thinking in the EU and American diplomatic inattention, and how Putin&#8217;s agenda continues to be widely misunderstood in the West. The author then examines events in the wake of the Uprising-the military coup in Crimea, the election of President Petro Poroshenko, the Malaysia Airlines tragedy, rising tensions among all of Russia&#8217;s neighbors, both friend and foe, and more. Ukraine Crisis provides an important, accurate record of events that unfolded in Ukraine in 2014. It also rings a clear warning that the unresolved problems of the region have implications well beyond Ukrainian borders.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ukraine-crisis-what-it-means-for-the-west-andrew-wilson-abridged/">Ukraine Crisis : What It Means for the West &#8211; Andrew Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Grand Strategy &#8211; John Lewis Gaddis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-grand-strategy-john-lewis-gaddis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-grand-strategy-john-lewis-gaddis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A training manual for our troubled times &#8230; It makes sense of our world, but is also capable of beautifully crafted pithy historical judgements. &#8230; It is a book that cares about liberty, choice and a moral compass, that warns against hubris&#8217; Roger Boyes, The Times John Lewis Gaddis, the distinguished historian and acclaimed author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-grand-strategy-john-lewis-gaddis-abridged/">On Grand Strategy &#8211; John Lewis Gaddis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A training manual for our troubled times &#8230; It  makes sense of our world, but is also capable of beautifully crafted  pithy historical judgements. &#8230; It is a book that cares about liberty,  choice and a moral compass, that warns against hubris&#8217; Roger Boyes, The Times    </p>
<p>                    John Lewis Gaddis, the distinguished historian and acclaimed author of The Cold War,   has for almost two decades co-taught the grand strategy seminar at  Yale  University with his colleagues Charles Hill and Paul Kennedy. Now,  in On Grand Strategy, Gaddis reflects with insight and wit on what he has learned.    </p>
<p>                    In   chapters extending from the ancient world through World War II, Gaddis   assesses grand strategic theory and practice in Herodotus, Thucydides,   Sun Tzu, Octavian/Augustus, Saint Augustine, Machiavelli,Elizabeth I,   Philip II, the American Founding Fathers, Clausewitz, Tolstoy,Lincoln,   Wilson, Franklin D. Roosevelt, and Isaiah Berlin.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;For the past 16 years Gaddis has taught a course on grand strategy to   students at Yale University. Reading his book, you wish every  university  could offer it. Gaddis roves across the centuries, offering  advice on  subjects from statecraft and warfare to leading a worthwhile  life&#8217;  Phillip Delves Broughton, Evening Standard</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-grand-strategy-john-lewis-gaddis-abridged/">On Grand Strategy &#8211; John Lewis Gaddis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Siege : Trump Under Fire &#8211; Michael Wolff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/siege-trump-under-fire-michael-wolff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/siege-trump-under-fire-michael-wolff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With Fire and Fury, Michael Wolff defined the first phase of the Trump administration; now, in Siege, he has written an equally essential and explosive book about a presidency that is under fire from almost every side. A stunningly fresh narrative that begins just as Trump&#8217;s second year as president is getting underway and ends [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/siege-trump-under-fire-michael-wolff-abridged/">Siege : Trump Under Fire &#8211; Michael Wolff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With Fire and Fury, Michael Wolff defined the first phase of the Trump administration; now, in Siege, he has written an equally essential and explosive book about a presidency that is under fire from almost every side. A stunningly fresh narrative that begins just as Trump&#8217;s second year as president is getting underway and ends with the delivery of the Mueller report, Siege reveals an administration that is perpetually beleaguered by investigations and a president who is increasingly volatile, erratic and exposed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/siege-trump-under-fire-michael-wolff-abridged/">Siege : Trump Under Fire &#8211; Michael Wolff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS     </p>
<p>                    ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**     </p>
<p>                    Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding of what makes civilizations rise and fall. Now, at a time when crises are erupting around the world, heexplores what makes certain nations resilient, and reveals the factors that influence how nations and individuals can respond to enormous challenges.     </p>
<p>                    In a riveting journey into the recent past, he traces how six distinctive modern nations &#8211; Finland, Chile, Indonesia, Japan, Germany and Australia &#8211; have survived defining catastrophes, and identifies patterns in their recovery. Looking ahead, he investigates the risk that the United States and other countries, faced by grave threat, are set on a course towards catastrophe.     </p>
<p>                    Adding a rich psychological dimension to the in-depth history, geography, biology and anthropology that underpin all of Diamond&#8217;s writing, Upheaval is epic in scope, but also his most personal book yet.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating &#8230; I finished the book even more optimistic about our ability to solve problems than I started&#8217; BILL GATES    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jared Diamond does it again: another rich, original and fascinating chapter in the human saga &#8211; with vital lessons for our difficult times&#8217; STEVEN PINKER</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power. In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power.    </p>
<p>                    In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a mass retirement that will enervate capital supplies; and how it is the ever-ravenous American economy that is rapidly approaching energy independence. Combined, these factors are overturning the global system and ushering in a new (dis)order. For most, that is a disaster-in-waiting, but not for the Americans. The shale revolution allows Americans to sidestep a dangerous energy market. Only the U.S. boasts a youth population large enough to escape the sucking maw of global aging. Geography will matter more than ever in a de-globalizing world, and America&#8217;s geography is simply sublime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blowout : Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth &#8211; Rachel Maddow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Big Oil and Gas Versus Democracy&#8211;Winner Take All &#8220;A rollickingly well-written book, filled with fascinating, exciting, and alarming stories about the impact of the oil and gas industry on the world today.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review In 2010, the words &#8220;earthquake swarm&#8221; entered the lexicon in Oklahoma. That [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/">Blowout : Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth &#8211; Rachel Maddow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Big Oil and Gas Versus Democracy&#8211;Winner Take All     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A rollickingly well-written book, filled with fascinating, exciting, and alarming stories about the impact of the oil and gas industry on the world today.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review     </p>
<p>                     In 2010, the words &#8220;earthquake swarm&#8221; entered the lexicon in Oklahoma. That same year, a trove of Michael Jackson memorabilia&#8211;including his iconic crystal-encrusted white glove&#8211;was sold at auction for over $1 million to a guy who was, officially, just the lowly forestry minister of the tiny nation of Equatorial Guinea. And in 2014, revolutionaries in Ukraine raided the palace of their ousted president and found a zoo of peacocks, gilded toilets, and a floating restaurant modeled after a Spanish galleon. Unlikely as it might seem, there is a thread connecting these events, and Rachel Maddow follows it to its crooked source: the unimaginably lucrative and equally corrupting oil and gas industry.     </p>
<p>                     With her trademark black humor, Maddow takes us on a switchback journey around the globe, revealing the greed and incompetence of Big Oil and Gas along the way, and drawing a surprising conclusion about why the Russian government hacked the 2016 U.S. election. She deftly shows how Russia&#8217;s rich reserves of crude have, paradoxically, stunted its growth, forcing Vladimir Putin to maintain his power by spreading Russia&#8217;s rot into its rivals, its neighbors, the West&#8217;s most important alliances, and the United States. Chevron, BP, and a host of other industry players get their star turn, most notably ExxonMobil and the deceptively well-behaved Rex Tillerson. The oil and gas industry has weakened democracies in developed and developing countries, fouled oceans and rivers, and propped up authoritarian thieves and killers. But being outraged at it is, according to Maddow, &#8220;like being indignant when a lion takes down and eats a gazelle. You can&#8217;t really blame the lion. It&#8217;s in her nature.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                      Blowout is a call to contain the lion: to stop subsidizing the wealthiest businesses on earth, to fight for transparency, and to check the influence of the world&#8217;s most destructive industry and its enablers. The stakes have never been higher. As Maddow writes, &#8220;Democracy either wins this one or disappears.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/">Blowout : Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth &#8211; Rachel Maddow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rare : The High-Stakes Race to Satisfy Our Need for the Scarcest Metals on Earth &#8211; Keith Veronese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inorganic Chemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Materials Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metals Technology / Metallurgy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How will your life change when the supply of tantalum dries up? You may have never heard of this unusual metal, but without it smartphones would be instantly less omniscient, video game systems would falter, and laptops fail. Tantalum is not alone. Rhodium. Osmium. Niobium. Such refugees from the bottom of the periodic table are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/">Rare : The High-Stakes Race to Satisfy Our Need for the Scarcest Metals on Earth &#8211; Keith Veronese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How will your life change when the supply of tantalum dries up? You may have never heard of this unusual metal, but without it smartphones would be instantly less omniscient, video game systems would falter, and laptops fail. Tantalum is not alone. Rhodium. Osmium. Niobium. Such refugees from the bottom of the periodic table are key components of many consumer products like cell phones, hybrid car batteries, and flat screen televisions, as well as sophisticated medical devices and even weapon systems. Their versatile properties have led manufacturers to seek these elements out to maximize longevity, value, and efficiency, but not without a human price.     </p>
<p>                    In addition to explaining the chemistry behind rare earth metals, Rare delves into the economic and geopolitical issues surrounding these &#8220;conflict minerals,&#8221; blending tales of financial and political struggles with glimpses into the human lives that are shattered by the race to secure them. In the past decade, the Congo has been ravaged by tribal wars fought to obtain control of tantalum, tungsten, and tin supplies in the region, with over five million people dying at the crossroads of supply and demand. A burgeoning black market in China, Africa, and India is propped up by school-age children retrieving and purifying these metals while risking their lives and health in the process. Fears of future political struggles inside China, the world&#8217;s largest supplier of these metals, have already sent the United States, Great Britain, and Japan racing to find alternative sources.    </p>
<p>                    Will scientists be able to create lab substitutes for some or all of these metals? Will Afghanistan be the next big supplier of rare metals? What happens when the limited supply runs out? Whatever the answers, it is clear that our modern lifestyle, dependent on technology, is far from stable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/">Rare : The High-Stakes Race to Satisfy Our Need for the Scarcest Metals on Earth &#8211; Keith Veronese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
