<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Personnel &amp; Human Resources Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/personnel-human-resources-management/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/personnel-human-resources-management/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Personnel &amp; Human Resources Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/personnel-human-resources-management/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Person You Mean to Be : How Good People Fight Bias &#8211; Dolly Chugh, Foreword by Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-person-you-mean-to-be-how-good-people-fight-bias-dolly-chugh-foreword-by-laszlo-bock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-person-you-mean-to-be-how-good-people-fight-bias-dolly-chugh-foreword-by-laszlo-bock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Finally: an engaging, evidence-based book about how to battle biases, champion diversity and inclusion, and advocate for those who lack power and privilege. Dolly Chugh makes a convincing case that being an ally isn&#8217;t about being a good person-it&#8217;s about constantly striving to be a better person.&#8221; -Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-person-you-mean-to-be-how-good-people-fight-bias-dolly-chugh-foreword-by-laszlo-bock-abridged/">The Person You Mean to Be : How Good People Fight Bias &#8211; Dolly Chugh, Foreword by Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Finally: an engaging, evidence-based book about how to battle biases, champion diversity and inclusion, and advocate for those who lack power and privilege. Dolly Chugh makes a convincing case that being an ally isn&#8217;t about being a good person-it&#8217;s about constantly striving to be a better person.&#8221;  -Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Give and Take, Originals, and Option B with Sheryl Sandberg    </p>
<p>                    Foreword by Laszlo Bock, the bestselling author of Work Rules! and former Senior Vice President of People Operations at Google    </p>
<p>                    An inspiring guide from Dolly Chugh, an award-winning social psychologist at the New York University Stern School of Business, on how to confront difficult issues including sexism, racism, inequality, and injustice so that you can make the world (and yourself) better.    </p>
<p>                    Many of us believe in equality, diversity, and inclusion. But how do we stand up for those values in our turbulent world? The Person You Mean to Be is the smart, &#8220;semi-bold&#8221; person&#8217;s guide to fighting for what you believe in.    </p>
<p>                    Dolly reveals the surprising causes of inequality, grounded in the &#8220;psychology of good people&#8221;. Using her research findings in unconscious bias as well as work across psychology, sociology, economics, political science, and other disciplines, she offers practical tools to respectfully and effectively talk politics with family, to be a better colleague to people who don&#8217;t look like you, and to avoid being a well-intentioned barrier to equality. Being the person we mean to be starts with a look at ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    She argues that the only way to be on the right side of history is to be a good-ish- rather than good-person. Good-ish people are always growing. Second, she helps you find your &#8220;ordinary privilege&#8221;-the part of your everyday identity you take for granted, such as race for a white person, sexual orientation for a straight person, gender for a man, or education for a college graduate. This part of your identity may bring blind spots, but it is your best tool for influencing change. Third, Dolly introduces the psychological reasons that make it hard for us to see the bias in and around us. She leads you from willful ignorance to willful awareness. Finally, she guides you on how, when, and whom, to engage (and not engage) in your workplaces, homes, and communities. Her science-based approach is a method any of us can put to use in all parts of our life.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you are a long-time activist or new to the fight, you can start from where you are. Through the compelling stories Dolly shares and the surprising science she reports, Dolly guides each of us closer to being the person we mean to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-person-you-mean-to-be-how-good-people-fight-bias-dolly-chugh-foreword-by-laszlo-bock-abridged/">The Person You Mean to Be : How Good People Fight Bias &#8211; Dolly Chugh, Foreword by Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Effective SMEs : A Trainer&#8217;s Guide for Helping Subject Matter Experts Facilitate Learning &#8211; Dale Ludwig, Greg Owen-Boger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/effective-smes-a-trainers-guide-for-helping-subject-matter-experts-facilitate-learning-dale-ludwig-greg-owen-boger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/effective-smes-a-trainers-guide-for-helping-subject-matter-experts-facilitate-learning-dale-ludwig-greg-owen-boger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Content expertise isn&#8217;t enough for the training room. Partnering with subject matter experts can really pay off. SMEs (we pronounce it smees) bring credibility and relevance to live training. They enrich learning programs with their insight and depth of experience. But content expertise alone isn&#8217;t enough to deliver effective training. . . . SMEs want [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/effective-smes-a-trainers-guide-for-helping-subject-matter-experts-facilitate-learning-dale-ludwig-greg-owen-boger-abridged/">Effective SMEs : A Trainer&#8217;s Guide for Helping Subject Matter Experts Facilitate Learning &#8211; Dale Ludwig, Greg Owen-Boger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Content expertise isn&#8217;t enough for the training room.    </p>
<p>                    Partnering with subject matter experts can really pay off. SMEs (we pronounce it smees) bring credibility and relevance to live training. They enrich learning programs with their insight and depth of experience. But content expertise alone isn&#8217;t enough to deliver effective training. . . .    </p>
<p>                    SMEs want to do well in the classroom, but it&#8217;s often unfamiliar terrain. They&#8217;re authorities on content, not talent development. Without guidance, they may overshare or find themselves unable to facilitate a productive discussion&#8212;all of which frustrate learners. But, with the right approach, you can bring SMEs into the training room successfully, in a way that makes learners, instructors, and managers feel like their goals are being met.     </p>
<p>                    Effective SMEs: A Trainer&#8217;s Guide for Helping Subject Matter Experts Facilitate Learning is the blueprint to managing SME-led training. Authors Dale Ludwig and Greg Owen-Boger offer first-rate advice gleaned from decades helping presenters, instructional designers, and SMEs become better communicators. Underlying all their tips is their belief that SMEs and instructional designers must get comfortable with each other&#8217;s role. The authors lay the groundwork for you, describing the fundamental principles of a successful training event and the personal approach they contend every SME and ID bring to the training table. You&#8217;ll discover how to design learning events with the needs of SMEs in mind. And you&#8217;ll try out best practices for coaching SMEs to deliver training efficiently and effectively. The authors also share detailed and relatable workplace scenarios drawn from their vast business experience as well as job aids to assist you in a variety of learning situations.     </p>
<p>                    Effective SMEs is the rare book that addresses both designing for SMEs to deliver training and coaching them to be effective once they&#8217;re in the training room. Don&#8217;t plan your next live training event without it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/effective-smes-a-trainers-guide-for-helping-subject-matter-experts-facilitate-learning-dale-ludwig-greg-owen-boger-abridged/">Effective SMEs : A Trainer&#8217;s Guide for Helping Subject Matter Experts Facilitate Learning &#8211; Dale Ludwig, Greg Owen-Boger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Challenging Coaching : Going Beyond Traditional Coaching to Face the FACTS &#8211; Ian Day, John Blakey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/challenging-coaching-going-beyond-traditional-coaching-to-face-the-facts-ian-day-john-blakey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/challenging-coaching-going-beyond-traditional-coaching-to-face-the-facts-ian-day-john-blakey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Challenging Coaching is a real-world, timely and provocative book which provides a wake-up call to move beyond the limitations of traditional coaching. Based on the authors&#8217; extensive experience working at board and management levels, they suggest that for far too long coaching approaches have shied away from adopting a more challenging stance &#8211; a stance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/challenging-coaching-going-beyond-traditional-coaching-to-face-the-facts-ian-day-john-blakey-abridged/">Challenging Coaching : Going Beyond Traditional Coaching to Face the FACTS &#8211; Ian Day, John Blakey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Challenging Coaching is a real-world, timely and provocative book which provides a wake-up call to move beyond the limitations of traditional coaching. Based on the authors&#8217; extensive experience working at board and management levels, they suggest that for far too long coaching approaches have shied away from adopting a more challenging stance &#8211; a stance that can provoke greater performance and unlock deeper potential in business leaders and their teams.    </p>
<p>                    The authors detail their unique FACTS coaching model, which provides a practical and pragmatic approach focusing on Feedback, Accountability, Courageous goals, Tension and Systems thinking. The authors explore FACTS coaching in theory and in practice using case studies, example dialogues and practical exercises so that the reader will be able to successfully challenge others using respectful yet direct techniques.    </p>
<p>                    This is an original and thought-provoking book that dares the reader to go beyond traditional coaching and face the FACTS.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/challenging-coaching-going-beyond-traditional-coaching-to-face-the-facts-ian-day-john-blakey-abridged/">Challenging Coaching : Going Beyond Traditional Coaching to Face the FACTS &#8211; Ian Day, John Blakey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tribal Leadership : Leveraging Natural Groups to Build a Thriving Organization &#8211; Dave Logan, John King, Halee Fischer-Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tribal-leadership-leveraging-natural-groups-to-build-a-thriving-organization-dave-logan-john-king-halee-fischer-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tribal-leadership-leveraging-natural-groups-to-build-a-thriving-organization-dave-logan-john-king-halee-fischer-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In &#8220;Tribal Leadership&#8221;, management consultants Dave Logan and John King show corporate leaders how they can use tribes &#8211; the groups that naturally form within any company &#8211; to maximize productivity and profit within their own firms. Based on a rigorous eight-year study that covered more than two dozen companies and 24,000 people, &#8220;Tribal Leadership&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tribal-leadership-leveraging-natural-groups-to-build-a-thriving-organization-dave-logan-john-king-halee-fischer-wright-abridged/">Tribal Leadership : Leveraging Natural Groups to Build a Thriving Organization &#8211; Dave Logan, John King, Halee Fischer-Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In &#8220;Tribal Leadership&#8221;, management consultants Dave Logan and John King show corporate leaders how they can use tribes &#8211; the groups that naturally form within any company &#8211; to maximize productivity and profit within their own firms. Based on a rigorous eight-year study that covered more than two dozen companies and 24,000 people, &#8220;Tribal Leadership&#8221; includes interviews with leading business figures such as Brian France, chairman and CEO of NASCAR, and Dilbert creator Scott Adams, and shows leaders from companies of any size and of any industry that the health and success of their firms ultimately depend on the hundreds of tribes within.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tribal-leadership-leveraging-natural-groups-to-build-a-thriving-organization-dave-logan-john-king-halee-fischer-wright-abridged/">Tribal Leadership : Leveraging Natural Groups to Build a Thriving Organization &#8211; Dave Logan, John King, Halee Fischer-Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Glass Closet : Why Coming Out is Good Business &#8211; John Browne (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-glass-closet-why-coming-out-is-good-business-john-browne-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay Studies (Gay Men)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-glass-closet-why-coming-out-is-good-business-john-browne-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I wish I had been brave enough to come out earlier in my tenure as CEO of BP. I regret it to this day. I know that if I had done so I would have made more of an impact for other gay men and women. With The Glass Closet, I hope to give some [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-glass-closet-why-coming-out-is-good-business-john-browne-abridged/">The Glass Closet : Why Coming Out is Good Business &#8211; John Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I wish I had been brave enough to come out earlier in my tenure as CEO of BP. I regret it to this day. I know that if I had done so I would have made more of an impact for other gay men and women. With The Glass Closet, I hope to give some of them the courage to make an impact of their own.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Whether you&#8217;re lesbian, gay, transgender or straight, John Browne&#8217;s message is simple and clear, it&#8217;s better for you and it&#8217;s better for business when you bring your authentic self to work.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on his personal experiences and the experience of other gay and lesbian business leaders, and by investigating the research and the social contexts, The Glass Closet strives to give courage and inspire the LGBT community that despite the risks involved, self-disclosure is best for employees and for the businesses that support them.    </p>
<p>                     Every CEO, every HR Manager, every team leader &#8211; anyone who is responsible for the culture and success of their business should read The Glass Closet. And for anyone fearful or lacking the confidence to bring their true self into work every day, this book was written for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-glass-closet-why-coming-out-is-good-business-john-browne-abridged/">The Glass Closet : Why Coming Out is Good Business &#8211; John Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge. When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality. In Leaders Eat Last, Simon [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge.    </p>
<p>                    When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality.    </p>
<p>                    In Leaders Eat Last, Simon Sinek, internationally bestselling author of Start With Why, investigates these great leaders from Marine Corps Officers, who don&#8217;t just sacrifice their place at the table but often their own comfort and even their lives for those in their care, to the heads of big business and government &#8211; each putting aside their own interests to protect their teams.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Simple and elegant, it shows us how leaders should lead&#8217; William Ury, co-author of Getting to Yes</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Widgets: The 12 New Rules for Managing Your Employees as if They&#8217;re Real People &#8211; Rodd Wagner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author Rodd Wagner tackles one of the most destructive problems facing organizations today-the breakdown of the relationship between employees and the organizations they work for &#8220;Your people are not your greatest asset. They&#8217;re not yours, and they&#8217;re not assets.&#8221; With this declaration, one of the leading authorities on employee performance rolls [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/">Widgets: The 12 New Rules for Managing Your Employees as if They&#8217;re Real People &#8211; Rodd Wagner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author Rodd Wagner tackles one of the most destructive problems facing organizations today-the breakdown of the relationship between employees and the organizations they work for    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Your people are not your greatest asset. They&#8217;re not yours, and they&#8217;re not assets.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    With this declaration, one of the leading authorities on employee performance rolls up his sleeves against the weasel words, contradictions, bad habits, and intrusions that reduce people to &#8220;human resources.&#8221; To &#8220;FTEs.&#8221; To &#8220;human capital.&#8221; To flesh-and-blood widgets.    </p>
<p>                    Armed with empirical evidence from the provocative studies he leads around the globe, Wagner guides you through the new realities of what it takes to get the highest levels of intensity from people in a more mercenary, skeptical, and wired work world. He explains how elements such as individualization, fearlessness, transparency, recognition, and coolness are reciprocated with loyalty, productivity, innovation, and&#8211;inescapably&#8211;corporate reputation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/">Widgets: The 12 New Rules for Managing Your Employees as if They&#8217;re Real People &#8211; Rodd Wagner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Build It : The Rebel Playbook for World-Class Employee Engagement &#8211; Debra Corey, Glenn Elliott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/build-it-the-rebel-playbook-for-world-class-employee-engagement-debra-corey-glenn-elliott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/build-it-the-rebel-playbook-for-world-class-employee-engagement-debra-corey-glenn-elliott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The current way of treating people at work has failed. Globally, only 30% of employees are engaged in their jobs, and in this fast-paced world that&#8217;s just not enough. The world&#8217;s best companies understand this, and have been quietly treating people differently for nearly two decades. Now you can learn their secrets and discover The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/build-it-the-rebel-playbook-for-world-class-employee-engagement-debra-corey-glenn-elliott-abridged/">Build It : The Rebel Playbook for World-Class Employee Engagement &#8211; Debra Corey, Glenn Elliott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The current way of treating people at work has failed. Globally, only 30% of employees are engaged in their jobs, and in this fast-paced world that&#8217;s just not enough. The world&#8217;s best companies understand this, and have been quietly treating people differently for nearly two decades.     </p>
<p>                    Now you can learn their secrets and discover The Engagement Bridge (TM) model, proven to build bottom line value for companies through sustainable employee engagement.     </p>
<p>                    Companies with the best cultures generate stock market returns of twice the general market and enjoy half the employee turnover of their peers. Their staff innovate more, deliver better customer service and, hands-down, beat the competition. These companies outperform and disrupt their markets. They break the rules of traditional HR, they rebel against the status quo.     </p>
<p>                    Build it has found these rebels and the rulebreakers. From small startups to global powerhouses, this book shows that courage, commitment, and a people-centric mindset, rather than money and resources, are what you need to turn an average business into a category leader.     </p>
<p>                    The book follows the clear and proven Engagement Bridge (TM) model, developed from working with thousands of leading companies worldwide on their own employee engagement journeys. The practical model highlights the areas that leaders need to examine in order to build a highly engaged company culture and provides a framework for success.     </p>
<p>                    Build it is packed with tips, tools and real-life examples from employers including NASDAQ, Unilever, IBM, KPMG, 3M, and McDonald&#8217;s to help you start doing this not tomorrow, but today. Readers will learn:     </p>
<p>                    How employee engagement helps companies perform<br />
                    The key factors that drive engagement, and how they work together<br />
                    What the world&#8217;s most rebellious companies have done to break the rules of traditional HR and improve engagement<br />
                    How to implement The Engagement BridgeTM model to boost productivity, innovation, and better decision-making    </p>
<p>                     Unique in this category, Build it is written from two sharply different perspectives. Glenn Elliott is a multi-award winning Entrepreneur of the Year, CEO and growth investor. He talks candidly about the mistakes and missteps he has made whilst building Reward Gateway into a $300m category leader in employee engagement technology.     </p>
<p>                    Debra Corey brings 30 years experience in senior level HR roles at global companies such as Gap, Quintiles, Honeywell and Merlin Entertainments. She shares the practical tools and case studies that can kickstart your employee engagement plan, bringing her own pragmatic and engaging style to each situation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/build-it-the-rebel-playbook-for-world-class-employee-engagement-debra-corey-glenn-elliott-abridged/">Build It : The Rebel Playbook for World-Class Employee Engagement &#8211; Debra Corey, Glenn Elliott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Essential HR Handbook &#8211; Tenth Anniversary Edition : A Quick and Handy Resource for Any Manager or HR Professional &#8211; Sharon Armstrong, Barbara Mitchell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-essential-hr-handbook-tenth-anniversary-edition-a-quick-and-handy-resource-for-any-manager-or-hr-professional-sharon-armstrong-barbara-mitchell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-essential-hr-handbook-tenth-anniversary-edition-a-quick-and-handy-resource-for-any-manager-or-hr-professional-sharon-armstrong-barbara-mitchell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Only HR Book You&#8217;ll Ever Need! &#8220;Whether you&#8217;re a small business owner, a manager in a business without an HR department, or even a seasoned HR professional, this book will help you handle any personnel problem&#8211;from on-boarding to outplacement&#8211;quickly and easily.&#8221;&#8211;Solutions Review For more than a decade, busy managers by the tens of thousands [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-essential-hr-handbook-tenth-anniversary-edition-a-quick-and-handy-resource-for-any-manager-or-hr-professional-sharon-armstrong-barbara-mitchell-abridged/">The Essential HR Handbook &#8211; Tenth Anniversary Edition : A Quick and Handy Resource for Any Manager or HR Professional &#8211; Sharon Armstrong, Barbara Mitchell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Only HR Book You&#8217;ll Ever Need!     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Whether you&#8217;re a small business owner, a manager in a business without an HR department, or even a seasoned HR professional, this book will help you handle any personnel problem&#8211;from on-boarding to outplacement&#8211;quickly and easily.&#8221;&#8211;Solutions Review     </p>
<p>                    For more than a decade, busy managers by the tens of thousands have turned to this best-selling book as a handy guide to the ins and outs of human resources. And no wonder! Because whether you&#8217;re a small business owner, a manager in a business without an HR department, or even a seasoned HR professional, The Essential HR Handbook will help you handle any personnel problem&#8211;from onboarding to outplacement&#8211;quickly and easily. This fully updated 10th anniversary edition is packed with information, tools, checklists, sample forms, and timely tips to guide you through the maze of personnel issues in today&#8217;s complex business environment.     </p>
<p>                    In The Essential HR Handbook you&#8217;ll find out how to:     </p>
<p>                    Attract talented staff through social media recruitingIdentify legal pitfalls to avoid lawsuits and regulatory interferenceTrain a diverse and inclusive multigenerational workforceProvide the compensation and benefits package that will make your organization an &#8220;employer of choice&#8221;Streamline your orientation and onboarding practices so new employees hit the ground running    </p>
<p>                    Whenever personnel problems arise, having The Essential HR Handbook on your bookshelf is like having a team of expert HR consultants at your beck and call!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-essential-hr-handbook-tenth-anniversary-edition-a-quick-and-handy-resource-for-any-manager-or-hr-professional-sharon-armstrong-barbara-mitchell-abridged/">The Essential HR Handbook &#8211; Tenth Anniversary Edition : A Quick and Handy Resource for Any Manager or HR Professional &#8211; Sharon Armstrong, Barbara Mitchell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212; Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International    </p>
<p>                      &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! There, I learned the fundamentals of guest service that consistently gave Disney a tremendous advantage in the marketplace. Now, anyone can know these secrets of success thanks to Doug Lipp&#8217;s informative book. No matter what your business, the lessons taught at DisneyUniversity will prove invaluable.&#8221; &#8212; Michael Eisner, Former CEO and Chairman, The Walt Disney Company    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to world-class employees, few organizations rival Disney. Famous for their friendliness, knowledge, passion, and superior customer service, Disney&#8217;s employees have been fueling the iconic brand&#8217;s wild success for more than 50 years.    </p>
<p>                    How has Disney succeeded in maintaining such a powerful workforce for so many years? Why are so many corporations and executives drawn to study how Disney continues to exemplify service and leadership standards?    </p>
<p>                    The Disney University, founded by Van France, trains the supporting cast that helps create the world-famous Disney Magic. Now, for the first time, the secrets of this exemplary institution are revealed. In Disney U, Doug Lipp examines how Van perpetuated Walt Disney&#8217;s timeless company values and leadership lessons, creating a training and development dynasty. It contains never-before-told stories from numerous Disney legends. These pioneers share behind-the-scenes success stories of how they helped bring Walt Disney&#8217;s dream to life.    </p>
<p>                    Disney U reveals the heart of the Disney culture and describes the company&#8217;s values and operational philosophies that support the iconic brand. Doug Lipp lays out 13 timeless lessons Disney has used to drive profits and growth worldwide for more than half a century.    </p>
<p>                    To this day, the Disney University continues to turn out some of the most engaged, loyal, and customer-centered employees the business world has ever seen. Using the lessons outlined in Disney U will set your organization on a path of sustained success.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR Disney U:    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I highly recommend Disney U to anyone interested in building an enduring market presence and brand.&#8221; &#8212; Stephen Cannon, President and Chief Executive Officer, Mercedes-Benz USA    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lipp&#8217;s narratives reveal how Van and other Disney visionaries set the stage for a world-class organization by skillfully balancing both &#8216;people&#8217; and &#8216;technology.'&#8221; &#8212; Debi Aubee, Vice President of Sales, Bose Corporation    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every leader should have the equivalent of a Van France at his or her side. Thanks to Doug Lipp, we can now tap into the brilliance of a man who helped Walt createThe Happiest Place on Earth.&#8221; &#8212; David Overton, Founder and Chief Executive Officer, The Cheesecake Factory    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;How does Disney University create such enthusiastic, loyal, and customer-centered employees, year after year? Now, for the first time, Doug Lipp takes us on a journey backstage to answer this pivotal question.&#8221; &#8212; John G. Veres III, Ph.D., Chancellor, Auburn University at Montgomery    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Doug Lipp shares terrific stories about Disney that underscore the importance of creating an organizational culture with an unwavering dedication to superlativeservice and exceptional quality, both for employees and customers. He then takes it a step further by explaining how to bring these values to life for your organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Christine A. Morena, Executive Vice President of Human Resources, Saks Incorporated</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Misplaced Talent : A Guide to Making Better People Decisions &#8211; Joe Ungemah (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/misplaced-talent-a-guide-to-making-better-people-decisions-joe-ungemah-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/misplaced-talent-a-guide-to-making-better-people-decisions-joe-ungemah-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>High-value talent management must be relevant to today&#8217;s workplace Misplaced Talent takes a hard look at the cluttered field of Talent Management, and offers a clear guide to making better people decisions in any organization. Deliberately challenging practitioners to do more, this insightful discussion sorts through the tools and techniques developed over the last century [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/misplaced-talent-a-guide-to-making-better-people-decisions-joe-ungemah-abridged/">Misplaced Talent : A Guide to Making Better People Decisions &#8211; Joe Ungemah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>High-value talent management must be relevant to today&#8217;s workplace Misplaced Talent takes a hard look at the cluttered field of Talent Management, and offers a clear guide to making better people decisions in any organization. Deliberately challenging practitioners to do more, this insightful discussion sorts through the tools and techniques developed over the last century to examine their true relevance to the modern workplace. You&#8217;ll learn which activities show the greatest potential to improve the lives of employees and the organizations they work for, and identify which of your existing practices don&#8217;t really add enough value to be worth the expenditure of time, money, and potentially lost talent. The author asks you to make up your own mind about which approaches work best for your own specific talent decisions, but provides the best theory and practice available today as a foundation upon which to formulate a more relevant strategy. In a world of big data, the potential to understand employees and react appropriately has never been greater. So why is Talent Management as an industry relying on outdated theory and practices?<br />
                    This book is a guide to bringing HR up to date, giving you the tools, techniques, and perspective you need to demonstrate more value to your organization. * Adopt the tools and techniques most effective in today&#8217;s workplace * Identify and discard methods that don&#8217;t add value to the organization * Implement critical changes that can transform the HR function * Make better people decisions based on psychology and research Fundamentally, not much has changed in what constitutes good people practice. Practitioners must demonstrate the value of Talent Management, but the solutions implemented often fall short of the rigor and discipline they deserve. Misplaced Talent provides the insight you need to refocus attention and engage your organization about the value of better people decisions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/misplaced-talent-a-guide-to-making-better-people-decisions-joe-ungemah-abridged/">Misplaced Talent : A Guide to Making Better People Decisions &#8211; Joe Ungemah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Change Masters : Innovation and Entrepreneurship in the American Corporation &#8211; Rosabeth Moss Kanter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-change-masters-innovation-and-entrepreneurship-in-the-american-corporation-rosabeth-moss-kanter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-change-masters-innovation-and-entrepreneurship-in-the-american-corporation-rosabeth-moss-kanter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Simon &#038; Schuster, The Change Masters is Rosabeth Moss Kanter&#8217;s guide to innovation and entrepreneurship in the American corporation. The Change Masters looks behind the scenes at some of the most important companies in America, including Hewlett-Packard, General Electric, Polaroid, General Motors, Wang Laboratories and Honeywell, to describe their organizational structures, their corporate cultures, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-change-masters-innovation-and-entrepreneurship-in-the-american-corporation-rosabeth-moss-kanter-abridged/">The Change Masters : Innovation and Entrepreneurship in the American Corporation &#8211; Rosabeth Moss Kanter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Simon &#038; Schuster, The Change Masters is Rosabeth Moss Kanter&#8217;s guide to innovation and entrepreneurship in the American corporation.     </p>
<p>                    The Change Masters looks behind the scenes at some of the most important companies in America, including Hewlett-Packard, General Electric, Polaroid, General Motors, Wang Laboratories and Honeywell, to describe their organizational structures, their corporate cultures, and their specific strategies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-change-masters-innovation-and-entrepreneurship-in-the-american-corporation-rosabeth-moss-kanter-abridged/">The Change Masters : Innovation and Entrepreneurship in the American Corporation &#8211; Rosabeth Moss Kanter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ideal Team Player : How to Recognize and Cultivate The Three Essential Virtues &#8211; Patrick M. Lencioni (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ideal-team-player-how-to-recognize-and-cultivate-the-three-essential-virtues-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ideal-team-player-how-to-recognize-and-cultivate-the-three-essential-virtues-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his classic book, The Five Dysfunctions of a Team, Patrick Lencioni laid out a groundbreaking approach for tackling the perilous group behaviors that destroy teamwork. Here he turns his focus to the individual, revealing the three indispensable virtues of an ideal team player. In The Ideal Team Player, Lencioni tells the story of Jeff [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ideal-team-player-how-to-recognize-and-cultivate-the-three-essential-virtues-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/">The Ideal Team Player : How to Recognize and Cultivate The Three Essential Virtues &#8211; Patrick M. Lencioni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his classic book, The Five Dysfunctions of a Team, Patrick Lencioni laid out a groundbreaking approach for tackling the perilous group behaviors that destroy teamwork. Here he turns his focus to the individual, revealing the three indispensable virtues of an ideal team player. In The Ideal Team Player, Lencioni tells the story of Jeff Shanley, a leader desperate to save his uncle &#8216; company by restoring its cultural commitment to teamwork. Jeff must crack the code on the virtues that real team players possess, and then build a culture of hiring and development around those virtues. Beyond the fable, Lencioni presents a practical framework and actionable tools for identifying, hiring, and developing ideal team players.  Whether you re a leader trying to create a culture around teamwork, a staffing professional looking to hire real team players, or a team player wanting to improve yourself, this book will prove to be as useful as it is compelling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ideal-team-player-how-to-recognize-and-cultivate-the-three-essential-virtues-patrick-m-lencioni-abridged/">The Ideal Team Player : How to Recognize and Cultivate The Three Essential Virtues &#8211; Patrick M. Lencioni (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn or Die : Using Science to Build a Leading-Edge Learning Organization &#8211; Edward D. Hess (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To compete with today&#8217;s increasing globalization and rapidly evolving technologies, individuals and organizations must take their ability to learn-the foundation for continuous improvement, operational excellence, and innovation-to a much higher level. In Learn or Die, Edward D. Hess combines recent advances in neuroscience, psychology, behavioral economics, and education with key research on high-performance businesses to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/">Learn or Die : Using Science to Build a Leading-Edge Learning Organization &#8211; Edward D. Hess (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To compete with today&#8217;s increasing globalization and rapidly evolving technologies, individuals and organizations must take their ability to learn-the foundation for continuous improvement, operational excellence, and innovation-to a much higher level. In Learn or Die, Edward D. Hess combines recent advances in neuroscience, psychology, behavioral economics, and education with key research on high-performance businesses to create an actionable blueprint for becoming a leading-edge learning organization. Learn or Die examines the process of learning from an individual and an organizational standpoint. From an individual perspective, the book discusses the cognitive, emotional, motivational, attitudinal, and behavioral factors that promote better learning. Organizationally, Learn or Die focuses on the kinds of structures, culture, leadership, employee learning behaviors, and human resource policies that are necessary to create an environment that enables critical and innovative thinking, learning conversations, and collaboration.<br />
                    The volume also provides strategies to mitigate the reality that humans can be reflexive, lazy thinkers who seek confirmation of what they believe to be true and affirmation of their self-image. Exemplar learning organizations discussed include the secretive Bridgewater Associates, LP; Intuit, Inc.; United Parcel Service (UPS); W. L. Gore &#038; Associates; and IDEO.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/">Learn or Die : Using Science to Build a Leading-Edge Learning Organization &#8211; Edward D. Hess (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What You Don&#8217;t Know about Leadership, but Probably Should : Applications to Daily Life &#8211; Jeffrey A. Kottler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-you-dont-know-about-leadership-but-probably-should-applications-to-daily-life-jeffrey-a-kottler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-profitmaking Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-you-dont-know-about-leadership-but-probably-should-applications-to-daily-life-jeffrey-a-kottler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It is commonplace that counselors, therapists, teachers, business leaders, executives, coaches, and other helping professionals &#8211; specifically trained in group leadership &#8211; often fail to apply their knowledge and skills to settings in which they might matter most. The same practitioners who guide others may not be able to put that background to work when [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-you-dont-know-about-leadership-but-probably-should-applications-to-daily-life-jeffrey-a-kottler-abridged/">What You Don&#8217;t Know about Leadership, but Probably Should : Applications to Daily Life &#8211; Jeffrey A. Kottler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is commonplace that counselors, therapists, teachers, business leaders, executives, coaches, and other helping professionals &#8211; specifically trained in group leadership &#8211; often fail to apply their knowledge and skills to settings in which they might matter most. The same practitioners who guide others may not be able to put that background to work when they find themselves supervising peers, leading meetings, or even managing conflict at the dinner table. What<br />
                    You Don&#8217;t Know about Leadership, but Probably Should discusses ways that leadership skills and interventions can operate throughout daily life. Applications from group therapy and systemic intervention models will be applied to the realities that people face every day &#8211; inspiring others, facilitating<br />
                    meetings, running social events, guiding conversations, and empowering others. This text uniquely integrates the latest research, theory, concepts, and skills into a model that applies these ideas to every aspect of daily life. The author draws not only from the extensive literature in group dynamics, counseling, and psychology, but also includes insights from business leaders gleaned from over a dozen interviews he conducted.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-you-dont-know-about-leadership-but-probably-should-applications-to-daily-life-jeffrey-a-kottler-abridged/">What You Don&#8217;t Know about Leadership, but Probably Should : Applications to Daily Life &#8211; Jeffrey A. Kottler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover the secrets of one of the world&#8217;s leading talent acquisition experts In the newly revised Fourth Edition of Hire With Your Head: Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Great Teams, influential recruiting and hiring expert Lou Adler delivers a practical guide to consistently identifying and hiring the best people and scaling that process throughout your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/">Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover the secrets of one of the world&#8217;s leading talent acquisition experts    </p>
<p>                     In the newly revised Fourth Edition of Hire With Your Head: Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Great Teams, influential recruiting and hiring expert Lou Adler delivers a practical guide to consistently identifying and hiring the best people and scaling that process throughout your company.    </p>
<p>                     This book will help you address your hiring and recruitment issues, not just by making you more efficient, but also by reforming your entire process to align with how top talent actually look for new jobs, compare offers, and select opportunities.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll discover:    </p>
<p>                    Discover what it takes to ensure more Win-Win Hiring outcomes by hiring for the anniversary date rather than the start date<br />
                    How to use a &#8220;High Tech, High Touch&#8221; approach to raise the talent bar<br />
                    Expand the talent pool to include more outstanding, high potential and diverse talent by defining work as a series of key performance objectives    </p>
<p>                     Perfect for hiring managers, recruiters, and HR and business leaders, Hire with Your Head is a must-read resource for anyone seeking to improve their ability to find, attract, and retain the top talent the world has to offer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/">Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team of Teams : New Rules of Engagement for a Complex World &#8211; General Stanley McChrystal, David Silverman, Tantum Collins, Chris Fussell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Life & Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Tactics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Administration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if you could combine the agility, adaptability, and cohesion of a small team with the power and resources of a giant organization? When General Stanley McChrystal took command of the Joint Special Operations Task Force in Iraq in 2003, he quickly realized that conventional military tactics were failing. The allied forces had a huge [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/">Team of Teams : New Rules of Engagement for a Complex World &#8211; General Stanley McChrystal, David Silverman, Tantum Collins, Chris Fussell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What if you could combine the agility, adaptability, and cohesion of a small team with the power and resources of a giant organization?    </p>
<p>                    When General Stanley McChrystal took command of the Joint Special Operations Task Force in Iraq in 2003, he quickly realized that conventional military tactics were failing. The allied forces had a huge advantage in numbers, equipment and training &#8211; but none of the enemy&#8217;s speed and flexibility.    </p>
<p>                    McChrystal and his colleagues discarded a century of conventional wisdom to create a &#8216;team of teams&#8217; that combined extremely transparent communication with decentralized decision-making authority.     </p>
<p>                    Faster, flatter and more flexible, the task force beat back al-Qaeda.    </p>
<p>                    In this powerful book, McChrystal and his colleagues show how the challenges they faced in Iraq can be relevant to any leader. Through compelling examples, the authors demonstrate that the &#8216;team of teams&#8217; strategy has worked everywhere from hospital emergency rooms to NASA and has the potential to transform organizations large and small.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A bold argument that leaders can help teams become greater than the sum of their parts&#8217; Charles Duhigg, author of The Power of Habit    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An indispensable guide to organizational change&#8217; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/">Team of Teams : New Rules of Engagement for a Complex World &#8211; General Stanley McChrystal, David Silverman, Tantum Collins, Chris Fussell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Compound Effect (10th Anniversary Edition) : Jumpstart Your Income, Your Life, Your Success &#8211; Darren Hardy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-compound-effect-10th-anniversary-edition-jumpstart-your-income-your-life-your-success-darren-hardy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-compound-effect-10th-anniversary-edition-jumpstart-your-income-your-life-your-success-darren-hardy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want success? More success than you have now? And even more success than you ever imagined possible? That is what this book is about. Achieving it. No gimmicks. No hyperbole. Finally, just the truth on what it takes to earn success As the central curator of the success media industry for over 25 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-compound-effect-10th-anniversary-edition-jumpstart-your-income-your-life-your-success-darren-hardy-abridged/">The Compound Effect (10th Anniversary Edition) : Jumpstart Your Income, Your Life, Your Success &#8211; Darren Hardy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want success? More success than you have now? And even more success than you ever imagined possible? That is what this book is about. Achieving it.<br />
                    No gimmicks. No hyperbole. Finally, just the truth on what it takes to earn success<br />
                    As the central curator of the success media industry for over 25 years, author Darren Hardy has heard it all, seen it all, and tried most of it. This book reveals the core principles that drive success. The Compound Effect contains the essence of what every superachiever needs to know, practice, and master to obtain extraordinary success. Inside you will find strategies on: How to win&#8211;every time! The No. 1 strategy to achieve any goal and triumph over any competitor, even if they&#8217;re smarter, more talented or more experienced.Eradicating your bad habits (some you might be unaware of!) that are derailing your progress.Painlessly installing the few key disciplines required for major breakthroughs.The real, lasting keys to motivation&#8211;how to get yourself to do things you don&#8217;t feel like doing.Capturing the elusive, awesome force of momentum. Catch this, and you&#8217;ll be unstoppable.The acceleration secrets of superachievers. Do they have an unfair advantage? Yes, they do, and now you can too!If you&#8217;re serious about living an extraordinary life, use the power of The Compound Effect to create the success you desire. Begin your journey today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-compound-effect-10th-anniversary-edition-jumpstart-your-income-your-life-your-success-darren-hardy-abridged/">The Compound Effect (10th Anniversary Edition) : Jumpstart Your Income, Your Life, Your Success &#8211; Darren Hardy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Humanity Works : Merging Technologies and People for the Workforce of the Future &#8211; Alexandra Levit (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/humanity-works-merging-technologies-and-people-for-the-workforce-of-the-future-alexandra-levit-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Systems & Equipment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humanity-works-merging-technologies-and-people-for-the-workforce-of-the-future-alexandra-levit-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DISTINGUISHED FAVOURITE: Independent Press Award 2020 &#8211; Business General Category The professional landscape is transforming, and the only way to maintain competitive advantage is to maximize the unique skills of your workforce. In Humanity Works, bestselling author, global workplace consultant and futurist Alexandra Levit provides a guide to making the most of the human traits [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humanity-works-merging-technologies-and-people-for-the-workforce-of-the-future-alexandra-levit-abridged/">Humanity Works : Merging Technologies and People for the Workforce of the Future &#8211; Alexandra Levit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DISTINGUISHED FAVOURITE: Independent Press Award 2020 &#8211; Business General Category    </p>
<p>                    The professional landscape is transforming, and the only way to maintain competitive advantage is to maximize the unique skills of your workforce. In Humanity Works, bestselling author, global workplace consultant and futurist Alexandra Levit provides a guide to making the most of the human traits of creativity, judgement, problem solving and interpersonal sensitivity. Revealing what the &#8216;robot takeover&#8217; will really look like, how talent and machines can work side by side and how you can make organizational structures more agile and innovation focused, this book will prepare you to lead organizations of the future.    </p>
<p>                    Humanity Works doesn&#8217;t just explain the fascinating trends of the future of work; it condenses cutting-edge academic and business thinking to show what you can do about the future right now. Original, real-life case studies including Nestle, The Washington Post, Deloitte, and Pepsi combined with exercises and workplace tools will equip you for staying innovative and successful in the wake of major workplace disruption. Everything hinges on capturing the human edge in your organization.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humanity-works-merging-technologies-and-people-for-the-workforce-of-the-future-alexandra-levit-abridged/">Humanity Works : Merging Technologies and People for the Workforce of the Future &#8211; Alexandra Levit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE BUSINESS BOOK AWARDS 2021 In The 4 Day Week, entrepreneur and business innovator Andrew Barnes makes the case for the four-day work week as the answer to many of the ills of the 21st-century global economy. Barnes conducted an experiment in his own business, the New Zealand trust company Perpetual Guardian, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/">The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE BUSINESS BOOK AWARDS 2021    </p>
<p>                    In The 4 Day Week, entrepreneur and business innovator Andrew Barnes makes the case for the four-day work week as the answer to many of the ills of the 21st-century global economy.     </p>
<p>                     Barnes conducted an experiment in his own business, the New Zealand trust company Perpetual Guardian, and asked his staff to design a four-day week that would permit them to meet their existing productivity requirements on the same salary but with a 20% cut in work hours. The outcomes of this trial, which no business leader had previously attempted on these terms, were stunning. People were happier and healthier, more engaged in their personal lives, and more focused and productive in the office.    </p>
<p>                     The world of work has seen a dramatic shift in recent times: the former security and benefits associated with permanent employment are being displaced by the less stable gig economy. Barnes explains the dangers of a focus on flexibility at the expense of hard-won worker protections, and argues that with the four-day week, we can have the best of all worlds: optimal productivity, work-life balance, worker benefits and, at long last, a solution to pervasive economic inequities such as the gender pay gap and lack of diversity in business and governance.     </p>
<p>                     The 4 Day Week is a practical, how-to guide for business leaders and employees alike that is applicable to nearly every industry. Using qualitative and quantitative data from research gathered through the Perpetual Guardian trial and other sources by the University of Auckland and Auckland University of Technology, the book presents a step-by-step approach to preparing businesses for productivity-focused flexibility, from the necessary cultural conditions to the often complex legislative considerations.    </p>
<p>                     The story of Perpetual Guardian&#8217;s unprecedented work experiment has made headlines around the world and stormed social media, reaching a global audience in more than seventy countries. A mix of trenchant analysis, personal observation and actionable advice, The 4 Day Week is an essential guide for leaders and workers seeking to make a change for the better in their work world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/">The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Place To Work : The Art and Science of Creating an Extraordinary Workplace &#8211; Ron Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Malcolm Gladwell, Daniel Pink, and Freakonomics, comes a captivating and surprising journey through the science of workplace excellence. Why do successful companies reward failure? What can casinos teach us about building a happy workplace? How do you design an office that enhances both attention to detail and creativity? In The Best Place [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/">The Best Place To Work : The Art and Science of Creating an Extraordinary Workplace &#8211; Ron Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Malcolm Gladwell, Daniel Pink, and Freakonomics, comes a captivating and surprising journey through the science of workplace excellence.    </p>
<p>                     Why do successful companies reward failure?<br />
                     What can casinos teach us about building a happy workplace?<br />
                     How do you design an office that enhances both attention to detail and creativity?     </p>
<p>                     In The Best Place to Work, award-winning psychologist Ron Friedman, Ph.D. uses the latest research from the fields of motivation, creativity, behavioral economics, neuroscience, and management to reveal what really makes us successful at work. Combining powerful stories with cutting edge findings, Friedman shows leaders at every level how they can use scientifically-proven techniques to promote smarter thinking, greater innovation, and stronger performance.     </p>
<p>                     Among the many surprising insights, Friedman explains how learning to think like a hostage negotiator can help you diffuse a workplace argument, why placing a fish bowl near your desk can elevate your thinking, and how incorporating strategic distractions into your schedule can help you reach smarter decisions. Along the way, the book introduces the inventor who created the cubicle, the president who brought down the world&#8217;s most dangerous criminal, and the teenager who single-handedly transformed professional tennis&#8211;vivid stories that offer unexpected revelations on achieving workplace excellence.     </p>
<p>                     Brimming with counterintuitive insights and actionable recommendations, The Best Place to Work offers employees and executives alike game-changing advice for working smarter and turning any organization&#8211;regardless of its size, budgets, or ambitions&#8211;into an extraordinary workplace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-best-place-to-work-the-art-and-science-of-creating-an-extraordinary-workplace-ron-friedman-abridged/">The Best Place To Work : The Art and Science of Creating an Extraordinary Workplace &#8211; Ron Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Employee Experience Advantage : How to Win the War for Talent by Giving Employees the Workspaces they Want, the Tools they Need, and a Culture They Can Celebrate &#8211; Jacob Morgan, Foreword by Marshall Goldsmith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-employee-experience-advantage-how-to-win-the-war-for-talent-by-giving-employees-the-workspaces-they-want-the-tools-they-need-and-a-culture-they-can-celebrate-jacob-morgan-foreword-by-m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-employee-experience-advantage-how-to-win-the-war-for-talent-by-giving-employees-the-workspaces-they-want-the-tools-they-need-and-a-culture-they-can-celebrate-jacob-morgan-foreword-by-m/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Research Shows Organizations That Focus on Employee Experience Far Outperform Those That Don&#8217;t Recently a new type of organization has emerged, one that focuses on employee experiences as a way to drive innovation, increase customer satisfaction, find and hire the best people, make work more engaging, and improve overall performance. The Employee Experience Advantage is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-employee-experience-advantage-how-to-win-the-war-for-talent-by-giving-employees-the-workspaces-they-want-the-tools-they-need-and-a-culture-they-can-celebrate-jacob-morgan-foreword-by-m/">The Employee Experience Advantage : How to Win the War for Talent by Giving Employees the Workspaces they Want, the Tools they Need, and a Culture They Can Celebrate &#8211; Jacob Morgan, Foreword by Marshall Goldsmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Research Shows Organizations That Focus on Employee Experience Far Outperform Those That Don&#8217;t Recently a new type of organization has emerged, one that focuses on employee experiences as a way to drive innovation, increase customer satisfaction, find and hire the best people, make work more engaging, and improve overall performance. The Employee Experience Advantage is the first book of its kind to tackle this emerging topic that is becoming the #1 priority for business leaders around the world. Although everyone talks about employee experience nobody has really been able to explain concretely what it is and how to go about designing for it&#8230;until now. How can organizations truly create a place where employees want to show up to work versus need to show up to work? For decades the business world has focused on measuring employee engagement meanwhile global engagement scores remain at an all time low despite all the surveys and institutes that been springing up tackle this problem. Clearly something is not working. Employee engagement has become the short-term adrenaline shot that organizations turn to when they need to increase their engagement scores.<br />
                    Instead, we have to focus on designing employee experiences which is the long term organizational design that leads to engaged employees. This is the only long-term solution. Organizations have been stuck focusing on the cause instead of the effect. The cause is employee experience; the effect is an engaged workforce. Backed by an extensive research project that looked at over 150 studies and articles, featured extensive interviews with over 150 executives, and analyzed over 250 global organizations, this book clearly breaks down the three environments that make up every single employee experience at every organization around the world and how to design for them. These are the cultural, technological, and physical environments. This book explores the attributes that organizations need to focus on in each one of these environments to create COOL spaces, ACE technology, and a CELEBRATED culture. Featuring exclusive case studies, unique frameworks, and never before seen research, The Employee Experience Advantage guides readers on a journey of creating a place where people actually want to show up to work.<br />
                    Readers will learn: * The trends shaping employee experience * How to evaluate their own employee experience using the Employee Experience Score * What the world&#8217;s leading organizations are doing around employee experience * How to design for technology, culture, and physical spaces * The role people analytics place in employee experience * Frameworks for how to actually create employee experiences * The role of the gig economy * The future of employee experience * Nine types of organizations that focus on employee experience * And much more! There is no question that engaged employees perform better, aspire higher, and achieve more, but you can&#8217;t create employee engagement without designing employee experiences first. It&#8217;s time to rethink your strategy and implement a real-world framework that focuses on how to create an organization where people want to show up to work. The Employee Experience Advantage shows you how to do just that.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-employee-experience-advantage-how-to-win-the-war-for-talent-by-giving-employees-the-workspaces-they-want-the-tools-they-need-and-a-culture-they-can-celebrate-jacob-morgan-foreword-by-m/">The Employee Experience Advantage : How to Win the War for Talent by Giving Employees the Workspaces they Want, the Tools they Need, and a Culture They Can Celebrate &#8211; Jacob Morgan, Foreword by Marshall Goldsmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joy, Inc : How We Built a Workplace People Love &#8211; Richard Sheridan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A guidebook for how leaders can motivate, engage, and recognize their people all the while growing the business profitably.&#8221; &#8211;Forbes.com Every year, thousands of visitors come from around the world to visit Menlo Innovations, a small software company in Ann Arbor, Michigan. They make the trek not to learn about technology but to witness a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/">Joy, Inc : How We Built a Workplace People Love &#8211; Richard Sheridan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A guidebook for how leaders can motivate, engage, and recognize their people all the while growing the business profitably.&#8221; &#8211;Forbes.com     </p>
<p>                    Every year, thousands of visitors come from around the world to visit Menlo Innovations, a small software company in Ann Arbor, Michigan. They make the trek not to learn about technology but to witness a radically different approach to company culture.     </p>
<p>                    CEO Rich Sheridan removed the fear and ambiguity that typically make a workplace miserable. With joy as the explicit goal, he and his team changed everything about how the company was run. The results blew away all expectations. Menlo has won numerous growth awards and was named an Inc. magazine &#8220;audacious small company.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Joy, Inc. offers an inside look at how Menlo created its culture, and shows how any organization can follow their methods for a more passionate team and sustainable, profitable results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-inc-how-we-built-a-workplace-people-love-richard-sheridan-abridged/">Joy, Inc : How We Built a Workplace People Love &#8211; Richard Sheridan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Education, Continuous Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Services & Welfare, Criminology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants. As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants.    </p>
<p>                    As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise the question-how will they transform society, the economy, and politics? If companies need fewer workers due to automation and robotics, what happens to those who once held those jobs and don&#8217;t have the skills for new jobs? And since many social benefits are delivered through jobs, how are people outside the workforce for a lengthy period of time going to earn a living and get health care and social benefits?    </p>
<p>                    Looking past today&#8217;s headlines, political scientist and cultural observer Darrell M. West argues that society needs to rethink the concept of jobs, reconfigure the social contract, move toward a system of lifetime learning, and develop a new kind of politics that can deal with economic dislocations. With the U.S. governance system in shambles because of political polarization and hyper-partisanship, dealing creatively with the transition to a fully digital economy will vex political leaders and complicate the adoption of remedies that could ease the transition pain. It is imperative that we make major adjustments in how we think about work and the social contract in order to prevent society from spiraling out of control.    </p>
<p>                    This book presents a number of proposals to help people deal with the transition from an industrial to a digital economy. We must broaden the  concept of employment to include volunteering and parenting and pay greater attention to the opportunities for leisure time. New forms of identity will be possible when the &#8220;job&#8221; no longer defines people&#8217;s sense of personal meaning, and they engage in a broader range of activities. Workers will need help throughout their lifetimes to acquire new skills and develop new job capabilities. Political reforms will be necessary to  reduce polarization and restore civility so there can be open and healthy debate about where responsibility lies for economic well-being.    </p>
<p>                    This book is an important contribution to a discussion about tomorrow-one that needs to take place today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Great People Decisions : Why They Matter So Much, Why They are So Hard, and How You Can Master Them &#8211; Claudio Fernández-Aráoz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/great-people-decisions-why-they-matter-so-much-why-they-are-so-hard-and-how-you-can-master-them-claudio-fernandez-araoz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/great-people-decisions-why-they-matter-so-much-why-they-are-so-hard-and-how-you-can-master-them-claudio-fernandez-araoz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Great People Decisions &#8220;Fernandez-Araoz has captured the essence of building great teams with a masterful and entirely practical study of what goes into getting people selection right.&#8221; &#8211;JACK WELCH &#8220;Fernandez-Araoz does a great service with this wonderful book, teaching us how to accomplish the first task of any exceptional leader: get the right [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/great-people-decisions-why-they-matter-so-much-why-they-are-so-hard-and-how-you-can-master-them-claudio-fernandez-araoz-abridged/">Great People Decisions : Why They Matter So Much, Why They are So Hard, and How You Can Master Them &#8211; Claudio Fernández-Aráoz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Great People Decisions  &#8220;Fernandez-Araoz has captured the essence of building great teams with a masterful and entirely practical study of what goes into getting people selection right.&#8221; &#8211;JACK WELCH  &#8220;Fernandez-Araoz does a great service with this wonderful book, teaching us how to accomplish the first task of any exceptional leader: get the right people on the bus, and into the right seats. His enduring passion, deep practical experience, and analytical methods make his approach refreshing and powerful.&#8221;  &#8211;JIM COLLINS, bestselling author of Good to Great  &#8220;No matter your business or product, your service or strategy, it&#8217;s all done with people. Great results only come when great people fill the right roles. In Great People Decisions, Fernandez-Araoz clears away the fog of myth and fad that has long clouded people decisions, bringing passion, sound experience, and wisdom to these all-important questions.&#8221; &#8211;DANIEL GOLEMAN, bestselling author of Emotional Intelligence and Social Intelligence  &#8220;Great People Decisions is a groundbreaking, myth-busting, and standard-setting work.<br />
                    To prepare yourself for the dramatic workforce changes that are expected in the next decade, the first thing you should do is read this book. The second thing you should do is put Fernandez-Araoz&#8217;s advice into practice immediately.&#8221; &#8211;JIM KOUZES, bestselling coauthor of The Leadership Challenge and A Leader&#8217;s Legacy  &#8220;Too many people say &#8216;people are our most important assets&#8217; but then don&#8217;t act on it. In this important and eloquent book, Fernandez-Araoz provides compelling evidence for why making great people decisions is essential for anyone who aspires to become a great leader or build a great company. If you follow the sage advice he offers in this book, you are sure to make great people decisions.&#8221; &#8211;NITIN NOHRIA, Senior Associate Dean of Faculty Development, Harvard Business School, and coauthor of Paths to Power and In Their Time</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/great-people-decisions-why-they-matter-so-much-why-they-are-so-hard-and-how-you-can-master-them-claudio-fernandez-araoz-abridged/">Great People Decisions : Why They Matter So Much, Why They are So Hard, and How You Can Master Them &#8211; Claudio Fernández-Aráoz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dream Teams : Working Together Without Falling Apart &#8211; Shane Snow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dream-teams-working-together-without-falling-apart-shane-snow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dream-teams-working-together-without-falling-apart-shane-snow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An adventure into the very human science of making breakthroughs together.&#8217; &#8211; Charles Duhigg, Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist and author of The Power of Habit The best groups are more than the sum of their parts &#8211; but why does teamwork so often fail to fulfill this promise? Award-winning entrepreneur and journalist Shane Snow takes us [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dream-teams-working-together-without-falling-apart-shane-snow-abridged/">Dream Teams : Working Together Without Falling Apart &#8211; Shane Snow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An adventure into the very human science of making breakthroughs together.&#8217; &#8211; Charles Duhigg, Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist and author of The Power of Habit    </p>
<p>                    The best groups are more than the sum of their parts &#8211; but why does teamwork so often fail to fulfill this promise?     </p>
<p>                    Award-winning entrepreneur and journalist Shane Snow takes us on an extraordinary tour of the hidden science of team dynamics, revealing the counterintuitive reasons that some groups break out while far too many break down.    </p>
<p>                    Examining history-making groups like the Wu Tang Clan and the Russian national hockey side alongside teams whose failures have had lasting impact, Snow reveals the answers, and what the rest of us can learn from the rare teams that do the impossible together. In this stimulating, pacey adventure through history, neuroscience, psychology, sports and business, Snow explores the secrets of the best teams the world has to offer.     </p>
<p>                    You&#8217;ll discover:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; How ragtag teams &#8211; from soccer clubs to startups to gangs of pirates &#8211; beat the odds throughout history    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Why DaimlerChrysler flopped while the Wu-Tang Clan succeeded, and the surprising factor behind most failed mergers, marriages, and partnerships    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; What the Wright Brothers&#8217; daily arguments can teach us about group problem solving    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; The true stories of pioneering women in law enforcement, unlikely civil rights collaborators, and underdog armies that did the incredible together    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; The team players behind great social movements in history, and the science of becoming open-minded.    </p>
<p>                    Provocative and entertaining, Dream Teams is a landmark work that will change the way we think about progress and collaboration.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dream-teams-working-together-without-falling-apart-shane-snow-abridged/">Dream Teams : Working Together Without Falling Apart &#8211; Shane Snow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dying for a Paycheck &#8211; Jeffrey Pfeffer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dying-for-a-paycheck-jeffrey-pfeffer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dying-for-a-paycheck-jeffrey-pfeffer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In one survey, 61 percent of employees said that workplace stress had made them sick and 7 percent said they had actually been hospitalized. Job stress costs US employers more than $300 billion annually and may cause 120,000 excess deaths each year. In China, 1 million people a year may be dying from overwork. People [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dying-for-a-paycheck-jeffrey-pfeffer-abridged/">Dying for a Paycheck &#8211; Jeffrey Pfeffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In one survey, 61 percent of employees said that workplace stress had made them sick and 7 percent said they had actually been hospitalized. Job stress costs US employers more than $300 billion annually and may cause 120,000 excess deaths each year. In China, 1 million people a year may be dying from overwork. People are literally dying for a paycheck. And it needs to stop.    </p>
<p>                    In this timely, provocative book, Jeffrey Pfeffer contends that many modern management commonalities such as long work hours, work-family conflict, and economic insecurity are toxic to employees&#8211;hurting engagement, increasing turnover, and destroying people&#8217;s physical and emotional health&#8211;and also inimical to company performance. He argues that human sustainability should be as important as environmental stewardship.    </p>
<p>                    You don&#8217;t have to do a physically dangerous job to confront a health-destroying, possibly life-threatening, workplace. Just ask the manager in a senior finance role whose immense workload, once handled by several employees, required frequent all-nighters&#8211;leading to alcohol and drug addiction. Or the dedicated news media producer whose commitment to getting the story resulted in a sixty-pound weight gain thanks to having no down time to eat properly or exercise. Or the marketing professional prescribed antidepressants a week after joining her employer.    </p>
<p>                    In Dying for a Paycheck, Jeffrey Pfeffer marshals a vast trove of evidence and numerous examples from all over the world to expose the infuriating truth about modern work life: even as organizations allow management practices that literally sicken and kill their employees, those policies do not enhance productivity or the bottom line, thereby creating a lose-lose situation.    </p>
<p>                    Exploring a range of important topics including layoffs, health insurance, work-family conflict, work hours, job autonomy, and why people remain in toxic environments, Pfeffer offers guidance and practical solutions all of us&#8211;employees, employers, and the government&#8211;can use to enhance workplace wellbeing. We must wake up to the dangers and enormous costs of today&#8217;s workplace, Pfeffer argues. Dying for a Paycheck is a clarion call for a social movement focused on human sustainability. Pfeffer makes clear that the environment we work in is just as important as the one we live in, and with this urgent book, he opens our eyes and shows how we can make our workplaces healthier and better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dying-for-a-paycheck-jeffrey-pfeffer-abridged/">Dying for a Paycheck &#8211; Jeffrey Pfeffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anything You Want : 40 Lessons for a New Kind of Entrepreneur &#8211; Derek Sivers (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anything-you-want-40-lessons-for-a-new-kind-of-entrepreneur-derek-sivers-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anything-you-want-40-lessons-for-a-new-kind-of-entrepreneur-derek-sivers-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I love this book! If you want a true manifesto, a guidebook with clear signposts, and a fun ride you&#8217;ll return to again and again, you have it here in this book. I hope you enjoy it as much as I did&#8217; Tim Ferriss, author of The 4-Hour Workweek The iconic manifesto on lessons learned [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anything-you-want-40-lessons-for-a-new-kind-of-entrepreneur-derek-sivers-abridged/">Anything You Want : 40 Lessons for a New Kind of Entrepreneur &#8211; Derek Sivers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I love this book! If you want a true manifesto, a guidebook with clear signposts, and a fun ride you&#8217;ll return to again and again, you have it here in this book. I hope you enjoy it as much as I did&#8217; Tim Ferriss, author of The 4-Hour Workweek      </p>
<p>                    The iconic manifesto on lessons learned while becoming an entrepreneur    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;    </p>
<p>                    You don&#8217;t need a visionary master plan, loads of funding or a brilliant team to start a business.    </p>
<p>                    When Derek Sivers started CD Baby, he wasn&#8217;t planning on building a major business. He was a successful independent musician who just wanted to sell his CDs online. He started in 1998 by helping his friends sell their CDs too. In 2000, he hired his first employee. Eight years later, he sold CD Baby for $22 million.    </p>
<p>                    Sivers didn&#8217;t need a business plan and neither do you. You don&#8217;t need to think big; in fact, it&#8217;s better if you don&#8217;t. Anything You Want will inspire you to start with what you have, care about your customers more than yourself, and run your business like you don&#8217;t need the money.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Some of the best hours you&#8217;ll ever spend will be reading Derek Sivers&#8217;s new book&#8230;Anything You Want&#8217; Forbes</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anything-you-want-40-lessons-for-a-new-kind-of-entrepreneur-derek-sivers-abridged/">Anything You Want : 40 Lessons for a New Kind of Entrepreneur &#8211; Derek Sivers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leadership is Half the Story : A Fresh Look at Followership, Leadership, and Collaboration &#8211; Marc Hurwitz, Samantha Hurwitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leadership-is-half-the-story-a-fresh-look-at-followership-leadership-and-collaboration-marc-hurwitz-samantha-hurwitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-profitmaking Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leadership-is-half-the-story-a-fresh-look-at-followership-leadership-and-collaboration-marc-hurwitz-samantha-hurwitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Can you imagine a choreographer only training one dancer to lead while his or her partner sits in the lobby staring at the wall? Yet we do this all the time in organizations. Half the partnership is missing. Leadership is Half the Story introduces the first model to seamlessly integrate leadership, followership, and partnerships. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-is-half-the-story-a-fresh-look-at-followership-leadership-and-collaboration-marc-hurwitz-samantha-hurwitz-abridged/">Leadership is Half the Story : A Fresh Look at Followership, Leadership, and Collaboration &#8211; Marc Hurwitz, Samantha Hurwitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Can you imagine a choreographer only training one dancer to lead while his or her partner sits in the lobby staring at the wall? Yet we do this all the time in organizations. Half the partnership is missing.  Leadership is Half the Story introduces the first model to seamlessly integrate leadership, followership, and partnerships. This research-backed, field-tested book contributes many new ideas and practical advice for everyone in an organization &#8211; from CEO to HR director to front-line manager to consultant.  All of us lead, not just those with the formal title. All of us follow, not just front-line staff. In great collaborations, one moment we are leading and then we flip to following; in other words, the relationship between leadership and followership is dynamic, context-specific, and ever-evolving. This empowering perspective opens up leadership to everyone, normalizes followership, and enables more productive and innovative collaborations. Candid discussions about both roles allow for better coaching, mentoring, skill development, and interpersonal agility, and result in stronger teams.<br />
                    Marc and Samantha Hurwitz give us a category-busting book that &#8220;practically glows with energy and vision,&#8221; according to Marshall Goldsmith, executive coach and best-selling author of What Got You Here Won&#8217;t Get You There.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-is-half-the-story-a-fresh-look-at-followership-leadership-and-collaboration-marc-hurwitz-samantha-hurwitz-abridged/">Leadership is Half the Story : A Fresh Look at Followership, Leadership, and Collaboration &#8211; Marc Hurwitz, Samantha Hurwitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that philosophy and illustrates how successful businesses have redefined themselves in the new customer universe.    </p>
<p>                    Personality Not Included is a powerhouse resource packed with bold new insights that show you how to shed the lifeless armor of your business and rediscover the soul of your brand. Sharing stories from the ethos of the world&#8217;s weirdest city, to how Manga has taken the comic book industry by storm, to showcasing brands like Intel, Boeing, ING, and Dyson, Bhargava shows you why personality matters from the inside out.    </p>
<p>                    In Part One, you&#8217;ll be introduced to the key components to building a personality and learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    Recognize the greatest myth that most marketers blindly follow, and how to get past itUse the &#8220;UAT Filter&#8221; to understand the personality of your organization and products in order to develop a communication strategy that drives your marketingCreate your company&#8217;s &#8220;marketing backstory&#8221; using techniques pioneered by Hollywood screenwritersHarness the influence of &#8220;accidental spokespeople&#8221; and use it to your advantageNavigate the roadblocks of using personality that come from bosses, peers, investors, and lawyers, without getting fired or flamedPinpoint and capitalize on the moments where personality can make a difference<br />
                    Part Two is packed with guides, tools, and techniques to help you flawlessly implement your plan. It features practical, step-by-step lessons that help you effectively move from theory to action, and includes a valuable collection of guides, checklists, question forms, printable resources, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Don&#8217;t be another faceless company-learn the new rules for succeeding in the social media era with Personality Not Included.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Work Rules! : Insights from Inside Google That Will Transform How You Live and Lead &#8211; Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times and Wall Street Journal Bestseller Daily Telegraph, Huffington Post &#038; Business Insider Top Business Book to Read &#8216;Every year, 2 million people apply for a job at Google &#8211; so what&#8217;s the secret?&#8217; Guardian A compelling manifesto with the potential to change how we work and live, Work Rules! offers both [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/">Work Rules! : Insights from Inside Google That Will Transform How You Live and Lead &#8211; Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times and Wall Street Journal Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Daily Telegraph, Huffington Post &#038; Business Insider Top Business Book to Read     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Every year, 2 million people apply for a job at Google &#8211; so what&#8217;s the secret?&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    A compelling manifesto with the potential to change how we work and live, Work Rules! offers both a philosophy of the new world of work and a blueprint for attracting the most spectacular talent and ensuring the brightest and best prosper. The way we work is changing &#8211; are you?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/">Work Rules! : Insights from Inside Google That Will Transform How You Live and Lead &#8211; Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Co-Active Coaching : The proven framework for transformative conversations at work and in life &#8211; 4th edition &#8211; Henry Kimsey-House, Karen Kimsey-House, Phillip Sandahl, Alexis Phillips, Laura Whitworth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/co-active-coaching-the-proven-framework-for-transformative-conversations-at-work-and-in-life-4th-edition-henry-kimsey-house-karen-kimsey-house-phillip-sandahl-alexis-phillips-laura-whitworth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/co-active-coaching-the-proven-framework-for-transformative-conversations-at-work-and-in-life-4th-edition-henry-kimsey-house-karen-kimsey-house-phillip-sandahl-alexis-phillips-laura-whitworth/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The definitive edition &#8211; updated and expanded, with access to an online toolkit. &#8216;The bible of coaching guides&#8230;No other book gives you the tools, skills, and the fundamentals needed to succeed in these delicate relationships.&#8217; Stephen R. Covey, Author of The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People Co-Active Coaching offers current and aspiring coaches, leaders [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/co-active-coaching-the-proven-framework-for-transformative-conversations-at-work-and-in-life-4th-edition-henry-kimsey-house-karen-kimsey-house-phillip-sandahl-alexis-phillips-laura-whitworth/">Co-Active Coaching : The proven framework for transformative conversations at work and in life &#8211; 4th edition &#8211; Henry Kimsey-House, Karen Kimsey-House, Phillip Sandahl, Alexis Phillips, Laura Whitworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The definitive edition &#8211; updated and expanded, with access to an online toolkit.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The bible of coaching guides&#8230;No other book gives you the tools, skills, and the fundamentals needed to succeed in these delicate relationships.&#8217; Stephen R. Covey, Author of The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People    </p>
<p>                    Co-Active Coaching offers current and aspiring coaches, leaders and managers in organisations and anyone wanting to strengthen interpersonal relationships, a practical, yet transformative communication process called the Co-Active Model.  Since its creation by the authors more than 25 years ago, the Co-Active Model and the book have formed the foundation of the authors&#8217; six-part coach training program delivered globally to tens of thousands of individuals each year through the authors&#8217; training institute, CTI.      </p>
<p>                    With its origins in the coaching profession, the Co-Active Model also applies to work and interpersonal relationships because it is based on principles of effective communication backed by current scientific research. In this highly-anticipated new edition, the universal applicability of the the Co-Active Model is emphasised. It goes beyond the one-on-one coach/coachee structure to include guidance for leaders and managers on how they can add a coaching competency to their professional skill set.    </p>
<p>                    New to this edition:    </p>
<p>                    * Every chapter has been updated for relevance and direct application to coaching in all of its forms, including in the workplace<br />
                    * New material covering: current neuroscience research, Co-Active approaches to leadership development and working with groups and teams<br />
                    *       More examples drawn from the authors&#8217; first-hand experiences, especially in workplace settings<br />
                    * More examples of the Co-Active Model applied internationally<br />
                    *       Updated/fine-tuned glossary (less jargon)<br />
                    *       Web-based &#8216;Toolkit&#8217; with 27 exercises, questionnaires, checklists, and reproducible forms</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/co-active-coaching-the-proven-framework-for-transformative-conversations-at-work-and-in-life-4th-edition-henry-kimsey-house-karen-kimsey-house-phillip-sandahl-alexis-phillips-laura-whitworth/">Co-Active Coaching : The proven framework for transformative conversations at work and in life &#8211; 4th edition &#8211; Henry Kimsey-House, Karen Kimsey-House, Phillip Sandahl, Alexis Phillips, Laura Whitworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Extraordinary Influence : How Great Leaders Bring Out the Best in Others &#8211; Dr. Tim Irwin, Foreword by Tim Tassopoulos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/extraordinary-influence-how-great-leaders-bring-out-the-best-in-others-dr-tim-irwin-foreword-by-tim-tassopoulos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/extraordinary-influence-how-great-leaders-bring-out-the-best-in-others-dr-tim-irwin-foreword-by-tim-tassopoulos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The age-old question for every leader-how do we bring out the best in those we lead? Anyone who has run a company, raised a family, lead an army, or coached a team struggles to find the key to help others excel and realize their potential. It is surprising how often we resort to criticism vs. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/extraordinary-influence-how-great-leaders-bring-out-the-best-in-others-dr-tim-irwin-foreword-by-tim-tassopoulos-abridged/">Extraordinary Influence : How Great Leaders Bring Out the Best in Others &#8211; Dr. Tim Irwin, Foreword by Tim Tassopoulos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The age-old question for every leader-how do we bring out the best in those we lead? Anyone who has run a company, raised a family, lead an army, or coached a team struggles to find the key to help others excel and realize their potential. It is surprising how often we resort to criticism vs. an approach that actually results in a better worker and a better person.     </p>
<p>                     What if we could speak Words of Life that transform those under our influence and ignite fires of intrinsic motivation? What if those we lead found great purpose in what they do and worked at their jobs with all their heart? Isn&#8217;t that what leaders, parents and teachers really want? Ultimately, don&#8217;t we hope to foster intrinsic motivation so that the individuals we lead become better employees, better students or better athletes? Recent discoveries of brain science and the wisdom of top CEO&#8217;s that Dr. Tim Irwin interviewed for this book give us the answers we&#8217;ve long sought.    </p>
<p>                     In most organizations, the methods used to provide feedback to employees such as performance appraisal or multi-rater feedback systems, in fact, accomplish the exact opposite of what we intend. We inadvertently speak Words of Death. Brain science tells us that these methods tend to engage a natural &#8220;negativity bias&#8221; that is hardwired in us all.    </p>
<p>                     Science in recent years discovered that affirmation sets in motion huge positive changes in the brain. It releases certain neuro chemicals associated with well-being and higher performance. Amazingly, criticism creates just the opposite neural reaction. The most primitive part of the brain goes into hyper defense mode, compromising our performance, torpedoing our motivation and limiting access to our higher-order strengths.    </p>
<p>                     How do we redirect employees who are out-of-line without engaging our natural &#8220;negativity bias?&#8221; Leaders must forever ban the term, &#8220;Constructive Criticism.&#8221; Brain science tells us that we can establish a connection between the employee&#8217;s work and his or her aspirations. This book calls for a new approach to align workers with an organization&#8217;s mission, strategy and goals, called Alliance Feedback.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/extraordinary-influence-how-great-leaders-bring-out-the-best-in-others-dr-tim-irwin-foreword-by-tim-tassopoulos-abridged/">Extraordinary Influence : How Great Leaders Bring Out the Best in Others &#8211; Dr. Tim Irwin, Foreword by Tim Tassopoulos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Radical Collaboration : Five Essential Skills To Overcome Defensiveness And Build Successful Relationships &#8211; James W. Tamm, Ronald J. Luyet (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The second edition of the essential guide, updated with new research and observations to help twenty-first century organizations create models for effective collaboration. Collaborative skills have never been more important to a company&#8217;s success and these skills are essential for every worker today. Radical Collaboration is a how-to-manual for creating trusting, cooperative environments, and transforming [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/">Radical Collaboration : Five Essential Skills To Overcome Defensiveness And Build Successful Relationships &#8211; James W. Tamm, Ronald J. Luyet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The second edition of the essential guide, updated with new research and observations to help twenty-first century organizations create models for effective collaboration.    </p>
<p>                    Collaborative skills have never been more important to a company&#8217;s success and these skills are essential for every worker today. Radical Collaboration is a how-to-manual for creating trusting, cooperative environments, and transforming groups into motivated and empowered teams. James W. Tamm and Ronald J. Luyet provide tools that will help you increase your ability to work successfully with others, learn to be more aware of colleagues, and better problem-solve and negotiate.     </p>
<p>                    Radical Collaboration is an eye-opener for leaders, managers, HR professionals, agents, trainers, and consultants who are seeking constructive ways of getting the results they want.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-collaboration-five-essential-skills-to-overcome-defensiveness-and-build-successful-relationships-james-w-tamm-ronald-j-luyet-abridged/">Radical Collaboration : Five Essential Skills To Overcome Defensiveness And Build Successful Relationships &#8211; James W. Tamm, Ronald J. Luyet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Talent Magnetism : How to Build a Workplace That Attracts and Keeps the Best &#8211; Roberta Chinsky Matuson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/talent-magnetism-how-to-build-a-workplace-that-attracts-and-keeps-the-best-roberta-chinsky-matuson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/talent-magnetism-how-to-build-a-workplace-that-attracts-and-keeps-the-best-roberta-chinsky-matuson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Talent Magnetism offers straightforward, easy-to-apply techniques that help managers navigate the challenges of attracting and keeping talent to foster innovation and fuel growth. Roberta Matuson, bestselling author of Suddenly in Charge and award-winning management consultant, shows you how with: * Fresh techniques and creative ways to build an organization with talent magnetism, where top talent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/talent-magnetism-how-to-build-a-workplace-that-attracts-and-keeps-the-best-roberta-chinsky-matuson-abridged/">Talent Magnetism : How to Build a Workplace That Attracts and Keeps the Best &#8211; Roberta Chinsky Matuson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Talent Magnetism offers straightforward, easy-to-apply techniques that help managers navigate the challenges of attracting and keeping talent to foster innovation and fuel growth.     </p>
<p>                    Roberta Matuson, bestselling author of Suddenly in Charge and award-winning management consultant, shows you how with:     </p>
<p>                    * Fresh techniques and creative ways to build an organization with talent magnetism, where top talent is pulled in with minimal effort on the employer&#8217;s part.<br />
                    * Proven methods which focus on what today&#8217;s post-recession workers value most. Hint: It isn&#8217;t what you think!<br />
                    * Case studies of organizations that have achieved &#8220;magnetic&#8221; status without Toyotasized budgets.<br />
                    * Rules of Attraction: recommendations to propel you forward at warp speed.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on real-life case studies and examples, Matuson demonstrates the new rules of workplace attraction and retention, helping you and your organization develop irresistible talent magnetism.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/talent-magnetism-how-to-build-a-workplace-that-attracts-and-keeps-the-best-roberta-chinsky-matuson-abridged/">Talent Magnetism : How to Build a Workplace That Attracts and Keeps the Best &#8211; Roberta Chinsky Matuson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Workplace Wellness that Works : 10 Steps to Infuse Well-Being and Vitality into Any Organization &#8211; Laura Putnam (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/workplace-wellness-that-works-10-steps-to-infuse-well-being-and-vitality-into-any-organization-laura-putnam-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/workplace-wellness-that-works-10-steps-to-infuse-well-being-and-vitality-into-any-organization-laura-putnam-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A smarter framework for designing more effective workplace wellness programs Workplace Wellness That Works provides a fresh perspective on how to promote employee well-being in the workplace. In addressing the interconnectivity between wellness and organizational culture, this book shows you how to integrate wellness into your existing employee development strategy in more creative, humane, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/workplace-wellness-that-works-10-steps-to-infuse-well-being-and-vitality-into-any-organization-laura-putnam-abridged/">Workplace Wellness that Works : 10 Steps to Infuse Well-Being and Vitality into Any Organization &#8211; Laura Putnam (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A smarter framework for designing more effective workplace wellness programs Workplace Wellness That Works provides a fresh perspective on how to promote employee well-being in the workplace. In addressing the interconnectivity between wellness and organizational culture, this book shows you how to integrate wellness into your existing employee development strategy in more creative, humane, and effective ways. Based on the latest research and backed by real-world examples and case studies, this guide provides employers with the tools they need to start making a difference in their employees&#8217; health and happiness, and promoting an overall culture of well-being throughout the organization. You&#8217;ll find concrete, actionable advice for tackling the massive obstacle of behavioral change, and learn how to design and implement an approach that can most benefit your organization. Promoting wellness is a good idea. Giving employees the inspiration and tools they need to make changes in their lifestyles is a great idea. But the billion-dollar question is: what do they want, what do they need, and how do we implement programs to help them without causing more harm than good?<br />
                    Workplace Wellness That Works shows you how to assess your organization&#8217;s needs and craft a plan that actually benefits employees. * Build an effective platform for well-being * Empower employees to make better choices * Design and deliver the strategy that your organization needs * Drive quantifiable change through more creative implementation Today&#8217;s worksite wellness industry represents a miasma of competing trends, making it nearly impossible to come away with tangible solutions for real-world implementation. Harnessing a broader learning and development framework, Workplace Wellness That Works skips the fads and shows you how to design a smarter strategy that truly makes a difference in employees&#8217; lives and your company&#8217;s bottom line.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/workplace-wellness-that-works-10-steps-to-infuse-well-being-and-vitality-into-any-organization-laura-putnam-abridged/">Workplace Wellness that Works : 10 Steps to Infuse Well-Being and Vitality into Any Organization &#8211; Laura Putnam (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Growing Great Employees : Turning Ordinary People into Extraordinary Performers &#8211; Erika Andersen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/growing-great-employees-turning-ordinary-people-into-extraordinary-performers-erika-andersen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/growing-great-employees-turning-ordinary-people-into-extraordinary-performers-erika-andersen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to develop an all-star staff, even if you don&#8217;t know the first thing about managing &#8220;Your employees are, like you and me, flawed and hopeful human beings whose success is at least partly dependent on your skill as a manager, human beings who will thrive with skillful and consistent attention and wither without it.&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/growing-great-employees-turning-ordinary-people-into-extraordinary-performers-erika-andersen-abridged/">Growing Great Employees : Turning Ordinary People into Extraordinary Performers &#8211; Erika Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to develop an all-star staff, even if you don&#8217;t know the first thing about managing  &#8220;Your employees are, like you and me, flawed and hopeful human beings whose success is at least partly dependent on your skill as a manager, human beings who will thrive with skillful and consistent attention and wither without it.&#8221;  Erika Andersen has helped some of the best-managed companies in the world develop their employees. Now she explains how to stay ahead of the competition by investing in your people. You&#8217;ll discover that:<br />
                     &#8211; Listening is your most powerful asset. Use it to motivate and build commitment.<br />
                     &#8211; Everything you know about interviewing is wrong. Discover what you really need in a potential employee.<br />
                     &#8211; Successful companies hire for keeps. Get people feeling like part of the team from day one.  Whether you&#8217;re a first-time manager or a senior executive, Andersen will help you create a dynamic workplace, where the efforts you make today will blossom into success for years to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/growing-great-employees-turning-ordinary-people-into-extraordinary-performers-erika-andersen-abridged/">Growing Great Employees : Turning Ordinary People into Extraordinary Performers &#8211; Erika Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The No Asshole Rule : Building a Civilised Workplace and Surviving One That Isn&#8217;t &#8211; Robert Sutton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When the Harvard Business Review asked Robert Sutton for suggestions for its annual list of Breakthrough Ideas, he told them that the best business practice he knew of was &#8216;the no asshole rule&#8217;. Sutton&#8217;s piece became one of the most popular articles ever to appear in the HBR. Spurred on by the fear and despair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/">The No Asshole Rule : Building a Civilised Workplace and Surviving One That Isn&#8217;t &#8211; Robert Sutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When the Harvard Business Review asked Robert Sutton for suggestions for its annual list of Breakthrough Ideas, he told them that the best business practice he knew of was &#8216;the no asshole rule&#8217;. Sutton&#8217;s piece became one of the most popular articles ever to appear in the HBR. Spurred on by the fear and despair that people expressed, the tricks they used to survive with dignity in asshole-infested places, the revenge stories that made him laugh out loud and the other small wins that they celebrated against mean-spirited people, Sutton was persuaded to write THE NO ASSHOLE RULE.<br />
                    He believes passionately that civilised workplaces are not a naive dream, that they do exist, do bolster performance and that widespread contempt can be erased and replaced with mutual respect when a team or organisation is managed right. There is a huge temptation by executives and those in positions of authority to overlook this trait especially when exhibited by so-called producers, but Sutton shows how overall productivity suffers when the workplace is subjected to this kind of stress.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/">The No Asshole Rule : Building a Civilised Workplace and Surviving One That Isn&#8217;t &#8211; Robert Sutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Payoff : The Hidden Logic That Shapes Our Motivations &#8211; Dr Dan Ariely (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/payoff-the-hidden-logic-that-shapes-our-motivations-dr-dan-ariely-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/payoff-the-hidden-logic-that-shapes-our-motivations-dr-dan-ariely-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bestselling author Dan Ariely reveals fascinating new insights into motivation&#8211;showing that the subject is far more complex than we ever imagined. Every day we work hard to motivate ourselves, the people we live with, the people who work for and do business with us. In this way, much of what we do can be defined [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/payoff-the-hidden-logic-that-shapes-our-motivations-dr-dan-ariely-abridged/">Payoff : The Hidden Logic That Shapes Our Motivations &#8211; Dr Dan Ariely (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bestselling author Dan Ariely reveals fascinating new insights into motivation&#8211;showing that the subject is far more complex than we ever imagined.     </p>
<p>                    Every day we work hard to motivate ourselves, the people we live with, the people who work for and do business with us. In this way, much of what we do can be defined as being &#8220;motivators.&#8221; From the boardroom to the living room, our role as motivators is complex, and the more we try to motivate partners and children, friends and coworkers, the clearer it becomes that the story of motivation is far more intricate and fascinating than we&#8217;ve assumed.     </p>
<p>                    Payoff investigates the true nature of motivation, our partial blindness to the way it works, and how we can bridge this gap. With studies that range from Intel to a kindergarten classroom, Ariely digs deep to find the root of motivation&#8211;how it works and how we can use this knowledge to approach important choices in our own lives. Along the way, he explores intriguing questions such as: Can giving employees bonuses harm productivity? Why is trust so crucial for successful motivation? What are our misconceptions about how to value our work? How does your sense of your mortality impact your motivation?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/payoff-the-hidden-logic-that-shapes-our-motivations-dr-dan-ariely-abridged/">Payoff : The Hidden Logic That Shapes Our Motivations &#8211; Dr Dan Ariely (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of a Positive Team : Proven Principles and Practices that Make Great Teams Great &#8211; Jon Gordon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-a-positive-team-proven-principles-and-practices-that-make-great-teams-great-jon-gordon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-a-positive-team-proven-principles-and-practices-that-make-great-teams-great-jon-gordon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A book about teams to help teams become more positive, united and connected. Worldwide bestseller &#8211; the author of The Energy Bus and The Power of Positive Leadership shares the proven principles and practices that build great teams &#8211; and provides practical tools to help teams overcome negativity and enhance their culture, communication, connection, commitment [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-a-positive-team-proven-principles-and-practices-that-make-great-teams-great-jon-gordon-abridged/">The Power of a Positive Team : Proven Principles and Practices that Make Great Teams Great &#8211; Jon Gordon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A book about teams to help teams become more positive, united and connected.    </p>
<p>                     Worldwide bestseller &#8211; the author of The Energy Bus and The Power of Positive Leadership shares the proven principles and practices that build great teams &#8211; and provides practical tools to help teams overcome negativity and enhance their culture, communication, connection, commitment and performance.    </p>
<p>                     Jon Gordon doesn&#8217;t just research the keys to great teams, he has personally worked with some of the most successful teams on the planet and has a keen understanding of how and why they became great. In The Power of a Positive Team, Jon draws upon his unique team building experience as well as conversations with some of the greatest teams in history in order to provide an essential framework, filled with proven practices, to empower teams to work together more effectively and achieve superior results.    </p>
<p>                     Utilizing examples from the writing team who created the hit show Billions, the National Champion Clemson Football team, the World Series contending Los Angeles Dodgers, The Miami Heat and the greatest beach volleyball team of all time to Navy SEAL&#8217;s, Marching bands, Southwest Airlines, USC and UVA Tennis, Twitter, Apple and Ford, Jon shares innovative strategies to transform a group of individuals into a united, positive and powerful team.    </p>
<p>                     Jon not only infuses this book with the latest research, compelling stories, and strategies to maintain optimism through adversity&#8230; he also shares his best practices to transform negativity, build trust (through his favorite team building exercises) and practical ways to have difficult conversations-all designed to make a team more positive, cohesive, stronger and better.    </p>
<p>                     The Power of a Positive Team also provides a blueprint for addressing common pitfalls that cause teams to fail-including complaining, selfishness, inconsistency, complacency, unaccountability-while offering  solutions to enhance a team&#8217;s creativity, grit, innovation and growth.    </p>
<p>                     This book is meant for teams to read together. It&#8217;s written in such a way that if you and your team read it together, you will understand the obstacles you will face and what you must do to become a great team. If you read it together, stay positive together, and take action together you will accomplish amazing things TOGETHER.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-a-positive-team-proven-principles-and-practices-that-make-great-teams-great-jon-gordon-abridged/">The Power of a Positive Team : Proven Principles and Practices that Make Great Teams Great &#8211; Jon Gordon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peak : How Great Companies Get Their Mojo from Maslow Revised and Updated &#8211; Chip Conley, Foreword by Tony Hsieh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/peak-how-great-companies-get-their-mojo-from-maslow-revised-and-updated-chip-conley-foreword-by-tony-hsieh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/peak-how-great-companies-get-their-mojo-from-maslow-revised-and-updated-chip-conley-foreword-by-tony-hsieh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Proven principles for sustainable success, with new leadership insight PEAK is the popular, transformative guide to doing business better, written by a seasoned entrepreneur/CEO who has disrupted his favorite industry not once, but twice. Author Chip Conley, founder and former CEO of one of the world&#8217;s largest boutique hotel companies, turned to psychologist Abraham Maslow&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peak-how-great-companies-get-their-mojo-from-maslow-revised-and-updated-chip-conley-foreword-by-tony-hsieh-abridged/">Peak : How Great Companies Get Their Mojo from Maslow Revised and Updated &#8211; Chip Conley, Foreword by Tony Hsieh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proven principles for sustainable success, with new leadership insight    </p>
<p>                     PEAK is the popular, transformative guide to doing business better, written by a seasoned entrepreneur/CEO who has disrupted his favorite industry not once, but twice. Author Chip Conley, founder and former CEO of one of the world&#8217;s largest boutique hotel companies, turned to psychologist Abraham Maslow&#8217;s Hierarchy of Needs at a time when his company was in dire need. And years later, when the young founders of Airbnb asked him to help turn their start-up home sharing company into a world-class hospitality giant, Conley once again used the principles he&#8217;d developed in PEAK. In the decade since this book&#8217;s first edition, Conley&#8217;s PEAK strategy has been developed on six continents in organizations in virtually every industry. The author&#8217;s foundational premise is that great leaders become amateur psychologists by understanding the unique needs of three key relationships-with employees, customers, and investors-and this message has resonated with every kind of leader and company including some of the world&#8217;s best-known, from Apple to Facebook. Avid users of PEAK have found that the principles create greater loyalty and differentiation with their key stakeholders. This new second edition includes in-depth examples of real-world PEAK companies, including the author&#8217;s own at Airbnb, and exclusive PEAK leadership practices that will take you-and your company&#8217;s performance-to new heights.    </p>
<p>                     Whether you&#8217;re at a startup or a Fortune 500 company, at a for-profit, nonprofit, or governmental organization, this book can help you and your people reach potential you never realized you had.    </p>
<p>                    Understand how Maslow&#8217;s hierarchy makes for winning business practices<br />
                    Learn how PEAK drove some of today&#8217;s top businesses to success<br />
                    Help employees reach their full potential-and beyond    </p>
<p>                    Transform the customer experience and keep investors happy    </p>
<p>                     The PEAK framework succeeds because it elevates the business from the inside out. These same principles apply in the boardroom, the breakroom, and your living room at home, and have proven to be the foundation of healthy, fulfilled lives. Even if you think you&#8217;re doing great, you could always be doing better-and PEAK gives you a roadmap to the next level.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peak-how-great-companies-get-their-mojo-from-maslow-revised-and-updated-chip-conley-foreword-by-tony-hsieh-abridged/">Peak : How Great Companies Get Their Mojo from Maslow Revised and Updated &#8211; Chip Conley, Foreword by Tony Hsieh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Eight Essential People Skills for Project Management : Solving the Most Common People Problems for Team Leaders &#8211; Zachary Wong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-eight-essential-people-skills-for-project-management-solving-the-most-common-people-problems-for-team-leaders-zachary-wong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-eight-essential-people-skills-for-project-management-solving-the-most-common-people-problems-for-team-leaders-zachary-wong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Veteran project manager and University of California professor Zachary Wong identifies the eight most common people problems in managing projects and offers a flexible, customizable approach to solving them, based on a lifetime of research. Zachary Wong offers practical strategies, skills, and tools to help project managers diagnose and solve their toughest people problems. Based [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-eight-essential-people-skills-for-project-management-solving-the-most-common-people-problems-for-team-leaders-zachary-wong-abridged/">The Eight Essential People Skills for Project Management : Solving the Most Common People Problems for Team Leaders &#8211; Zachary Wong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Veteran project manager and University of California professor Zachary Wong identifies the eight most common people problems in managing projects and offers a flexible, customizable approach to solving them, based on a lifetime of research. Zachary Wong offers practical strategies, skills, and tools to help project managers diagnose and solve their toughest people problems. Based on decades in the trenches, the book shows how to confront and correct bad behavior, increase team performance and inclusion, turn around difficult people and poor performers, get people to do what you want them to do, boost employee motivation and attitude, reduce change resistance and risk aversion, and manage difficult bosses. Wong believes that the best team leaders are problem-solvers and facilitators, so this book provides problem-solving models and tools to diagnose people problems, and facilitative methods, processes, and techniques to correct them. It&#8217;s an approach that can be personalized to fit any person or situation. Each skill is explained with a well-balanced mix of case stories, examples, strategies, processes, tools, and techniques along with illustrations, graphics, tables, and other visuals to clarify key concepts and their workplace application. To reinforce the most important learnings, Wong includes a Memory Card and Skill Summary at the end of each chapter. Nothing is harder than leading people and managing project teams. Being successful takes a combination of knowing human psychology, organizational behaviors, and human factors; having supervisory, process, and communication skills; ensuring good teamwork, high integrity, and strong leadership; and having the ability to integrate and apply these skills to a diverse work team. The Eight Essential People Skills for Project Management is designed for individuals, team leaders, and managers who oversee and coordinate the daily performance of others and who are seeking solutions that they can apply immediately.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-eight-essential-people-skills-for-project-management-solving-the-most-common-people-problems-for-team-leaders-zachary-wong-abridged/">The Eight Essential People Skills for Project Management : Solving the Most Common People Problems for Team Leaders &#8211; Zachary Wong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Innovation for the Fatigued : How to Build a Culture of Deep Creativity &#8211; Alf Rehn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/innovation-for-the-fatigued-how-to-build-a-culture-of-deep-creativity-alf-rehn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/innovation-for-the-fatigued-how-to-build-a-culture-of-deep-creativity-alf-rehn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How many presentations on innovation have there been recently? Thousands? Millions? We are experiencing &#8216;innovation fatigue&#8217;: we feel cheated by the endless rounds of consultants who come into our organizations, deliver conceptual models that don&#8217;t stick with the realities of business and then leave again. Companies and teams are left feeling more deflated than before, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/innovation-for-the-fatigued-how-to-build-a-culture-of-deep-creativity-alf-rehn-abridged/">Innovation for the Fatigued : How to Build a Culture of Deep Creativity &#8211; Alf Rehn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How many presentations on innovation have there been recently? Thousands? Millions? We are experiencing &#8216;innovation fatigue&#8217;: we feel cheated by the endless rounds of consultants who come into our organizations, deliver conceptual models that don&#8217;t stick with the realities of business and then leave again. Companies and teams are left feeling more deflated than before, and with not one idea that&#8217;s impacted the bottom line. Innovation for the Fatigued argues it is worth fighting for the concept and study of innovation in organizations.    </p>
<p>                    Business leaders are always looking over their shoulders for the next Uber moment to overtake them, and they recognize that innovation needs to be a top priority. But how does one innovate? This book is the antidote to the empty promises that pervade the innovation industry. By designing a company culture that nurtures ideas, but also defends against incrementalism and fads, we can rediscover the powerful basics of imagination, empathy, play and courage, which are all instrumental in delivering real impactful innovation. Innovation for the Fatigued will detail where companies have got innovation wrong, whilst celebrating and studying the ones that lead the way. With unique, relatable and varied examples, renowned innovation and creativity professor Alf Rehn provides a practical model for getting innovation back on track, and instilling change at speed with real concern for market demands.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/innovation-for-the-fatigued-how-to-build-a-culture-of-deep-creativity-alf-rehn-abridged/">Innovation for the Fatigued : How to Build a Culture of Deep Creativity &#8211; Alf Rehn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Joy of Work : The No.1 Sunday Times Business Bestseller &#8211; 30 Ways to Fix Your Work Culture and Fall in Love with Your Job Again &#8211; Bruce Daisley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>__________________________ &#8216;Bruce Daisley is on a mission to change the world of work.&#8217; The Times __________________________ From the creator of hit podcast Eat Sleep Work Repeat comes a revolutionary re-envisioning of how to enjoy your job. Do you want to get more done, feel less stressed and love your job again? Sometimes having a job [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/">The Joy of Work : The No.1 Sunday Times Business Bestseller &#8211; 30 Ways to Fix Your Work Culture and Fall in Love with Your Job Again &#8211; Bruce Daisley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>__________________________<br />
                    &#8216;Bruce Daisley is on a mission to change the world of work.&#8217; The Times<br />
                    __________________________    </p>
<p>                    From the creator of hit podcast Eat Sleep Work Repeat comes a revolutionary re-envisioning of how to enjoy your job.    </p>
<p>                    Do you want to get more done, feel less stressed and love your job again?    </p>
<p>                    Sometimes having a job can feel like hard work. But between Monk Mode mornings, silent meetings and crisp Thursdays, the solutions are at your fingertips.    </p>
<p>                    Bruce Daisley knows a thing or two about the workplace. In the course of a career that has taken him from some of the world&#8217;s biggest media companies to Twitter, via Google and YouTube, he has become a leading expert on how we work now. And in his hugely popular podcast Eat Sleep Work Repeat, he has explored ways to fix it. Now he shares 30 brilliant &#8211; and refreshingly simple &#8211; tips on how to make your job more productive, more rewarding &#8211; and much, much more enjoyable.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;With just 30 changes, you can transform your work experience from bland and boring (or worse) to fulfilling, fun, and even joyful.&#8217; Daniel Pink, author of When and Drive    </p>
<p>                    __________________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is a warm, wise and funny book which provides a terrific summary of some of the science &#8211; and stories &#8211; behind what makes work a positive part of people&#8217;s lives. From the importance of lunch to the value of laughter, this book gives witty and practical advice. I loved it and I&#8217;ve already started changing some of the things I do at work, as a result!&#8221; &#8211; Professor Sophie Scott    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Don&#8217;t quit yet! In this book, Bruce shares remarkable advice that may well have you laughing while you work and truly loving your job.&#8221; &#8211; Biz Stone, Twitter co-founder    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Bruce Daisley&#8217;s The Joy of Work is a joy to read. It translates the best of workplace psychology research into practical ways of establishing creative and liveable cultures at work-a must read for all of us 9-5ers!&#8221; &#8211; Professor Sir Cary Cooper, ALLIANCE Manchester Business School, University of Manchester    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Bruce&#8217;s The Joy of Work is an important reminder of simple everyday practices to improve how we all work together, which will lead to greater team and individual happiness and performance. Great results will follow.&#8221; &#8211; Jack Dorsey, CEO of Twitter and Square    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;With just 30 changes, you can transform your work experience from bland and boring (or worse) to fulfilling, fun, and even joyful. Bruce Daisley has pulled together threads of research and woven them into a tapestry of strategies that actually work, and that don&#8217;t depend on the CEO&#8217;s sign-off for implementation. You can begin changing your work culture today at the individual, team, and organisational levels with these tactics that increase creativity, productivity, and satisfaction.&#8221; &#8211; Daniel Pink, author of WHEN and DRIVE</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-work-the-no-1-sunday-times-business-bestseller-30-ways-to-fix-your-work-culture-and-fall-in-love-with-your-job-again-bruce-daisley-abridged/">The Joy of Work : The No.1 Sunday Times Business Bestseller &#8211; 30 Ways to Fix Your Work Culture and Fall in Love with Your Job Again &#8211; Bruce Daisley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Third Door : The Wild Quest to Uncover How the World&#8217;s Most Successful People Launched Their Careers &#8211; Alex Banayan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/third-door-the-wild-quest-to-uncover-how-the-worlds-most-successful-people-launched-their-careers-alex-banayan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/third-door-the-wild-quest-to-uncover-how-the-worlds-most-successful-people-launched-their-careers-alex-banayan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FORBES #1 CAREER BOOK TO READ IN 2018 The larger-than-life journey of an 18-year-old college freshman who set out from his dorm room to track down Bill Gates, Lady Gaga, and dozens more of the world&#8217;s most successful people to uncover how they broke through and launched their careers. The Third Door takes readers on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/third-door-the-wild-quest-to-uncover-how-the-worlds-most-successful-people-launched-their-careers-alex-banayan-abridged/">Third Door : The Wild Quest to Uncover How the World&#8217;s Most Successful People Launched Their Careers &#8211; Alex Banayan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FORBES #1 CAREER BOOK TO READ IN 2018     </p>
<p>                    The larger-than-life journey of an 18-year-old college freshman who set out from his dorm room to track down Bill Gates, Lady Gaga, and dozens more of the world&#8217;s most successful people to uncover how they broke through and launched their careers.     </p>
<p>                    The Third Door takes readers on an unprecedented adventure&#8211;from hacking Warren Buffett&#8217;s shareholders meeting to chasing Larry King through a grocery store to celebrating in a nightclub with Lady Gaga&#8211;as Alex Banayan travels from icon to icon, decoding their success. After remarkable one-on-one interviews with Bill Gates, Maya Angelou, Steve Wozniak, Jane Goodall, Larry King, Jessica Alba, Pitbull, Tim Ferriss, Quincy Jones, and many more, Alex discovered the one key they have in common: they all took the Third Door.     </p>
<p>                     Life, business, success&#8230; it&#8217;s just like a nightclub. There are always three ways in. There&#8217;s the First Door: the main entrance, where ninety-nine percent of people wait in line, hoping to get in. The Second Door: the VIP entrance, where the billionaires and celebrities slip through. But what no one tells you is that there is always, always&#8230; the Third Door. It&#8217;s the entrance where you have to jump out of line, run down the alley, bang on the door a hundred times, climb over the dumpster, crack open the window, sneak through the kitchen&#8211;there&#8217;s always a way in. Whether it&#8217;s how Bill Gates sold his first piece of software or how Steven Spielberg became the youngest studio director in Hollywood history, they all took the Third Door.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/third-door-the-wild-quest-to-uncover-how-the-worlds-most-successful-people-launched-their-careers-alex-banayan-abridged/">Third Door : The Wild Quest to Uncover How the World&#8217;s Most Successful People Launched Their Careers &#8211; Alex Banayan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Discomfort Zone: How Leaders Turn Difficult Conversations Into Breakthroughs &#8211; Marcia Reynolds (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-discomfort-zone-how-leaders-turn-difficult-conversations-into-breakthroughs-marcia-reynolds-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-discomfort-zone-how-leaders-turn-difficult-conversations-into-breakthroughs-marcia-reynolds-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You want people to stretch their limits, but your conversations meant to help them often fall flat or backfire, creating more resistance than growth. Top leadership coach Marcia Reynolds offers a model for using the Discomfort Zone&#8211;the moment when the mind is most open to learning&#8211;to prompt people to think through problems, see situations more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-discomfort-zone-how-leaders-turn-difficult-conversations-into-breakthroughs-marcia-reynolds-abridged/">The Discomfort Zone: How Leaders Turn Difficult Conversations Into Breakthroughs &#8211; Marcia Reynolds (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You want people to stretch their limits, but your conversations meant to help them often fall flat or backfire, creating more resistance than growth. Top leadership coach Marcia Reynolds offers a model for using the Discomfort Zone&#8211;the moment when the mind is most open to learning&#8211;to prompt people to think through problems, see situations more strategically, and transcend their limitations.     </p>
<p>                     Drawing on recent discoveries in the neuroscience of learning, Reynolds shows how to ask the kinds of questions that short-circuit the brain&#8217;s defense mechanisms and habitual thought patterns. Then, instead of being told, people see for themselves the insightful and often profound solutions to what is stopping their progress. The exercises and case studies will help you use discomfort in your conversations to create lasting changes and an enlivened workforce.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-discomfort-zone-how-leaders-turn-difficult-conversations-into-breakthroughs-marcia-reynolds-abridged/">The Discomfort Zone: How Leaders Turn Difficult Conversations Into Breakthroughs &#8211; Marcia Reynolds (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feedback (and Other Dirty Words) : Why We Fear It, How to Fix It &#8211; M. Tamra Chandler, Laura Dowling Grealish (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/feedback-and-other-dirty-words-why-we-fear-it-how-to-fix-it-m-tamra-chandler-laura-dowling-grealish-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feedback-and-other-dirty-words-why-we-fear-it-how-to-fix-it-m-tamra-chandler-laura-dowling-grealish-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical and irreverent guide to taking the sting out of feedback and reclaiming it as a motivating, empowering experience for everyone involved. Feedback: the mere mention of the word can make our blood pressure rise and our defenses go up. For many of us, it&#8217;s a dirty word that we associate with bias, politics, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feedback-and-other-dirty-words-why-we-fear-it-how-to-fix-it-m-tamra-chandler-laura-dowling-grealish-abridged/">Feedback (and Other Dirty Words) : Why We Fear It, How to Fix It &#8211; M. Tamra Chandler, Laura Dowling Grealish (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical and irreverent guide to taking the sting out of feedback and reclaiming it as a motivating, empowering experience for everyone involved.     </p>
<p>                    Feedback: the mere mention of the word can make our blood pressure rise and our defenses go up. For many of us, it&#8217;s a dirty word that we associate with bias, politics, resentment, and self-doubt. However, if we take a step back and think about its true intent, we realize that feedback needn&#8217;t be a bad thing. After all, understanding how others experience us provides valuable opportunities to learn and grow.     </p>
<p>                    Authors M. Tamra Chandler and Laura Grealish explain how feedback got such a bad rap and how to recognize and minimize the negative physical and emotional responses that can erode trust and shut down communication. They offer a new and more ambitious definition of feedback, explore the roles we each play as Seeker, Extender, and Receiver, and introduce the three Fs of making feedback focused, fair, and frequent. You&#8217;ll also find valuable exercises and strategies, along with real-world examples that illustrate how you can put these ideas into action and join in the movement to fix feedback, once and for all.     </p>
<p>                    When it&#8217;s done right, feedback has been proven to be the most effective means of improving communication and performance for you and your organization. It&#8217;s too important to give up, and with Chandler and Grealish&#8217;s help, you&#8217;ll be able to use it deftly, equitably, and effectively.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feedback-and-other-dirty-words-why-we-fear-it-how-to-fix-it-m-tamra-chandler-laura-dowling-grealish-abridged/">Feedback (and Other Dirty Words) : Why We Fear It, How to Fix It &#8211; M. Tamra Chandler, Laura Dowling Grealish (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fearless Organization : Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth &#8211; Amy C. Edmondson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fearless-organization-creating-psychological-safety-in-the-workplace-for-learning-innovation-and-growth-amy-c-edmondson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fearless-organization-creating-psychological-safety-in-the-workplace-for-learning-innovation-and-growth-amy-c-edmondson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Conquer the most essential adaptation to the knowledge economy The Fearless Organization: Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth offers practical guidance for teams and organizations who are serious about success in the modern economy. With so much riding on innovation, creativity, and spark, it is essential to attract and retain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fearless-organization-creating-psychological-safety-in-the-workplace-for-learning-innovation-and-growth-amy-c-edmondson-abridged/">The Fearless Organization : Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth &#8211; Amy C. Edmondson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Conquer the most essential adaptation to the knowledge economy    </p>
<p>                     The Fearless Organization: Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth offers practical guidance for teams and organizations who are serious about success in the modern economy. With so much riding on innovation, creativity, and spark, it is essential to attract and retain quality talent-but what good does this talent do if no one is able to speak their mind? The traditional culture of &#8220;fitting in&#8221; and &#8220;going along&#8221; spells doom in the knowledge economy. Success requires a continuous influx of new ideas, new challenges, and critical thought, and the interpersonal climate must not suppress, silence, ridicule or intimidate. Not every idea is good, and yes there are stupid questions, and yes dissent can slow things down, but talking through these things is an essential part of the creative process. People must be allowed to voice half-finished thoughts, ask questions from left field, and brainstorm out loud; it creates a culture in which a minor flub or momentary lapse is no big deal, and where actual mistakes are owned and corrected, and where the next left-field idea could be the next big thing.     </p>
<p>                     This book explores this culture of psychological safety, and provides a blueprint for bringing it to life. The road is sometimes bumpy, but succinct and informative scenario-based explanations provide a clear path forward to constant learning and healthy innovation.    </p>
<p>                    Explore the link between psychological safety and high performance<br />
                    Create a culture where it&#8217;s &#8220;safe&#8221; to express ideas, ask questions, and admit mistakes<br />
                    Nurture the level of engagement and candor required in today&#8217;s knowledge economy    </p>
<p>                    Follow a step-by-step framework for establishing psychological safety in your team or organization    </p>
<p>                     Shed the &#8220;yes-men&#8221; approach and step into real performance. Fertilize creativity, clarify goals, achieve accountability, redefine leadership, and much more. The Fearless Organization helps you bring about this most critical transformation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fearless-organization-creating-psychological-safety-in-the-workplace-for-learning-innovation-and-growth-amy-c-edmondson-abridged/">The Fearless Organization : Creating Psychological Safety in the Workplace for Learning, Innovation, and Growth &#8211; Amy C. Edmondson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Snakes in Suits : When Psychopaths Go to Work &#8211; Dr. Paul Babiak, Dr. Robert D. Hare (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/snakes-in-suits-when-psychopaths-go-to-work-dr-paul-babiak-dr-robert-d-hare-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/snakes-in-suits-when-psychopaths-go-to-work-dr-paul-babiak-dr-robert-d-hare-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Snakes in Suits&#8221; is a compelling, frightening, and scientifically sound look at exactly how psychopaths work in the corporate environment: what kind of companies attract them, how they negotiate the hiring process, and how they function day by day. You&#8217;ll learn how they apply their &#8220;instinctive&#8221; manipulation techniques-assessing potential targets, controlling influential victims, and abandoning [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/snakes-in-suits-when-psychopaths-go-to-work-dr-paul-babiak-dr-robert-d-hare-abridged/">Snakes in Suits : When Psychopaths Go to Work &#8211; Dr. Paul Babiak, Dr. Robert D. Hare (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Snakes in Suits&#8221; is a compelling, frightening, and scientifically sound look at exactly how psychopaths work in the corporate environment: what kind of companies attract them, how they negotiate the hiring process, and how they function day by day. You&#8217;ll learn how they apply their &#8220;instinctive&#8221; manipulation techniques-assessing potential targets, controlling influential victims, and abandoning those no longer useful-to business processes such as hiring, political command and control, and executive succession, all while hiding within the corporate culture. It&#8217;s a must read for anyone in the business world, because whatever level you&#8217;re at, you&#8217;ll learn the subtle warning signs of psychopathic behaviour and be able to protect yourself and your company-before it&#8217;s too late.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/snakes-in-suits-when-psychopaths-go-to-work-dr-paul-babiak-dr-robert-d-hare-abridged/">Snakes in Suits : When Psychopaths Go to Work &#8211; Dr. Paul Babiak, Dr. Robert D. Hare (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Business Chemistry : Practical Magic for Crafting Powerful Work Relationships &#8211; Kim Christfort, Suzanne Vickberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/business-chemistry-practical-magic-for-crafting-powerful-work-relationships-kim-christfort-suzanne-vickberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/business-chemistry-practical-magic-for-crafting-powerful-work-relationships-kim-christfort-suzanne-vickberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A guide to putting cognitive diversity to work Ever wonder what it is that makes two people click or clash? Or why some groups excel while others fumble? Or how you, as a leader, can make or break team potential? Business Chemistry holds the answers. Based on extensive research and analytics, plus years of proven [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/business-chemistry-practical-magic-for-crafting-powerful-work-relationships-kim-christfort-suzanne-vickberg-abridged/">Business Chemistry : Practical Magic for Crafting Powerful Work Relationships &#8211; Kim Christfort, Suzanne Vickberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A guide to putting cognitive diversity to work    </p>
<p>                     Ever wonder what it is that makes two people click or clash? Or why some groups excel while others fumble? Or how you, as a leader, can make or break team potential?    </p>
<p>                     Business Chemistry holds the answers. Based on extensive research and analytics, plus years of proven success in the field, the Business Chemistry framework provides a simple yet powerful way to identify meaningful differences between people&#8217;s working styles. Who seeks possibilities and who seeks stability? Who values challenge and who values connection? Business Chemistry will help you grasp where others are coming from, appreciate the value they bring, and determine what they need in order to excel. It offers practical ways to be more effective as an individual and as a leader.    </p>
<p>                     Imagine you had a more in-depth understanding of yourself and why you thrive in some work environments and flounder in others. Suppose you had a clearer view on what to do about it so that you could always perform at your best.    </p>
<p>                     Imagine you had more insight into what makes people tick and what ticks them off, how some interactions unlock potential while others shut people down. Suppose you could gain people&#8217;s trust, influence them, motivate them, and get the very most out of your work relationships.    </p>
<p>                     Imagine you knew how to create a work environment where all types of people excel, even if they have conflicting perspectives, preferences and needs. Suppose you could activate the potential benefits of diversity on your teams and in your organizations, improving collaboration to achieve the group&#8217;s collective potential.    </p>
<p>                     Business Chemistry offers all of this&#8211;you don&#8217;t have to leave it up to chance, and you shouldn&#8217;t. Let this book guide you in creating great chemistry!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/business-chemistry-practical-magic-for-crafting-powerful-work-relationships-kim-christfort-suzanne-vickberg-abridged/">Business Chemistry : Practical Magic for Crafting Powerful Work Relationships &#8211; Kim Christfort, Suzanne Vickberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Awakening Compassion at Work : The Quiet Power That Elevates People and Organizations (16pt Large Print Edition) &#8211; Monica C Worline, Jane E Dutton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Caring Is a Competitive Advantage Suffering in the workplace can rob our colleagues and coworkers of humanity, dignity, and motivation and is an unrecognized and costly drain on organizational potential. Marshaling evidence from two decades of field research, scholars and consultants Monica Worline and Jane Dutton show that alleviating such suffering confers measurable competitive advantages [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/">Awakening Compassion at Work : The Quiet Power That Elevates People and Organizations (16pt Large Print Edition) &#8211; Monica C Worline, Jane E Dutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Caring Is a Competitive Advantage Suffering in the workplace can rob our colleagues and coworkers of humanity, dignity, and motivation and is an unrecognized and costly drain on organizational potential. Marshaling evidence from two decades of field research, scholars and consultants Monica Worline and Jane Dutton show that alleviating such suffering confers measurable competitive advantages in areas like innovation, collaboration, service quality, and talent attraction and retention. They outline four steps for meeting suffering with compassion and show how to build a capacity for compassion into the structures and practices of an organization-because ultimately, as they write, Compassion is an irreplaceable dimension of excellence for any organization that wants to make the most of its human capabilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/awakening-compassion-at-work-the-quiet-power-that-elevates-people-and-organizations-16pt-large-print-edition-monica-c-worline-jane-e-dutton-abridged/">Awakening Compassion at Work : The Quiet Power That Elevates People and Organizations (16pt Large Print Edition) &#8211; Monica C Worline, Jane E Dutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The E-Myth Revisited : Why Most Small Businesses Don&#8217;t Work and What to Do About It &#8211; Michael E. Gerber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>E-Myth &#8216;e-,&#8217;mith n 1: the entrepreneurial myth: the myth that most people who start small businesses are entrepreneurs 2: the fatal assumption that an individual who understands the technical work of a business can successfully run a business that does that technical work Voted #1 business book by Inc. 500 CEOs. An instant classic, this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/">The E-Myth Revisited : Why Most Small Businesses Don&#8217;t Work and What to Do About It &#8211; Michael E. Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>E-Myth  &#8216;e-,&#8217;mith n 1: the entrepreneurial myth: the myth that most people who start small businesses are entrepreneurs 2: the fatal assumption that an individual who understands the technical work of a business can successfully run a business that does that technical work  Voted #1 business book by Inc. 500 CEOs.  An instant classic, this revised and updated edition of the phenomenal bestseller dispels the myths about starting your own business. Small business consultant and author Michael E. Gerber, with sharp insight gained from years of experience, points out how common assumptions, expectations, and even technical expertise can get in the way of running a successful business.  Gerber walks you through the steps in the life of a business-from entrepreneurial infancy through adolescent growing pains to the mature entrepreneurial perspective: the guiding light of all businesses that succeed-and shows how to apply the lessons of franchising to any business, whether or not it is a franchise. Most importantly, Gerber draws the vital, often overlooked distinction between working on your business and working in your business.<br />
                    The E-Myth Revisited will help you grow your business in a productive, assured way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/">The E-Myth Revisited : Why Most Small Businesses Don&#8217;t Work and What to Do About It &#8211; Michael E. Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who : The A Method for Hiring &#8211; Geoff Smart, Randy Street (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-the-a-method-for-hiring-geoff-smart-randy-street-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-the-a-method-for-hiring-geoff-smart-randy-street-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this instant New York Times Bestseller, Geoff Smart and Randy Street provide a simple, practical, and effective solution to what The Economist calls &#8220;the single biggest problem in business today&#8221; unsuccessful hiring. The average hiring mistake costs a company $1.5 million or more a year and countless wasted hours. This statistic becomes even more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-the-a-method-for-hiring-geoff-smart-randy-street-abridged/">Who : The A Method for Hiring &#8211; Geoff Smart, Randy Street (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this instant New York Times Bestseller, Geoff Smart and Randy Street provide a simple, practical, and effective solution to what The Economist calls &#8220;the single biggest problem in business today&#8221; unsuccessful hiring. The average hiring mistake costs a company $1.5 million or more a year and countless wasted hours. This statistic becomes even more startling when you consider that the typical hiring success rate of managers is only 50 percent.     </p>
<p>                    The silver lining is that &#8220;who&#8221; problems are easily preventable. Based on more than 1,300 hours of interviews with more than 20 billionaires and 300 CEOs, Who presents Smart and Street&#8217;s A Method for Hiring. Refined through the largest research study of its kind ever undertaken, the A Method stresses fundamental elements that anyone can implement-and it has a 90 percent success rate.     </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re a member of a board of directors looking for a new CEO, the owner of a small business searching for the right people to make your company grow, or a parent in need of a new babysitter, it&#8217;s all about Who. Inside you&#8217;ll learn how to     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; avoid common &#8220;voodoo hiring&#8221; methods<br />
                    &#8211; define the outcomes you seek<br />
                    &#8211; generate a flow of A Players to your team-by implementing the #1 tactic used by successful businesspeople<br />
                    &#8211; ask the right interview questions to dramatically improve your ability to quickly distinguish an A Player from a B or C candidate<br />
                    &#8211; attract the person you want to hire, by emphasizing the points the candidate cares about most     </p>
<p>                    In business, you are who you hire. In Who, Geoff Smart and Randy Street offer simple, easy-to-follow steps that will put the right people in place for optimal success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-the-a-method-for-hiring-geoff-smart-randy-street-abridged/">Who : The A Method for Hiring &#8211; Geoff Smart, Randy Street (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coaching Habit &#8211; Bungay Michael Stainer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/coaching-habit-bungay-michael-stainer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/coaching-habit-bungay-michael-stainer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Look for Michael&#8217;s new book, The Advice Trap, which focuses on taming your Advice Monster so you can stay curious a little longer and change the way you lead forever. In Michael Bungay Stanier&#8217;s The Coaching Habit, coaching becomes a regular, informal part of your day so managers and their teams can work less hard [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coaching-habit-bungay-michael-stainer-abridged/">Coaching Habit &#8211; Bungay Michael Stainer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Look for Michael&#8217;s new book, The Advice Trap, which focuses on taming your Advice Monster so you can stay curious a little longer and change the way you lead forever. In Michael Bungay Stanier&#8217;s The Coaching Habit, coaching becomes a regular, informal part of your day so managers and their teams can work less hard and have more impact. Drawing on years of experience training more than 10,000 busy managers from around the globe in practical, everyday coaching skills, Bungay Stanier reveals how to unlock your peoples&#8217; potential. He unpacks seven essential coaching questions to demonstrate how-by saying less and asking more-you can develop coaching methods that produce great results. * Get straight to the point in any conversation with The Kickstart Question * Stay on track during any interaction with The Awe Question * Save hours of time for yourself with The Lazy Question, and hours of time for others with The Strategic Question * Get to the heart of any interpersonal or external challenge with The Focus Question and The Foundation Question * Finally ensure others find your coaching as beneficial as you do with The Learning Question A fresh innovative take on the traditional how-to manual, the book combines insider information with research based in neuroscience and behavioural economics, together with interactive training tools to turn practical advice into practiced habits. Witty and conversational, The Coaching Habit takes your work-and your workplace-from good to great. &#8216;Coaching is an art and it&#8217;s far easier said than done. It takes courage to ask a question rather than offer up advice, provide and answer, or unleash a solution. giving another person the opportunity to find their own way, make their own mistakes, and create their own wisdom is both brave and vulnerable. In this practical and inspiring book, Michael shares seven transformative questions that can make a difference in how we lead and support. And he guides us through the tricky part-how to take this new information and turn it into habits and a daily practice. -Brene Brown, author of Rising Strong and Daring Greatly.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coaching-habit-bungay-michael-stainer-abridged/">Coaching Habit &#8211; Bungay Michael Stainer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Back to Human : How Great Leaders Create Connection in the Age of Isolation &#8211; Dan Schawbel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/back-to-human-how-great-leaders-create-connection-in-the-age-of-isolation-dan-schawbel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/back-to-human-how-great-leaders-create-connection-in-the-age-of-isolation-dan-schawbel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Back to Human explains how a more socially connected workforce creates greater fulfillment, productivity, and engagement while preventing burnout and turnover. New York Times bestselling author Dan Schawbel guides the next generation of leaders to create a workplace where teammates feel genuinely connected, engaged, and empowered to grow strong interpersonal skills rather than relying on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-to-human-how-great-leaders-create-connection-in-the-age-of-isolation-dan-schawbel-abridged/">Back to Human : How Great Leaders Create Connection in the Age of Isolation &#8211; Dan Schawbel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Back to Human explains how a more socially connected workforce creates greater fulfillment, productivity, and engagement while preventing burnout and turnover.     </p>
<p>                    New York Times bestselling author Dan Schawbel guides the next generation of leaders to create a workplace where teammates feel genuinely connected, engaged, and empowered to grow strong interpersonal skills rather than relying on technology. Based on Schawbel&#8217;s exclusive research studies&#8211;featuring the perspectives of over 2,000 managers and employees across different age groups and from the US, UK, China, India, Brazil and other countries &#8211; Back to Human reveals why electronic and virtual communication, though vital and useful, actually contributes to a stronger sense of isolation at work than ever before.     </p>
<p>                    The corporate cultures we are experiencing right now need to change, and Schawbel offers a new leadership model featuring The Work-Life Balance Myth (we should consider work-life integration instead, which creates more synergies between all areas of your life and puts you in control of how you allocate your time), Shared Learning (how sharing knowledge allows you to stay relevant despite industry disruptions), and more. The book includes:    </p>
<p>                    -Interviews with 100 leaders from notable companies including Facebook, Honeywell, HBO, Starbucks, General Mills, GE, Nike, American Express, Four Seasons, Walmart, TIME, LinkedIn, and The U.S. Air Force.<br />
                    -A self-assessment called &#8220;The Work Connectivity Index&#8221; that measures that strength of team relationships.<br />
                    -Exercises, examples and activities that readers can work on individually, or as a team, which will help them improve their leadership skills.<br />
                    -Tips and strategies on how to increase personal productivity, be more collaborative and become more fulfilled at work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-to-human-how-great-leaders-create-connection-in-the-age-of-isolation-dan-schawbel-abridged/">Back to Human : How Great Leaders Create Connection in the Age of Isolation &#8211; Dan Schawbel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Turn The Ship Around! : A True Story of Building Leaders by Breaking the Rules &#8211; L. David Marquet, Foreword by Stephen R Covey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/turn-the-ship-around-a-true-story-of-building-leaders-by-breaking-the-rules-l-david-marquet-foreword-by-stephen-r-covey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/turn-the-ship-around-a-true-story-of-building-leaders-by-breaking-the-rules-l-david-marquet-foreword-by-stephen-r-covey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>David Marquet is the kind of leader who comes around only once in a generation &#8230; his ideas and lessons are invaluable&#8217; Simon Sinek, author of Start With Why Captain David Marquet was used to giving orders. In the high-stress environment of the USS Santa Fe, a nuclear-powered submarine, it was crucial his men did [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/turn-the-ship-around-a-true-story-of-building-leaders-by-breaking-the-rules-l-david-marquet-foreword-by-stephen-r-covey-abridged/">Turn The Ship Around! : A True Story of Building Leaders by Breaking the Rules &#8211; L. David Marquet, Foreword by Stephen R Covey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>David Marquet is the kind of leader who comes around only once in a generation &#8230; his ideas and lessons are invaluable&#8217; Simon Sinek, author of Start With Why    </p>
<p>                    Captain David Marquet was used to giving orders. In the high-stress environment of the USS Santa Fe, a nuclear-powered submarine, it was crucial his men did their job well. But the ship was dogged by poor morale, poor performance and the worst retention in the fleet.     </p>
<p>                    One day, Marquet unknowingly gave an impossible order, and his crew tried to follow it anyway. He realized he was leading in a culture of followers, and they were all in danger unless they fundamentally changed the way they did things.     </p>
<p>                    Marquet took matters into his own hands and pushed for leadership at every level. Before long, his crew became fully engaged and the Santa Fe skyrocketed from worst to first in the fleet.     </p>
<p>                    No matter your business or position, you can apply Marquet&#8217;s approach to create a workplace where everyone takes responsibility for their actions, people are healthier and happier &#8211; and everyone is a leader.    </p>
<p>                    In his latest book, Leadership is Language, Marquet builds on what he teaches in Turn the Ship Around!, showing us how to lead our teams to success through the language that we use.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/turn-the-ship-around-a-true-story-of-building-leaders-by-breaking-the-rules-l-david-marquet-foreword-by-stephen-r-covey-abridged/">Turn The Ship Around! : A True Story of Building Leaders by Breaking the Rules &#8211; L. David Marquet, Foreword by Stephen R Covey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Powerful : Building a Culture of Freedom and Responsibility &#8211; Patty McCord (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/powerful-building-a-culture-of-freedom-and-responsibility-patty-mccord-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/powerful-building-a-culture-of-freedom-and-responsibility-patty-mccord-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Powerful, Patty McCord shares what she learned at Netflix and elsewhere in Silicon Valley. Advocating the practice of radical honesty in the workplace, saying good-bye to employees who don&#8217;t fit the company&#8217;s emerging needs, and motivating with challenging work, not promises, perks, and bonus plans.McCord argues that the old standbys of corporate HR &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/powerful-building-a-culture-of-freedom-and-responsibility-patty-mccord-abridged/">Powerful : Building a Culture of Freedom and Responsibility &#8211; Patty McCord (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Powerful, Patty McCord shares what she learned at Netflix and elsewhere in Silicon Valley. Advocating the practice of radical honesty in the workplace, saying good-bye to employees who don&#8217;t fit the company&#8217;s emerging needs, and motivating with challenging work, not promises, perks, and bonus plans.McCord argues that the old standbys of corporate HR &#8211; annual performance reviews, retention plans, employee empowerment and engagement programs &#8211; often end up being a colossal waste of time and resources. Her road-tested advice, offered with humour and irreverence, provides readers a different path for creating a culture of high performance and profitability. Powerful will change how you think about work and the way a business should be run.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/powerful-building-a-culture-of-freedom-and-responsibility-patty-mccord-abridged/">Powerful : Building a Culture of Freedom and Responsibility &#8211; Patty McCord (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Effective HR Communication : A Framework for Communicating HR Programmes with Impact &#8211; Debra Corey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/effective-hr-communication-a-framework-for-communicating-hr-programmes-with-impact-debra-corey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/effective-hr-communication-a-framework-for-communicating-hr-programmes-with-impact-debra-corey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s competitive environment where we are doing everything we can to compete for talent, effective communication ensures we are showcasing our HR programmes in a way which will help us attract, retain and engage talent. Effective HR Communication is a practical guide to develop and deliver effective communication campaigns, ensuring that teams have the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/effective-hr-communication-a-framework-for-communicating-hr-programmes-with-impact-debra-corey-abridged/">Effective HR Communication : A Framework for Communicating HR Programmes with Impact &#8211; Debra Corey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s competitive environment where we are doing everything we can to compete for talent, effective communication ensures we are showcasing our HR programmes in a way which will help us attract, retain and engage talent. Effective HR Communication is a practical guide to develop and deliver effective communication campaigns, ensuring that teams have the knowledge, skills and tools to achieve the desired objectives.     </p>
<p>                    Whether introducing new HR programmes or re-launching existing ones, communications help us deliver the key messages so that employees understand, appreciate and action them to meet our HR and business objectives.     </p>
<p>                    Effective HR Communication introduces a six-step &#8216;IMPACT&#8217; model to explain and demonstrate the critical steps to be followed when developing a communications campaign.  This includes steps such as understanding the communication needs and requirements of employees, developing the most robust objectives, selecting and developing the appropriate medium, planning a campaign in an effective manner, leveraging the support of business partners, developing effective communications content, and measuring the success of the campaign.      </p>
<p>                    Using a combination of theory, examples, tips and tools from leading experts, this book provides practical information which can easily be used to create effective and impactful communications.  Case studies from leading organizations such as BT, LV=, Merlin Entertainments and Reward Gateway are included to further illustrate how communication has been done effectively.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/effective-hr-communication-a-framework-for-communicating-hr-programmes-with-impact-debra-corey-abridged/">Effective HR Communication : A Framework for Communicating HR Programmes with Impact &#8211; Debra Corey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Culture Engine : A Framework for Driving Results, Inspiring Your Employees, and Transforming Your Workplace &#8211; S. Chris Edmonds (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-culture-engine-a-framework-for-driving-results-inspiring-your-employees-and-transforming-your-workplace-s-chris-edmonds-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-culture-engine-a-framework-for-driving-results-inspiring-your-employees-and-transforming-your-workplace-s-chris-edmonds-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An organizational &#8220;North Star,&#8221; codifying valued behaviors for optimal performance The Culture Engine shows leaders how to create a high performing, values aligned culture through the creation of an organizational constitution. With practical step-by-step guidance, readers learn how to define their organization&#8217;s culture, delineate the behaviors that contribute to greater performance and greater engagement, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-culture-engine-a-framework-for-driving-results-inspiring-your-employees-and-transforming-your-workplace-s-chris-edmonds-abridged/">The Culture Engine : A Framework for Driving Results, Inspiring Your Employees, and Transforming Your Workplace &#8211; S. Chris Edmonds (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An organizational &#8220;North Star,&#8221; codifying valued behaviors for optimal performance The Culture Engine shows leaders how to create a high performing, values aligned culture through the creation of an organizational constitution. With practical step-by-step guidance, readers learn how to define their organization&#8217;s culture, delineate the behaviors that contribute to greater performance and greater engagement, and draft a document that codifies those behaviors into a constitution that guides behavior towards an ideal: a safe, inspiring workplace. The discussion focuses on people, including who should be involved at the outset and how to engage employees from start to finish, while examples of effective constitutions provide guidance toward drafting a document that can actualize an organization&#8217;s potential. Culture drives everything that happens in an organization day to day, including focus, priorities, and the treatment of employees and customers. A great culture drives great performance, and can help attract and retain great talent. But a great culture isn&#8217;t something that evolves naturally.<br />
                    The Culture Engine is a guide to strategically planning a culture by compiling the company&#8217;s guiding principles and behaviors into an organizational constitution. * Decide which behaviors and attitudes are desired in the organization * Secure leader commitment to planning, drafting, and implementing the document * Learn the most effective way to socialize the draft statement and get everyone on board * Model desired behaviors to boost employee engagement throughout the process Organizational culture is not an amorphous thing it comes down from the top, inspired and exemplified by the leadership. It can steer a company up or down, keep it on mission or force it off-course. For an organization to fulfill its potential, the culture must be on-point, truly reflecting the heart of the company from leaders to team members across the company. The Culture Engine helps leaders define the playing field, pushing performance to the next level.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-culture-engine-a-framework-for-driving-results-inspiring-your-employees-and-transforming-your-workplace-s-chris-edmonds-abridged/">The Culture Engine : A Framework for Driving Results, Inspiring Your Employees, and Transforming Your Workplace &#8211; S. Chris Edmonds (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myths of Creativity : The Truth About How Innovative Companies and People Generate Great Ideas &#8211; David Burkus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-myths-of-creativity-the-truth-about-how-innovative-companies-and-people-generate-great-ideas-david-burkus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myths-of-creativity-the-truth-about-how-innovative-companies-and-people-generate-great-ideas-david-burkus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to get past the most common myths about creativity to design truly innovative strategies We tend to think of creativity in terms reminiscent of the ancient muses: divinely-inspired, unpredictable, and bestowed upon a lucky few. But when our jobs challenge us to be creative on demand, we must develop novel, useful ideas that will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-creativity-the-truth-about-how-innovative-companies-and-people-generate-great-ideas-david-burkus-abridged/">The Myths of Creativity : The Truth About How Innovative Companies and People Generate Great Ideas &#8211; David Burkus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to get past the most common myths about creativity to design truly innovative strategies We tend to think of creativity in terms reminiscent of the ancient muses: divinely-inspired, unpredictable, and bestowed upon a lucky few. But when our jobs challenge us to be creative on demand, we must develop novel, useful ideas that will keep our organizations competitive. The Myths of Creativity demystifies the processes that drive innovation. Based on the latest research into how creative individuals and firms succeed, David Burkus highlights the mistaken ideas that hold us back and shows us how anyone can embrace a practical approach, grounded in reality, to finding the best new ideas, projects, processes, and programs. * Answers questions such as: What causes us to be creative in one moment and void in the next? What makes someone more or less creative than his or her peers? Where do our flashes of creative insight come from, and how can we generate more of them?<br />
                    * Debunks 10 common myths, including: the Eureka Myth; the Lone Creator Myth; the Incentive Myth; and The Brainstorming Myth * Written by David Burkus, founder of popular leadership blog LDRLB For anyone who struggles with creativity, or who makes excuses for delaying the work of innovation, The Myths of Creativity will help you overcome your obstacles to finding new ideas.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-creativity-the-truth-about-how-innovative-companies-and-people-generate-great-ideas-david-burkus-abridged/">The Myths of Creativity : The Truth About How Innovative Companies and People Generate Great Ideas &#8211; David Burkus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody Matters : The Extraordinary Power of Caring for Your People Like Family &#8211; Bob Chapman, Raj Sisodia (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everybody-matters-the-extraordinary-power-of-caring-for-your-people-like-family-bob-chapman-raj-sisodia-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everybody-matters-the-extraordinary-power-of-caring-for-your-people-like-family-bob-chapman-raj-sisodia-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re ready for a new way of doing business, this is the book for you&#8217; Daniel H. Pink, author of To Sell Is Human and Drive &#8216;Bob Chapman is on a mission to change the way businesses treat their employees&#8217; Inc.magazine Do you want to boost the morale, loyalty, creativity and performance of your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-matters-the-extraordinary-power-of-caring-for-your-people-like-family-bob-chapman-raj-sisodia-abridged/">Everybody Matters : The Extraordinary Power of Caring for Your People Like Family &#8211; Bob Chapman, Raj Sisodia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re ready for a new way of doing business, this is the book for you&#8217; Daniel H. Pink, author of To Sell Is Human and Drive    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Bob Chapman is on a mission to change the way businesses treat their employees&#8217; Inc.magazine     </p>
<p>                    Do you want to boost the morale, loyalty, creativity and performance of your employees?     </p>
<p>                    In Everybody Matters, CEO Bob Chapman and bestselling author Raj Sisodia challenge traditional thinking about how to run a business and show you how to lead your company so that everyone feels valued.      </p>
<p>                     As CEO of Barry-Wehmiller, Bob Chapman has pioneered a dramatically different approach to leadership that has created a high performing and happy culture. At Barry-Wehmiller, every single person matters, just like in a family. That&#8217;s not a cliche; it&#8217;s the bedrock of the company&#8217;s success.    </p>
<p>                     In Everybody Matters, Chapman shows how any organization can stop viewing its employees are simply func tions, to be moved around, &#8216;managed&#8217; with carrots and sticks, or discarded at will. By doing so, disengaged workers begin to share their gifts and talents toward a shared future. Uninspired workers stop feeling that their jobs have no meaning. And everyone stops counting the minutes until it&#8217;s time to go home.    </p>
<p>                     Everybody Matters provides clear steps to transform your own workplace, whether you lead two or two hundred thousand people.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-matters-the-extraordinary-power-of-caring-for-your-people-like-family-bob-chapman-raj-sisodia-abridged/">Everybody Matters : The Extraordinary Power of Caring for Your People Like Family &#8211; Bob Chapman, Raj Sisodia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leadership Jazz &#8211; Revised Edition : The Essential Elements of a Great Leader &#8211; Max De Pree (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leadership-jazz-revised-edition-the-essential-elements-of-a-great-leader-max-de-pree-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leadership-jazz-revised-edition-the-essential-elements-of-a-great-leader-max-de-pree-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since it was first published to wide acclaim in 1992, the bestselling Leadership Jazz has firmly placed itself among the great business classics. Former President Bill Clinton called it &#8220;astonishing,&#8221; and the late Peter Drucker advised, &#8220;Read this slowly. This book is wisdom in action.&#8221; Now updated for first time in well over a decade, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-jazz-revised-edition-the-essential-elements-of-a-great-leader-max-de-pree-abridged/">Leadership Jazz &#8211; Revised Edition : The Essential Elements of a Great Leader &#8211; Max De Pree (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since it was first published to wide acclaim in 1992, the bestselling Leadership Jazz has firmly placed itself among the great business classics. Former President Bill Clinton called it &#8220;astonishing,&#8221; and the late Peter Drucker advised, &#8220;Read this slowly. This book is wisdom in action.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Now updated for first time in well over a decade, this powerful book reveals why today, more than ever, leadership is more an art than a science. Today&#8217;s best leaders, De Pree says, are attuned to the needs and ideas of their followers, and even step aside at times to be followers themselves. Filled with insightful stories from De Pree&#8217;s experience as the chairman of Herman Miller and from people he&#8217;s met along the way, Leadership Jazz reveals how to:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Hold people accountable and give them space to reach their potential<br />
                    &#8211; See the needs of employees and those of the company as the same<br />
                    &#8211; Inspire change and innovation<br />
                    &#8211; Work effectively with creative people     </p>
<p>                    Complete with an extensive new introduction from De Pree on why his philosophy is more relevant now than ever before, Leadership Jazz gives you an entirely new way to look at the difficult job of leader.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-jazz-revised-edition-the-essential-elements-of-a-great-leader-max-de-pree-abridged/">Leadership Jazz &#8211; Revised Edition : The Essential Elements of a Great Leader &#8211; Max De Pree (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
