<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Military Engineering Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/military-engineering/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/military-engineering/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Military Engineering Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/military-engineering/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Accessory to War : The Unspoken Alliance Between Astrophysics and the Military &#8211; Neil deGrasse Tyson</title>
		<link>/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating foray into the millennia-long relationship between science and military power, acclaimed astrophysicist and &#8220;the world&#8217;s best science communicator&#8221; (Times Literary Supplement) Neil deGrasse Tyson and writer-researcher Avis Lang examine how the methods and tools of astrophysics have been enlisted in the service of war. &#8220;The overlap is strong, and the knowledge flows [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/">Accessory to War : The Unspoken Alliance Between Astrophysics and the Military &#8211; Neil deGrasse Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating foray into the millennia-long relationship between science and military power, acclaimed astrophysicist and &#8220;the world&#8217;s best science communicator&#8221; (Times Literary Supplement) Neil deGrasse Tyson and writer-researcher Avis Lang examine how the methods and tools of astrophysics have been enlisted in the service of war. &#8220;The overlap is strong, and the knowledge flows in both directions&#8221;, say the authors, because astrophysicists and military planners care about many of the same things: multi-spectral detection, ranging, tracking, imaging, high ground, nuclear fusion and access to space. Tyson and Lang call it a &#8220;curiously complicit&#8221; alliance. &#8220;The universe is both the ultimate frontier and the highest of high grounds&#8221;, they write. &#8220;Shared by both space scientists and space warriors, it&#8217;s a laboratory for one and a battlefield for the other. The explorer wants to understand it; the soldier wants to dominate it. But without the right technology-which is more or less the same technology for both parties-nobody can get to it, operate in it, scrutinise it, dominate it or use it to their advantage and someone else&#8217;s disadvantage.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                     Spanning early celestial navigation to satellite-enabled warfare, Accessory to War is a richly researched and provocative examination of the intersection of science, technology, industry and power that will introduce Tyson&#8217;s millions of fans to yet another dimension of how the universe has shaped our lives and our world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/">Accessory to War : The Unspoken Alliance Between Astrophysics and the Military &#8211; Neil deGrasse Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan. Kaplan probes the inner corridors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan.    </p>
<p>                     Kaplan probes the inner corridors of the National Security Agency, the beyond-top-secret cyber units in the Pentagon, the &#8220;information warfare&#8221; squads of the military services, and the national security debates in the White House, to tell this never-before-told story of the officers, policymakers, scientists, and spies who devised this new form of warfare and who have been planning and (more often than people know) fighting these wars for decades.    </p>
<p>                     From the 1991 Gulf War to conflicts in Haiti, Serbia, Syria, the former Soviet republics, Iraq, and Iran, where cyber warfare played a significant role, Dark Territory chronicles, in fascinating detail, a little-known past that shines an unsettling light on our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sea Power : The History and Geopolitics of the World&#8217;s Oceans &#8211; Admiral James Stavridis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Naval Forces & Warfare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From one of the most admired admirals of his generation-and the only admiral to serve as Supreme Allied Commander at NATO-comes a remarkable voyage through all of the world&#8217;s most important bodies of water, providing the story of naval power as a driver of human history and a crucial element in our current geopolitical path. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/">Sea Power : The History and Geopolitics of the World&#8217;s Oceans &#8211; Admiral James Stavridis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From one of the most admired admirals of his generation-and the only admiral to serve as Supreme Allied Commander at NATO-comes a remarkable voyage through all of the world&#8217;s most important bodies of water, providing the story of naval power as a driver of human history and a crucial element in our current geopolitical path.     </p>
<p>                     From the time of the Greeks and the Persians clashing in the Mediterranean, sea power has determined world power.  To an extent that is often underappreciated, it still does. No one understands this better than Admiral Jim Stavridis. In Sea Power, Admiral Stavridis takes us with him on a tour of the world&#8217;s oceans from the admiral&#8217;s chair, showing us how the geography of the oceans has shaped the destiny of nations, and how naval power has in a real sense made the world we live in today, and will shape the world we live in tomorrow.      </p>
<p>                     Not least, Sea Power is marvelous naval history, giving us fresh insight into great naval engagements from the battles of Salamis and Lepanto through to Trafalgar, the Battle of the Atlantic, and submarine conflicts of the Cold War. It is also a keen-eyed reckoning with the likely sites of our next major naval conflicts, particularly the Arctic Ocean, Eastern Mediterranean, and the South China Sea. Finally, Sea Power steps back to take a holistic view of the plagues to our oceans that are best seen that way, from piracy to pollution.    </p>
<p>                     When most of us look at a globe, we focus on the shape of the of the seven continents. Admiral Stavridis sees the shapes of the seven seas.  After reading Sea Power, you will too. Not since Alfred Thayer Mahan&#8217;s legendary The Influence of Sea Power upon History have we had such a powerful reckoning with this vital subject.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/">Sea Power : The History and Geopolitics of the World&#8217;s Oceans &#8211; Admiral James Stavridis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
