<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Information Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/information-theory/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/information-theory/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Information Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/information-theory/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Black Swan : The Impact of the Highly Improbable &#8211; Nassim Nicholas Taleb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-black-swan-the-impact-of-the-highly-improbable-nassim-nicholas-taleb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Risk Assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-black-swan-the-impact-of-the-highly-improbable-nassim-nicholas-taleb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The phenomenal international bestseller that shows us how to stop trying to predict everything &#8211; and take advantage of uncertainty What have the invention of the wheel, Pompeii, the Wall Street Crash, Harry Potter and the internet got in common? Why are all forecasters con-artists? Why should you never run for a train or read [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-black-swan-the-impact-of-the-highly-improbable-nassim-nicholas-taleb-abridged/">The Black Swan : The Impact of the Highly Improbable &#8211; Nassim Nicholas Taleb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The phenomenal international bestseller that shows us how to stop trying to predict everything &#8211; and take advantage of uncertainty    </p>
<p>                    What have the invention of the wheel, Pompeii, the Wall Street Crash, Harry Potter and the internet got in common? Why are all forecasters  con-artists? Why should you never run for a train or read a newspaper?     </p>
<p>                    This book is all about Black Swans: the random events that underlie our lives, from bestsellers to world disasters. Their impact is huge; they&#8217;re impossible to predict; yet after they happen we always try to rationalize them.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Taleb is a bouncy and even exhilarating  guide &#8230; I came to relish what he said, and even develop a sneaking affection for him as a person&#8217; Will Self, Independent on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;He leaps like some superhero of the mind&#8217; Boyd Tonkin, Independent</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-black-swan-the-impact-of-the-highly-improbable-nassim-nicholas-taleb-abridged/">The Black Swan : The Impact of the Highly Improbable &#8211; Nassim Nicholas Taleb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Information Grows : The Evolution of Order, from Atoms to Economies &#8211; Cesar Hidalgo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-information-grows-the-evolution-of-order-from-atoms-to-economies-cesar-hidalgo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-information-grows-the-evolution-of-order-from-atoms-to-economies-cesar-hidalgo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Why Information Grows, rising star Cesar Hidalgo offers a radical interpretation of global economics What is economic growth? And why, historically, has it occurred in only a few places? Previous efforts to answer these questions have focused on institutions, geography, finances, and psychology. But MIT professor Cesar Hidalgo argues that in order to fully [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-information-grows-the-evolution-of-order-from-atoms-to-economies-cesar-hidalgo-abridged/">Why Information Grows : The Evolution of Order, from Atoms to Economies &#8211; Cesar Hidalgo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Why Information Grows, rising star Cesar Hidalgo offers a radical interpretation of global economics    </p>
<p>                    What is economic growth? And why, historically, has it occurred in only a few places? Previous efforts to answer these questions have focused on institutions, geography, finances, and psychology. But MIT professor Cesar Hidalgo argues that in order to fully grasp the nature of economic growth we need to transcend the social sciences and turn to the science of information, networks and complexity. The growth of economies, he explains, is deeply connected with the growth of order &#8211; or information.    </p>
<p>                    At first glance, the universe seems hostile to order. Thermodynamics dictates that over time, order will disappear. But thermodynamics also has loopholes that promote the growth of information in pockets. Our cities are such pockets where information grows, but they are not all the same. For every Silicon Valley, Tokyo, and London, there are dozens of places with underdeveloped economies. Why does the US economy outstrip Brazil&#8217;s, and Brazil&#8217;s that of Chad? Why did the technology corridor along Boston&#8217;s Route 128 languish while Silicon Valley blossomed? In each case, the key is how people, companies, and the networks they form process information &#8211; it is all about their knowledge, knowhow and imagination. As Hidalgo compellingly shows, economies are made of networks of people and society is a collective computer. The problem of economic development is in fact the problem of making these networks more powerful.    </p>
<p>                    A radical new interpretation of global economics, Why Information Grows overturns traditional assumptions about the development of economies and the origins of wealth and takes a crucial step toward making economics less the dismal science and more the insightful one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-information-grows-the-evolution-of-order-from-atoms-to-economies-cesar-hidalgo-abridged/">Why Information Grows : The Evolution of Order, from Atoms to Economies &#8211; Cesar Hidalgo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
