<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Learning Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/learning/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/learning/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Learning Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/learning/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How We Learn : Throw out the rule book and unlock your brain&#8217;s potential &#8211; Benedict Carey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-we-learn-throw-out-the-rule-book-and-unlock-your-brains-potential-benedict-carey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-we-learn-throw-out-the-rule-book-and-unlock-your-brains-potential-benedict-carey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book will help you to learn Spanish &#8211; or the Spanish guitar &#8211; faster. This book will give an athlete the edge to turn Silver into Gold. This book will give any child the chance to perform better in exams. Full stop. How We Learn is a landmark book that shakes up everything we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-we-learn-throw-out-the-rule-book-and-unlock-your-brains-potential-benedict-carey-abridged/">How We Learn : Throw out the rule book and unlock your brain&#8217;s potential &#8211; Benedict Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book will help you to learn Spanish &#8211; or the Spanish guitar &#8211; faster.    </p>
<p>                    This book will give an athlete the edge to turn Silver into Gold.    </p>
<p>                    This book will give any child the chance to perform better in exams. Full stop.    </p>
<p>                    How We Learn is a landmark book that shakes up everything we thought we knew about how the brain absorbs and retains information. Filled with powerful &#8211; and often thrillingly counter-intuitive &#8211; wisdom, stories and practical tips, it gets to the very heart of the learning process; and gives us the keys to reach our very fullest potential in every walk of life.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is a revelation. I feel as if I&#8217;ve owned a brain for 54 years and only now discovered the operating manual . . . Benedict Carey serves up fascinating, surprising and valuable discoveries with clarity, wit, and heart.&#8217; Mary Roach, bestselling author of Stiff    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Whether you struggle to remember a client&#8217;s name, aspire to learn a new language, or are a student battling to prepare for the next test, this book is a must. I know of no other source that pulls together so much of what we know about the science of memory, and couples it with practical, practicable advice.&#8217;  Daniel T. Willingham, Professor of Psychology, University of Virginia    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Buy this book for yourself and for anyone who wants to learn faster and better.&#8217; Daniel Coyle, bestselling author of The Talent Code    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;As fun to read as it is important, and as much about how to live as it is about how to learn. Benedict Carey&#8217;s skills as a writer, plus his willingness to mine his own history as a student, give the book a wonderful narrative quality that makes it all the more accessible &#8211; and all the more effective as a tutorial.&#8217; Robert A. Bjork, Distinguished Professor of Psychology, University of California</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-we-learn-throw-out-the-rule-book-and-unlock-your-brains-potential-benedict-carey-abridged/">How We Learn : Throw out the rule book and unlock your brain&#8217;s potential &#8211; Benedict Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For centuries, experts have argued that learning was about memorizing information: You&#8217;re supposed to study facts, dates, and details; burn them into your memory; and then apply that knowledge at opportune times. But this approach to learning isn&#8217;t nearly enough for the world that we live in today, and in Learn Better journalist and education [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/">Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For centuries, experts have argued that learning was about memorizing information: You&#8217;re supposed to study facts, dates, and details; burn them into your memory; and then apply that knowledge at opportune times. But this approach to learning isn&#8217;t nearly enough for the world that we live in today, and in Learn Better journalist and education researcher Ulrich Boser demonstrates that how we learn can matter just as much as what we learn.     </p>
<p>                    In this brilliantly researched book, Boser maps out the new science of learning, showing how simple techniques like comprehension check-ins and making material personally relatable can help people gain expertise in dramatically better ways. He covers six key steps to help you &#8220;learn how to learn,&#8221; all illuminated with fascinating stories like how Jackson Pollock developed his unique painting style and why an ancient Japanese counting device allows kids to do math at superhuman speeds. Boser&#8217;s witty, engaging writing makes this book feel like a guilty pleasure, not homework.    </p>
<p>                    Learn Better will revolutionize the way students and society alike approach learning and makes the case that being smart is not an innate ability&#8211;learning is a skill everyone can master. With Boser as your guide, you will be able to fully capitalize on your brain&#8217;s remarkable ability to gain new skills and open up a whole new world of possibilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/">Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Range : How Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/range-how-generalists-triumph-in-a-specialized-world-david-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/range-how-generalists-triumph-in-a-specialized-world-david-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating . . . If you&#8217;re a generalist who has ever felt overshadowed by your specialist colleagues, this book is for you&#8217; &#8211; Bill Gates The instant Sunday Times Top Ten and New York Times bestseller Shortlisted for the Financial Times/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award A Financial Times Essential Reads A powerful argument [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/range-how-generalists-triumph-in-a-specialized-world-david-epstein-abridged/">Range : How Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating . . . If you&#8217;re a generalist who has ever felt overshadowed by your specialist colleagues, this book is for you&#8217; &#8211; Bill Gates    </p>
<p>                    The instant Sunday Times Top Ten and New York Times bestseller<br />
                    Shortlisted for the Financial Times/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award<br />
                    A Financial Times Essential Reads    </p>
<p>                    A powerful argument for how to succeed in any field: develop broad interests and skills while everyone around you is rushing to specialize.     </p>
<p>                    From the &#8216;10,000 hours rule&#8217; to the power of Tiger parenting, we have been taught that success in any field requires early specialization and many hours of deliberate practice. And, worse, that if you dabble or delay, you&#8217;ll never catch up with those who got a head start.     </p>
<p>                    This is completely wrong.    </p>
<p>                    In this landmark book, David Epstein shows you that the way to succeed is by sampling widely, gaining a breadth of experiences, taking detours, experimenting relentlessly, juggling many interests &#8211; in other words, by developing range.    </p>
<p>                    Studying the world&#8217;s most successful athletes, artists, musicians, inventors and scientists, Epstein demonstrates why in most fields &#8211; especially those that are complex and unpredictable &#8211; generalists, not specialists are primed to excel. No matter what you do, where you are in life, whether you are a teacher, student, scientist, business analyst, parent, job hunter, retiree, you will see the world differently after you&#8217;ve read Range. You&#8217;ll understand better how we solve problems, how we learn and how we succeed. You&#8217;ll see why failing a test is the best way to learn and why frequent quitters end up with the most fulfilling careers.     </p>
<p>                    As experts silo themselves further while computers master more of the skills once reserved for highly focused humans, Range shows how people who think broadly and embrace diverse experiences and perspectives will increasingly thrive and why spreading your knowledge across multiple domains is the key to your success, and how to achieve it.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I loved Range&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Urgent and important. . . an essential read for bosses, parents, coaches, and anyone who cares about improving performance.&#8217; &#8211; Daniel H. Pink    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;So much crucial and revelatory information about performance, success, and education.&#8217; &#8211; Susan Cain, bestselling author of Quiet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/range-how-generalists-triumph-in-a-specialized-world-david-epstein-abridged/">Range : How Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Addiction & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life    </p>
<p>                    We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can we kick bad habits &#8211; and stick with it?    </p>
<p>                    According to psychologist and behaviour researcher Dr Sean Young, the answer is to stop trying to change the person, and instead change the process. In Stick With It, Dr Young draws on his own research and that of other leading experts to explain how the mind often interferes with breaking bad habits, and how we can outsmart it, increasing the likelihood of lasting change by 200%.     </p>
<p>                    Packed with practical exercises and real-life case studies, Stick With It shows that it is possible to control spending, stick to a diet, exercise regularly and overcome problem behaviours &#8211; forever.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Scientifically grounded and personally implementable. It&#8217;s a winner&#8217; &#8211; Robert Cialdini, author of Influence and Pre-Suasion    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A must-read for anyone who&#8217;s been unable to keep a New Year&#8217;s resolution or failed at making a lasting change in any other area of their life or work. &#8211; Jonah Berger, author of Contagious    </p>
<p>                    Dr Sean Young is one of the world&#8217;s leading experts in the field of habit-forming. He is an acclaiedpsychologist and the founder and Executive Director of the UCLA Center for Digital Behavior. His research involves the study of cutting-edge ways of using social media and mobile technologies to change and predict human behaviour.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
