<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Horror Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/horror/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/horror/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Horror Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/horror/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Vampire World: Blood Brothers bk. 1 &#8211; Brian Lumley</title>
		<link>/vampire-world-blood-brothers-bk-1-brian-lumley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/vampire-world-blood-brothers-bk-1-brian-lumley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The vampires have been vanquished! Harry Keogh and the armies of the dead have destroyed the evil that once plagued the world. Nathan and Nestor, secret twin sons of the Necroscope and a proud gypsy woman, were children when their father, his humanity poisoned by his fearsome struggles, sacrificed himself to save mankind.Yet there are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vampire-world-blood-brothers-bk-1-brian-lumley/">Vampire World: Blood Brothers bk. 1 &#8211; Brian Lumley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The vampires have been vanquished! Harry Keogh and the armies of the dead have destroyed the evil that once plagued the world. Nathan and Nestor, secret twin sons of the Necroscope and a proud gypsy woman, were children when their father, his humanity poisoned by his fearsome struggles, sacrificed himself to save mankind.Yet there are vampires still, vampires crueler and stranger than any the Necroscope had faced. When these new, merciless killers swoop out of the sky, Nathan and Nestor are men&#8211;but they have few of Harry Keogh&#8217;s miraculous powers.Torn from each other by battle, the sons of the Necroscope journey across the vampire world, exploring its mysteries, each seeking the powerful, terrible vampires, his missing brother&#8230;.and the woman they both love!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vampire-world-blood-brothers-bk-1-brian-lumley/">Vampire World: Blood Brothers bk. 1 &#8211; Brian Lumley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Last Aerie &#8211; Brian Lumley</title>
		<link>/the-last-aerie-brian-lumley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-last-aerie-brian-lumley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nestor and Nathan Kiklu are the twin sons of Harry Keogh, the Necroscope, the man who talked to the dead, rallying them to mankind&#8217;s side for great battles against the vampires. The twins, linked by blood and the unique mental powers they inherited from their father, are driven apart by their love for the same [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-last-aerie-brian-lumley/">The Last Aerie &#8211; Brian Lumley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nestor and Nathan Kiklu are the twin sons of Harry Keogh, the Necroscope, the man who talked to the dead, rallying them to mankind&#8217;s side for great battles against the vampires.<br />
                    The twins, linked by blood and the unique mental powers they inherited from their father, are driven apart by their love for the same woman&#8230;and by their very different attitudes toward the vampires who prey upon their people.<br />
                    Nathan takes up the struggle against the vampires, defending home and family, while Nestor, fascinated by the vampires&#8217; unearthly powers and eerie evil, has become his twin&#8217;s worst nightmare: a vampire Lord!<br />
                    Nathan is imprisoned by a megalomaniac ESPer who plans to invade the vampire world. Rescued by the members of E-Branch, the British psychic-powered spy organization once led by Harry Keogh, Nathan finds himself fighting side by side with his father&#8217;s oldest friends.<br />
                    Nathan Kiklu, like Harry Keogh, is a necroscope. He must win the friendship of the dead before he can return to his own world.<br />
                    Nestor, growing ever more powerful among the vampire hierarchy, plots the ruination of all his enemies and the complete domination of the human race.<br />
                    Harry Keogh&#8217;s sons have become the bitterest of enemies, each determined to destroy the other. When next they meet, one will surely die!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-last-aerie-brian-lumley/">The Last Aerie &#8211; Brian Lumley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Four Past Midnight: The Sun Dog &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/four-past-midnight-the-sun-dog-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/four-past-midnight-the-sun-dog-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Sun Dog, the concluding novella in Stephen King&#8217;s best-selling Four Past Midnight, the source of terror is a simple Polaroid camera owned by a 15-year-old boy in the small town of Castle Rock, Maine. No matter where Kevin Delevan aims the camera, it produces a photograph of an enormous, ugly, vicious looking dog. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/four-past-midnight-the-sun-dog-stephen-king/">Four Past Midnight: The Sun Dog &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Sun Dog, the concluding novella in Stephen King&#8217;s best-selling Four Past Midnight, the source of terror is a simple Polaroid camera owned by a 15-year-old boy in the small town of Castle Rock, Maine. No matter where Kevin Delevan aims the camera, it produces a photograph of an enormous, ugly, vicious looking dog. In each successive picture, the menacing creature draws nearer to the flat surface of the Polaroid film as if it intends to break through. When old Pop Merrill, the towns sharpest trader, gets wind of this phenomenon, he envisions a way to profit from itbut the Sun Dog, a beast that shouldnt exist at all, turns out to be a very dangerous investment.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/four-past-midnight-the-sun-dog-stephen-king/">Four Past Midnight: The Sun Dog &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Angel Fire (Immortal Legacy Book 1) &#8211; Ella Sumers</title>
		<link>/angel-fire-immortal-legacy-book-1-ella-sumers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/angel-fire-immortal-legacy-book-1-ella-sumers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cadence Lightbringer, daughter of an archangel, has trained from birth to one day drink the Nectar of the gods and ascend to the angels’ ranks. She’s always been the perfect soldier. She’s always known exactly where her life is headed. Until she is assigned to a mission with Damiel Dragonsire, Master Interrogator of the Legion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/angel-fire-immortal-legacy-book-1-ella-sumers/">Angel Fire (Immortal Legacy Book 1) &#8211; Ella Sumers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cadence Lightbringer, daughter of an archangel, has trained from birth to one day drink the Nectar of the gods and ascend to the angels’ ranks. She’s always been the perfect soldier. She’s always known exactly where her life is headed.</p>
<p>Until she is assigned to a mission with Damiel Dragonsire, Master Interrogator of the Legion of Angels.</p>
<p>Powerful, paranoid, and brutally intelligent, Damiel has built up a reputation for hunting down each and every traitor hiding within the Legion’s ranks. And his latest suspect is Cadence. Convinced she is not the perfect soldier everyone believes her to be, he will stop at nothing to expose her.</p>
<p>Angel Fire is the first book in the Immortal Legacy series.</p>
<p>The Immortal Legacy series:<br />
Angel Fire<br />
Angel Fury<br />
Angel Fever</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/angel-fire-immortal-legacy-book-1-ella-sumers/">Angel Fire (Immortal Legacy Book 1) &#8211; Ella Sumers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Carrie &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/carrie-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/carrie-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s legendary debut, about a teenage outcast and the revenge she enacts on her classmates. Carrie White may be picked on by her classmates, but she has a gift. She can move things with her mind. Doors lock. Candles fall. This is her power and her problem. Then, an act of kindness, as spontaneous [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/carrie-stephen-king/">Carrie &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s legendary debut, about a teenage outcast and the revenge she enacts on her classmates.     </p>
<p>                    Carrie White may be picked on by her classmates, but she has a gift. She can move things with her mind. Doors lock. Candles fall. This is her power and her problem. Then, an act of kindness, as spontaneous as the vicious taunts of her classmates, offers Carrie a chance to be a normal&#8230;until an unexpected cruelty turns her gift into a weapon of horror and destruction that no one will ever forget.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/carrie-stephen-king/">Carrie &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just After Sunset &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/just-after-sunset-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/just-after-sunset-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Just after sunset, as darkness grips the imagination, is the time when you feel the unexpected creep into the every day. As familiar journeys take a different turn, ordinary objects assume extraordinary powers. A blind intruder visits a dying man &#8211; and saves his life, with a kiss. A woman receives a phone call from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-after-sunset-stephen-king/">Just After Sunset &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just after sunset, as darkness grips the imagination, is the time when you feel the unexpected creep into the every day. As familiar journeys take a different turn, ordinary objects assume extraordinary powers.</p>
<p>                    A blind intruder visits a dying man &#8211; and saves his life, with a kiss. </p>
<p>                    A woman receives a phone call from her husband. Her late husband. </p>
<p>                    In the emotional aftermath of her baby&#8217;s sudden death, Emily starts running. And running. Her curiosity leads her right into the hands of a murderer . . . and soon her legs are her only hope for survival.</p>
<p>                    Enter a world of masterful suspense, dark comedy and thrilling twists which will keep you riveted from the first page.</p>
<p>                    Enter the world of No. 1 bestseller Stephen King.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-after-sunset-stephen-king/">Just After Sunset &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Only Good Indians &#8211; Stephen Graham Jones</title>
		<link>/the-only-good-indians-stephen-graham-jones/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-only-good-indians-stephen-graham-jones/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Thrilling, literate, scary, immersive.&#8221; &#8211; Stephen King The Stoker, Bradbury and Alex Award-winning, NYT-bestselling gothic horror about cultural identity, the price of tradition and revenge for fans of Adam Nevill&#8217;s The Ritual. Ricky, Gabe, Lewis and Cassidy are men bound to their heritage, bound by society, and trapped in the endless expanses of the landscape. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-only-good-indians-stephen-graham-jones/">The Only Good Indians &#8211; Stephen Graham Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Thrilling, literate, scary, immersive.&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211; Stephen King<br />
                    The Stoker, Bradbury and Alex Award-winning, NYT-bestselling gothic horror about cultural identity, the price of tradition and revenge for fans of Adam Nevill&#8217;s The Ritual.</p>
<p>                    Ricky, Gabe, Lewis and Cassidy are men bound to their heritage, bound by society, and trapped in the endless expanses of the landscape. Now, ten years after a fateful elk hunt, which remains a closely guarded secret between them, these men &#8211; and their children &#8211; must face a ferocious spirit that is coming for them, one at a time. A spirit which wears the faces of the ones they love, tearing a path into their homes, their families and their most sacred moments of faith.</p>
<p>                    Ten years after that fateful hunt, these men are being stalked themselves. Soaked with a powerful gothic atmosphere, the endless expanses of the landscape press down on these men &#8211; and their children &#8211; as the ferocious spirit comes for them one at a time.</p>
<p>                    The Only Good Indians, charts Nature&#8217;s revenge on a lost generation that maybe never had a chance. Cleaved to their heritage, these parents, husbands, sons and Indians, men live on the fringes of a society that has rejected them, refusing to challenge their exile to limbo.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-only-good-indians-stephen-graham-jones/">The Only Good Indians &#8211; Stephen Graham Jones</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Past Midnight: The Langoliers &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/one-past-midnight-the-langoliers-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/one-past-midnight-the-langoliers-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first of a four-part audio series from Stephen King&#8217;s best-selling book, Four Past Midnight. On a redeye flight from Los Angeles to Boston, only 11 passengers survivebut landing in a dead world makes them wish they hadn&#8217;t.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-past-midnight-the-langoliers-stephen-king/">One Past Midnight: The Langoliers &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first of a four-part audio series from Stephen King&#8217;s best-selling book, Four Past Midnight. On a redeye flight from Los Angeles to Boston, only 11 passengers survivebut landing in a dead world makes them wish they hadn&#8217;t.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-past-midnight-the-langoliers-stephen-king/">One Past Midnight: The Langoliers &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Road Rage &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/road-rage-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anime & Manga]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror & Ghost]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/road-rage-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed novelist/Eisner-winning graphic novelist Joe Hill collaborated with his father, Stephen King, in Throttle, for the first time on a tale that paid tribute to Richard Matheson&#8217;s classic tale, Duel. Now, IDW is proud to present comic-book tellings of both stories in Road Rage, adapted by Chris Ryall with art by Nelson Daniel and Rafa [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/road-rage-stephen-king/">Road Rage &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed novelist/Eisner-winning graphic novelist Joe Hill collaborated with his father, Stephen King, in Throttle, for the first time on a tale that paid tribute to Richard Matheson&#8217;s classic tale, Duel. Now, IDW is proud to present comic-book tellings of both stories in Road Rage, adapted by Chris Ryall with art by Nelson Daniel and Rafa Garres.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/road-rage-stephen-king/">Road Rage &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gerald&#8217;s Game &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/geralds-game-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/geralds-game-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A game. A husband and wife game. Gerald&#8217;s Game. But this time Jesse doesn&#8217;t want to play. Lying there, spread-eagled and handcuffed to the bedstead while he looms and drools over her, she feels angry and humiliated. So she kicks out hard. Aims to hit him where it hurts. He isn&#8217;t meant to die, leaving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/geralds-game-stephen-king/">Gerald&#8217;s Game &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A game. A husband and wife game. Gerald&#8217;s Game.    </p>
<p>                     But this time Jesse doesn&#8217;t want to play. Lying there, spread-eagled and handcuffed to the bedstead while he looms and drools over her, she feels angry and humiliated.    </p>
<p>                     So she kicks out hard. Aims to hit him where it hurts.    </p>
<p>                     He isn&#8217;t meant to die, leaving Jesse alone and helpless in a lakeside holiday cabin. Miles from anywhere. No-one to hear her screams.    </p>
<p>                     Alone.  Except for the stray dog that smells her blood, the voices in her head which begin to chatter, and the board which creaks stealthily at nightfall, signalling that something or someone else is close by.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/geralds-game-stephen-king/">Gerald&#8217;s Game &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everything&#8217;s Eventual : 14 DARK TALES &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/everythings-eventual-14-dark-tales-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everythings-eventual-14-dark-tales-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Includes a Dark Tower story entitled &#8216;The Little Sisters of Eluria&#8217;. Nothing is quite as it seems. Expect the unexpected in this veritable treasure trove of enthralling, witty, dark tales that could only come from the imagination of the greatest storyteller of our time. In this eerie, enchanting compilation, Stephen King takes readers down a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everythings-eventual-14-dark-tales-stephen-king/">Everything&#8217;s Eventual : 14 DARK TALES &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Includes a Dark Tower story entitled &#8216;The Little Sisters of Eluria&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    Nothing is quite as it seems.    </p>
<p>                    Expect the unexpected in this veritable treasure trove of enthralling, witty, dark tales that could only come from the imagination of the greatest storyteller of our time.    </p>
<p>                    In this eerie, enchanting compilation, Stephen King takes readers down a road less travelled (for good reason) in the blockbuster e-book &#8216;Riding the Bullet&#8217;. Terror becomes deja vu all over again when you get &#8216;That Feeling, You Can Only Say What It Is in French&#8217;. &#8216;LT&#8217;s Theory of Pets&#8217; will make you stop and think before giving a dog to a loved one. And there are eleven more stories that will keep you awake until dawn.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everythings-eventual-14-dark-tales-stephen-king/">Everything&#8217;s Eventual : 14 DARK TALES &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cell &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/cell-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cell-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s bestselling apocalyptic thriller. &#8216;Civilization slipped into its second dark age on an unsurprising track of blood but with a speed that could not have been foreseen by even the most pessimistic futurist. By Halloween, every major city from New York to Moscow stank to the empty heavens and the world as it had [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cell-stephen-king/">Cell &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s bestselling apocalyptic thriller.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Civilization slipped into its second dark age on an unsurprising track of blood but with a speed that could not have been foreseen by even the most pessimistic futurist. By Halloween, every major city from New York to Moscow stank to the empty heavens and the world as it had been was a memory.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    The event became known as The Pulse. The virus was carried by every cell phone operating within the entire world. Within hours, those receiving calls would be infected.    </p>
<p>                    A young artist Clayton Riddell realises what is happening. He flees the devastation of explosive, burning Boston, desperate to reach his son before his son switches on his little red mobile phone . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cell-stephen-king/">Cell &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cycle of the Werewolf &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/cycle-of-the-werewolf-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anime & Manga]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cycle-of-the-werewolf-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic masterpiece by #1 New York Times bestselling author Stephen King&#8211;illustrated by the legendary artist Bernie Wrightson! Terror began in January&#8211;by the light of the full moon&#8230; The first scream came from the snowbound railwayman who felt the werewolf&#8217;s fangs ripping at his throat. The next month there was a scream of ecstatic agony [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cycle-of-the-werewolf-stephen-king/">Cycle of the Werewolf &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic masterpiece by #1 New York Times bestselling author Stephen King&#8211;illustrated by the legendary artist Bernie Wrightson!     </p>
<p>                    Terror began in January&#8211;by the light of the full moon&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    The first scream came from the snowbound railwayman who felt the werewolf&#8217;s fangs ripping at his throat. The next month there was a scream of ecstatic agony from the woman attacked in her cozy bedroom. Now scenes of unbelievable horror unfold each time the full moon shines on the isolated Maine town of Tarker&#8217;s Mills. No one knows who will be attacked next. But one thing is sure. When the full moon rises, a paralyzing fear sweeps through Tarker&#8217;s Mills. For snarls that sound like human words can be heard whining through the wind. And all around are the footprints of a monster whose hunger cannot be sated&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cycle-of-the-werewolf-stephen-king/">Cycle of the Werewolf &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Christine &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/christine-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/christine-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a stunning new cover look, King&#8217;s bestselling supernatural tale about a boy, his girlfriend and a possessed &#8217;58 Plymouth Fury called Christine. This is the story of a lover&#8217;s triangle . . . It was bad from the start. And it got worse in a hurry. Christine is eating into his mind, burrowing into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/christine-stephen-king/">Christine &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a stunning new cover look, King&#8217;s bestselling supernatural tale about a boy, his girlfriend and a possessed &#8217;58 Plymouth Fury called Christine.    </p>
<p>                    This is the story of a lover&#8217;s triangle . . . It was bad from the start. And it got worse in a hurry.    </p>
<p>                    Christine is eating into his mind, burrowing into his unconscious.    </p>
<p>                    Christine, blood-red, fat, and finned, is twenty. Her promise lies all in her past. Greedy and big, she is Arnie&#8217;s obsession, a &#8217;58 Plymouth Fury. Broken down but not finished.    </p>
<p>                    There is still power in her &#8211; a frightening power that leaks like sump oil, staining and corrupting. A malign power that corrodes the mind and turns ownership into Possession.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/christine-stephen-king/">Christine &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Insomnia &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/insomnia-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/insomnia-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ll lose a lot of sleep . . . Ralph does. At first he starts waking up earlier. And earlier. Then the hallucinations start &#8211; the colours, shapes and strange auras. Not to mention the bald doctors who always turn up at the scene of a death. That&#8217;s when Ralph begins to lose a lot [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/insomnia-stephen-king/">Insomnia &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ll lose a lot of sleep . . .    </p>
<p>                    Ralph does.  At first he starts waking up earlier.  And earlier.  Then the hallucinations start &#8211; the colours, shapes and strange auras.  Not to mention the bald doctors who always turn up at the scene of a death.    </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s when Ralph begins to lose a lot more than sleep.  When he begins to understand why his hitherto mild-mannered friend, Ed, is getting out of control &#8211; dangerously so.  And why his home town is about to become the new Armageddon . . .    </p>
<p>                    Insomnia is a relentless waking nightmare in which the master of horror and suspense guarantees you sure won&#8217;t rest in peace.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/insomnia-stephen-king/">Insomnia &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It : The classic book from Stephen King with a new film tie-in cover to IT: CHAPTER 2, due for release September 2019 &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/it-the-classic-book-from-stephen-king-with-a-new-film-tie-in-cover-to-it-chapter-2-due-for-release-september-2019-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Unexplained Phenomena / The Paranormal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/it-the-classic-book-from-stephen-king-with-a-new-film-tie-in-cover-to-it-chapter-2-due-for-release-september-2019-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This tie-in edition will be available from 16 July TIE IN TO A NEW MAJOR MOTION PICTURE, IT: CHAPTER 2, ADAPTED FROM KING&#8217;S TERRIFYING CLASSIC 27 years later, the Losers Club have grown up and moved away, until a devastating phone call brings them back&#8230; Derry, Maine was just an ordinary town: familiar, well-ordered for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-the-classic-book-from-stephen-king-with-a-new-film-tie-in-cover-to-it-chapter-2-due-for-release-september-2019-stephen-king/">It : The classic book from Stephen King with a new film tie-in cover to IT: CHAPTER 2, due for release September 2019 &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This tie-in edition will be available from 16 July </p>
<p>                    TIE IN TO A NEW MAJOR MOTION PICTURE, IT: CHAPTER 2, ADAPTED FROM KING&#8217;S TERRIFYING CLASSIC</p>
<p>                    27 years later, the Losers Club have grown up and moved away, until a devastating phone call brings them back&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Derry, Maine was just an ordinary town: familiar, well-ordered for the most part, a good place to live.</p>
<p>                    It was a group of children who saw- and felt- what made Derry so horribly different. In the storm drains, in the sewers, IT lurked, taking on the shape of every nightmare, each one&#8217;s deepest dread. Sometimes IT appeared as an evil clown named Pennywise and sometimes IT reached up, seizing, tearing, killing . . .</p>
<p>                    Time passed and the children grew up, moved away and forgot. THEN they are called back, once more to confront IT as IT stirs and coils in the sullen depths of their memories, emerging again to make their past nightmares a terrible present reality&#8230;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;They&#8217;ll float&#8230;and when you&#8217;re down here with me, you&#8217;ll float too&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-the-classic-book-from-stephen-king-with-a-new-film-tie-in-cover-to-it-chapter-2-due-for-release-september-2019-stephen-king/">It : The classic book from Stephen King with a new film tie-in cover to IT: CHAPTER 2, due for release September 2019 &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Needful Things &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/needful-things-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/needful-things-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There was a new shop in town. Run by a stranger. Needful Things, the sign said. The oddest name. A name that caused some gossip and speculation among the good folks of Castle Rock, Maine, while they waited for opening day. Eleven-year-old Brian Rusk was the first customer and he got just what he wanted, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/needful-things-stephen-king/">Needful Things &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There was a new shop in town. Run by a stranger.     </p>
<p>                    Needful Things, the sign said. The oddest name. A name that caused some gossip and speculation among the good folks of Castle Rock, Maine, while they waited for opening day.    </p>
<p>                    Eleven-year-old Brian Rusk was the first customer and he got just what he wanted, a very rare 1956 Sandy Koufax baseball card. Signed. Cyndi Rose Martin was next. A Lalique vase. A perfect match for her living room decor.     </p>
<p>                    Something for everyone. Something you really had to have. And always at a price you could just about afford. The cash price that is. Because there was another price. There always is when your heart&#8217;s most secret, true desire is for sale . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/needful-things-stephen-king/">Needful Things &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>11/22/63 &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/11-22-63-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/11-22-63-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the Ten Best Books of The New York Times Book Review Winner of the Los Angeles Times Book Prize Now a miniseries from Hulu starring James Franco ON NOVEMBER 22, 1963, THREE SHOTS RANG OUT IN DALLAS, PRESIDENT KENNEDY DIED, AND THE WORLD CHANGED. WHAT IF YOU COULD CHANGE IT BACK? In this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/11-22-63-stephen-king/">11/22/63 &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the Ten Best Books of The New York Times Book Review<br />
                     Winner of the Los Angeles Times Book Prize<br />
                     Now a miniseries from Hulu starring James Franco </p>
<p>                    ON NOVEMBER 22, 1963, THREE SHOTS RANG OUT IN DALLAS, PRESIDENT KENNEDY DIED, AND THE WORLD CHANGED. WHAT IF YOU COULD CHANGE IT BACK? </p>
<p>                    In this brilliantly conceived tour de force, Stephen King&#8211;who has absorbed the social, political, and popular culture of his generation more imaginatively and thoroughly than any other writer&#8211;takes readers on an incredible journey into the past and the possibility of altering it. </p>
<p>                    It begins with Jake Epping, a thirty-five-year-old English teacher in Lisbon Falls, Maine, who makes extra money teaching GED classes. He asks his students to write about an event that changed their lives, and one essay blows him away&#8211;a gruesome, harrowing story about the night more than fifty years ago when Harry Dunning&#8217;s father came home and killed his mother, his sister, and his brother with a sledgehammer. Reading the essay is a watershed moment for Jake, his life&#8211;like Harry&#8217;s, like America&#8217;s in 1963&#8211;turning on a dime. Not much later his friend Al, who owns the local diner, divulges a secret: his storeroom is a portal to the past, a particular day in 1958. And Al enlists Jake to take over the mission that has become his obsession&#8211;to prevent the Kennedy assassination. </p>
<p>                    So begins Jake&#8217;s new life as George Amberson, in a different world of Ike and JFK and Elvis, of big American cars and sock hops and cigarette smoke everywhere. From the dank little city of Derry, Maine (where there&#8217;s Dunning business to conduct), to the warmhearted small town of Jodie, Texas, where Jake falls dangerously in love, every turn is leading eventually, of course, to a troubled loner named Lee Harvey Oswald and to Dallas, where the past becomes heart-stoppingly suspenseful, and where history might not be history anymore. Time-travel has never been so believable. Or so terrifying.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/11-22-63-stephen-king/">11/22/63 &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black House &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/black-house-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-house-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A comfortable, solid, middle-American town &#8211; inhabited by a serial killer&#8230; Children are disappearing, lost to the world, horrifically murdered. The best clue the detectives have &#8211; a serial killer from a century ago. Jack Sawyer, retired from the LAPD at 35, plagued by visions of another world. As a child, Jack visited the Territories, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-house-stephen-king/">Black House &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A comfortable, solid, middle-American town &#8211; inhabited by a serial killer&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Children are disappearing, lost to the world, horrifically murdered.     </p>
<p>                    The best clue the detectives have &#8211; a  serial killer from a century ago.     </p>
<p>                    Jack Sawyer, retired from the LAPD at 35, plagued by visions of another world.     </p>
<p>                    As a child, Jack visited the Territories,  a menacing place of violence and madness, to save his dying mother. Now, if the latest child victim is to be saved, Jack must retrieve his lost childhood memories, and revisit the one place he hoped never to see again.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-house-stephen-king/">Black House &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elevation &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/elevation-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/elevation-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A quick, satisfying read . . . the sign of a master simply elevating his own legendary game yet again&#8217; USA Today In the small town of Castle Rock word gets around quickly. That&#8217;s why Scott Carey only confides in his friend Doctor Bob Ellis about his strange condition. Every day he&#8217;s losing weight &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elevation-stephen-king/">Elevation &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A quick, satisfying read . . . the sign of a master simply elevating his own legendary game yet again&#8217; USA Today    </p>
<p>                    In the small town of Castle Rock word gets around quickly.  That&#8217;s why Scott Carey only confides in his friend Doctor Bob Ellis about his strange condition.  Every day he&#8217;s losing weight &#8211; but without looking any different.       </p>
<p>                      Meanwhile a new couple, Deirdre and Missy, owners of a &#8216;fine dining experience&#8217; in town, have moved in next door.  Scott is not happy that their dogs keep fouling on his lawn.    </p>
<p>                      But as the town prepares for its annual Thanksgiving 12K run, Scott starts to understand the prejudices his neighbours face.  Soon, they forge a friendship which may just help him through his mysterious affliction&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Includes illustrations  (c) Mark Edward Geyer.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elevation-stephen-king/">Elevation &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dreamcatcher &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/dreamcatcher-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dreamcatcher-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Derry, Maine, four young boys once stood together and did a brave thing. Something that changed them in ways they hardly understand. A quarter of a century later, the boys are men who have gone their separate ways. Though they still get together once a year, to go hunting in the north woods of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dreamcatcher-stephen-king/">Dreamcatcher &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Derry, Maine, four young boys once stood together and did a brave thing.  Something that changed them in ways they hardly understand.    </p>
<p>                    A quarter of a century later, the boys are men who have gone their separate ways. Though they still get together once a year, to go hunting in the north woods of Maine.  But this time is different.  This time a man comes stumbling into their camp, lost, disoriented and muttering about lights in the sky.    </p>
<p>                    Before long, these old friends will be plunged into the most remarkable events of their lives as they struggle with a terrible creature from another world.  Their only chance of survival is locked in their shared past &#8211; and in the Dreamcatcher.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dreamcatcher-stephen-king/">Dreamcatcher &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Three Past Midnight: The Library Policeman &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/three-past-midnight-the-library-policeman-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/three-past-midnight-the-library-policeman-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Playaway is the simplest way to listen to audio on the go. Each Playaway comes with the digital content already pre-loaded on it and a battery to make it play. Simply plug in earbuds and enjoy. Each ultra-portable Playaway weighs only two ounces and comes packaged with earbuds and a standard AAA battery to allow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/three-past-midnight-the-library-policeman-stephen-king/">Three Past Midnight: The Library Policeman &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Playaway is the simplest way to listen to audio on the go. Each Playaway comes with the digital content already pre-loaded on it and a battery to make it play. Simply plug in earbuds and enjoy. Each ultra-portable Playaway weighs only two ounces and comes packaged with earbuds and a standard AAA battery to allow for immediate listening. Every Playaway comes ready to shelve in drop-box friendly packaging, complete with title inserts and instructions. Playaway is being circulated in over 11,000 public, academic, military and government libraries with a 99% library customer satisfaction rate. With 70 respected publishing partners, a growing collection of over 1,500 titles across 30 genres is available. No Cassettes. No CD&#8217;s. No downloads. Just Play.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/three-past-midnight-the-library-policeman-stephen-king/">Three Past Midnight: The Library Policeman &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bag of Bones &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/bag-of-bones-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's General Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bag-of-bones-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Mike Noonan&#8217;s wife dies unexpectedly, the bestselling author suffers from writer&#8217;s block. Until he is drawn to his summer home, the beautiful lakeside retreat called Sara Laughs. Here Mike finds the once familiar town in the tyrannical grip of millionaire Max Devore. Devore is hell-bent on getting custody of his deceased son&#8217;s daughter and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bag-of-bones-stephen-king/">Bag of Bones &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Mike Noonan&#8217;s wife dies unexpectedly, the bestselling author suffers from writer&#8217;s block.  Until he is drawn to his summer home, the beautiful lakeside retreat called Sara Laughs.    </p>
<p>                    Here Mike finds the once familiar town in the tyrannical grip of millionaire Max Devore.  Devore is hell-bent on getting custody of his deceased son&#8217;s daughter and is twisting the fabric of the community to this purpose.    </p>
<p>                      Three year old Kyra and her young mother turn to Mike for help. And Mike finds them increasingly irresistible.    </p>
<p>                    But there are other more sinister forces at Sara Laughs &#8211; and Kyra can feel them too&#8230;.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bag-of-bones-stephen-king/">Bag of Bones &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bachman Books &#8211; Richard Bachman</title>
		<link>/the-bachman-books-richard-bachman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bachman-books-richard-bachman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For years, readers wrote asking if Richard Bachman was really world-bestselling Stephen King writing under another name. Now the secret is out &#8211; and so, brought together in one volume, are these three spellbinding stories of future shock and suspense. The Long Walk: A chilling look at the ultra-conservative America of the future where a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bachman-books-richard-bachman/">The Bachman Books &#8211; Richard Bachman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For years, readers wrote asking if Richard Bachman was really world-bestselling Stephen King writing under another name. Now the secret is out &#8211; and so, brought together in one volume, are these three spellbinding stories of future shock and suspense.    </p>
<p>                    The Long Walk: A chilling look at the ultra-conservative America of the future where a grueling 450-mile marathon is the ultimate sports competition.    </p>
<p>                    Roadwork: An immovable man refuses to surrender to the irresistible force of progress.    </p>
<p>                    The Running Man: TV&#8217;s future-favourite game show, where contestants are hunted to death in the attempt to win a $1 billion jackpot.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bachman-books-richard-bachman/">The Bachman Books &#8211; Richard Bachman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nightmares and Dreamscapes &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/nightmares-and-dreamscapes-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nightmares-and-dreamscapes-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Stephen King Amusement Park &#8211; an unnerving experience, with rides every which way to hell . . . and a few to glory. A solitary finger pokes out of a drain. Novelty teeth turn predatory. The Nevada desert swallows a Cadillac. Meanwhile, the legend of Castle Rock returns . . . and grows on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nightmares-and-dreamscapes-stephen-king/">Nightmares and Dreamscapes &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Stephen King Amusement Park &#8211; an unnerving experience, with rides every which way to hell . . . and a few to glory.    </p>
<p>                    A solitary finger pokes out of a drain. Novelty teeth turn predatory. The Nevada desert swallows a Cadillac. Meanwhile, the legend of Castle Rock returns . . . and grows on you. What does it all mean? What else could it mean? Stephen King is here with a powerful collection of stories &#8211; a vast, many-chambered cave of a volume.    </p>
<p>                    The long reach of Stephen King&#8217;s imagination will take you on a roller coaster to places you&#8217;ve never been before. You will lose sleep. But Stephen King, writing to beat the devil, will do your dreaming for you.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nightmares-and-dreamscapes-stephen-king/">Nightmares and Dreamscapes &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Full Dark, No Stars : featuring 1922, now a Netflix film &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/full-dark-no-stars-featuring-1922-now-a-netflix-film-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/full-dark-no-stars-featuring-1922-now-a-netflix-film-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to fully know anyone? Even those we love the most? What tips someone over the edge to commit a crime? For a Nebraska farmer, the turning point comes when his wife threatens to sell off the family homestead. A cozy mystery writer plots a savage revenge after a brutal encounter with a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/full-dark-no-stars-featuring-1922-now-a-netflix-film-stephen-king/">Full Dark, No Stars : featuring 1922, now a Netflix film &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to fully know anyone? Even those we love the most? What tips someone over the edge to commit a crime?</p>
<p>                    For a Nebraska farmer, the turning point comes when his wife threatens to sell off the family homestead.</p>
<p>                    A cozy mystery writer plots a savage revenge after a brutal encounter with a stranger.</p>
<p>                    Dave Streeter gets the chance to cure himself from illness &#8211; if he agrees to impose misery on an old rival.</p>
<p>                    And Darcy Anderson discovers a box containing her husband&#8217;s dark and terrifying secrets &#8211; he&#8217;s not the man who keeps his nails short and collects coins.  And now he&#8217;s heading home . . .</p>
<p>                    Like DIFFERENT SEASONS and FOUR PAST MIDNIGHT, which generated such enduring hit films as The Shawshank Redemption and Stand by Me, FULL DARK, NO STARS proves Stephen King a master of the long story form.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/full-dark-no-stars-featuring-1922-now-a-netflix-film-stephen-king/">Full Dark, No Stars : featuring 1922, now a Netflix film &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Desperation &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/desperation-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/desperation-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to Desperation. Once a thriving copper mining town in the middle of the Nevada desert, Desperation is now eerily abandoned. It&#8217;s the last place that travellers like the Carver family, bound for vacation, and writer Johnny Marinville, astride his Harley, would expect to be stopped and charged. But Desperation still has a local cop [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/desperation-stephen-king/">Desperation &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to Desperation.    </p>
<p>                    Once a thriving copper mining town in the middle of the Nevada desert, Desperation is now eerily abandoned. It&#8217;s the last place that travellers like the Carver family, bound for vacation, and writer Johnny Marinville, astride his Harley, would expect to be stopped and charged. But Desperation still has a local cop &#8211; a unique regulator who patrols the wilderness highway.    </p>
<p>                    The secrets buried in Desperation are as terrifying as the forces summoned to encounter them. A terrifying transformation is taking place and the travellers will soon discover the true meaning of desperation . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/desperation-stephen-king/">Desperation &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Misery &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/misery-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/misery-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the true classics of psychological suspense, about a writer and his No. 1 fan, now with a stunning new cover look. Paul Sheldon used to write for a living. Now he&#8217;s writing to stay alive. Misery Chastain is dead. Paul Sheldon has just killed her &#8211; with relief, with joy. Misery made him [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/misery-stephen-king/">Misery &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the true classics of psychological suspense, about a writer and his No. 1 fan, now with a stunning new cover look.    </p>
<p>                    Paul Sheldon used to write for a living. Now he&#8217;s writing to stay alive.    </p>
<p>                      Misery Chastain is dead.  Paul Sheldon has just killed her &#8211; with relief, with joy.  Misery made him rich; she was the heroine of a string of bestsellers.  And now he wants to get on to some real writing.     </p>
<p>                      That&#8217;s when the car accident happens, and he wakes up splinted and in pain, in the remote mountain home of his rescuer, Annie Wilkes.     </p>
<p>                      The good news is that Annie was a nurse and has pain-killing drugs.  The bad news is that she has long been Paul&#8217;s Number One Fan.  And when she finds out what Paul has done to Misery, she doesn&#8217;t like it.  She doesn&#8217;t like it at all . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/misery-stephen-king/">Misery &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Godless : Feathers and Fire Book 7 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</title>
		<link>/godless-feathers-and-fire-book-7-shayne-silvers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/godless-feathers-and-fire-book-7-shayne-silvers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Slaughter is the best medicine. Callie Penrose is back to murder vampires and chew bubblegum. And she&#8217;s all out of bubblegum. Callie has had a rough few days. Five minutes after discovering she had a Godfather, she learned that the future of the world depended on the two of them taking an immediate road trip. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/godless-feathers-and-fire-book-7-shayne-silvers/">Godless : Feathers and Fire Book 7 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Slaughter is the best medicine.</p>
<p>                    Callie Penrose is back to murder vampires and chew bubblegum. And she&#8217;s all out of bubblegum.</p>
<p>                    Callie has had a rough few days. Five minutes after discovering she had a Godfather, she learned that the future of the world depended on the two of them taking an immediate road trip.</p>
<p>                    To Castle Dracula-a place even the supernatural community believed to be an urban myth, dead and abandoned long ago when Dracula had perished at the hands of Van Helsing, Mina, and Jonathan Harker.</p>
<p>                    Except&#8230;Dracula and his castle were alive and well. Worse, he had been secretly running the Sanguine Council-the governmental body of every vampire in the world-ever since his alleged death, with none the wiser. Not even the vampires.</p>
<p>                    And Callie&#8217;s first Godfather-daughter dance was to go assassinate the Sultan of Suck once and for all.</p>
<p>                    But she soon learns that Dracula is the absolute least of her concerns. And that some bonds should never be forged. Because once made, they can never be broken&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Callie Penrose is about to show the world fear in a palmful of blood.</p>
<p>                    If you like Jim Butcher, Kevin Hearne, Steve McHugh, Michael Anderle, Ilona Andrews, Patricia Briggs, Shannon Mayer, or K.F. Breene, you won&#8217;t be able to put down the highly addictive Feathers and Fire Series, or anything else in the Temple Verse.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Shayne Silvers, Jim Butcher, and Kevin Hearne are easily my favorite Urban Fantasy Authors. In that order.&#8221; &#8211; Michael Anderle, Amazon Top 25 Bestselling Author</p>
<p>                    More than 1m copies downloaded and thousands of five-star reviews. Available in digital, print, and audiobook formats.</p>
<p>                    What Amazon readers are saying: </p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His foul-mouthed unicorn murders rainbows!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Move over Dresden!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;The Temple Verse HAS to be picked up by Netflix soon.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Silvers could write a grocery list on a dirty napkin and make it an international bestseller.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I went from crying my eyes out to laughing uncontrollably, repeatedly.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;It&#8217;s like the characters walked off the page, joined me at the bar, and bought me a drink.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I am astounded as to how the author keeps the story fresh and exciting.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I usually see plot twists a mile away. Shayne has proven me wrong. Every time.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Best books I&#8217;ve read in thirty years.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His intense actions scenes let you see the fangs and claws, hear the gunshots, feel the magic, and smell the fear.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Everything you thought you knew about vampires, shifters, dragons, wizards, fairies and gods is flat wrong.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Publishers who didn&#8217;t snap up this series are missing out on a gold mine.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Silvers has pleasured over one million readers with the Temple Universe. Now it&#8217;s your turn for a little pleasuring&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/godless-feathers-and-fire-book-7-shayne-silvers/">Godless : Feathers and Fire Book 7 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dolores Claiborne &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/dolores-claiborne-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dolores-claiborne-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>King&#8217;s Number One bestselling suspense novel, &#8216;a compelling masterpiece&#8217; (Sunday Telegraph) about a housekeeper with a long-hidden secret from her past, now with a stunning new cover look. The sheets . . . had to be hung perfectly. She&#8217;d go to that window, year in and year out and yell at me: &#8216;Six pins, now, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dolores-claiborne-stephen-king/">Dolores Claiborne &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>King&#8217;s Number One bestselling suspense novel, &#8216;a compelling masterpiece&#8217; (Sunday Telegraph) about a housekeeper with a long-hidden secret from her past, now with a stunning new cover look.    </p>
<p>                    The sheets . . . had to be hung perfectly.  She&#8217;d go to that window, year in and year out and yell at me: &#8216;Six pins, now, Dolores!  You mind me, now . . . I&#8217;m counting, and my eyes are just as good now as they ever were!    </p>
<p>                    When Vera Donovan is found dead at the bottom of the stairs, the police want to question her housekeeper Dolores Claiborne.      </p>
<p>                    And Dolores does have a confession to make.  But it&#8217;s not what the police are expecting to hear as they listen to her life story &#8211; a story which hearkens back to her abusive marriage and the suspicious death of her husband in the small Maine community of Little Tall Island.    </p>
<p>                    Dolores Claiborne has a story to tell.  And you&#8217;d better pay attention or else.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dolores-claiborne-stephen-king/">Dolores Claiborne &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Holy Smoke : The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files (Book 8 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</title>
		<link>/holy-smoke-the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-book-8-of-10-craig-halloran/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/holy-smoke-the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-book-8-of-10-craig-halloran/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Friend or Foe? A mysterious vampire might be the key to defeat the enemy. Smoke and Sid have a tough choice to make. Do they aid the vampire shifter, Vormus, or hand him over to the fiends that spawned him? Either way, they are risking their necks. Their efforts take them down into an even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-smoke-the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-book-8-of-10-craig-halloran/">Holy Smoke : The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files (Book 8 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Friend or Foe? A mysterious vampire might be the key to defeat the enemy.</p>
<p>                    Smoke and Sid have a tough choice to make. Do they aid the vampire shifter, Vormus, or hand him over to the fiends that spawned him? Either way, they are risking their necks.</p>
<p>                    Their efforts take them down into an even deeper well of lies that The Drake weaves so well. The closer Smoke and Sid get to the truth, the more their relationship is tested. </p>
<p>                    Meanwhile, Megan and Allison resurface unexpectedly and Reginald the doppelganger is back up to his old games. To complicate matters further, Kane remains preoccupied with Sid and, as he sees things, their time together is far from over. </p>
<p>                    Who will stop them? Will their relationship survive?</p>
<p>                    If you like Jim Butcher&#8217;s The Dresden Files, Monster Hunter International and shows such as the X Files and Supernatural, suspenseful action and humor, then this dynamic pair is just for you! </p>
<p>                    Scroll Up And Grab Your Copy Today!</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;Think Mulder and Scully but with more personality and better action.&#8221; -Annie S.</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;I felt so sorry for poor Smoke after each of the supernatural encounters are over with-you will see what I mean by how the FBI treats people who help them.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211; Sheila LS</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;a lot of humor and suspense &#8211; and over it all is the threat of something more sinister than the monsters.&#8221; &#8211; Birgit Hoener</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/holy-smoke-the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-book-8-of-10-craig-halloran/">Holy Smoke : The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files (Book 8 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From a Buick 8 &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/from-a-buick-8-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/from-a-buick-8-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestseller from Stephen King&#8211;a novel about the fascination deadly things have for us and about our insistence on answers when there are none&#8230; Since 1979, the state police of Troop D in rural Pennsylvania have kept a secret in the shed out behind the barracks. Ennis Rafferty and Curtis Wilcox [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-a-buick-8-stephen-king/">From a Buick 8 &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestseller from Stephen King&#8211;a novel about the fascination deadly things have for us and about our insistence on answers when there are none&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    Since 1979, the state police of Troop D in rural Pennsylvania have kept a secret in the shed out behind the barracks. Ennis Rafferty and Curtis Wilcox had answered a strange call just down the road and came back with an abandoned 1953 Buick Roadmaster. Curt Wilcox knew old cars, and this one was&#8230;just wrong. As it turned out, the Buick 8 was worse than dangerous&#8211;and the members of Troop D decided that it would be better if the public never found out about it. Now, more than twenty years later, Curt&#8217;s son Ned starts hanging around the barracks and is allowed into the Troop D family. And one day he discovers the family secret&#8211;a mystery that begins to stir once more, not only in the minds and hearts of these veteran troopers, but out in the shed as well, for there&#8217;s more power under the hood than anyone can handle&#8230;.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-a-buick-8-stephen-king/">From a Buick 8 &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Regulators &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-regulators-stephen-king-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-regulators-stephen-king-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wentworth, Ohio: a small friendly town where the Carver children bicker over sweets in the E-Z shop and writer Johnny Marinville is the only resident who minds his own business. On Poplar Street, apart from the impending storm, it&#8217;s just a normal summer&#8217;s day &#8211; with Frisbees flying, lawn mowers humming and barbeques grilling. As [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-regulators-stephen-king-2/">The Regulators &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wentworth, Ohio: a small friendly town where the Carver children bicker over sweets in the E-Z shop and writer Johnny Marinville is the only resident who minds his own business.    </p>
<p>                     On Poplar Street, apart from the impending storm, it&#8217;s just a normal summer&#8217;s day &#8211; with Frisbees flying, lawn mowers humming and barbeques grilling. As the paperboy makes his round, he is unaware of the chrome red van idling up the hill . . .    </p>
<p>                    Soon the residents will be caught up in a game of wills as the regulators arrive in force to face a child whose powers of expression are just awakening.    </p>
<p>                    If you like THE REGULATORS, don&#8217;t miss DESPERATION, written as an unidentical pair.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-regulators-stephen-king-2/">The Regulators &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Firestarter &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/firestarter-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/firestarter-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>King&#8217;s classic thriller about a young girl with a terrifying gift. You&#8217;re a firestarter honey . . . just one big zippo lighter. A year ago, he was an upstanding instructor of English at Harrison State College. Now Andy is on the run with his daughter. A pigtailed girl named Charlie. A girl with an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/firestarter-stephen-king/">Firestarter &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>King&#8217;s classic thriller about a young girl with a terrifying gift.    </p>
<p>                    You&#8217;re a firestarter honey . . . just one big zippo lighter.    </p>
<p>                    A year ago, he was an upstanding instructor of English at Harrison State College.  Now Andy is on the run with his daughter.  A pigtailed girl named Charlie.  A girl with an unimaginably terrifying gift.    </p>
<p>                    A gift which could be useful to corrupt authorities.  Soon Charlie will be caught up in the menace of a fateful drug experiment and a sinister government ploy . . .     </p>
<p>                    Let the reader beware: FIRESTARTER is Stephen King at his most mesmerising . . . and menacing.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/firestarter-stephen-king/">Firestarter &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Smoke Signals (Book 7 out of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</title>
		<link>/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-signals-book-7-out-of-10-craig-halloran/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-signals-book-7-out-of-10-craig-halloran/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unexpected proposal turns to blood in the water for the Black Slate. Having fought for their very lives to escape the clutches of Kane Lancaster, Smoke and Sid find themselves face to face with one of the most important decisions of their lives &#8211; Marriage! While Sid mulls over Smoke&#8217;s proposition, Smoke sets out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-signals-book-7-out-of-10-craig-halloran/">The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Smoke Signals (Book 7 out of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unexpected proposal turns to blood in the water for the Black Slate.</p>
<p>                    Having fought for their very lives to escape the clutches of Kane Lancaster, Smoke and Sid find themselves face to face with one of the most important decisions of their lives &#8211; Marriage! </p>
<p>                    While Sid mulls over Smoke&#8217;s proposition, Smoke sets out for a lengthy visit with Sid&#8217;s parents, Sally &#038; Keith. However, when he departs he finds himself at the center of a man hunt. He is chased down by a group of strange, goggle-wearing thugs that he has never encountered before.</p>
<p>                    Fighting for his life, Smoke&#8217;s special skills and talents are pushed to the limit as he fights for his life and the hope that Sid will become his wife. Will they make it across the church threshold or will dark forces intervene and crush their nuptials forever?</p>
<p>                    If you like Jim Butcher&#8217;s The Dresden Files, Monster Hunter International and shows such as the X Files and Supernatural, suspenseful action and humor, then this dynamic pair is just for you! </p>
<p>                    Scroll Up And Grab Your Copy Today!</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;Think Mulder and Scully but with more personality and better action.&#8221; -Annie S.</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;I felt so sorry for poor Smoke after each of the supernatural encounters are over with-you will see what I mean by how the FBI treats people who help them.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211; Sheila LS</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;a lot of humor and suspense &#8211; and over it all is the threat of something more sinister than the monsters.&#8221; &#8211; Birgit Hoener</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-signals-book-7-out-of-10-craig-halloran/">The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Smoke Signals (Book 7 out of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Night Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/night-game-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/night-game-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this &#8220;suspenseful&#8230;captivating&#8221; (Publishers Weekly) novel in GhostWalker series, #1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan tracks the desperate steps of a wanted woman-betrayed, avenging, and dangerously irresistible&#8230; Gator Fontenot of the Special Forces paranormal squad can&#8217;t refuse an urgent request to save the elusive Iris &#8220;Flame&#8221; Johnson, a victim of the same horrific [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/night-game-christine-feehan/">Night Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this &#8220;suspenseful&#8230;captivating&#8221; (Publishers Weekly) novel in GhostWalker series, #1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan tracks the desperate steps of a wanted woman-betrayed, avenging, and dangerously irresistible&#8230;    </p>
<p>                     Gator Fontenot of the Special Forces paranormal squad can&#8217;t refuse an urgent request to save the elusive Iris &#8220;Flame&#8221; Johnson, a victim of the same horrific experiments that warped Gator. Now unleashed, she&#8217;s a red-haired weapon of unimaginable destructive powers, a walking time bomb bent on revenge in the sultry bayous of New Orleans, and hunted by a shadowy assassin. It&#8217;s Gator&#8217;s job to reel Flame in. But can two people haunted by violent betrayals trust the passion that soon ignites between them? Or is one of them just playing another seductive and deadly night game?    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/night-game-christine-feehan/">Night Game &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ur &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/ur-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ur-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FIRST TIME ON AUDIO&#8230; An Unabridged Novella Unavailable In Any Collection! Tapping into our primal fears of modern technology that made Cell a #1 bestseller, Stephen King sets his sights on the latest high-tech gadget in UR, in which a mysterious e-book reader opens a disturbing window into other worlds. Reeling from a painful break-up, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ur-stephen-king/">Ur &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FIRST TIME ON AUDIO&#8230;<br />
                    An Unabridged Novella Unavailable In Any Collection! </p>
<p>                    Tapping into our primal fears of modern technology that made Cell a #1 bestseller, Stephen King sets his sights on the latest high-tech gadget in UR,  in which a mysterious e-book reader opens a disturbing window into other worlds. </p>
<p>                    Reeling from a painful break-up, English instructor and avid book lover Wesley Smith is haunted by his ex-girlfriend&#8217;s parting shot: Why can&#8217;t you just read off the computer like everyone else? He buys an e-book reader out of spite, but soon finds he can use the device to glimpse realities he had never before imagined, discovering literary riches beyond his wildest dreams&#8230;and all-too-human tragedies that surpass his most terrible nightmares. </p>
<p>                    From vintage cars (Christine and From a Buick 8) to household appliances (Maximum Overdrive) to exercise equipment (Stationary Bike), Stephen King has mesmerized us with tales of apparently ordinary machines that take on lives of their own. UR gives this classic theme an up-to-the-minute spin, resulting in a horror masterpiece for our time and for the ages.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ur-stephen-king/">Ur &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Acres : The Complete Collection &#8211; Ambrose Ibsen</title>
		<link>/black-acres-the-complete-collection-ambrose-ibsen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-acres-the-complete-collection-ambrose-ibsen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s No Place Like Home&#8230;Kim and Julian Taylor are in the market for their first home, and a visit to the secluded Beacon estate finds them enamored. It&#8217;s a peculiar home, rather large and in need of some renovations. The price is right however, and after a tour, they snap the house up without hesitation.The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-acres-the-complete-collection-ambrose-ibsen/">Black Acres : The Complete Collection &#8211; Ambrose Ibsen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s No Place Like Home&#8230;Kim and Julian Taylor are in the market for their first home, and a visit to the secluded Beacon estate finds them enamored. It&#8217;s a peculiar home, rather large and in need of some renovations. The price is right however, and after a tour, they snap the house up without hesitation.The man who sells them the house has one last detail to share before they sign on the dotted line. The previous owners of the home disappeared under mysterious circumstances nearly eight years ago and have recently been declared dead in absentia. Unperturbed by this fact, Kim and Julian set about making the home their own.It quickly becomes clear that the two of them are not alone there, however.This volume contains all four installments of the serialized novel Black Acres: In Absentia, The Borderland, The Amber Light and In Darkness. It also contains a brief preface by the author.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-acres-the-complete-collection-ambrose-ibsen/">Black Acres : The Complete Collection &#8211; Ambrose Ibsen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Smoke on the Water (Book 4 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</title>
		<link>/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-on-the-water-book-4-of-10-craig-halloran/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-on-the-water-book-4-of-10-craig-halloran/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When the FBI sends Sid packing, who will continue the battle against evil? Now that Sidney is no longer an FBI agent, she is restless. Not knowing what to do with herself, she leaves Megan with the grandparents so she can have some time alone to figure things out. An unexpected Shootout erupts during a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-on-the-water-book-4-of-10-craig-halloran/">The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Smoke on the Water (Book 4 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When the FBI sends Sid packing, who will continue the battle against evil?</p>
<p>                    Now that Sidney is no longer an FBI agent, she is restless. Not knowing what to do with herself, she leaves Megan with the grandparents so she can have some time alone to figure things out. </p>
<p>                    An unexpected Shootout erupts during a visit to the shooting range things get interesting when an old guy called Big Jake out-shoots Sid and then saves her from two huge goons who smell like the Drake. </p>
<p>                    Matters take a turn for the worst soon after when Big Jake turns up dead. Missing Smoke and hoping to find out where he is, but saying she wants help finding Big Jake&#8217;s killers, Sid sends a text to Phat Sam and Guppy.</p>
<p>                    If you like Jim Butcher&#8217;s The Dresden Files, Monster Hunter International and shows such as the X Files and Supernatural, suspenseful action and humor, then this dynamic pair is just for you! </p>
<p>                    Scroll Up And Grab Your Copy Today!</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;Think Mulder and Scully but with more personality and better action.&#8221; -Annie S.</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;I felt so sorry for poor Smoke after each of the supernatural encounters are over with-you will see what I mean by how the FBI treats people who help them.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211; Sheila LS</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;a lot of humor and suspense &#8211; and over it all is the threat of something more sinister than the monsters.&#8221; &#8211; Birgit Hoener</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-on-the-water-book-4-of-10-craig-halloran/">The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Smoke on the Water (Book 4 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alien &#8211; Sea of Sorrows (Book 2) &#8211; James A. Moore</title>
		<link>/alien-sea-of-sorrows-book-2-james-a-moore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alien-sea-of-sorrows-book-2-james-a-moore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As a deputy commissioner for the ICC, Alan Decker&#8217;s job is to make sure the settlements on LV178 follow all the rules, keeping the colonists safe. But the planet known as New Galveston holds secrets, lurking deep beneath the toxic sands dubbed the Sea of Sorrows. The Weyland-Yutani Corporation has secrets of its own, as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alien-sea-of-sorrows-book-2-james-a-moore/">Alien &#8211; Sea of Sorrows (Book 2) &#8211; James A. Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As a deputy commissioner for the ICC, Alan Decker&#8217;s job is to make sure the settlements on LV178 follow all the rules, keeping the colonists safe. But the planet known as New Galveston holds secrets, lurking deep beneath the toxic sands dubbed the Sea of Sorrows.  The Weyland-Yutani Corporation has secrets of its own, as Decker discovers when he is forced to join a team of mercenaries sent to investigate an ancient excavation. Somewhere in that long-forgotten dig lies the thing the company wants most in the universe &#8211; a living Xenomorph.  Decker doesn&#8217;t understand why they need him, until his own past comes back to haunt him. Centuries ago, his ancestor fought the Aliens, launching a bloody vendetta that was never satisfied. That was when the creatures swore revenge on the Destroyer &#8211; Ellen Ripley.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alien-sea-of-sorrows-book-2-james-a-moore/">Alien &#8211; Sea of Sorrows (Book 2) &#8211; James A. Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Up in Smoke (Book 6 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</title>
		<link>/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-up-in-smoke-book-6-of-10-craig-halloran/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-up-in-smoke-book-6-of-10-craig-halloran/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unexpected visitor turns everyone&#8217;s life inside out. Bounty Hunter John Smoke has been at a loss ever since Sidney Shaw&#8217;s abrupt departure. After weeks of finding no trace of her Smoke has an unanticipated encounter with Reginald, the Doppelganger. Searching for Sidney, Smoke discovers that if he wants to see Sid again, he needs [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-up-in-smoke-book-6-of-10-craig-halloran/">The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Up in Smoke (Book 6 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unexpected visitor turns everyone&#8217;s life inside out. </p>
<p>                    Bounty Hunter John Smoke has been at a loss ever since Sidney Shaw&#8217;s abrupt departure. After weeks of finding no trace of her Smoke has an unanticipated encounter with Reginald, the Doppelganger. </p>
<p>                    Searching for Sidney, Smoke discovers that if he wants to see Sid again, he needs to perform a mission, hunt down and take out a rival criminal underworld called The Many. He finds out that he has been played, but he has no choice but to go along with it if he wants to see Sidney again. Smoke sets out into another one of The Drake&#8217;s twisted labyrinth&#8217;s. </p>
<p>                    Will Smoke survive? Can he find Sid? Perhaps Sid doesn&#8217;t want to be found, but Smoke will stop at nothing to find her.</p>
<p>                    If you like Jim Butcher&#8217;s The Dresden Files, Monster Hunter International and shows such as the X Files and Supernatural, suspenseful action and humor, then this dynamic pair is just for you! </p>
<p>                    Scroll Up And Grab Your Copy Today!</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;Think Mulder and Scully but with more personality and better action.&#8221; -Annie S.</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;I felt so sorry for poor Smoke after each of the supernatural encounters are over with-you will see what I mean by how the FBI treats people who help them.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211; Sheila LS</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;a lot of humor and suspense &#8211; and over it all is the threat of something more sinister than the monsters.&#8221; &#8211; Birgit Hoener</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-up-in-smoke-book-6-of-10-craig-halloran/">The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Up in Smoke (Book 6 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Smoke and Mirrors (Book 5 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</title>
		<link>/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-and-mirrors-book-5-of-10-craig-halloran/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-and-mirrors-book-5-of-10-craig-halloran/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Smoke is back on the loose and someone is going to pay. With John Smoke now free from prison, Sidney Shaw&#8217;s life doesn&#8217;t get any easier. No longer an FBI agent and with the bills stacking up, she takes up the Bounty Hunter business. Together, her and Smoke, go after another villainous fiend on the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-and-mirrors-book-5-of-10-craig-halloran/">The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Smoke and Mirrors (Book 5 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Smoke is back on the loose and someone is going to pay. </p>
<p>                    With John Smoke now free from prison, Sidney Shaw&#8217;s life doesn&#8217;t get any easier. No longer an FBI agent and with the bills stacking up, she takes up the Bounty Hunter business. Together, her and Smoke, go after another villainous fiend on the Black Slate. </p>
<p>                    Success quickly turns to failure as Congressman Wilhelm is shot and video evidence reveals John Smoke as the shooter. The manhunt for Smoke begins and Sid&#8217;s life is turned upside down trying to exonerate the man she thinks she loves. </p>
<p>                    Keeping the faith in her man, Sid fights to save Smoke before the Drake gets to him first.</p>
<p>                    If you like Jim Butcher&#8217;s The Dresden Files, Monster Hunter International and shows such as the X Files and Supernatural, suspenseful action and humor, then this dynamic pair is just for you! </p>
<p>                    Scroll Up And Grab Your Copy Today!</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;Think Mulder and Scully but with more personality and better action.&#8221; -Annie S.</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;I felt so sorry for poor Smoke after each of the supernatural encounters are over with-you will see what I mean by how the FBI treats people who help them.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211; Sheila LS</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8220;a lot of humor and suspense &#8211; and over it all is the threat of something more sinister than the monsters.&#8221; &#8211; Birgit Hoener</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-supernatural-bounty-hunter-files-smoke-and-mirrors-book-5-of-10-craig-halloran/">The Supernatural Bounty Hunter Files : Smoke and Mirrors (Book 5 of 10) &#8211; Craig Halloran</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Winter Haunting &#8211; Dan Simmons</title>
		<link>/a-winter-haunting-dan-simmons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-winter-haunting-dan-simmons/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A once-respected college professor and novelist, Dale Stewart has sabotaged his career and his marriage &#8212; and now darkness is closing in on him. In the last hours of Halloween he has returned to the dying town of Elm Haven, his boyhood home, where he hopes to find peace in isolation. But moving into a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-winter-haunting-dan-simmons/">A Winter Haunting &#8211; Dan Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A once-respected college professor and novelist, Dale Stewart has sabotaged his career and his marriage &#8212; and now darkness is closing in on him. In the last hours of Halloween he has returned to the dying town of Elm Haven, his boyhood home, where he hopes to find peace in isolation. But moving into a long-deserted farmhouse on the far outskirts of town &#8212; the one-time residence of a strange and brilliant friend who lost his young life in a grisly accident back in the terrible summer of 1960 &#8212; is only the latest in his long succession of recent mistakes. Because Dale is not alone here. He has been followed to this house of shadows by private demons who are now twisting his reality into horrifying new forms. And a thick, blanketing early snow is starting to fall &#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-winter-haunting-dan-simmons/">A Winter Haunting &#8211; Dan Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pet Sematary : King&#8217;s #1 bestseller &#8211; soon to be a major motion picture &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/pet-sematary-kings-1-bestseller-soon-to-be-a-major-motion-picture-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pet-sematary-kings-1-bestseller-soon-to-be-a-major-motion-picture-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major motion picture from Paramount Pictures starring John Lithgow, Jason Clarke, and Amy Seimetz! King&#8217;s iconic, beloved classic is &#8216;so beautifully paced that you cannot help but be pulled in&#8217; Guardian &#8216;SOMETIMES&#8230;DEAD IS BETTER&#8217; The house looked right, felt right to Dr Louis Creed. Rambling, old, unsmart and comfortable. A place [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pet-sematary-kings-1-bestseller-soon-to-be-a-major-motion-picture-stephen-king/">Pet Sematary : King&#8217;s #1 bestseller &#8211; soon to be a major motion picture &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major motion picture from Paramount Pictures starring John Lithgow, Jason Clarke, and Amy Seimetz!  King&#8217;s iconic, beloved classic is &#8216;so beautifully paced that you cannot help but be pulled in&#8217; Guardian </p>
<p>                    &#8216;SOMETIMES&#8230;DEAD IS BETTER&#8217;</p>
<p>                    The house looked right, felt right to Dr Louis Creed.</p>
<p>                    Rambling, old, unsmart and comfortable. A place where the family could settle; the children grow and play and explore. The rolling hills and meadows of Maine seemed a world away from the fume-choked dangers of Chicago.</p>
<p>                    Only the occasional big truck out on the two-lane highway, grinding up through the gears, hammering down the long gradients, growled out an intrusive threat.</p>
<p>                    But behind the house and far away from the road: that was safe. Just a carefully cleared path up into the woods where generations of local children have processed with the solemn innocence of the young, taking with them their dear departed pets for burial.</p>
<p>                    A sad place maybe, but safe. Surely a safe place. Not a place to seep into your dreams, to wake you, sweating with fear and foreboding.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;King can make the flesh creep half a world away&#8217; &#8211; The Times<br />
                    &#8216;So beautifully paced that you cannot help but be pulled in&#8217; &#8211; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;The most frightening novel Stephen King has ever written&#8217; &#8211; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly<br />
                    &#8216;Wild, powerful, disturbing&#8217; &#8211; Washington Post Book Review</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pet-sematary-kings-1-bestseller-soon-to-be-a-major-motion-picture-stephen-king/">Pet Sematary : King&#8217;s #1 bestseller &#8211; soon to be a major motion picture &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8216;Salem&#8217;s Lot &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/salems-lot-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/salems-lot-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ben Mears has returned to Jerusalem&#8217;s Lot in the hopes that living in an old mansion, long the subject of town lore, will help him cast out his own devils and provide inspiration for his new book. But when two young boys venture into the woods and only one comes out alive, Mears begins to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salems-lot-stephen-king/">&#8216;Salem&#8217;s Lot &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ben Mears has returned to Jerusalem&#8217;s Lot in the hopes that living in an old mansion, long the subject of town lore, will help him cast out his own devils and provide inspiration for his new book. But when two young boys venture into the woods and only one comes out alive, Mears begins to realize that there may be something sinister at work and that his hometown is under siege by forces of darkness far beyond his control.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salems-lot-stephen-king/">&#8216;Salem&#8217;s Lot &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bazaar of Bad Dreams &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-bazaar-of-bad-dreams-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bazaar-of-bad-dreams-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The short story OBITS won the 2016 Edgar for best short story. The No.1 bestselling author delivers an &#8216;outstanding&#8217; (USA Today) collection of thrilling stories, introducing each one with a fascinating piece on when, where or how he came to write it. There is a treasure here for every reader: a man who keeps reliving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bazaar-of-bad-dreams-stephen-king/">The Bazaar of Bad Dreams &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The short story OBITS won the 2016 Edgar for best short story.</p>
<p>                    The No.1 bestselling author delivers an &#8216;outstanding&#8217; (USA Today) collection of thrilling stories, introducing each one with a fascinating piece on when, where or how he came to write it.</p>
<p>                    There is a treasure here for every reader: a man who keeps reliving exactly the same life, repeating his mistakes over and over again; a columnist who kills people by writing their obituaries; a poignant tale about the end of the human race and a firework competition between neighbours which reaches an explosive climax. And, exclusive to this paperback edition (and the eBook from 6 September), a brand new story &#8216;Cookie Jar&#8217;.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I made them especially for you,&#8217; says King. &#8216;Feel free to examine them, but please be careful. The best of them have teeth.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    TABLE OF CONTENTS FOR THE BAZAAR OF BAD DREAMS</p>
<p>                    Introduction<br />
                    Mile 81<br />
                    Premium Harmony<br />
                    Batman and Robin Have an Altercation<br />
                    The Dune<br />
                    Bad Little Kid<br />
                    A Death<br />
                    The Bone Church<br />
                    Morality<br />
                    Afterlife<br />
                    Ur<br />
                    Herman Wouk Is Still Alive<br />
                    Under the Weather<br />
                    Blockade Billy<br />
                    Mister Yummy<br />
                    Tommy<br />
                    The Little Green God of Agony<br />
                    Cookie Jar<br />
                    That Bus Is Another World<br />
                    Obits<br />
                    Drunken Fireworks<br />
                    Summer Thunder</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bazaar-of-bad-dreams-stephen-king/">The Bazaar of Bad Dreams &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thinner &#8211; Richard Bachman</title>
		<link>/thinner-richard-bachman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thinner-richard-bachman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Thinner&#8217; &#8211; the old gypsy man barely whispers the word. Billy feels the touch of a withered hand on his cheek. Billy Halleck, prosperous if overweight citizen, happily married, shuddered then turned angrily away. The old woman&#8217;s death had been none of his fault. The courts had cleared him. She&#8217;d just stumbled in front of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinner-richard-bachman/">Thinner &#8211; Richard Bachman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Thinner&#8217; &#8211; the old gypsy man barely whispers the word. Billy feels the touch of a withered hand on his cheek.    </p>
<p>                    Billy Halleck, prosperous if overweight citizen, happily married, shuddered then turned angrily away. The old woman&#8217;s death had been none of his fault. The courts had cleared him. She&#8217;d just stumbled in front of his car. Now he simply wanted to forget the whole messy business.    </p>
<p>                    Later, when the scales told him he was losing weight, it was what the doctor ordered. His wife was pleased &#8211; as she should have been. But . . .    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thinner&#8217; &#8211; the word, the old man&#8217;s curse, has lodged in Billy&#8217;s mind like a fattening worm, eating at his flesh, at his reason. And with his despair, comes violence.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinner-richard-bachman/">Thinner &#8211; Richard Bachman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Green Mile &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-green-mile-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-green-mile-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s international bestselling and highly acclaimed novel, also a hugely successful film starring Tom Hanks The Green Mile: those who walk it do not return, because at the end of that walk is the room in which sits Cold Mountain penitentiary&#8217;s electric chair. In 1932 the newest resident on death row is John Coffey, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-green-mile-stephen-king/">The Green Mile &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s international bestselling and highly acclaimed novel, also a hugely successful film starring Tom Hanks    </p>
<p>                    The Green Mile: those who walk it do not return, because at the end of that walk is the room in which sits Cold Mountain penitentiary&#8217;s electric chair.  In 1932 the newest resident on death row is John Coffey, a giant black man convicted of the brutal murder of two little girls. But nothing is as it seems with John Coffey, and around him unfolds a bizarre and horrifying story.      </p>
<p>                    Evil murderer or holy innocent &#8211; whichever he is &#8211; Coffey has strange powers which may yet offer salvation to others, even if they can do nothing to save him.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-green-mile-stephen-king/">The Green Mile &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stephen King, American Master : A Creepy Corpus of Facts About Stephen King &#038; His Work &#8211; Stephen Spignesi</title>
		<link>/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Companions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fun and informative compendium for Stephen King fans-interviews, essays, and loads of facts and details about all of his work. Fascinating facts, trivia, and little-known details about the Master of the Macabre&#8217;s life and work, plus interviews, essays, and insights for King fans, from the casual to the fanatical! Did you know&#8230;? In his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/">Stephen King, American Master : A Creepy Corpus of Facts About Stephen King &#038; His Work &#8211; Stephen Spignesi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fun and informative compendium for Stephen King fans-interviews, essays, and loads of facts and details about all of his work.</p>
<p>                    Fascinating facts, trivia, and little-known details about the Master of the Macabre&#8217;s life and work, plus interviews, essays, and insights for King fans, from the casual to the fanatical!</p>
<p>                    Did you know&#8230;?</p>
<p>                    In his early teens, Stephen King sold typed copies of his short stories at school.<br />
                    King originally thought his novel Pet Sematary was too frightening to publish.<br />
                    King&#8217;s legendary Dark Tower series took him more than 30 years to write.<br />
                    Thinner was the novel that revealed his &#8220;Richard Bachman&#8221; pseudonym to the world.<br />
                    King wrote The Eyes of the Dragon for his daughter Naomi.<br />
                    He has never liked Stanley Kubrick&#8217;s film version of his novel The Shining.<br />
                    It took him four years to write what some consider his magnum opus, IT.<br />
                    The 2017 film version of IT has grossed more than $700 million worldwide.<br />
                    In addition to novels, King has written essays, plays, screenplays, and even poetry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/">Stephen King, American Master : A Creepy Corpus of Facts About Stephen King &#038; His Work &#8211; Stephen Spignesi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Running Man &#8211; Richard Bachman</title>
		<link>/the-running-man-richard-bachman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-running-man-richard-bachman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not just a game when you&#8217;re running for your life. Every night they tuned in to the nation&#8217;s favourite prime-time TV game show. They all watched, from the sprawling slums to the security-obsessed enclaves of the rich. They all watched the ultimate live death game as the contestants tried to bet not the clock, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-running-man-richard-bachman/">The Running Man &#8211; Richard Bachman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not just a game when you&#8217;re running for your life.    </p>
<p>                    Every night they tuned in to the nation&#8217;s favourite prime-time TV game show.    </p>
<p>                    They all watched, from the sprawling slums to the security-obsessed enclaves of the rich. They all watched the ultimate live death game as the contestants tried to bet not the clock, but annihhilation at the hands of the Hunters. Survive thirty days and win the billion dollar jackpot &#8211; that was the promise. But the odds were brutal and the game rigged. Best score so far was eight days.    </p>
<p>                    And now there was a new contestant, the latest running man, staking his life while a nation watched.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-running-man-richard-bachman/">The Running Man &#8211; Richard Bachman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mist &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-mist-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mist-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The No. 1 bestselling author Stephen King&#8217;s terrifying novella about a town engulfed in a dense, mysterious mist &#8211; originally published in the acclaimed short story collection Skeleton Crew and made into a feature film by Frank Darabont &#8211; is now available as a stand-alone publication. A man staggered into the market . . . [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mist-stephen-king/">The Mist &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The No. 1 bestselling author Stephen King&#8217;s terrifying novella about a town engulfed in a dense, mysterious mist &#8211; originally published in the acclaimed short story collection Skeleton Crew and made into a feature film by Frank Darabont &#8211; is now available as a stand-alone publication.</p>
<p>                    A man staggered into the market . . . &#8216;Something in the fog!&#8217; he screamed</p>
<p>                    Following a freak summer storm, David Drayton, his son Billy, and their neighbour Brent Norton join dozens of others and head to the local grocery store to replenish supplies.</p>
<p>                    Once there, they become trapped by a strange mist that has enveloped the town. Violent forces concealed in the mist are starting to emerge.  And there is another shocking threat from within &#8211; one group of survivors, led by a religious zealot, is calling for a sacrifice.</p>
<p>                    Now David and his son must try to escape. But what&#8217;s outside may be even more dangerous.</p>
<p>                    This exhilarating novella explores the horror in both the enemy you know &#8211; and the one you can only imagine.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mist-stephen-king/">The Mist &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alien Resurrection: The Official Movie Novelization &#8211; A. C. Crispin</title>
		<link>/alien-resurrection-the-official-movie-novelization-a-c-crispin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alien-resurrection-the-official-movie-novelization-a-c-crispin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At the farthest reaches of the solar system, Ellen Ripley awakens on board the space station Auriga. Her last memory is of her own fiery death. And yet she is somehow alive. Ripley discovers that her &#8220;resurrection&#8221; is a result of an incredible experiment which has altered both her and the creature she has been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alien-resurrection-the-official-movie-novelization-a-c-crispin/">Alien Resurrection: The Official Movie Novelization &#8211; A. C. Crispin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the farthest reaches of the solar system, Ellen Ripley awakens on board the space station Auriga. Her last memory is of her own fiery death. And yet she is somehow alive. Ripley discovers that her &#8220;resurrection&#8221; is a result of an incredible experiment which has altered both her and the creature she has been carrying. To combat the incalculable alien menace, she teams up with a renegade band of space smugglers.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alien-resurrection-the-official-movie-novelization-a-c-crispin/">Alien Resurrection: The Official Movie Novelization &#8211; A. C. Crispin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shifting Sands Resort Omnibus Volume 1 &#8211; Zoe Chant</title>
		<link>/shifting-sands-resort-omnibus-volume-1-zoe-chant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shifting-sands-resort-omnibus-volume-1-zoe-chant/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Adventure, romance, and laughter: escape to Shifting Sands Resort! Set at a tropical luxury resort for shifters only, this quirky, fan-favorite series is a romance thrill ride with humor and heart. Each book weaves into a compelling mystery about the island and the secrets that it&#8217;s hiding&#8230; An undercover spy, a wounded warrior, and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shifting-sands-resort-omnibus-volume-1-zoe-chant/">Shifting Sands Resort Omnibus Volume 1 &#8211; Zoe Chant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Adventure, romance, and laughter: escape to Shifting Sands Resort!</p>
<p>                    Set at a tropical luxury resort for shifters only, this quirky, fan-favorite series is a romance thrill ride with humor and heart. Each book weaves into a compelling mystery about the island and the secrets that it&#8217;s hiding&#8230;</p>
<p>                    An undercover spy, a wounded warrior, and a bartender wearing a cowboy hat all find their fated mates in these three standalone novels of healing and finding family. Come for the hot sand and cold drinks, stay for the love and laughs.</p>
<p>                    This volume includes the novels</p>
<p>                    Tropical Tiger Spy</p>
<p>                    Tropical Wounded Wolf</p>
<p>                    Tropical Bartender Bear</p>
<p>                    and three short stories, two of which are exclusive to this collection. This omnibus edition is in the author&#8217;s preferred reading order.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shifting-sands-resort-omnibus-volume-1-zoe-chant/">Shifting Sands Resort Omnibus Volume 1 &#8211; Zoe Chant</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Stand &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-stand-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-stand-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s apocalyptic vision of a world blasted by virus and tangled in an elemental struggle between good and evil remains as riveting and eerily plausible as when it was first published. Soon to be a television series. &#8216;THE STAND is a masterpiece&#8217; (Guardian). Set in a virus-decimated US, King&#8217;s thrilling American fantasy epic, is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stand-stephen-king/">The Stand &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s apocalyptic vision of a world blasted by virus and tangled in an elemental struggle between good and evil remains as riveting and eerily plausible as when it was first published.</p>
<p>                    Soon to be a television series.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;THE STAND is a masterpiece&#8217; (Guardian). Set in a virus-decimated US, King&#8217;s thrilling American fantasy epic, is a Classic.</p>
<p>                    First come the days of the virus. Then come the dreams.</p>
<p>                    Dark dreams that warn of the coming of the dark man. The apostate of death, his worn-down boot heels tramping the night roads. The warlord of the charnel house and Prince of Evil.</p>
<p>                    His time is at hand. His empire grows in the west and the Apocalypse looms.</p>
<p>                    When a man crashes his car into a petrol station, he brings with him the foul corpses of his wife and daughter. He dies and it doesn&#8217;t take long for the virus which killed him to spread across America and the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stand-stephen-king/">The Stand &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Long Walk &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-long-walk-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-long-walk-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this #1 national bestseller, &#8220;master storyteller&#8221; (Houston Chronicle) Stephen King, writing as Richard Bachman, tells the tale of the contestants of a grueling walking competition where there can only be one winner&#8211;the one that survives. &#8220;I give my congratulations to the winner among your number, and my acknowledgements of valor to the losers.&#8221; Against [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-long-walk-stephen-king/">The Long Walk &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this #1 national bestseller, &#8220;master storyteller&#8221; (Houston Chronicle) Stephen King, writing as Richard Bachman, tells the tale of the contestants of a grueling walking competition where there can only be one winner&#8211;the one that survives.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I give my congratulations to the winner among your number, and my acknowledgements of valor to the losers.&#8221;      </p>
<p>                    Against the wishes of his mother, sixteen-year-old Ray Garraty is about to compete in the annual grueling match of stamina and wits known as The Long Walk. One hundred boys must keep a steady pace of four miles per hour without ever stopping&#8230;with the winner being awarded &#8220;The Prize&#8221;&#8211;anything he wants for the rest of his life. But, as part of this national tournament that sweeps through a dystopian America year after year, there are some harsh rules that Garraty and ninety-nine others must adhere to in order to beat out the rest. There is no finish line&#8211;the winner is the last man standing. Contestants cannot receive any outside aid whatsoever. Slow down under the speed limit and you&#8217;re given a warning. Three warnings and you&#8217;re out of the game&#8211;permanently&#8230;.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-long-walk-stephen-king/">The Long Walk &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Obsidian Son : A Nate Temple Supernatural Thriller &#8211; Shayne Silvers</title>
		<link>/obsidian-son-a-nate-temple-supernatural-thriller-shayne-silvers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/obsidian-son-a-nate-temple-supernatural-thriller-shayne-silvers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To do list: Cow-tip the Minotaur. Cure a reptile dysfunction. My name is Nate Temple, and I&#8217;m secretly a wizard. I ride a foul-mouthed unicorn, I drink with Achilles, and I&#8217;m pals with the Four Horsemen. I&#8217;ve even cow-tipped the Minotaur. I understand the theory of following the rules&#8230;I&#8217;m just not very good at the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/obsidian-son-a-nate-temple-supernatural-thriller-shayne-silvers/">Obsidian Son : A Nate Temple Supernatural Thriller &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To do list: Cow-tip the Minotaur. Cure a reptile dysfunction.</p>
<p>                    My name is Nate Temple, and I&#8217;m secretly a wizard. I ride a foul-mouthed unicorn, I drink with Achilles, and I&#8217;m pals with the Four Horsemen. I&#8217;ve even cow-tipped the Minotaur. I understand the theory of following the rules&#8230;I&#8217;m just not very good at the application.</p>
<p>                    Because rules were meant to be broken.</p>
<p>                    Especially when I find out a monster just murdered my parents. Now all I can hear is the sweet, soothing song of vengeance in my ears, playing on repeat.</p>
<p>                    But when shifter dragons come to town, I&#8217;m forced to step away from hunting down the scumbag murderer. Because I know the cure for a reptile dysfunction, and the dragons aren&#8217;t going to like it.</p>
<p>                    This fight soon opens up Pandora&#8217;s Box, and suddenly every flavor of supernatural thug is after me. The only way out of it-to save my city-is to murder my best friend.</p>
<p>                    I didn&#8217;t want, ask for, or start any of this. But I will finish it. It&#8217;s time I show St. Louis that magic is very, very real. And that an angry wizard is truly something to see-at least once in your life.</p>
<p>                    You know, right before he puts you and everyone you&#8217;ve ever met in the grave&#8230;</p>
<p>                    If you like Jim Butcher, Kevin Hearne, Steve McHugh, Michael Anderle, Ilona Andrews, Patricia Briggs, Shannon Mayer, or K.F. Breene, you won&#8217;t be able to put down the highly addictive Nate Temple Series.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Shayne Silvers, Jim Butcher, and Kevin Hearne are easily my favorite Urban Fantasy Authors. In that order.&#8221; &#8211; Michael Anderle, Amazon Top 25 Bestselling Author</p>
<p>                    More than 1m copies downloaded and thousands of five-star reviews. Available in digital, print, and audiobook formats.</p>
<p>                    What Amazon readers are saying: </p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His foul-mouthed unicorn murders rainbows!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Move over Dresden!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;The Temple Verse HAS to be picked up by Netflix soon.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Silvers could write a grocery list on a dirty napkin and make it an international bestseller.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I went from crying my eyes out to laughing uncontrollably, repeatedly.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;It&#8217;s like the characters walked off the page, joined me at the bar, and bought me a drink.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I am astounded as to how the author keeps the story fresh and exciting.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I usually see plot twists a mile away. Shayne has proven me wrong. Every time.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Best books I&#8217;ve read in thirty years.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His intense actions scenes let you see the fangs and claws, hear the gunshots, feel the magic, and smell the fear.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Everything you thought you knew about vampires, shifters, dragons, wizards, fairies and gods is flat wrong.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Publishers who didn&#8217;t snap up this series are missing out on a gold mine.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Silvers has pleasured over one million readers with the Temple Universe. Now it&#8217;s your turn for a little pleasuring&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/obsidian-son-a-nate-temple-supernatural-thriller-shayne-silvers/">Obsidian Son : A Nate Temple Supernatural Thriller &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dark Half &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-dark-half-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dark-half-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Creating George Stark was easy. Getting rid of him won&#8217;t be . . . The sparrows are flying again. The idea &#8211; unbidden, inexplicable &#8211; haunts the edge of Thad Beaumont&#8217;s mind. Thad should be happy. For years now it is his secret persona &#8216;George Stark&#8217;, author of super-violent pulp thrillers, who has paid the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-half-stephen-king/">The Dark Half &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Creating George Stark was easy. Getting rid of him won&#8217;t be . . .    </p>
<p>                    The sparrows are flying again. The idea &#8211; unbidden, inexplicable &#8211; haunts the edge of Thad Beaumont&#8217;s mind.    </p>
<p>                    Thad should be happy. For years now it is his secret persona &#8216;George Stark&#8217;, author of super-violent pulp thrillers, who has paid the family bills. But now, Thad is writing seriously again under his own name, and his menacing pseudonym has been buried forever.    </p>
<p>                    And yet . . . the sparrows are flying again, and something is terribly wrong in Thad Beaumont&#8217;s world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-half-stephen-king/">The Dark Half &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-girl-who-loved-tom-gordon-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-girl-who-loved-tom-gordon-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vintage King&#8217;, a delightful suspense novel in which King&#8217;s &#8216;trump card is his ability to arouse empathy for the plight of his young heroine&#8217; (Independent on Sunday), now with a stunning new cover look. The world had teeth and it could bite you with them anytime it wanted. Trisha McFarland discovered this when she was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-girl-who-loved-tom-gordon-stephen-king/">The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vintage King&#8217;, a delightful suspense novel in which King&#8217;s &#8216;trump card is his ability to arouse empathy for the plight of his young heroine&#8217; (Independent on Sunday), now with a stunning new cover look.    </p>
<p>                    The world had teeth and it could bite you with them anytime it wanted. Trisha McFarland discovered this when she was nine years old. Lost in the woods.     </p>
<p>                     Trisha has only veered a little way off the trail.  But in her panic to get back to her family, she takes a turning that leads deeper into the tangled undergrowth.      </p>
<p>                     At first it&#8217;s just the bugs, midges and mosquitoes. Then comes the hunger. For comfort she tunes her Walkman into broadcasts of the Red Sox baseball games and the performances of her hero Tom Gordon.     </p>
<p>                     But as darkness begins to fall, Trisha realises that she is not alone. There&#8217;s something else in the woods &#8211; watching. Waiting . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-girl-who-loved-tom-gordon-stephen-king/">The Girl Who Loved Tom Gordon &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In the Tall Grass &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/in-the-tall-grass-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-the-tall-grass-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>`Mile 81` meets &#8220;N.&#8220; in this collaboration between Stephen King and Joe Hill.As `USA TODAY` said of Stephen King&#8217;s `Mile 81` `Park and scream. Could there be any better place to set a horror story than an abandoned rest stop?` `In the Tall Grass` begins with a sister and brother who pull off to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-the-tall-grass-stephen-king/">In the Tall Grass &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>`Mile 81` meets &#8220;N.&#8220; in this collaboration between Stephen King and Joe Hill.As `USA TODAY` said of Stephen King&#8217;s `Mile 81` `Park and scream. Could there be any better place to set a horror story than an abandoned rest stop?` `In the Tall Grass` begins with a sister and brother who pull off to the side of the road after hearing a young boy crying for help from beyond the tall grass. Within minutes they are disoriented, in deeper than seems possible, and they&#8217;ve lost one another. The boy&#8217;s cries are more and more desperate. What follows is a terrifying, entertaining, and masterfully told tale, as only Stephen King and Joe Hill can deliver.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-the-tall-grass-stephen-king/">In the Tall Grass &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sleeping Beauties &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/sleeping-beauties-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sleeping-beauties-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this spectacular father/son collaboration, Stephen King and Owen King tell the highest of high-stakes stories: what might happen if women disappeared from the world of men? All around the world, something is happening to women when they fall asleep; they become shrouded in a cocoon-like gauze. If awakened, if the gauze wrapping their bodies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleeping-beauties-stephen-king/">Sleeping Beauties &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this spectacular father/son collaboration, Stephen King and Owen King tell the highest of high-stakes stories: what might happen if women disappeared from the world of men?    </p>
<p>                    All around the world, something is happening to women when they fall asleep; they become shrouded in a cocoon-like gauze.  If awakened, if the gauze wrapping their bodies is disturbed, the women become feral and spectacularly violent&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    In the small town of Dooling, West Virginia, the virus is spreading through a women&#8217;s prison, affecting all the inmates except one. Soon, word spreads about the mysterious Evie, who seems able to sleep &#8211; and wake. Is she a medical anomaly or a demon to be slain?     </p>
<p>                    The abandoned men, left to their increasingly primal devices, are fighting each other, while Dooling&#8217;s Sheriff, Lila Norcross, is just fighting to stay awake.    </p>
<p>                    And the sleeping women are about to open their eyes to a new world altogether&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleeping-beauties-stephen-king/">Sleeping Beauties &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wind through the Keyhole : A Dark Tower Novel &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-wind-through-the-keyhole-a-dark-tower-novel-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wind-through-the-keyhole-a-dark-tower-novel-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For readers new to The Dark Tower, The Wind Through the Keyhole is a stand-alone novel, and a wonderful introduction to the series. The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba. The No. 1 Sunday Times bestseller The Wind through the Keyhole is a perfect bridge between the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wind-through-the-keyhole-a-dark-tower-novel-stephen-king/">The Wind through the Keyhole : A Dark Tower Novel &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For readers new to The Dark Tower, The Wind Through the Keyhole is a stand-alone novel, and a wonderful introduction to the series. The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba.</p>
<p>                    The No. 1 Sunday Times bestseller The Wind through the Keyhole is a perfect bridge between the fourth and fifth novels in Stephen King&#8217;s epic masterpiece. A story within a story which features both the younger and older gunslinger, it is also a wonderful introduction to The Dark Tower series.</p>
<p>                    As Roland Deschain, and his ka-tet leave the Emerald city, a ferocious storm halts their progress along the Path of the Beam. While they shelter from the starkblast, Roland tells a story about his younger days, when he was sent by his father to investigate evidence of a murderous shape-changer. </p>
<p>                    At the scene of the crime he had tried to comfort a terrified young boy called Bill Streeter by reciting a story from The Magic Tales of the Eld that his mother used to read to him at bedtime, &#8216;The Wind through the Keyhole&#8217;. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A person&#8217;s never too old for stories,&#8217; he said to Bill. &#8216;Man and boy, girl and woman, we live for them.&#8217;<br />
                    And stories like these, they live for us.</p>
<p>                    JOIN THE QUEST FOR THE DARK TOWER&#8230;</p>
<p>                    THE DARK TOWER SERIES:<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER I: THE GUNSLINGER<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER II: THE DRAWING OF THE THREE<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER III: THE WASTE LANDS<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER IV: WIZARD AND GLASS<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER V: WOLVES OF THE CALLA<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER VI: SONG OF SUSANNAH<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER VII: THE DARK TOWER<br />
                    THE WIND THROUGH THE KEYHOLE: A DARK TOWER NOVEL</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wind-through-the-keyhole-a-dark-tower-novel-stephen-king/">The Wind through the Keyhole : A Dark Tower Novel &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Storm of the Century &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-storm-of-the-century-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-storm-of-the-century-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Stephen King presents an original screenplay and major television event set in Maine&#8217;s remote Little Tall Island. They&#8217;re calling it the Storm of the Century, and it&#8217;s coming hard. The residents of Little Tall Island have seen their share of nasty Maine Nor&#8217;easters, but this one is different. Not [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storm-of-the-century-stephen-king/">The Storm of the Century &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Stephen King presents an original screenplay and major television event set in Maine&#8217;s remote Little Tall Island. </p>
<p>                    They&#8217;re calling it the Storm of the Century, and it&#8217;s coming hard. The residents of Little Tall Island have seen their share of nasty Maine Nor&#8217;easters, but this one is different. Not only is it packing hurricane-force winds and up to five feet of snow, it&#8217;s bringing something worse. Something even the islanders have never seen before. Something no one wants to see. </p>
<p>                    Just as the first flakes begin to fall, Martha Clarendon, one of Little Tall Island&#8217;s oldest residents, suffers an unspeakably violent death. While her blood dries, Andre Linoge, the man responsible sits calmly in Martha&#8217;s easy chair holding his cane topped with a silver wolf&#8217;s head&#8230;waiting. </p>
<p>                    Linoge knows the townsfolk will come to arrest him. He will let them. For he has come to the island for one reason. And when he meets Constable Mike Anderson, his beautiful wife and child, and the rest of Little Tall&#8217;s tight-knit community, this stranger will make one simple proposition to them all: </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you give me what I want, I&#8217;ll go away.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storm-of-the-century-stephen-king/">The Storm of the Century &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book of Life : A Novel &#8211; Deborah Harkness</title>
		<link>/the-book-of-life-a-novel-deborah-harkness/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-of-life-a-novel-deborah-harkness/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling series finale and sequel to A Discovery of Witches and Shadow of Night. Look for the hit series &#8220;A Discovery of Witches&#8221; streaming on Sundance Now and Shudder, and coming to television this April on AMC and BBC America. Fans of the All Souls Trilogy sent this highly anticipated [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-life-a-novel-deborah-harkness/">The Book of Life : A Novel &#8211; Deborah Harkness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling series finale and sequel to A Discovery of Witches and Shadow of Night.     </p>
<p>                     Look for the hit series &#8220;A Discovery of Witches&#8221; streaming on Sundance Now and Shudder, and coming to television this April on AMC and BBC America.    </p>
<p>                    Fans of the All Souls Trilogy sent this highly anticipated finale straight to #1 on the New York Times hardcover bestseller list. Bringing the series&#8217; magic and suspense to a deeply satisfying conclusion, The Book of Life is poised to become an even bigger phenomenon in paperback.    </p>
<p>                    Diana and Matthew time-travel back from Elizabethan London to make a dramatic return to the present-facing new crises and old enemies. At Matthew&#8217;s ancestral home, Sept-Tours, they reunite with the beloved cast of characters from A Discovery of Witches-with one significant exception. But the real threat to their future has yet to be revealed, and when it is, the search for Ashmole 782 and its missing pages takes on even more urgency.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-life-a-novel-deborah-harkness/">The Book of Life : A Novel &#8211; Deborah Harkness</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Storm Cursed &#8211; Patricia Briggs</title>
		<link>/storm-cursed-patricia-briggs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monsters & Legendary Beings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/storm-cursed-patricia-briggs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful entry in the #1 New York Times bestselling series, Mercy Thompson must face a deadly enemy to defend all she loves&#8230; My name is Mercedes Athena Thompson Hauptman, and I am a car mechanic. And a coyote shapeshifter. And the mate of the Alpha of the Columbia Basin werewolf pack. Even so, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/storm-cursed-patricia-briggs/">Storm Cursed &#8211; Patricia Briggs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this powerful entry in the #1 New York Times bestselling series, Mercy Thompson must face a deadly enemy to defend all she loves&#8230; </p>
<p>                     My name is Mercedes Athena Thompson Hauptman, and I am a car mechanic.<br />
                    And a coyote shapeshifter.<br />
                    And the mate of the Alpha of the Columbia Basin werewolf pack. </p>
<p>                     Even so, none of that would have gotten me into trouble if, a few months ago, I hadn&#8217;t stood upon a bridge and taken responsibility for the safety of the citizens who lived in our territory. It seemed like the thing to do at the time. It should have only involved hunting down killer goblins, zombie goats, and an occasional troll. Instead, our home was viewed as neutral ground, a place where humans would feel safe to come and treat with the fae. </p>
<p>                     The reality is that nothing and no one is safe. As generals and politicians face off with the Gray Lords of the fae, a storm is coming and her name is Death. </p>
<p>                     But we are pack, and we have given our word. </p>
<p>                     We will die to keep it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/storm-cursed-patricia-briggs/">Storm Cursed &#8211; Patricia Briggs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dark Tower V: Wolves of the Calla : (Volume 5) &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-dark-tower-v-wolves-of-the-calla-volume-5-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dark-tower-v-wolves-of-the-calla-volume-5-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WOLVES OF THE CALLA is the fifth volume in Stephen King&#8217;s epic Dark Tower series. The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba. In the fifth novel in StephenKing&#8217;s bestselling fantasy series, Roland and his ka-tet are bearing through the forests of the Mid-World on their journey to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-tower-v-wolves-of-the-calla-volume-5-stephen-king/">The Dark Tower V: Wolves of the Calla : (Volume 5) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WOLVES OF THE CALLA is the fifth volume in Stephen King&#8217;s epic Dark Tower series.  The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba.</p>
<p>                    In the fifth novel in StephenKing&#8217;s bestselling fantasy series, Roland and his ka-tet are bearing through the forests of the Mid-World on their journey to the Dark Tower. </p>
<p>                    Tracking their every move is a group of farmers from the town of Calla Bryn Sturgis. The trackers have been warned that the Wolves, a band of masked riders, are about to gallop out of the dark land of Thunderclap and raid their town. And they want to enlist the help of the four gunslingers.</p>
<p>                    How can Roland and his tet both protect the innocent community and return to New York to save our world&#8217;s incarnation of the Dark Tower from the machinations of the evil Sombra Corporation?</p>
<p>                    JOIN THE QUEST FOR THE DARK TOWER&#8230;</p>
<p>                    THE DARK TOWER SERIES:<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER I: THE GUNSLINGER<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER II: THE DRAWING OF THE THREE<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER III: THE WASTE LANDS<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER IV: WIZARD AND GLASS<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER V: WOLVES OF THE CALLA<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER VI: SONG OF SUSANNAH<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER VII: THE DARK TOWER<br />
                    THE WIND THROUGH THE KEYHOLE: A DARK TOWER NOVEL</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-tower-v-wolves-of-the-calla-volume-5-stephen-king/">The Dark Tower V: Wolves of the Calla : (Volume 5) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>War God: Nights of the Witch : War God Trilogy Book One &#8211; Graham Hancock</title>
		<link>/war-god-nights-of-the-witch-war-god-trilogy-book-one-graham-hancock/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/war-god-nights-of-the-witch-war-god-trilogy-book-one-graham-hancock/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A young girl called Tozi stands at the bottom of a pyramid, waiting to be led to the top where her heart will be cut out&#8230; Pepillo, a Spanish orphan who serves a sadistic Dominican friar, is aboard the Spanish fleet as it sails towards Mexico&#8230; This is the epic story of the clash of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/war-god-nights-of-the-witch-war-god-trilogy-book-one-graham-hancock/">War God: Nights of the Witch : War God Trilogy Book One &#8211; Graham Hancock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A young girl called Tozi stands at the bottom of a pyramid, waiting to be led to the top where her heart will be cut out&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Pepillo, a Spanish orphan who serves a sadistic Dominican friar, is aboard the Spanish fleet as it sails towards Mexico&#8230;</p>
<p>                    This is the epic story of the clash of two empires, two armies and two gods of war. Five hundred desperate adventurers are about to pit themselves against the most brutal armies of the ancient Americas, armies hundreds of thousands strong. </p>
<p>                    This is a war of gods and men. Dark powers that work behind the scenes of history show their hand as the prophecy of the return of Quetzalcoatl is fulfilled with the arrival of Cortes. The Aztec ruler Moctezuma fights to maintain the demands of the war god Huitzilopochtli for human sacrifice. The Spanish Inquisition is planning an even greater blood-letting. </p>
<p>                    Caught up in the headlong collision between two gods of war are Tozi, Pepillo and the beautiful Malinal whose hatred of Moctezuma runs so deep she will sell out her own land and people to destroy him.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/war-god-nights-of-the-witch-war-god-trilogy-book-one-graham-hancock/">War God: Nights of the Witch : War God Trilogy Book One &#8211; Graham Hancock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Murder at Sunrise Lake &#8211; Christine Feehan</title>
		<link>/murder-at-sunrise-lake-christine-feehan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/murder-at-sunrise-lake-christine-feehan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan reaches new heights of passion and suspense in this thrilling novel that takes readers deep into the California backcountry, where a woman is tormented by visions of a killer. It starts in her dreams. Hideous flashes from a nightmare only she can stop. Images of a murderer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/murder-at-sunrise-lake-christine-feehan/">Murder at Sunrise Lake &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 New York Times bestselling author Christine Feehan reaches new heights of passion and suspense in this thrilling novel that takes readers deep into the California backcountry, where a woman is tormented by visions of a killer.  </p>
<p>                    It starts in her dreams. Hideous flashes from a nightmare only she can stop. Images of a murderer stalking the ones she cares about most&#8230;  </p>
<p>                    Stella Harrison thought she got away from the traumas of her past. Running the Sunrise Lake resort high in the Sierra Nevada mountains has brought her peace, even though she doesn&#8217;t truly share her quiet life with anyone. Not even Sam, the hired handyman that notices everything and always seems to know exactly what she needs. </p>
<p>                    Stella doesn&#8217;t know anything about Sam&#8217;s past, but somehow over the last two years his slow, steady presence has slipped past her defenses. Still, she knows she can&#8217;t tell him about her recent premonitions. So far there&#8217;s been no murder. No body. No way to prove what&#8217;s about to happen without destroying the life she&#8217;s built for herself. </p>
<p>                    But a killer is out there. And Stella knows that this time she&#8217;ll do whatever it takes to stop him.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/murder-at-sunrise-lake-christine-feehan/">Murder at Sunrise Lake &#8211; Christine Feehan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Night Shift &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/night-shift-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/night-shift-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s first collection of short stories showcases the darkest depths of his brilliant imagination and will chill the cockles of many a heart (Chicago Tribune). Featuring &#8220;Jerusalem&#8217;s Lot,&#8221; the basis for the upcoming tv series Chapelwaite. Here we see mutated rats gone bad (&#8220;Graveyard Shift&#8221;); a cataclysmic virus that threatens humanity (&#8220;Night Surf,&#8221; the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/night-shift-stephen-king/">Night Shift &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s first collection of short stories showcases the darkest depths of his brilliant imagination and will chill the cockles of many a heart (Chicago Tribune). Featuring &#8220;Jerusalem&#8217;s Lot,&#8221; the basis for the upcoming tv series Chapelwaite.    </p>
<p>                    Here we see mutated rats gone bad (&#8220;Graveyard Shift&#8221;); a cataclysmic virus that threatens humanity (&#8220;Night Surf,&#8221; the basis for The Stand); a possessed, evil lawnmower (&#8220;The Lawnmower Man&#8221;); unsettling children from the heartland (&#8220;Children of the Corn&#8221;); a smoker who will try anything to stop (&#8220;Quitters, Inc.&#8221;); a reclusive alcoholic who begins a gruesome transformation (&#8220;Gray Matter&#8221;); and many more shadows and visions that will haunt you long after the last page is turned.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/night-shift-stephen-king/">Night Shift &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rose Madder &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/rose-madder-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rose-madder-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Roused by a single drop of blood, Rosie Daniels wakes up to the chilling realisation that her husband is going to kill her. And she takes flight &#8211; with his credit card. Alone in a strange city, Rosie begins to build a new life: she meets Bill and she finds an odd junk shop painting, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rose-madder-stephen-king/">Rose Madder &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Roused by a single drop of blood, Rosie Daniels wakes up to the chilling realisation that her husband is going to kill her. And she takes flight &#8211; with his credit card.    </p>
<p>                     Alone in a strange city, Rosie begins to build a new life: she meets Bill and she finds an odd junk shop painting, &#8216;Rose Madder&#8217;, which strangely seems to want her as much as she wants it.    </p>
<p>                     But it&#8217;s hard for Rosie not to keep looking over her shoulder. Norman is a corrupt cop with the instincts of a predator. A man almost mythic in his monstrosity.  For Rosie to survive, she must enter the myth and become a person she never knew she could be &#8211; Rose Madder.    </p>
<p>                    Because Norman is getting close. Rosie can feel how close he is getting . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rose-madder-stephen-king/">Rose Madder &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Skeleton Crew : featuring The Mist &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/skeleton-crew-featuring-the-mist-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/skeleton-crew-featuring-the-mist-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Includes the brilliant story &#8216;The Mist&#8217;, now adapted into a major Netflix series. Hold tight. We are going into a number of dark places, but I think I know the way. Just don&#8217;t let go of my arm . . . Unrivalled master of suspense Stephen King takes the unsuspecting reader on a fantastic journey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/skeleton-crew-featuring-the-mist-stephen-king/">Skeleton Crew : featuring The Mist &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Includes the brilliant story &#8216;The Mist&#8217;, now adapted into a major Netflix series.<br />
                    Hold tight. We are going into a number of dark places, but I think I know the way. Just don&#8217;t let go of my arm . . .    </p>
<p>                     Unrivalled master of suspense Stephen King takes the unsuspecting reader on a fantastic journey through the dark shadows of our innermost fears.    </p>
<p>                     Do the dead sing?    </p>
<p>                     In this bumper collection of chilling tales, we meet: a woman who has never crossed The Reach, the water dividing her from the mainland; a gramma who only wants to hug little George, even after she is dead; an innocent looking toy with sinister powers; and a primeval sea creature with an insatiable appetite.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/skeleton-crew-featuring-the-mist-stephen-king/">Skeleton Crew : featuring The Mist &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Institute &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-institute-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-institute-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It does everything you&#8217;d expect of a masterpiece &#8211; and it is one&#8217; Sunday Express &#8216;Hums and crackles with delicious unease&#8217; Independent &#8216;Captivating&#8217; The Sunday Times &#8216;An absorbing thriller&#8217; Mail on Sunday NO ONE HAS EVER ESCAPED FROM THE INSTITUTE. Luke Ellis, a super-smart twelve-year-old with an exceptional gift, is the latest in a long [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-institute-stephen-king/">The Institute &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It does everything you&#8217;d expect of a masterpiece &#8211; and it is one&#8217; Sunday Express</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hums and crackles with delicious unease&#8217; Independent</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captivating&#8217; The Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An absorbing thriller&#8217; Mail on Sunday</p>
<p>                    NO ONE HAS EVER ESCAPED FROM THE INSTITUTE.</p>
<p>                    Luke Ellis, a super-smart twelve-year-old with an exceptional gift, is the latest in a long line of kids abducted and taken to a secret government facility, hidden deep in the forest in Maine.</p>
<p>                    Here, kids with special talents &#8211; telekinesis and telepathy &#8211; like Luke&#8217;s new friends Kalisha, Nick and Iris, are subjected to a series of experiments.</p>
<p>                    There seems to be no hope of escape. Until Luke teams up with an even younger boy whose powers of telepathy are off the scale.</p>
<p>                    Meanwhile, far away in a small town in South Carolina, former cop Tim Jamieson, looking for the quiet life, has taken a job working for the local sheriff.  He doesn&#8217;t know he&#8217;s about to take on the biggest case of his career . . .</p>
<p>                    THERE&#8217;S ONLY ONE WAY OUT.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An epic tale of childhood betrayal and hope regained&#8230; an immersive tale full of suspense and thrills that will keep readers up late at night racing towards a heartbreaking yet glorious finale&#8230; a dazzling achievement&#8217; &#8211; Daily Express</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-institute-stephen-king/">The Institute &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whispers : Feathers and Fire Book 3 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</title>
		<link>/whispers-feathers-and-fire-book-3-shayne-silvers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whispers-feathers-and-fire-book-3-shayne-silvers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SILVERS HAS SOLD OVER 500,000 BOOKS, AND IS A DRAGON AWARD NOMINATED AUTHOR The Vatican is broken&#8230; And Callie&#8217;s hearing Whispers in the dark corners of her mind&#8230; One of the Vatican&#8217;s most infamous Shepherds has been murdered, and Callie&#8217;s friends are the prime suspects. To prove them innocent, Roland and Callie must risk their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whispers-feathers-and-fire-book-3-shayne-silvers/">Whispers : Feathers and Fire Book 3 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SILVERS HAS SOLD OVER 500,000 BOOKS, AND IS A DRAGON AWARD NOMINATED AUTHOR<br />
                    The Vatican is broken&#8230; And Callie&#8217;s hearing Whispers in the dark corners of her mind&#8230;</p>
<p>                    One of the Vatican&#8217;s most infamous Shepherds has been murdered, and Callie&#8217;s friends are the prime suspects. To prove them innocent, Roland and Callie must risk their very souls&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Because Callie can&#8217;t reveal that she&#8217;s hearing strange Whispers when she uses her magic, or that she&#8217;s harboring an Angel&#8217;s Grace. And if the Shepherds discover the hellish bargain Roland made, the streets of Rome will flow with blood as brother turns against brother.</p>
<p>                    And with the Antipope pressuring the Vatican for change, and Nate Temple arriving unannounced to demand an audience with the Shepherds, things couldn&#8217;t get any more chaotic.</p>
<p>                    Until Callie learns of an ancient order of traitors hiding in the Vatican, and they&#8217;ll do anything to bring it down &#8211; brick by brick.</p>
<p>                    The only way to find the traitor, keep her secrets, and save those she loves is to raise her blade against these Holy warriors of God, shattering the Vatican itself.</p>
<p>                    And the Whispers in her head find all of this so terribly&#8230; amusing.</p>
<p>                    If you like Patricia Briggs, Ilona Andrews, Linsey Hall, K.F. Breene or Shannon Mayer, you will LOVE the THIRD installment of the Feathers and Fire series.Click or tap BUY NOW to jump into this high-octane world TODAY!INTERVIEW WITH THE AUTHOR: Q: So, what makes your writing so special?<br />
                    A:  I wanted to write stories that mirrored the books I liked to read in my childhood. My top picks were usually urban fantasy, paranormal best sellers, and of course, books featuring your classic gritty, pulp-fiction heroes. Basically, anything with a lot of creepy crawly supernatural characters: mythical creatures, ancient heroes, super villains, and gods. You will find that my stories focus on the ancient myths, characters, and stories we all know, fear, and love. Then twist them up and toss them back like an empty beer can.</p>
<p>                    Q: What other books do you write?<br />
                    A:  I also write the Amazon Bestselling Nate Temple Series that crosses over (if you&#8217;re into that) with the Feathers and Fire Series.</p>
<p>                    Q: So, why should readers give your books a try?<br />
                    A:  Because my writing is a present day thrill-ride that takes no prisoners. Dragons, Angels, Demons, Greek Legends, Wizards, werewolves, and a whole slew of other supernatural &#8216;Freaks&#8217; abound in my stories. My books have hit the #1 bestsellers list on Kindle for Science Fiction and Fantasy dozens of times. The plots twist and turn until the last page, and my twisted sense of humor will have you laughing out loud at things you really shouldn&#8217;t be laughing at.Feathers and Fire Series eBook categories: Dark FantasySupernatural ThrillerWitches &#038; WizardsUrban Fantasy ThrillerSupernatural ShifterAngels &#038; DemonsScience Fiction &#038; FantasyParanormal and Urban RomanceSupernatural Mystery and SuspenseVampires and Werewolves<br />
                    Scroll up and tap or click BUY NOW to jump face-first into this wild ride with demons, angels, shifters, and vampires TODAY!!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whispers-feathers-and-fire-book-3-shayne-silvers/">Whispers : Feathers and Fire Book 3 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unchained : Feathers and Fire Book 1 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</title>
		<link>/unchained-feathers-and-fire-book-1-shayne-silvers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unchained-feathers-and-fire-book-1-shayne-silvers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SILVERS HAS SOLD OVER 500,000 BOOKS, AND IS A DRAGON AWARD NOMINATED AUTHOR Meet Callie Penrose. Is she Heaven&#8217;s Devil, or Hell&#8217;s Angel? Callie is a middle-class, Midwest American girl. And a wizard in training. She works for Roland, a member of the Vatican Shepherds &#8211; an elite group of twelve warrior priests who travel [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unchained-feathers-and-fire-book-1-shayne-silvers/">Unchained : Feathers and Fire Book 1 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SILVERS HAS SOLD OVER 500,000 BOOKS, AND IS A DRAGON AWARD NOMINATED AUTHOR<br />
                    Meet Callie Penrose. Is she Heaven&#8217;s Devil, or Hell&#8217;s Angel?</p>
<p>                    Callie is a middle-class, Midwest American girl. And a wizard in training. She works for Roland, a member of the Vatican Shepherds &#8211; an elite group of twelve warrior priests who travel the world smiting whatever offends them or their Good Lord.</p>
<p>                    One problem. Callie isn&#8217;t a huge fan of churches&#8230; Not even a minor fan, really.</p>
<p>                    She trains with Roland only to learn how to use those strange magical powers inside her. And because Roland had once saved her and her friend from monsters in a dark alley.</p>
<p>                    But when a Heavenly spear enters an auction in Kansas City, and Roland is gravely wounded, Callie finds herself forced to step up as an interim Shepherd, and her first night on the job puts her in a bidding war against the infamous Nate Temple &#8211; the billionaire wizard from St. Louis. And when demons, shifter bears, vampires, and Nephilim attack the auction for the spear, Nate and Callie are forced to join teams, and one-time foes become hesitant allies.</p>
<p>                    Callie must learn where she stands as a wizard. Will she hide behind a man, or light Kansas City afire with a name of her own? And will she finally come to appreciate God? Or will the demons and monsters in the shadows take her for themselves?</p>
<p>                    Because Callie soon learns she isn&#8217;t just a wizard, and it was never just about the spear. Monsters have evidently been hunting Callie her entire life, and now, they&#8217;ve finally found her&#8230;</p>
<p>                    If you like Patricia Briggs, Ilona Andrews, Linsey Hall, K.F. Breene or Shannon Mayer, you will LOVE the first installment of the Feathers and Fire series.Click or tap BUY NOW to jump into this high-octane world TODAY!INTERVIEW WITH THE AUTHOR: Q: So, what makes your writing so special?<br />
                    A:  I wanted to write stories that mirrored the books I liked to read in my childhood. My top picks were usually urban fantasy, paranormal best sellers, and of course, books featuring your classic gritty, pulp-fiction heroes. Basically, anything with a lot of creepy crawly supernatural characters: mythical creatures, ancient heroes, super villains, and gods. You will find that my stories focus on the ancient myths, characters, and stories we all know, fear, and love. Then twist them up and toss them back like an empty beer can.</p>
<p>                    Q: What other books do you write?<br />
                    A:  I also write the Amazon Bestselling Nate Temple Series that crosses over (if you&#8217;re into that) with the Feathers and Fire Series.</p>
<p>                    Q: So, why should readers give your books a try?<br />
                    A:  Because my writing is a present day thrill-ride that takes no prisoners. Dragons, Angels, Demons, Greek Legends, Wizards, werewolves, and a whole slew of other supernatural &#8216;Freaks&#8217; abound in my stories. My books have hit the #1 bestsellers list on Kindle for Science Fiction and Fantasy dozens of times. The plots twist and turn until the last page, and my twisted sense of humor will have you laughing out loud at things you really shouldn&#8217;t be laughing at.Feathers and Fire Series eBook categories: Dark FantasySupernatural ThrillerWitches &#038; WizardsUrban Fantasy ThrillerSupernatural ShifterAngels &#038; DemonsScience Fiction &#038; FantasyParanormal and Urban RomanceSupernatural Mystery and SuspenseVampires and Werewolves<br />
                    Scroll up and tap or click BUY NOW to jump face-first into this wild ride with demons, angels, shifters, and vampires TODAY!!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unchained-feathers-and-fire-book-1-shayne-silvers/">Unchained : Feathers and Fire Book 1 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tiny Gods : Nate Temple Series Book 6 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</title>
		<link>/tiny-gods-nate-temple-series-book-6-shayne-silvers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tiny-gods-nate-temple-series-book-6-shayne-silvers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Power is patient, power is kind&#8230; No, wait. That&#8217;s not right. Power corrupts, and absolute power corrupts absolutely&#8230; Just ask Nate&#8217;s ex-fiancée. It&#8217;s almost this wizard&#8217;s birthday, so, he can cry if he wants to. That is, if he lives to see it&#8230; Because a lot of people want him dead: his fiancée, his long-lost [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tiny-gods-nate-temple-series-book-6-shayne-silvers/">Tiny Gods : Nate Temple Series Book 6 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Power is patient, power is kind&#8230;</p>
<p>                    No, wait. That&#8217;s not right. Power corrupts, and absolute power corrupts absolutely&#8230; Just ask Nate&#8217;s ex-fiancée.</p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s almost this wizard&#8217;s birthday, so, he can cry if he wants to. That is, if he lives to see it&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Because a lot of people want him dead: his fiancée, his long-lost ancestor, the good wizards, the dark wizards, and&#8230; Look, it&#8217;s easier to list who doesn&#8217;t want to kill him.</p>
<p>                    To prevent a Shifter vs. Wizard War, Nate steps in to draw a line in the sand, picking a fight with the deadliest magic slingers on the planet&#8230; and then he tries to rob them.</p>
<p>                    And with Achilles angry at Nate for crashing his Fight Night, the Horsemen of the Apocalypse breathing down his neck, Gods hiding behind mortal skins, and an accidental shifter infection with a cheerful Swedish male dancer, Nate has his hands full.</p>
<p>                    But when his enemies decide to wake a God, the only way for Nate to level the playing field is to open an early birthday present from the Mad Hatter&#8230; And that&#8217;s when he finds out that nothing is ever simple, and that no one was ever who he thought they were all these years.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Shayne Silvers, Jim Butcher, and Kevin Hearne are easily my favorite Urban Fantasy Authors. In that order.&#8221; &#8211; Michael Anderle, Amazon Top 25 Bestselling Author</p>
<p>                    More than 1m copies downloaded and thousands of five-star reviews. Available in digital, print, and audiobook formats.</p>
<p>                    What Amazon readers are saying: </p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His foul-mouthed unicorn murders rainbows!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Move over Dresden!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;The Temple Verse HAS to be picked up by Netflix soon.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Silvers could write a grocery list on a dirty napkin and make it an international bestseller.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I went from crying my eyes out to laughing uncontrollably, repeatedly.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;It&#8217;s like the characters walked off the page, joined me at the bar, and bought me a drink.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I am astounded as to how the author keeps the story fresh and exciting.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I usually see plot twists a mile away. Shayne has proven me wrong. Every time.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Best books I&#8217;ve read in thirty years.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His intense actions scenes let you see the fangs and claws, hear the gunshots, feel the magic, and smell the fear.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Everything you thought you knew about vampires, shifters, dragons, wizards, fairies and gods is flat wrong.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Publishers who didn&#8217;t snap up this series are missing out on a gold mine.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Silvers has pleasured over one million readers with the Temple Universe. Now it&#8217;s your turn for a little pleasuring&#8230;</p>
<p>                    ★★ SILVERS WAS A DRAGON AWARD FINALIST FOR BEST FANTASY NOVEL OF THE YEAR IN BOTH 2017 AND 2018. FIND OUT WHY&#8230; ★★</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tiny-gods-nate-temple-series-book-6-shayne-silvers/">Tiny Gods : Nate Temple Series Book 6 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stationary Bike &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/stationary-bike-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stationary-bike-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King s bestselling thriller is now available, unabridged, for only $14.99! When commercial artist Richard Sifkitz finally gets around to having that physical he d been putting off for years, and his cholesterol comes back dangerously high, he does what so many thirty-something, junk food-eating couch potatoes have done before him: He buys a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stationary-bike-stephen-king/">Stationary Bike &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King s bestselling thriller is now available, unabridged, for only $14.99!<br />
                    When commercial artist Richard Sifkitz finally gets around to having that physical he d been putting off for years, and his cholesterol comes back dangerously high, he does what so many thirty-something, junk food-eating couch potatoes have done before him: He buys a stationary bike, and vows to ride it regularly.<br />
                     Unlike many a mid-life exercise convert, however, Richard actually starts to ride his new stationary bike. A lot. Soon he s spending so much time on his bike that he decides to put his artistic talents to use and paint a mural on the wall opposite his stationary bike. But it turns out that Richard s mural is no ordinary picture, and soon his stationary bike is taking him places he doesn t want to go, and can&#8217;t stay away from.<br />
                     A riveting take on artistic frustration, mid-life mortality, and hard-won redemption, &#8220;Stationary Bike&#8221; is a thrill ride that could come only from the mind of Stephen King.&#8221;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stationary-bike-stephen-king/">Stationary Bike &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wild Side : Nate Temple Series Book 7 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</title>
		<link>/wild-side-nate-temple-series-book-7-shayne-silvers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wild-side-nate-temple-series-book-7-shayne-silvers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To become a Godkiller you have to awaken the monster inside you&#8230; Almost a year has passed since Nate&#8217;s ex-fiancée woke up a Greek god intent on world domination and war. The problem? He doesn&#8217;t know which god. And the promised war hasn&#8217;t started yet. With the Four Horsemen refusing to help, and an army [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wild-side-nate-temple-series-book-7-shayne-silvers/">Wild Side : Nate Temple Series Book 7 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To become a Godkiller you have to awaken the monster inside you&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Almost a year has passed since Nate&#8217;s ex-fiancée woke up a Greek god intent on world domination and war. The problem? He doesn&#8217;t know which god. And the promised war hasn&#8217;t started yet.</p>
<p>                    With the Four Horsemen refusing to help, and an army of monsters living on his lawn, Nate resorts to the one thing he&#8217;s best at-pissing off demigods and Greek Heroes in hopes of jump-starting the war.</p>
<p>                    But then he receives an ominous invitation that he literally cannot refuse. A dark, deadly place where nightmares roam free demands an audience. The Land of the Fae.</p>
<p>                    He must forget every story he&#8217;s heard about the Fae. They&#8217;re nothing like he imagined, nothing like he&#8217;s been told&#8230; Because to kill a god, he needs to learn how to become a monster.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Shayne Silvers, Jim Butcher, and Kevin Hearne are easily my favorite Urban Fantasy Authors. In that order.&#8221; &#8211; Michael Anderle, Amazon Top 25 Bestselling Author</p>
<p>                    More than 1m copies downloaded and thousands of five-star reviews. Available in digital, print, and audiobook formats.</p>
<p>                    What Amazon readers are saying: </p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His foul-mouthed unicorn murders rainbows!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Move over Dresden!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;The Temple Verse HAS to be picked up by Netflix soon.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Silvers could write a grocery list on a dirty napkin and make it an international bestseller.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I went from crying my eyes out to laughing uncontrollably, repeatedly.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;It&#8217;s like the characters walked off the page, joined me at the bar, and bought me a drink.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I am astounded as to how the author keeps the story fresh and exciting.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I usually see plot twists a mile away. Shayne has proven me wrong. Every time.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Best books I&#8217;ve read in thirty years.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His intense actions scenes let you see the fangs and claws, hear the gunshots, feel the magic, and smell the fear.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Everything you thought you knew about vampires, shifters, dragons, wizards, fairies and gods is flat wrong.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Publishers who didn&#8217;t snap up this series are missing out on a gold mine.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Silvers has pleasured over one million readers with the Temple Universe. Now it&#8217;s your turn for a little pleasuring&#8230;</p>
<p>                    ★★ SILVERS WAS A DRAGON AWARD FINALIST FOR BEST FANTASY NOVEL OF THE YEAR IN BOTH 2017 AND 2018. FIND OUT WHY&#8230; ★★</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wild-side-nate-temple-series-book-7-shayne-silvers/">Wild Side : Nate Temple Series Book 7 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dark Tower II: The Drawing Of The Three : (Volume 2) &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-dark-tower-ii-the-drawing-of-the-three-volume-2-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dark-tower-ii-the-drawing-of-the-three-volume-2-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE DRAWING OF THE THREE is the second volume in Stephen King&#8217;s epic Dark Tower series. The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba. In the second novel of Stephen King&#8217;s bestselling fantasy masterpiece, Roland of Gilead, the Last Gunslinger, encounters three mysterious doors which open &#8211; for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-tower-ii-the-drawing-of-the-three-volume-2-stephen-king/">The Dark Tower II: The Drawing Of The Three : (Volume 2) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE DRAWING OF THE THREE is the second volume in Stephen King&#8217;s epic Dark Tower series.  The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba.</p>
<p>                    In the second novel of Stephen King&#8217;s bestselling fantasy masterpiece, Roland of Gilead, the Last Gunslinger, encounters three mysterious doors which open &#8211; for Roland, and Roland alone &#8211; to different times in our world. He must draw the three who should accompany him on the road. </p>
<p>                    In 1980s New York, Roland joins forces with defiant Eddie Dean. The second door leads to the 1960s and conflicted civil rights activist Odetta Holmes. The final door reveals Jack Mort, a deadly serial killer, in the 1970s. Mort is stalking Jake, the young boy Roland met in Mid-World.</p>
<p>                    As titanic forces gather, a savage struggle between underworld evil and otherworldly enemies threatens to bring an end to Roland&#8217;s journey toward the Dark Tower&#8230;</p>
<p>                    JOIN THE QUEST FOR THE DARK TOWER&#8230;</p>
<p>                    THE DARK TOWER SERIES:<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER I: THE GUNSLINGER<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER II: THE DRAWING OF THE THREE<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER III: THE WASTE LANDS<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER IV: WIZARD AND GLASS<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER V: WOLVES OF THE CALLA<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER VI: SONG OF SUSANNAH<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER VII: THE DARK TOWER<br />
                     THE WIND THROUGH THE KEYHOLE: A DARK TOWER NOVEL</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-tower-ii-the-drawing-of-the-three-volume-2-stephen-king/">The Dark Tower II: The Drawing Of The Three : (Volume 2) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Eyes of the Dragon &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-eyes-of-the-dragon-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-eyes-of-the-dragon-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While evidence is gathered, and the land of Delain mourns, Flagg the King&#8217;s magician, unscrupulous, greedy and powerful, plots. Soon the King&#8217;s elder son, Peter, is imprisoned in the needle, the top of a high tower, for his father&#8217;s murder. And Thomas inherits the throne. Only Peter knows the truth of his innocence, and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-eyes-of-the-dragon-stephen-king/">The Eyes of the Dragon &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While evidence is gathered, and the land of Delain mourns, Flagg the King&#8217;s magician, unscrupulous, greedy and powerful, plots. Soon the King&#8217;s elder son, Peter, is imprisoned in the needle, the top of a high tower, for his father&#8217;s murder. And Thomas inherits the throne.    </p>
<p>                    Only Peter knows the truth of his innocence, and the true evil that is Flagg. Only Peter can save Delain from the horror the magician has in store. He has a plan, but it is rife with danger. And if he fails, he won&#8217;t get a second chance . . .    </p>
<p>                    A captivating tale of heroic adventure, of dragons and princes, of mysterious mice and men from the pen of the master storyteller.There is a reason why Stephen King is one of the bestselling writers in the world, ever. Described in the Daily Express as &#8216;a fabulous teller of stories&#8217;, Stephen King writes books that draw you in and are impossible to put down.    </p>
<p>                    The King is dead, murdered by an unusual poison.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-eyes-of-the-dragon-stephen-king/">The Eyes of the Dragon &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dead Zone &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-dead-zone-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dead-zone-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s fan-favourite thriller. Also available in audio for the first time, read by Academy Award nominee James Franco. The two things that conjured up that horrible night, were his run of luck at the Wheel of Fortune, and the mask . . . Meet Johnny Smith. A young man whose streak of luck ends [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dead-zone-stephen-king/">The Dead Zone &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stephen King&#8217;s fan-favourite thriller. Also available in audio for the first time, read by Academy Award nominee James Franco.    </p>
<p>                    The two things that conjured up that horrible night, were his run of luck at the Wheel of Fortune, and the mask . . .    </p>
<p>                    Meet Johnny Smith.  A young man whose streak of luck ends dramatically in a major car crash.  Followed by blackness.  A long, long time in cold limbo.    </p>
<p>                    When he wakes up life has been turned upside down. His fiancee has met someone else.  And Johnny is cursed with the power to perceive evil in men&#8217;s souls.  He&#8217;s had these hunches since he had an ice-skating accident as a child.  Now he has an ability to see into the future. An ability which will bring him into a terrifying confrontation with a charismatic, power-hungry and dangerous man . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dead-zone-stephen-king/">The Dead Zone &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Splendor of Fear &#8211; Ambrose Ibsen</title>
		<link>/the-splendor-of-fear-ambrose-ibsen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-splendor-of-fear-ambrose-ibsen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Something stirs in the town of Newsom&#8217;s Landing . . . Penny hates the outdoors, but when her boyfriend, Jared, plans a romantic weekend getaway in the woods, she decides to tag along. The pair drive to a remote Kentucky campground with a strange and sordid history. Within the confines of the Swan Creek State [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-splendor-of-fear-ambrose-ibsen/">The Splendor of Fear &#8211; Ambrose Ibsen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Something stirs in the town of Newsom&#8217;s Landing . . .  Penny hates the outdoors, but when her boyfriend, Jared, plans a romantic weekend getaway in the woods, she decides to tag along. The pair drive to a remote Kentucky campground with a strange and sordid history. Within the confines of the Swan Creek State Park are the ruins of a town abandoned under terrifying circumstances in the 19th century. The town of Newsom&#8217;s Landing had been the site of the last-known witch trial in U.S. history, and the ghost of its defendant, the infamous Ellie Pomeroy, is said to still linger. Arriving on the anniversary of Pomeory&#8217;s murder, the pair find they have the entire park to themselves. Or, nearly. Something else is stalking the woods&#8211;watching in the night, wandering through the ruins. It brings a plague of hallucinatory terror wherever it goes, and before long, Penny and Jared can&#8217;t parse reality from nightmare. Lost in the woods, the pair are faced with a choice: Find a way to end the century-long curse, or be consumed by it&#8211;body and soul.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-splendor-of-fear-ambrose-ibsen/">The Splendor of Fear &#8211; Ambrose Ibsen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>War Hammer : Nate Temple Series Book 8 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</title>
		<link>/war-hammer-nate-temple-series-book-8-shayne-silvers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/war-hammer-nate-temple-series-book-8-shayne-silvers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two old dudes want to kill me. Oh, and one of them is my ancestor&#8230; And after centuries of practice, they&#8217;re pretty good at the whole murder thing. But at least they want to kill each other just as badly. Now, I&#8217;ve taken down a Greek Goddess, worn a Horseman&#8217;s Mask, and I ride a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/war-hammer-nate-temple-series-book-8-shayne-silvers/">War Hammer : Nate Temple Series Book 8 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two old dudes want to kill me. Oh, and one of them is my ancestor&#8230;</p>
<p>                    And after centuries of practice, they&#8217;re pretty good at the whole murder thing. But at least they want to kill each other just as badly.</p>
<p>                    Now, I&#8217;ve taken down a Greek Goddess, worn a Horseman&#8217;s Mask, and I ride a homicidal unicorn who hates rainbows with a passion. Some might say sending two senior citizens to a permanent retirement home should be a breeze.</p>
<p>                    It ain&#8217;t.</p>
<p>                    Because that&#8217;s not my biggest concern. One of my friends is in danger, or possibly dying, and I need to get her back before her fiancé kills me. But finding her introduces me to new worlds of pain. The biggest of these being my own past-which has been a blatant lie-and a parting gift from my parents-which might have just been the coin toss for the Apocalypse Olympics.</p>
<p>                    I&#8217;m beginning to realize that none of the old Gods, Legends, or Monsters have been idle the last few centuries. They&#8217;ve been waiting, picking sides, and scheming schemes.</p>
<p>                    Of course, maybe one of those two old dudes will punch my ticket and save me the headache. A wizard can Hope, right? Because either way, I&#8217;m about to have a very bad series of days&#8230;</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Shayne Silvers, Jim Butcher, and Kevin Hearne are easily my favorite Urban Fantasy Authors. In that order.&#8221; &#8211; Michael Anderle, Amazon Top 25 Bestselling Author</p>
<p>                    More than 1m copies downloaded and thousands of five-star reviews. Available in digital, print, and audiobook formats.</p>
<p>                    What Amazon readers are saying: </p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His foul-mouthed unicorn murders rainbows!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Move over Dresden!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;The Temple Verse HAS to be picked up by Netflix soon.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Silvers could write a grocery list on a dirty napkin and make it an international bestseller.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I went from crying my eyes out to laughing uncontrollably, repeatedly.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;It&#8217;s like the characters walked off the page, joined me at the bar, and bought me a drink.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I am astounded as to how the author keeps the story fresh and exciting.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;I usually see plot twists a mile away. Shayne has proven me wrong. Every time.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Best books I&#8217;ve read in thirty years.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;His intense actions scenes let you see the fangs and claws, hear the gunshots, feel the magic, and smell the fear.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Everything you thought you knew about vampires, shifters, dragons, wizards, fairies and gods is flat wrong.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ★★★★★ &#8216;Publishers who didn&#8217;t snap up this series are missing out on a gold mine.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Silvers has pleasured over one million readers with the Temple Universe. Now it&#8217;s your turn for a little pleasuring&#8230;</p>
<p>                    ★★ SILVERS WAS A DRAGON AWARD FINALIST FOR BEST FANTASY NOVEL OF THE YEAR IN BOTH 2017 AND 2018. FIND OUT WHY&#8230; ★★</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/war-hammer-nate-temple-series-book-8-shayne-silvers/">War Hammer : Nate Temple Series Book 8 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lisey&#8217;s Story &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/liseys-story-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/liseys-story-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*Soon to be an Apple TV+ limited series starring Julianne Moore and Clive Owen* Every marriage has two hearts, one light and one dark. Lisey knew it when she first fell for Scott. And now he&#8217;s dead, she knows it for sure. Lisey was the light to Scott Landon&#8217;s dark for twenty-five years. As his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/liseys-story-stephen-king/">Lisey&#8217;s Story &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*Soon to be an Apple TV+ limited series starring Julianne Moore and Clive Owen*    </p>
<p>                    Every marriage has two hearts, one light and one dark.    </p>
<p>                    Lisey knew it when she first fell for Scott. And now he&#8217;s dead, she knows it for sure.    </p>
<p>                    Lisey was the light to Scott Landon&#8217;s dark for twenty-five years. As his wife, only she saw the truth behind the public face of the famous author &#8211; that he was a haunted man whose bestselling novels were based on a terrifying reality.    </p>
<p>                    Now Scott has gone, Lisey wants to lock herself away with her memories. But the fans have other ideas. And when the sinister threats begin, Lisey realises that, just as Scott depended on her strength &#8211; her light &#8211; to live, so she will have to draw on his darkness to survive.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/liseys-story-stephen-king/">Lisey&#8217;s Story &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rage : Feathers and Fire Book 2 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</title>
		<link>/rage-feathers-and-fire-book-2-shayne-silvers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rage-feathers-and-fire-book-2-shayne-silvers/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SILVERS HAS SOLD OVER 500,000 BOOKS, AND IS A DRAGON AWARD NOMINATED AUTHOR Hell hath no fury like Callie Penrose&#8230; Ever since Callie &#8211; the Vatican&#8217;s rookie monster hunter &#8211; killed a demon a few weeks ago, Kansas City&#8217;s been eerily quiet. But she soon learns it&#8217;s just the calm before the storm. Because werewolves [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rage-feathers-and-fire-book-2-shayne-silvers/">Rage : Feathers and Fire Book 2 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SILVERS HAS SOLD OVER 500,000 BOOKS, AND IS A DRAGON AWARD NOMINATED AUTHOR<br />
                    Hell hath no fury like Callie Penrose&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Ever since Callie &#8211; the Vatican&#8217;s rookie monster hunter &#8211; killed a demon a few weeks ago, Kansas City&#8217;s been eerily quiet.</p>
<p>                    But she soon learns it&#8217;s just the calm before the storm.</p>
<p>                    Because werewolves begin abducting young women in Kansas City, and a new church opens its doors, pronouncing death to all idols, including these &#8216;make-believe&#8217; monsters and wizards.</p>
<p>                    But when one of their congregation is disemboweled by a monster on the steps of the church with the phrase God is dead painted in blood, someone in the church decides to take a lesson from the Salem Witch Trials&#8230; And the police seem to be helping.</p>
<p>                    Callie must catch the killer before Kansas City erupts in civil war. A civil war she inadvertently started. Before everyone decides to kill each other. Or worse yet, her.</p>
<p>                    But she&#8217;s being stalked. By something unseen. More than one something&#8230; And with so many new faces coming to Missouri &#8211; gods, legends, and nightmares &#8211; Callie begins to realize it&#8217;s all someone&#8217;s sick idea of a game.</p>
<p>                    And that Hell never really left Kansas City. Or Callie Penrose.</p>
<p>                    After all, they say Missouri loves company&#8230;</p>
<p>                    If you like Patricia Briggs, Ilona Andrews, Linsey Hall, K.F. Breene or Shannon Mayer, you will LOVE the SECOND installment of the Feathers and Fire series.Click or tap BUY NOW to jump into this high-octane world TODAY!INTERVIEW WITH THE AUTHOR: Q: So, what makes your writing so special?<br />
                    A:  I wanted to write stories that mirrored the books I liked to read in my childhood. My top picks were usually urban fantasy, paranormal best sellers, and of course, books featuring your classic gritty, pulp-fiction heroes. Basically, anything with a lot of creepy crawly supernatural characters: mythical creatures, ancient heroes, super villains, and gods. You will find that my stories focus on the ancient myths, characters, and stories we all know, fear, and love. Then twist them up and toss them back like an empty beer can.</p>
<p>                    Q: What other books do you write?<br />
                    A:  I also write the Amazon Bestselling Nate Temple Series that crosses over (if you&#8217;re into that) with the Feathers and Fire Series.</p>
<p>                    Q: So, why should readers give your books a try?<br />
                    A:  Because my writing is a present day thrill-ride that takes no prisoners. Dragons, Angels, Demons, Greek Legends, Wizards, werewolves, and a whole slew of other supernatural &#8216;Freaks&#8217; abound in my stories. My books have hit the #1 bestsellers list on Kindle for Science Fiction and Fantasy dozens of times. The plots twist and turn until the last page, and my twisted sense of humor will have you laughing out loud at things you really shouldn&#8217;t be laughing at.Feathers and Fire Series eBook categories: Dark FantasySupernatural ThrillerWitches &#038; WizardsUrban Fantasy ThrillerSupernatural ShifterAngels &#038; DemonsScience Fiction &#038; FantasyParanormal and Urban RomanceSupernatural Mystery and SuspenseVampires and Werewolves<br />
                    Scroll up and tap or click BUY NOW to jump face-first into this wild ride with demons, angels, shifters, and vampires TODAY!!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rage-feathers-and-fire-book-2-shayne-silvers/">Rage : Feathers and Fire Book 2 &#8211; Shayne Silvers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Storm Gathering &#8211; Rebecca Zanetti</title>
		<link>/storm-gathering-rebecca-zanetti/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/storm-gathering-rebecca-zanetti/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Even before surviving the Scorpius bacterium, Greyson Storm was a lone wolf navigating minefields. As a kid, he learned to take a hit and find safety. As an adult, he joined the military and quickly learned how to protect and defend. When the world ended, he created a mercenary camp with military precision, no entanglements, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/storm-gathering-rebecca-zanetti/">Storm Gathering &#8211; Rebecca Zanetti</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even before surviving the Scorpius bacterium, Greyson Storm was a lone wolf navigating minefields. As a kid, he learned to take a hit and find safety. As an adult, he joined the military and quickly learned how to protect and defend. When the world ended, he created a mercenary camp with military precision, no entanglements, and a promise to avenge a fallen friend. As part of that vow, he kidnapped Maureen Shadow, but now that he has let her go, her blue eyes and intriguing mind keep haunting him&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    As possibly the only Biotechnology Engineer still living, Maureen Shadow might be humanity&#8217;s one hope to survive the aftermath of Scorpius, making her frighteningly valuable to both allies and enemies. Even after sexual tension explodes between her and Greyson, she&#8217;s not sure which camp he belongs to&#8211;friend or foe? Worse yet, survival may mean thwarting his prime mission, putting her in even more peril. When danger and seduction collide, there is no safety in this new world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/storm-gathering-rebecca-zanetti/">Storm Gathering &#8211; Rebecca Zanetti</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mist in the Mirror &#8211; Susan Hill</title>
		<link>/the-mist-in-the-mirror-susan-hill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mist-in-the-mirror-susan-hill/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A terrifying ghost story by the bestselling author of The Woman in Black. One dark and rainy night, Sir James Monmouth returns to London after years spent travelling alone. Intent on uncovering the secrets of his childhood hero, the mysterious Conrad Vane, he begins to investigate Vane&#8217;s life, but he finds himself warned off at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mist-in-the-mirror-susan-hill/">The Mist in the Mirror &#8211; Susan Hill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A terrifying ghost story by the bestselling author of The Woman in Black.</p>
<p>                    One dark and rainy night, Sir James Monmouth returns to London after years spent travelling alone. </p>
<p>                    Intent on uncovering the secrets of his childhood hero, the mysterious Conrad Vane, he begins to investigate Vane&#8217;s life, but he finds himself warned off at every turn. </p>
<p>                    Before long he realises he is being followed too. A pale, thin boy is haunting his every step but every time he tries to confront the boy he disappears. And what of the chilling scream and desperate sobbing only he can hear? </p>
<p>                    His quest leads him eventually to the old lady of Kittiscar Hall, where he discovers something far more terrible at work than he could ever have imagined.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thoroughly frightening&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Chills the blood&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mist-in-the-mirror-susan-hill/">The Mist in the Mirror &#8211; Susan Hill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Roman : Florentine Series, Book 3 &#8211; Sylvain Reynard</title>
		<link>/the-roman-florentine-series-book-3-sylvain-reynard/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-roman-florentine-series-book-3-sylvain-reynard/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Paperback edition includes bonus content. Raven and her sister, Cara, are at the mercy of a small detachment of Florentine vampyres who are delivering them as a peace offering to the feared Curia in Rome. Though she&#8217;s unsure William survived the coup that toppled his principality, Raven is determined to protect her sister at all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-roman-florentine-series-book-3-sylvain-reynard/">The Roman : Florentine Series, Book 3 &#8211; Sylvain Reynard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Paperback edition includes bonus content.    </p>
<p>                    Raven and her sister, Cara, are at the mercy of a small detachment of Florentine vampyres who are delivering them as a peace offering to the feared Curia in Rome.    </p>
<p>                    Though she&#8217;s unsure William survived the coup that toppled his principality, Raven is determined to protect her sister at all costs, even if it means challenging Borek, the commander of the detachment.    </p>
<p>                    In an effort to keep Raven from falling into the hands of his enemies, William puts himself at the mercy of the Roman, the dangerous and mysterious vampyre king of Italy. But the Roman is not what he expects &#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Alliances and enmities will shift and merge as William struggles to save the woman he loves and his principality, without plunging the vampyre population into a world war.    </p>
<p>                    This stunning conclusion to the Florentine series will take readers across Italy and beyond as the lovers fight to remain together.  Forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-roman-florentine-series-book-3-sylvain-reynard/">The Roman : Florentine Series, Book 3 &#8211; Sylvain Reynard</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fire Touched &#8211; Patricia Briggs</title>
		<link>/fire-touched-patricia-briggs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monsters & Legendary Beings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fire-touched-patricia-briggs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mercy Thompson has been hailed as &#8220;a heroine who&#8230;always remains true to herself&#8221; (Library Journal). Now she&#8217;s back, and she&#8217;ll soon discover that when the fae stalk the human world, it&#8217;s the children who suffer&#8230; Tensions between the fae and humans are coming to a head. And when coyote shapeshifter Mercy and her Alpha werewolf [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-touched-patricia-briggs/">Fire Touched &#8211; Patricia Briggs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mercy Thompson has been hailed as &#8220;a heroine who&#8230;always remains true to herself&#8221; (Library Journal). Now she&#8217;s back, and she&#8217;ll soon discover that when the fae stalk the human world, it&#8217;s the children who suffer&#8230;     </p>
<p>                     Tensions between the fae and humans are coming to a head. And when coyote shapeshifter Mercy and her Alpha werewolf mate, Adam, are called upon to stop a rampaging troll, they find themselves with something that could be used to make the fae back down and forestall out-and-out war: a human child stolen long ago by the fae.     </p>
<p>                     Defying the most powerful werewolf in the country, the humans, and the fae, Mercy, Adam, and their pack choose to protect the boy no matter what the cost. But who will protect them from a boy who is fire touched?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-touched-patricia-briggs/">Fire Touched &#8211; Patricia Briggs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dark Tower IV: Wizard and Glass : (Volume 4) &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-dark-tower-iv-wizard-and-glass-volume-4-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dark-tower-iv-wizard-and-glass-volume-4-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WIZARD AND GLASS is the fourth volume in Stephen King&#8217;s epic Dark Tower series. The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba. In the fourth novel in Stephen King&#8217;s bestselling fantasy quest, the Dark Tower beckons Roland, the Last Gunslinger, and the four companions he has gathered along [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-tower-iv-wizard-and-glass-volume-4-stephen-king/">The Dark Tower IV: Wizard and Glass : (Volume 4) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WIZARD AND GLASS is the fourth volume in Stephen King&#8217;s epic Dark Tower series.  The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba.</p>
<p>                    In the fourth novel in Stephen King&#8217;s bestselling fantasy quest, the Dark Tower beckons Roland, the Last Gunslinger, and the four companions he has gathered along the road.</p>
<p>                    In a terrifying journey where hidden dangers lurk at every junction, the pilgrims find themselves stranded in an alternate version of Topeka, Kansas, that has been ravaged by a superflu virus.</p>
<p>                    While following the deserted highway toward a distant glass palace, Roland recounts his tragic story about a seaside town called Hambry, where he fell in love with a girl named Susan Delgado and where he and his old tet-mates Alain and Cuthbert battled the forces of an evil harrier who ignited Mid-World&#8217;s final war. </p>
<p>                    JOIN THE QUEST FOR THE DARK TOWER&#8230;</p>
<p>                    THE DARK TOWER SERIES:<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER I: THE GUNSLINGER<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER II: THE DRAWING OF THE THREE<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER III: THE WASTE LANDS<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER IV: WIZARD AND GLASS<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER V: WOLVES OF THE CALLA<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER VI: SONG OF SUSANNAH<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER VII: THE DARK TOWER<br />
                     THE WIND THROUGH THE KEYHOLE: A DARK TOWER NOVEL</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-tower-iv-wizard-and-glass-volume-4-stephen-king/">The Dark Tower IV: Wizard and Glass : (Volume 4) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cujo &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/cujo-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cujo-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a stunning new cover look, King&#8217;s classic tale of survival sees a young mother and her son trapped in a car by a horrifyingly familiar monster. Once upon a time, not so long ago, a monster came to the small town of Castle Rock, Maine . . . Cujo is a huge Saint Bernard [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cujo-stephen-king/">Cujo &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a stunning new cover look, King&#8217;s classic tale of survival sees a young mother and her son trapped in a car by a horrifyingly familiar monster.    </p>
<p>                    Once upon a time, not so long ago, a monster came to the small town of Castle Rock, Maine . . .    </p>
<p>                    Cujo is a huge Saint Bernard dog, the best friend Brett Camber has ever had.  Then one day Cujo chases a rabbit into a bolt-hole. Except it isn&#8217;t a rabbit warren any more. It is a cave inhabited by rabid bats.    </p>
<p>                    And Cujo falls sick. Very sick. And the gentle giant who once protected the family becomes a vortex of horror inexorably drawing in all the people around him . . .    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cujo-stephen-king/">Cujo &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Girl Next Door &#8211; Jack Ketchum</title>
		<link>/the-girl-next-door-jack-ketchum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-girl-next-door-jack-ketchum/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A teenage girl is held captive and brutally tortured by neighborhood children. Based on a true story, this shocking novel reveals the depravity of which we are all capable. This novel contains graphic content and is recommended for regular readers of horror novels.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-girl-next-door-jack-ketchum/">The Girl Next Door &#8211; Jack Ketchum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A teenage girl is held captive and brutally tortured by neighborhood children. Based on a true story, this shocking novel reveals the depravity of which we are all capable.    </p>
<p>                    This novel contains graphic content and is recommended for regular readers of horror novels.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-girl-next-door-jack-ketchum/">The Girl Next Door &#8211; Jack Ketchum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secret Window, Secret Garden : Two Past Midnight &#8211; James Woods</title>
		<link>/secret-window-secret-garden-two-past-midnight-james-woods/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/secret-window-secret-garden-two-past-midnight-james-woods/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The second of a four-part audio series from Stephen King s bestselling book, Four Past Midnight. Recently divorced writer Mort Rainey is alone at Tashmore Lakethat is, until a figure named John Shooter arrives, pointing an accusing finger.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secret-window-secret-garden-two-past-midnight-james-woods/">Secret Window, Secret Garden : Two Past Midnight &#8211; James Woods</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The second of a four-part audio series from Stephen King s bestselling book, Four Past Midnight. Recently divorced writer Mort Rainey is alone at Tashmore Lakethat is, until a figure named John Shooter arrives, pointing an accusing finger.&#8221;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secret-window-secret-garden-two-past-midnight-james-woods/">Secret Window, Secret Garden : Two Past Midnight &#8211; James Woods</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Shining &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-shining-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-shining-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Before Doctor Sleep, there was The Shining, a classic of modern American horror from the undisputed master, Stephen King. Jack Torrance&#8217;s new job at the Overlook Hotel is the perfect chance for a fresh start. As the off-season caretaker at the atmospheric old hotel, he&#8217;ll have plenty of time [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-shining-stephen-king/">The Shining &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Before Doctor Sleep, there was The Shining, a classic of modern American horror from the undisputed master, Stephen King.     </p>
<p>                    Jack Torrance&#8217;s new job at the Overlook Hotel is the perfect chance for a fresh start. As the off-season caretaker at the atmospheric old hotel, he&#8217;ll have plenty of time to spend reconnecting with his family and working on his writing. But as the harsh winter weather sets in, the idyllic location feels ever more remote . . . and more sinister. And the only one to notice the strange and terrible forces gathering around the Overlook is Danny Torrance, a uniquely gifted five-year-old.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-shining-stephen-king/">The Shining &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rabbit Hunter &#8211; Lars Kepler</title>
		<link>/the-rabbit-hunter-lars-kepler/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rabbit-hunter-lars-kepler/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The sixth gripping thriller in Lars Kepler&#8217;s bestselling series featuring Joona Linna. Perfect for fans of Stieg Larsson and Jo Nesbo. There&#8217;s a face at the window. A stranger wearing a mask stands in the shadow of a garden. He&#8217;s watching his first victim through the window. He will kill him slowly, make it last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rabbit-hunter-lars-kepler/">The Rabbit Hunter &#8211; Lars Kepler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The sixth gripping thriller in Lars Kepler&#8217;s bestselling series featuring Joona Linna. Perfect for fans of Stieg Larsson and Jo Nesbo.</p>
<p>                              There&#8217;s a face at the window.<br />
                    A stranger wearing a mask stands in the shadow of a garden. He&#8217;s watching his first victim through the window. He will kill him slowly, make it last &#8211; play him a nursery rhyme &#8211; make him pay.</p>
<p>                              A killer in your house.<br />
                    There&#8217;s only one person the police can turn to &#8211; ex-Detective Joona Linna &#8211; but he&#8217;s serving time in a high-security prison. So they offer him a chance to secure his freedom: help Superintendent Saga Bauer track down the vicious killer known as the Rabbit Hunter, before he strikes again.</p>
<p>                              Only one man can stop him.<br />
                    Soon another three victims have been murdered and Stockholm is in the grip of terror. Joona Linna must catch a disturbed predator, whose trail of destruction leads back to one horrific night of violence &#8211; with consequences more terrifying than anyone could have imagined&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rabbit-hunter-lars-kepler/">The Rabbit Hunter &#8211; Lars Kepler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Accidental Mermaid &#8211; Hollie Jackson, Dakota Cassidy</title>
		<link>/the-accidental-mermaid-hollie-jackson-dakota-cassidy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-accidental-mermaid-hollie-jackson-dakota-cassidy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Esther Williams Sanchez is busy living her life the way she&#8217;s always done. Spending time with her pets, working as a divorce mediator, and enjoying her newly renovated cottage on the beach. She&#8217;s also decided it&#8217;s high time she learn how to swim to prepare for an upcoming cruise. It&#8217;s time to let go of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-mermaid-hollie-jackson-dakota-cassidy/">The Accidental Mermaid &#8211; Hollie Jackson, Dakota Cassidy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Esther Williams Sanchez is busy living her life the way she&#8217;s always done. Spending time with her pets, working as a divorce mediator, and enjoying her newly renovated cottage on the beach. She&#8217;s also decided it&#8217;s high time she learn how to swim to prepare for an upcoming cruise. It&#8217;s time to let go of a horrible past experience and take some lessons. So at thirty-two, Esther enrolls in the only class at the Y with a spot left. A Mommy and Me class-which seems quite tame, considering her oldest classmate aside from her is three-years-old. Learn to swim with a bunch of babies and toddlers? Easy-squeezy, right? Er, no. As Esther leaves the pool after her very first lesson, she sprouts a magnificent tail and fins. Oh, and hair the color of a rainbow. Lots and lots of luscious hair. Lucky for her, the OOPS girls are on site, and as they set about finding out how this happened to Esther, they run into a hunky Australian merman named Tucker Pearson who happens to be the key to Esther&#8217;s problem. But Tucker has problems of his own, and they include being kicked out of his family&#8217;s bottled water company, booted from his pod, and accused of embezzling over a million bucks. Oh, and killing someone . . . OOPS, here we go again!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-mermaid-hollie-jackson-dakota-cassidy/">The Accidental Mermaid &#8211; Hollie Jackson, Dakota Cassidy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Two Lost Mountains : An Action-Packed Jack West Thriller &#8211; Matthew Reilly</title>
		<link>/the-two-lost-mountains-an-action-packed-jack-west-thriller-matthew-reilly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Egyptian Archaeology / Egyptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Underwater Archaeology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-two-lost-mountains-an-action-packed-jack-west-thriller-matthew-reilly/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE HOTTEST ACTION WRITER AROUND&#8217; EVENING TELEGRAPH THE LATEST ADVENTURE IN THE WILDLY ENTERTAINING, ACTION-PACKED JACK WEST SERIES Former SAS soldier Jack West is on a mission to save the world, no matter what &#8211; or who &#8211; it might cost him. Still reeling from the loss of his daughter, and with his rivals far [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-two-lost-mountains-an-action-packed-jack-west-thriller-matthew-reilly/">The Two Lost Mountains : An Action-Packed Jack West Thriller &#8211; Matthew Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE HOTTEST ACTION WRITER AROUND&#8217; EVENING TELEGRAPH<br />
                    THE LATEST ADVENTURE IN THE WILDLY ENTERTAINING, ACTION-PACKED JACK WEST SERIES</p>
<p>                    Former SAS soldier Jack West is on a mission to save the world, no matter what &#8211; or who &#8211; it might cost him.</p>
<p>                    Still reeling from the loss of his daughter, and with his rivals far ahead of him, Jack must race across the globe to complete the ancient Trial of the Mountains.</p>
<p>                    With the odds already against them, Jack and his crew will soon discover that a new player has entered the race, a general so feared that he had been locked away in the deepest of dungeons.</p>
<p>                    Only now this general has escaped and he has a horrifying plan of his own&#8230;</p>
<p>                    * * * * *</p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR THE JACK WEST THRILLERS<br />
                    &#8216;An action hero worthy of Lee Child&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling, action-packed adventure from cover to cover&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Nobody writes action like Matthew Reilly&#8217; Vince Flynn</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Get ready for a wild ride&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Exciting and entertaining&#8217; Chicago Sun-Times</p>
<p>                    * * * * *</p>
<p>                    READERS LOVE THE JACK WEST THRILLERS</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Indiana Jones in a book . . . Immensely entertaining&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A super duper kick ass soldier&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A first class all-action historical thriller&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Heart-pounding stuff&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Enjoy the rollercoaster ride&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-two-lost-mountains-an-action-packed-jack-west-thriller-matthew-reilly/">The Two Lost Mountains : An Action-Packed Jack West Thriller &#8211; Matthew Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crimson Death &#8211; Laurell K. Hamilton</title>
		<link>/crimson-death-laurell-k-hamilton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crimson-death-laurell-k-hamilton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In her twenty-fifth adventure, vampire hunter and necromancer Anita Blake learns that evil is in the eye of the beholder&#8230; Anita has never seen Damian, her vampire servant, in such a state. The rising sun doesn&#8217;t usher in the peaceful death that he desperately needs. Instead, he&#8217;s being bombarded with violent nightmares and blood sweats. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crimson-death-laurell-k-hamilton/">Crimson Death &#8211; Laurell K. Hamilton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In her twenty-fifth adventure, vampire hunter and necromancer Anita Blake learns that evil is in the eye of the beholder&#8230;    </p>
<p>                     Anita has never seen Damian, her vampire servant, in such a state. The rising sun doesn&#8217;t usher in the peaceful death that he desperately needs. Instead, he&#8217;s being bombarded with violent nightmares and blood sweats.     </p>
<p>                     And now, with Damian at his most vulnerable, Anita needs him the most. The vampire who created him, who subjected him to centuries of torture, might be losing control, allowing rogue vampires to run wild and break one of their kind&#8217;s few strict taboos.     </p>
<p>                     Some say love is a great motivator, but hatred gets the job done, too. And when Anita joins forces with her friend Edward to stop the carnage, Damian will be at their side, even if it means traveling back to the land where all his nightmares spring from&#8230;a place that couldn&#8217;t be less welcoming to a vampire, an assassin, and a necromancer: Ireland.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crimson-death-laurell-k-hamilton/">Crimson Death &#8211; Laurell K. Hamilton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Newly Witch Game : Magic and Mayhem Universe: Magic and Mayhem, Book Ten &#8211; Robyn Peterman</title>
		<link>/the-newly-witch-game-magic-and-mayhem-universe-magic-and-mayhem-book-ten-robyn-peterman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-newly-witch-game-magic-and-mayhem-universe-magic-and-mayhem-book-ten-robyn-peterman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s all fun and games until someone throws a dirty jumper rollup and you lose out in the Cornhole tournament of life. According to Baba Yoscarybutt, it&#8217;s time for me to witch up or step back down into the Cornholio minor leagues. While Cornhole is definitely not my beanbag, I can&#8217;t stand to lose. I [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-newly-witch-game-magic-and-mayhem-universe-magic-and-mayhem-book-ten-robyn-peterman/">The Newly Witch Game : Magic and Mayhem Universe: Magic and Mayhem, Book Ten &#8211; Robyn Peterman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s all fun and games until someone throws a dirty jumper rollup and you lose out in the Cornhole tournament of life.    </p>
<p>                    According to Baba Yoscarybutt, it&#8217;s time for me to witch up or step back down into the Cornholio minor leagues. While Cornhole is definitely not my beanbag, I can&#8217;t stand to lose.    </p>
<p>                    I don&#8217;t want to be the next Baba Yaga. I&#8217;m doing just peachy as the Shifter Wanker who heals the clumsy idiots of Assjacket, West Virginia. I love my life. My werewolf mate is hotter than asphalt in August, my twins are adorable, my dad and brother rock, and I have real friends for the first time in my life.    </p>
<p>                    However, when my evil nemesis, Medusa Jones, steps up to throw a floppy bag and steal the title of Future Baba Yaga from me, all bets are off.    </p>
<p>                    I will challenge the nasty piece of work to win back the job I didn&#8217;t want in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    With Sassy and Fuc*ing Derrick by my side, I will finally own my destiny. Of course, Fuc*ing Derrick is prone to meltdowns and Sassy is trying to learn Canadian, but one deals with the floppy bags they&#8217;ve been dealt and tosses them anyway.    </p>
<p>                    It will be dangerous.    </p>
<p>                    It will be cornfusing.    </p>
<p>                    It will be fashionably disastrous.    </p>
<p>                    It will be televised on the magical Charm Channel.    </p>
<p>                    Whatever. A few four baggers, a couple of woodies, a Bigfoot and spell or two should do the trick.    </p>
<p>                    The future of the magical Universe is on the line and I&#8217;m the only one who can save us.    </p>
<p>                    May the Goddess help us all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-newly-witch-game-magic-and-mayhem-universe-magic-and-mayhem-book-ten-robyn-peterman/">The Newly Witch Game : Magic and Mayhem Universe: Magic and Mayhem, Book Ten &#8211; Robyn Peterman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark Tower I: The Gunslinger : (Volume 1) &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/dark-tower-i-the-gunslinger-volume-1-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-tower-i-the-gunslinger-volume-1-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba. &#8216;The man in black fled across the desert, and the gunslinger followed.&#8217; The iconic opening line of Stephen King&#8217;s groundbreaking series, The Dark Tower, introduces one of his most enigmatic and powerful heroes: Roland of Gilead, the Last Gunslinger. Roland [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-tower-i-the-gunslinger-volume-1-stephen-king/">Dark Tower I: The Gunslinger : (Volume 1) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The man in black fled across the desert, and the gunslinger followed.&#8217; The iconic opening line of Stephen King&#8217;s groundbreaking series, The Dark Tower, introduces one of his most enigmatic and powerful heroes: Roland of Gilead, the Last Gunslinger. </p>
<p>                    Roland is a haunting figure, a loner, on a spellbinding journey toward the mysterious Dark Tower, in a desolate world which frighteningly echoes our own. </p>
<p>                    On his quest, Roland begins a friendship with a kid from New York named Jake, encounters an alluring woman and faces an agonising choice between damnation and salvation as he pursues the Man in Black.</p>
<p>                    JOIN THE QUEST FOR THE DARK TOWER&#8230;</p>
<p>                    THE DARK TOWER SERIES:<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER I: THE GUNSLINGER<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER II: THE DRAWING OF THE THREE<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER III: THE WASTE LANDS<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER IV: WIZARD AND GLASS<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER V: WOLVES OF THE CALLA<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER VI: SONG OF SUSANNAH<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER VII: THE DARK TOWER<br />
                    THE WIND THROUGH THE KEYHOLE: A DARK TOWER NOVEL</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-tower-i-the-gunslinger-volume-1-stephen-king/">Dark Tower I: The Gunslinger : (Volume 1) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Cabin at the End of the World &#8211; Paul Tremblay</title>
		<link>/the-cabin-at-the-end-of-the-world-paul-tremblay/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-cabin-at-the-end-of-the-world-paul-tremblay/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Bram Stoker Award for Superior Achievement in a Novel 2019 &#8211; The Cabin at the End of the World adds an inventive twist to the home invasion horror story in a heart-palpitating novel of psychological suspense. Seven-year-old Wen and her parents, Eric and Andrew, are vacationing at a remote cabin on a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-cabin-at-the-end-of-the-world-paul-tremblay/">The Cabin at the End of the World &#8211; Paul Tremblay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Bram Stoker Award for Superior Achievement in a Novel 2019 &#8211; The Cabin at the End of the World adds an inventive twist to the home invasion horror story in a heart-palpitating novel of psychological suspense.</p>
<p>                    Seven-year-old Wen and her parents, Eric and Andrew, are vacationing at a remote cabin on a quiet New Hampshire lake, with their closest neighbours more than two miles in either direction.</p>
<p>                    As Wen catches grasshoppers in the front yard, a stranger unexpectedly appears in the driveway. Leonard is the largest man Wen has ever seen but he is young and friendly. Leonard and Wen talk and play until Leonard abruptly apologises and tells Wen, &#8220;None of what&#8217;s going to happen is your fault&#8221;. Three more strangers arrive at the cabin carrying unidentifiable, menacing objects. As Wen sprints inside to warn her parents, Leonard calls out, &#8220;Your dads won&#8217;t want to let us in, Wen. But they have to. We need your help to save the world.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    So begins an unbearably tense, gripping tale of paranoia, sacrifice, apocalypse, and survival that escalates to a shattering conclusion, one in which the fate of a loving family and quite possibly all of humanity are intertwined.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-cabin-at-the-end-of-the-world-paul-tremblay/">The Cabin at the End of the World &#8211; Paul Tremblay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lie In Wait &#8211; Eric Rickstad</title>
		<link>/lie-in-wait-eric-rickstad/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lie-in-wait-eric-rickstad/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times and USA Today bestselling author of The Silent Girls comes another unforgettable thriller set in Vermont&#8217;s Northeast Kingdom, featuring Detective Sonja Test Even in a quiet Vermont town, unspeakable acts of the past can destroy the peace of the present. In the remote pastoral hamlet of Canaan, Vermont, a high-profile [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lie-in-wait-eric-rickstad/">Lie In Wait &#8211; Eric Rickstad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times and USA Today bestselling author of The Silent Girls comes another unforgettable thriller set in Vermont&#8217;s Northeast Kingdom, featuring Detective Sonja Test  Even in a quiet Vermont town, unspeakable acts of the past can destroy the peace of the present.  In the remote pastoral hamlet of Canaan, Vermont, a high-profile legal case shatters the town&#8217;s sense of peace and community. Anger simmers. Fear and prejudice awaken. Old friends turn on each other. Violence threatens.  So when a young teenage girl is savagely murdered while babysitting at the house of the lead attorney in the case, Detective Sonja Test believes the girl&#8217;s murder and the divisive case must be linked.  However, as the young detective digs deeper into her first murder case, she discovers sordid acts hidden for decades, and learns that behind the town&#8217;s idyllic facade of pristine snow lurks a capacity in some for great darkness and the betrayal of innocents. And Sonja Test, a mother of two, will do anything to protect the innocent.  &#8220;Gripping, topical, and wrenching-everything you want in a top-flight mystery.&#8221;-Meg Gardiner, Edgar(R) Award-winning Author</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lie-in-wait-eric-rickstad/">Lie In Wait &#8211; Eric Rickstad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myth Manifestation &#8211; Johanna Parker, Lisa Shearin</title>
		<link>/the-myth-manifestation-johanna-parker-lisa-shearin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myth-manifestation-johanna-parker-lisa-shearin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The agents of Supernatural Protection &#038; Investigations (SPI) protect people from predatory supernaturals. This time, we&#8217;re the ones who need protection. New York is one of the most popular convention destinations in the world&#8211;for humans and supernaturals. Every hundred years, rulers of the world&#8217;s supernatural races come together to negotiate and renew a peace treaty. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-manifestation-johanna-parker-lisa-shearin/">The Myth Manifestation &#8211; Johanna Parker, Lisa Shearin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The agents of Supernatural Protection &#038; Investigations (SPI) protect people from predatory supernaturals. This time, we&#8217;re the ones who need protection.     </p>
<p>                    New York is one of the most popular convention destinations in the world&#8211;for humans and supernaturals. Every hundred years, rulers of the world&#8217;s supernatural races come together to negotiate and renew a peace treaty. Meeting in the same hotel are the governors of our world&#8217;s goblin and elf colonies. SPI is saddled with the security nightmare of keeping the living delegates alive and the undead delegates from becoming permanently deceased. We&#8217;ve got our work cut out for us.     </p>
<p>                    I&#8217;m Makenna Fraser, seer for SPI. Our security nightmare becomes real when monsters from the delegates&#8217; mythologies begin mysteriously appearing in the flesh to hunt delegates from every side of the debate. And when the hotel gets sucked into another dimension, there&#8217;s no escape. We discover that we&#8217;re all pieces in an elaborate and deadly game. A game about to spill out into the real world. Failing to escape is game over and not an option. We have to save the world&#8211;but first, we have to save ourselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-manifestation-johanna-parker-lisa-shearin/">The Myth Manifestation &#8211; Johanna Parker, Lisa Shearin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Brightest Embers Lib/E &#8211; Jeaniene Frost, Read by Tavia Gilbert</title>
		<link>/the-brightest-embers-lib-e-jeaniene-frost-read-by-tavia-gilbert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-brightest-embers-lib-e-jeaniene-frost-read-by-tavia-gilbert/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You can run from your destiny, but you can&#8217;t hide &#8230; Ivy thought that she and Adrian had conquered their fates. Yet with thousands of innocents still trapped in the demon realms, she&#8217;s determined to locate the final hallowed weapon and harness its unparalleled power to free them. But the last relic nearly put Ivy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brightest-embers-lib-e-jeaniene-frost-read-by-tavia-gilbert/">The Brightest Embers Lib/E &#8211; Jeaniene Frost, Read by Tavia Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You can run from your destiny, but you can&#8217;t hide &#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Ivy thought that she and Adrian had conquered their fates. Yet with thousands of innocents still trapped in the demon realms, she&#8217;s determined to locate the final hallowed weapon and harness its unparalleled power to free them. But the last relic nearly put Ivy in the grave-there&#8217;s probably no coming back from this one.     </p>
<p>                    Adrian&#8217;s dark lineage has made him the most powerful of his kind, yet even his incredible abilities might not be enough now. Instead, the treacherous fate he has fought so hard to escape might be the only way he can save Ivy. Their scintillating bond has been tested before, but never with so much on the line. Now fate will come head-to-head against true love, and nothing they&#8217;ve endured can prepare Ivy and Adrian for the unthinkable choices they&#8217;ll face.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brightest-embers-lib-e-jeaniene-frost-read-by-tavia-gilbert/">The Brightest Embers Lib/E &#8211; Jeaniene Frost, Read by Tavia Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moonshadow &#8211; Thea Harrison</title>
		<link>/moonshadow-thea-harrison/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/moonshadow-thea-harrison/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From bestselling author Thea Harrison comes the first in an explosive new trilogy set in the Elder Races world&#8230;. Her past is a blank, her future uncertain&#8230;. Recovering from a shooting, LAPD witch consultant Sophie Ross leaves her job and travels to the U.K. to search for answers about her childhood. When she encounters a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moonshadow-thea-harrison/">Moonshadow &#8211; Thea Harrison</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From bestselling author Thea Harrison comes the first in an explosive new trilogy set in the Elder Races world&#8230;.    </p>
<p>                    Her past is a blank, her future uncertain&#8230;.    </p>
<p>                    Recovering from a shooting, LAPD witch consultant Sophie Ross leaves her job and travels to the U.K. to search for answers about her childhood. When she encounters a Daoine Sidhe knight of the Dark Court, she becomes entangled in an ancient hatred between two arcane forces.    </p>
<p>                    He has given his body and soul to fight for his people&#8230;.    </p>
<p>                    Barred from his homeland along with his surviving brother knights, Nikolas Sevigny is embroiled in a conflict that threatens everything he holds dear. Only by uniting his people&#8217;s resources can they hope to prevail against Isabeau, the deadly Queen of the Light Court. He will do anything and use anyone to return home to Lyonesse.    </p>
<p>                    When Nikolas encounters Sophie, he sees a tool to be used. The insouciant witch might be the key to unlocking every passageway that has been barred to the knights of the Dark Court, even as a fascination for her takes root in what&#8217;s left of his soul.    </p>
<p>                    Sophie has no intention of becoming anyone&#8217;s pawn, yet the fierce Nikolas is so compelling, she can&#8217;t deny the temptation that endangers her guarded heart.    </p>
<p>                    As magic threatens Lyonesse, Queen Isabeau unleashes her merciless Hounds, and Nikolas and Sophie become embroiled in a race for survival. Meanwhile, the passion that ignites between them burns too hot to be denied and quickly turns into obsession.    </p>
<p>                    Thank goodness they both know better than to fall in love&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moonshadow-thea-harrison/">Moonshadow &#8211; Thea Harrison</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dark Tower VII: The Dark Tower : (Volume 7) &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-dark-tower-vii-the-dark-tower-volume-7-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Novels: Superheroes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dark-tower-vii-the-dark-tower-volume-7-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE DARK TOWER is the seventh volume in Stephen King&#8217;s epic Dark Tower series. The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba. The final book in King&#8217;s epic The Dark Tower series, sees gunslinger Roland on a roller-coaster ride of exhilarating triumph and aching loss in his unrelenting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-tower-vii-the-dark-tower-volume-7-stephen-king/">The Dark Tower VII: The Dark Tower : (Volume 7) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE DARK TOWER is the seventh volume in Stephen King&#8217;s epic Dark Tower series.  The Dark Tower is now a major motion picture starring Matthew McConaughey and Idris Elba.</p>
<p>                    The final book in King&#8217;s epic The Dark Tower series, sees gunslinger Roland on a roller-coaster ride of exhilarating triumph and aching loss in his unrelenting quest to reach the dark tower.</p>
<p>                    Roland Deschain and his ka-tet have journeyed together and apart, scattered far and wide across multilayered worlds of wheres and whens. The destinies of Roland, Susannah, Jake, Father Callahan, Oy, and Eddie are bound in the Dark Tower itself, which now pulls them ever closer to their own endings and beginnings and into a maelstrom of emotion, violence, and discovery.</p>
<p>                    And as he closes in on the Tower, Roland&#8217;s every step is shadowed by a terrible and sinister creation. Finally, he realises, he may have to walk the last dark strait alone&#8230;</p>
<p>                     JOIN THE QUEST FOR THE DARK TOWER&#8230;</p>
<p>                    THE DARK TOWER SERIES:<br />
                    THE DARK TOWER I: THE GUNSLINGER<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER II: THE DRAWING OF THE THREE<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER III: THE WASTE LANDS<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER IV: WIZARD AND GLASS<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER V: WOLVES OF THE CALLA<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER VI: SONG OF SUSANNAH<br />
                     THE DARK TOWER VII: THE DARK TOWER<br />
                     THE WIND THROUGH THE KEYHOLE: A DARK TOWER NOVEL</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dark-tower-vii-the-dark-tower-volume-7-stephen-king/">The Dark Tower VII: The Dark Tower : (Volume 7) &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Terror : A Novel &#8211; Dan Simmons</title>
		<link>/the-terror-a-novel-dan-simmons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-terror-a-novel-dan-simmons/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dan Simmons writes with the salty grace and precision of Patrick O&#8217;Brian. But in piling supernatural nightmare upon historical nightmare, layering mystery upon mystery, he has produced a turbocharged vision of popular doom.&#8221; -Men&#8217;s JournalGreeted with excited critical praise, this extraordinary novel-inspired by the true story of two ice ships that disappeared in the Arctic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-terror-a-novel-dan-simmons/">The Terror : A Novel &#8211; Dan Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dan Simmons writes with the salty grace and precision of Patrick O&#8217;Brian. But in piling supernatural nightmare upon historical nightmare, layering mystery upon mystery, he has produced a turbocharged vision of popular doom.&#8221; -Men&#8217;s JournalGreeted with excited critical praise, this extraordinary novel-inspired by the true story of two ice ships that disappeared in the Arctic Circle during an 1845 expedition-swells with the heart-stopping suspense and heroic adventure that have won Dan Simmons praise as &#8220;a writer who not only makes big promises but keeps them&#8221; (Seattle Post-Intelligencer). THE TERROR chills readers to the core.&#8221;Brutal, relentless, yet oddly uplifting, THE TERROR is a masterfully chilling work.&#8221; -Entertainment Weekly&#8221;In the hands of a lesser writer than Dan Simmons, THE TERROR might well have dissolved into a series of frigid days and three-dog nights. But Simmons is too good a writer to ignore the real gold in his story-its beleaguered cast.&#8221; -Bookpage&#8221;Guaranteed to have readers pulling their covers up to their noses, THE TERROR will make for a blood-freezing, bedtime read this winter-and any season thereafter.&#8221; -Pages    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-terror-a-novel-dan-simmons/">The Terror : A Novel &#8211; Dan Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tommyknockers &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/the-tommyknockers-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UFOs & Extraterrestrial Beings]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tommyknockers-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everything is familiar. But everything has changed. Coming back to the little community is like walking into a nightmare for Jim Gardener, poet, drunk, potential suicide. It all looks the same, the house, the furniture, Jim&#8217;s friend Bobbi, her beagle (though ageing), even the woods out at the back. But it was in the woods [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tommyknockers-stephen-king/">The Tommyknockers &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything is familiar. But everything has changed.    </p>
<p>                    Coming back to the little community is like walking into a nightmare for Jim Gardener, poet, drunk, potential suicide.    </p>
<p>                    It all looks the same, the house, the furniture, Jim&#8217;s friend Bobbi, her beagle (though ageing), even the woods out at the back.    </p>
<p>                    But it was in the woods that Bobbi stumbled over the odd, part-buried object and felt a peculiar tingle as she brushed the soft earth away.    </p>
<p>                    Everything is familiar. But everything is about to change.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tommyknockers-stephen-king/">The Tommyknockers &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
