<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Coping With Old Age Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/coping-with-old-age/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/coping-with-old-age/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Coping With Old Age Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/coping-with-old-age/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ageless Soul : An uplifting meditation on the art of growing older &#8211; Thomas Moore</title>
		<link>/ageless-soul-an-uplifting-meditation-on-the-art-of-growing-older-thomas-moore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Body]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ageless-soul-an-uplifting-meditation-on-the-art-of-growing-older-thomas-moore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF CARE OF THE SOUL COMES AN UPLIFTING MEDITATION ON THE ART OF GROWING OLDER &#8216;Thomas Moore convinces us that we age best when we embrace our age, live agelessly, and remember every day to find the endless joy nestled inside our soul&#8217; Dr Rudolph E. Tanzi, Professor [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ageless-soul-an-uplifting-meditation-on-the-art-of-growing-older-thomas-moore/">Ageless Soul : An uplifting meditation on the art of growing older &#8211; Thomas Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF CARE OF THE SOUL COMES AN UPLIFTING MEDITATION ON THE ART OF GROWING OLDER </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Thomas Moore convinces us that we age best when we embrace our age, live agelessly, and remember every day to find the endless joy nestled inside our soul&#8217;<br />
                    Dr Rudolph E. Tanzi, Professor of Neurology, Harvard Medical School,  and New York Times bestselling author of Super Brain and Super Genes</p>
<p>                    Ageless Soul reveals a fresh, optimistic and rewarding path towards ageing. Renowned psychotherapist and bestselling author Thomas Moore shows us that as we grow older we become more distinctive and complex.</p>
<p>                     Drawing on stories from his practice as a psychotherapist and teacher, Moore argues for a new vision of ageing and shows readers how to embrace the richness of the experience and how to feel fulfilled as they grow older.</p>
<p>                    Thomas Moore is the New York Times bestselling author of Care of the Soul,as well as many other books on enriching your life. At turns he has been a monk, a musician, a university professor, and a psychotherapist. Today he lectures widely on creating a more soulful world and on spirituality.</p>
<p>                      &#8216;With Ageless Soul, Thomas Moore extends a magnificent invitation to reflect, grow up with joy and intention, and give back with an open heart. Accept and pleasure follows.&#8217;<br />
                    Marc Freedman, founder and CEO of Encore.org and author of The Big Shift</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ageless-soul-an-uplifting-meditation-on-the-art-of-growing-older-thomas-moore/">Ageless Soul : An uplifting meditation on the art of growing older &#8211; Thomas Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pensions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface* Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time? Many of us have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface*    </p>
<p>                    Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time?     </p>
<p>                    Many of us have been raised on the traditional notion of a three-stage approach to our working lives: education, followed by work and then retirement.  But this well-established pathway is already beginning to collapse &#8211; life expectancy is rising, final-salary pensions are vanishing, and increasing numbers of people are juggling multiple careers. Whether you are 18, 45 or 60, you will need to do things very differently from previous generations and learn to structure your life in completely new ways.    </p>
<p>                    The 100-Year Life is here to help.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the unique pairing of their experience in psychology and economics, Lynda Gratton and Andrew J. Scott offer a broad-ranging analysis as well as a raft of solutions, showing how to rethink your finances, your education, your career and your relationships and create a fulfilling 100-year life.     </p>
<p>                    * How can you fashion a career and life path that defines you and your values and creates a shifting balance between work and leisure?    </p>
<p>                    * What are the most effective ways of boosting your physical and mental health over a longer and more dynamic lifespan?    </p>
<p>                    * How can you make the most of your intangible assets &#8211; such as family and friends &#8211; as you build a productive, longer life?    </p>
<p>                    * In a multiple-stage life how can you learn to make the transitions that will be so crucial and experiment with new ways of living, working and learning?    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award and featuring a new preface, The 100-Year Life is a wake-up call that describes what to expect and considers the choices and options that you will face. It is also fundamentally a call to action for individuals, politicians, firms and governments and offers the clearest demonstration that a 100-year life can be a wonderful and inspiring one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maturation & Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life. From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life.    </p>
<p>                    From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of his career. He knows that everyone thinks they want to live forever, until they hit middle age and witness the suffering of their parents and even their peers. So how do we solve the paradox of wanting to live to a ripe old age-but enjoy the benefits of youth?    </p>
<p>                    This groundbreaking book holds the answer. Working with thousands of patients, Dr. Gundry has discovered that the &#8220;diseases of aging&#8221; we most fear are not simply a function of age; rather, they are a byproduct of the way we have lived over the decades. In The Longevity Paradox, he maps out a new approach to aging well-one that is based on supporting the health of the &#8220;oldest&#8221; parts of us: the microorganisms that live within our bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Our gut bugs-the bacteria that make up the microbiome-largely determine our health over the years. From diseases like cancer and Alzheimer&#8217;s to common ailments like arthritis to our weight and the appearance of our skin, these bugs are in the driver&#8217;s seat, controlling our quality of life as we age.    </p>
<p>                    The good news is, it&#8217;s never too late to support these microbes and give them what they need to help them-and you-thrive. In The Longevity Paradox, Dr. Gundry outlines a nutrition and lifestyle plan to support gut health and live well for decades to come. A progressive take on the new science of aging, The Longevity Paradox offers an action plan to prevent and reverse disease as well as simple hacks to help anyone look and feel younger and more vital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age. Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age.    </p>
<p>                              Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more than twenty years, he has been on a quest to find innovative, science-backed methods to upgrade human biology and redefine the limits of the mind, body, and spirit. The results speak for themselves. Now in his forties, Dave is smarter, happier, and more fit and successful than ever before.    </p>
<p>                              In Super Human, he shows how this is level of health and performance possible for all of us. While we assume we will peak in middle age and then decline, Asprey&#8217;s research reveals there is another way. It is possible to make changes on the sub-cellular level to dramatically extend life span. And the tools to live longer also give you more energy and brainpower right now.    </p>
<p>                              The answers lie in Dave&#8217;s Seven Pillars of Ageing that contribute to degeneration and disease while diminishing your performance in the moment. Using simple interventions &#8211; like diet, sleep, light, exercise, and little-known but powerful hacks from ozone therapy to proper jaw alignment, you can decelerate cellular ageing and supercharge your body&#8217;s ability to heal and rejuvenate.    </p>
<p>                              A self-proclaimed human guinea pig, Asprey arms readers with practical advice to maximize their lives at every age with his signature mix of science-geek wonder, candour, and enthusiasm. Getting older no longer has to mean decline. Now it&#8217;s an opportunity to become Super Human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End : Practical Advice for Living Life and Facing Death &#8211; Dr Bj Miller, Shoshana Berger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-beginners-guide-to-the-end-practical-advice-for-living-life-and-facing-death-dr-bj-miller-shoshana-berger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Household Hints]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-beginners-guide-to-the-end-practical-advice-for-living-life-and-facing-death-dr-bj-miller-shoshana-berger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gentle, knowledgeable guide to a fate we all share&#8221; (The Washington Post): the first and only all-encompassing action plan for the end of life. &#8220;There is nothing wrong with you for dying,&#8221; hospice physician B.J. Miller and journalist and caregiver Shoshana Berger write in A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End. &#8220;Our ultimate purpose here [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-beginners-guide-to-the-end-practical-advice-for-living-life-and-facing-death-dr-bj-miller-shoshana-berger-abridged/">A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End : Practical Advice for Living Life and Facing Death &#8211; Dr Bj Miller, Shoshana Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gentle, knowledgeable guide to a fate we all share&#8221; (The Washington Post): the first and only all-encompassing action plan for the end of life.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There is nothing wrong with you for dying,&#8221; hospice physician B.J. Miller and journalist and caregiver Shoshana Berger write in A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End. &#8220;Our ultimate purpose here isn&#8217;t so much to help you die as it is to free up as much life as possible until you do.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Theirs is a clear-eyed and big-hearted action plan for approaching the end of life, written to help readers feel more in control of an experience that so often seems anything but controllable. Their book offers everything from step-by-step instructions for how to do your paperwork and navigate the healthcare system to answers to questions you might be afraid to ask your doctor, like whether or not sex is still okay when you&#8217;re sick. Get advice for how to break the news to your employer, whether to share old secrets with your family, how to face friends who might not be as empathetic as you&#8217;d hoped, and how to talk to your children about your will. (Don&#8217;t worry: if anyone gets snippy, it&#8217;ll likely be their spouses, not them.) There are also lessons for survivors, like how to shut down a loved one&#8217;s social media accounts, clean out the house, and write a great eulogy.     </p>
<p>                    An honest, surprising, and detail-oriented guide to the most universal of all experiences, A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End is &#8220;a book that every family should have, the equivalent of Dr. Spock but for this other phase of life&#8221; (New York Times bestselling author Dr. Abraham Verghese).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-beginners-guide-to-the-end-practical-advice-for-living-life-and-facing-death-dr-bj-miller-shoshana-berger-abridged/">A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End : Practical Advice for Living Life and Facing Death &#8211; Dr Bj Miller, Shoshana Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a New Afterword Must We Age? Nearly all scientists who study the biology of aging agree that we will someday be able to substantially slow down the aging process, extending our productive, youthful lives. Dr. Aubrey de Grey is perhaps the most bullish of all such researchers. As has been reported in media outlets [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/">Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a New Afterword     </p>
<p>                    Must We Age?     </p>
<p>                    Nearly all scientists who study the biology of aging agree that we will someday be able to substantially slow down the aging process, extending our productive, youthful lives. Dr. Aubrey de Grey is perhaps the most bullish of all such researchers. As has been reported in media outlets ranging from 60 Minutes to The New York Times,  Dr. de Grey believes that the key biomedical technology required to eliminate aging-derived debilitation and death entirely&#8211;technology that would not only slow but periodically reverse age-related physiological decay, leaving us biologically young into an indefinite future&#8211;is now within reach.     </p>
<p>                    In Ending Aging,  Dr. de Grey and his research assistant Michael Rae describe the details of this biotechnology. They explain that the aging of the human body, just like the aging of man-made machines, results from an accumulation of various types of damage. As with man-made machines, this damage can periodically be repaired, leading to indefinite extension of the machine&#8217;s fully functional lifetime, just as is routinely done with classic cars. We already know what types of damage accumulate in the human body, and we are moving rapidly toward the comprehensive development of technologies to remove that -damage. By demystifying aging and its postponement for the nonspecialist reader, de Grey and Rae systematically dismantle the fatalist presumption that aging will forever defeat the efforts of medical science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ending-aging-the-rejuvenation-breakthroughs-that-could-reverse-human-aging-in-our-lifetime-aubrey-de-grey-michael-rae-abridged/">Ending Aging : The Rejuvenation Breakthroughs That Could Reverse Human Aging in Our Lifetime &#8211; Aubrey De Grey, Michael Rae (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seven Sins of Memory Updated Edition : How the Mind Forgets and Remembers &#8211; Daniel L Schacter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seven-sins-of-memory-updated-edition-how-the-mind-forgets-and-remembers-daniel-l-schacter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seven-sins-of-memory-updated-edition-how-the-mind-forgets-and-remembers-daniel-l-schacter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>By one of the world&#8217;s foremost psychologists, a groundbreaking and award-winning study updated for the 20th anniversary with new research that delves into the complex behavior of memory Twenty years ago, The Seven Sins of Memory offered the first framework that explained common memory vices&#8211;and their surprising virtues. Now, in this updated edition, Daniel L. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seven-sins-of-memory-updated-edition-how-the-mind-forgets-and-remembers-daniel-l-schacter-abridged/">The Seven Sins of Memory Updated Edition : How the Mind Forgets and Remembers &#8211; Daniel L Schacter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By one of the world&#8217;s foremost psychologists, a groundbreaking and award-winning study updated for the 20th anniversary with new research that delves into the complex behavior of memory     </p>
<p>                    Twenty years ago, The Seven Sins of Memory offered the first framework that explained common memory vices&#8211;and their surprising virtues. Now, in this updated edition, Daniel L. Schacter revisits his groundbreaking research with the twenty-first century&#8217;s cultural trends and scientific discoveries. How does our ever-increasing reliance on Google, Instagram, and other websites harm our mind&#8217;s ability to store and retrieve memories? How has repeated exposure to &#8220;fake news&#8221; and other false statements increased our bias and made it easier for us to think these statements are true? Exploring the memory miscues that occur in everyday life&#8211;absentmindedness, transience, blocking, misattribution, suggestibility, bias, and persistence&#8211;Schacter delves into the striking scientific research, giving us a glimpse of the fascinating neurology of memory. Together, the stories and the scientific results provide a new look at our brains and at what we more generally think of as our minds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seven-sins-of-memory-updated-edition-how-the-mind-forgets-and-remembers-daniel-l-schacter-abridged/">The Seven Sins of Memory Updated Edition : How the Mind Forgets and Remembers &#8211; Daniel L Schacter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
