<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Web Programming Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/web-programming/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/web-programming/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Web Programming Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/web-programming/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lean UX is synonymous with modern product design and development. By combining human-centric design, agile ways of working, and a strong business sense, designers, product managers, developers, and scrum masters around the world are making Lean UX the leading approach for digital product teams today In the third edition of this award-winning book, authors Jeff [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/">Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lean UX is synonymous with modern product design and development. By combining human-centric design, agile ways of working, and a strong business sense, designers, product managers, developers, and scrum masters around the world are making Lean UX the leading approach for digital product teams today    </p>
<p>                    In the third edition of this award-winning book, authors Jeff Gothelf and Josh Seiden help you focus on the product experience rather than deliverables. You&#8217;ll learn tactics for integrating user experience design, product discovery, agile methods, and product management. And you&#8217;ll discover how to drive your design in short, iterative cycles to assess what works best for businesses and users. Lean UX guides you through this change&#8211;for the better.    </p>
<p>                    Facilitate the Lean UX process with your team with the Lean UX Canvas<br />
                    Ensure every project starts with clear customer-centric success criteria<br />
                    Understand the role of the designer on an agile team<br />
                    Write and contribute design and experiment stories to the backlog<br />
                    Ensure design work takes place in every sprint<br />
                    Build product discovery into the team&#8217;s &#8220;velocity&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/">Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want. Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want.    </p>
<p>                    Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, product managers, entrepreneurs, and aspiring strategists simple to advanced methods that can be applied right away. You&#8217;ll gain valuable perspective through business cases and historical context. This second edition includes new real-world examples, updated techniques, and a chapter on conducting qualitative online user research.    </p>
<p>                    Define value propositions and validate target users through provisional personas and customer discovery techniques<br />
                    Explore marketplace opportunities by conducting competitive research and analysis<br />
                    Design experiments using rapid prototypes that are focused on the business model<br />
                    Conduct online user research to gain valuable insights quickly on any budget<br />
                    Test business ideas and validate marketing channels by running online advertising and landing page campaigns</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Desktop Publishing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WE DESIGN TO ELICIT RESPONSES from people. We want them to buy something, read more, or take action of some kind. Designing without understanding what makes people act the way they do is like exploring a new city without a map: results will be haphazard, confusing, and inefficient. This book combines real science and research [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/">100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WE DESIGN TO ELICIT RESPONSES from people. We want them to buy something, read more, or take action of some kind. Designing without understanding what makes people act the way they do is like exploring a new city without a map: results will be haphazard, confusing, and inefficient. This book combines real science and research with practical examples to deliver a guide every designer needs. With this book you&#8217;ll design more intuitive and engaging apps, software, websites and products that match the way people think, decide and behave.    </p>
<p>                      INCREASE THE EFFECTIVENESS OF YOUR PRODUCTS.    </p>
<p>                      Apply psychology and behavioral science to your designs.    </p>
<p>                      Here are some of the questions this book will answer:    </p>
<p>                      * What grabs and holds attention.    </p>
<p>                      * What makes memories stick?    </p>
<p>                      * What is more important, peripheral or central vision?    </p>
<p>                      * Can you predict the types of errors people will make?    </p>
<p>                      * What is the limit to someone&#8217;s social circle?    </p>
<p>                      * What line length for text is best?    </p>
<p>                      * Are some fonts better than others?    </p>
<p>                      These are just a few of the questions that the book answers in its deep-dive exploration of what makes people tick.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/">100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on building a product that people will actually buy and use. By rigorously following the techniques described in Running Lean, you can eliminate waste &#8211; whether it&#8217;s time, money, effort, or all of the above &#8211; and get your product to market quickly. Refined through the real-world experiences of dozens of startup companies, these techniques are part of Eric Ries&#8217; Lean Startup methodology. Principles covered in this book include: * Find a problem worth solving, then define a solution * Demo before building * Pricing is part of the product * Maximize for speed, learning, and focus * Build a continuous feedback loop with customers throughout the product development cycle * Right Action, Right Time * Build a path to customers from day one</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
