<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Autobiography: Arts &amp; Entertainment Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/autobiography-arts-entertainment/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/autobiography-arts-entertainment/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:09:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Autobiography: Arts &amp; Entertainment Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/autobiography-arts-entertainment/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How to Fail : Everything I&#8217;Ve Ever Learned from Things Going Wrong &#8211; Elizabeth Day</title>
		<link>/how-to-fail-everything-ive-ever-learned-from-things-going-wrong-elizabeth-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-fail-everything-ive-ever-learned-from-things-going-wrong-elizabeth-day/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Inspired by her hugely popular podcast, How To Fail is Elizabeth Day&#8217;s brilliantly funny, painfully honest and insightful celebration of things going wrong. This is a book for anyone who has ever failed. Which means it&#8217;s a book for everyone. If I have learned one thing from this shockingly beautiful venture called life, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-everything-ive-ever-learned-from-things-going-wrong-elizabeth-day/">How to Fail : Everything I&#8217;Ve Ever Learned from Things Going Wrong &#8211; Elizabeth Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Inspired by her hugely popular podcast, How To Fail is Elizabeth Day&#8217;s brilliantly funny, painfully honest and insightful celebration of things going wrong.</p>
<p>This is a book for anyone who has ever failed. Which means it&#8217;s a book for everyone.</p>
<p>If I have learned one thing from this shockingly beautiful venture called life, it is this: failure has taught me lessons I would never otherwise have understood. I have evolved more as a result of things going wrong than when everything seemed to be going right. Out of crisis has come clarity, and sometimes even catharsis.</p>
<p>Part memoir, part manifesto, and including chapters on dating, work, sport, babies, families, anger and friendship, it is based on the simple premise that understanding why we fail ultimately makes us stronger. It&#8217;s a book about learning from our mistakes and about not being afraid.</p>
<p>Uplifting, inspiring and rich in stories from Elizabeth&#8217;s own life, How to Fail reveals that failure is not what defines us; rather it is how we respond to it that shapes us as individuals.</p>
<p>Because learning how to fail is actually learning how to succeed better. And everyone needs a bit of that.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-everything-ive-ever-learned-from-things-going-wrong-elizabeth-day/">How to Fail : Everything I&#8217;Ve Ever Learned from Things Going Wrong &#8211; Elizabeth Day</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kiss and Make-Up &#8211; Gene Simmons</title>
		<link>/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heavy Metal Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>KISS has released thirty-seven records and sold 80 million albums worldwide. Gene Simmons has also acted in films and on television, has written and produced albums for other recording artists, has managed the recording career of, among others, Liza Minelli, and was founder and president of his own recording label, Simmons Records/RCA. He also launched [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/">Kiss and Make-Up &#8211; Gene Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KISS has released thirty-seven records and sold 80 million albums worldwide. Gene Simmons has also acted in films and on television, has written and produced albums for other recording artists, has managed the recording career of, among others, Liza Minelli, and was founder and president of his own recording label, Simmons Records/RCA. He also launched his film and TV producing career with Detroit Rock City for New Line Cinema. Gene Simmons lives in Beverley Hills, California, and was recently the rock star teacher on Channel 4&#8217;s Rock School.    </p>
<p>                    Here for the first time Gene Simmons, the notorious mainman of the explosive rock and roll group KISS, tells his story. Delivered in Gene&#8217;s own honest, outrageous and uncensored voice, he tells of his early beginnings in Israel, of his arrival in New York at the age of eight, his first taste of 1950s pop culture and his developing thirst for fame, fun and girls. Undoubtedly one of the most infamous rock and roll legends alive, Gene tells the never before revealed story of KISS&#8217;s reign as the biggest and most popular band in the world. Finally, the real story of the man behind the make-up.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/">Kiss and Make-Up &#8211; Gene Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore</title>
		<link>/inside-out-demi-moore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inside-out-demi-moore/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year. Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir. For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                                A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year.</p>
<p>                                Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir.</p>
<p>                              For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore has never been far from the spotlight &#8211; or the headlines.</p>
<p>                              Even as Demi was becoming the highest paid actress in Hollywood, however, she was always outrunning her past, just one step ahead of the doubts and insecurities that defined her childhood. Throughout her rise to fame and during some of the most pivotal moments of her life, Demi battled addiction, body image issues, and childhood trauma that would follow her for years &#8211; all while juggling a skyrocketing career and at times negative public perception.  As her success grew, Demi found herself questioning if she belonged in Hollywood, if she was a good mother, a good actress &#8211; and, always, if she was simply good enough.</p>
<p>                              As much as her story is about adversity, it is also about tremendous resilience. In this deeply candid and reflective memoir, Demi pulls back the curtain and opens up about her career and personal life &#8211; laying bare her tumultuous relationship with her mother, her marriages, her struggles balancing stardom with raising a family, and her journey toward open heartedness. Inside Outis a story of survival, success, and surrender &#8211; a wrenchingly honest portrayal of one woman&#8217;s at once ordinary and iconic life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</title>
		<link>/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Home Renovation & Extension]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV Tie-in Humour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE ENTERTAINING AND HEARTWARMING SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER. Like many couples, Dick and Angel had long dreamed of living in France, but where others might settle for a modest bolthole in the French countryside, the Strawbridges fell in love with a 19th-century fairytale chateau, complete with 45 rooms, seven outbuildings, 12 acres of land and its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/">A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE ENTERTAINING AND HEARTWARMING SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER.</p>
<p>                    Like many couples, Dick and Angel had long dreamed of living in France, but where others might settle for a modest bolthole in the French countryside, the Strawbridges fell in love with a 19th-century fairytale chateau, complete with 45 rooms, seven outbuildings, 12 acres of land and its own moat.</p>
<p>                    Throwing caution to the wind, Dick and Angel swapped their two-bedroom flat in East London for an abandoned and derelict castle in the heart of the Loire valley and embarked on the adventure of a lifetime with their two young children Arthur and Dorothy.</p>
<p>                    Sharing their full journey for the first time, A Year at the Chateau follows Dick and Angel from when they first moved to France in the depths of winter and found bedrooms infested with flies, turrets inhabited by bats, the wind rattling through cracked windows, and just one working toilet, which flushed into the moat, through to the monumental efforts that went into readying the chateau for their unforgettable wedding and their incredibly special first Christmas.</p>
<p>                    Along the way we&#8217;ll read glorious descriptions of rural life in France, with charming characters, delicious food and wonderful seasonal produce, together with the extraordinary list of renovations and restorations Dick and Angel completed, many of which were never shown on TV.</p>
<p>                    As warm and entertaining as their much-loved show, A Year at the Chateau is a truly irresistible story of adventure and heart, epic ambitions and a huge amount of hard graft.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/">A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just as I Am : A Memoir &#8211; Cicely Tyson</title>
		<link>/just-as-i-am-a-memoir-cicely-tyson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/just-as-i-am-a-memoir-cicely-tyson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In her long and extraordinary career, Cicely Tyson has not only succeeded as an actor, she has shaped the course of history.&#8221; -President Barack Obama, 2016 Presidential Medal of Freedom ceremony &#8220;Just as I Am is my truth. It is me, plain and unvarnished, with the glitter and garland set aside. In these pages, I [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-as-i-am-a-memoir-cicely-tyson/">Just as I Am : A Memoir &#8211; Cicely Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In her long and extraordinary career, Cicely Tyson has not only succeeded as an actor, she has shaped the course of history.&#8221; -President Barack Obama, 2016 Presidential Medal of Freedom ceremony    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Just as I Am is my truth. It is me, plain and unvarnished, with the glitter and garland set aside. In these pages, I am indeed Cicely, the actress who has been blessed to grace the stage and screen for six decades. Yet I am also the church girl who once rarely spoke a word. I am the teenager who sought solace in the verses of the old hymn for which this book is named. I am a daughter and a mother, a sister and a friend. I am an observer of human nature and the dreamer of audacious dreams. I am a woman who has hurt as immeasurably as I have loved, a child of God divinely guided by his hand. And here in my ninth decade, I am a woman who, at long last, has something meaningful to say.&#8221; -Cicely Tyson    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-as-i-am-a-memoir-cicely-tyson/">Just as I Am : A Memoir &#8211; Cicely Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</title>
		<link>/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Golf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>President Donald J. Trump lays out his professional and personal worldview in this classic work&#8211;a firsthand account of the rise of America&#8217;s foremost deal-maker. &#8220;I like thinking big. I always have. To me it&#8217;s very simple: If you&#8217;re going to be thinking anyway, you might as well think big.&#8221;&#8211;Donald J. Trump Here is Trump in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/">Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>President Donald J. Trump lays out his professional and personal worldview in this classic work&#8211;a firsthand account of the rise of America&#8217;s foremost deal-maker. </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I like thinking big. I always have. To me it&#8217;s very simple: If you&#8217;re going to be thinking anyway, you might as well think big.&#8221;&#8211;Donald J. Trump </p>
<p>                    Here is Trump in action&#8211;how he runs his organization and how he runs his life&#8211;as he meets the people he needs to meet, chats with family and friends, clashes with enemies, and challenges conventional thinking. But even a maverick plays by rules, and Trump has formulated time-tested guidelines for success. He isolates the common elements in his greatest accomplishments; he shatters myths; he names names, spells out the zeros, and fully reveals the deal-maker&#8217;s art. And throughout, Trump talks&#8211;really talks&#8211;about how he does it. Trump: The Art of the Deal is an unguarded look at the mind of a brilliant entrepreneur&#8211;the ultimate read for anyone interested in the man behind the spotlight. </p>
<p>                     Praise for Trump: The Art of the Deal </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Trump makes one believe for a moment in the American dream again.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times  </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Donald Trump is a deal maker. He is a deal maker the way lions are carnivores and water is wet.&#8221;&#8211;Chicago Tribune</p>
<p>                     &#8220;Fascinating . . . wholly absorbing . . . conveys Trump&#8217;s larger-than-life demeanor so vibrantly that the reader&#8217;s attention is instantly and fully claimed.&#8221;&#8211;Boston Herald</p>
<p>                     &#8220;A chatty, generous, chutzpa-filled autobiography.&#8221;&#8211;New York Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/">Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</title>
		<link>/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is Me &#8211; the joyously funny, honest and moving story of the most enduringly successful singer/songwriter of all time.<br />
                    ______________</p>
<p>                    Christened Reginald Dwight, he was a shy boy with Buddy Holly glasses who grew up in the London suburb of Pinner and dreamed of becoming a pop star.  By the age of twenty-three, he was performing his first gig in America, facing an astonished audience in his bright yellow dungarees, a star-spangled T-shirt and boots with wings. Elton John had arrived and the music world would never be the same again.</p>
<p>                    His life has been full of drama, from the early rejection of his work with songwriting partner Bernie Taupin to spinning out of control as a chart-topping superstar; from half-heartedly trying to drown himself in his LA swimming pool to disco-dancing with the Queen; from friendships with John Lennon, Freddie Mercury and George Michael to setting up his AIDS Foundation. All the while, Elton was hiding a drug addiction that would grip him for over a decade.</p>
<p>                    In Me Elton also writes powerfully about getting clean and changing his life, about finding love with David Furnish and becoming a father.   In a voice that is warm, humble and open, this is Elton on his music and his relationships, his passions and his mistakes.  This is a story that will stay with you, by a living legend.<br />
                    ______________</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Self-deprecating, funny . . . You cannot help but enjoy his company throughout, temper tantrums and all&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Racy, pacy and crammed with scurrilous anecdotes &#8211; what more could you ask from the rocket man&#8217; Guardian (Book of the Week)</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Chatty, gossipy, amusing and at times brutally candid&#8217; Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Face the Music : A Life Exposed &#8211; Paul Stanley</title>
		<link>/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES and INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER In Face the Music, Paul Stanley-the co-founder and famous &#8220;Starchild&#8221; frontman of KISS-reveals for the first time the incredible highs and equally incredible lows in his life both inside and outside the band. Face the Music is the shocking, funny, smart, inspirational story of one of rock&#8217;s most enduring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/">Face the Music : A Life Exposed &#8211; Paul Stanley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES and INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER  In Face the Music, Paul Stanley-the co-founder and famous &#8220;Starchild&#8221; frontman of KISS-reveals for the first time the incredible highs and equally incredible lows in his life both inside and outside the band. Face the Music is the shocking, funny, smart, inspirational story of one of rock&#8217;s most enduring icons and the group he helped create, define, and immortalize.  Stanley mixes compelling personal revelations and gripping, gritty war stories that will surprise even the most steadfast member of the KISS Army. He takes us back to his childhood in the 1950s and &#8217;60s, a traumatic time made more painful thanks to a physical deformity. Born with a condition called microtia, he grew up partially deaf, with only one ear. But this instilled in him an inner drive to succeed in the most unlikely of pursuits: music.  With never-before-seen photos and images throughout, Stanley&#8217;s memoir is a fully realized and unflinching portrait of a rock star, a chronicle of the stories behind the famous anthems, the many brawls and betrayals, and all the drama and pyrotechnics on and off the stage.<br />
                    Raw and confessional, Stanley offers candid insights into his personal relationships, and the turbulent dynamics with his bandmates over the past four decades. And no one comes out unscathed-including Stanley himself.  &#8220;People say I was brave to write such a revealing book, but I wrote it because I needed to personally reflect on my own life. I know everyone will see themselves somewhere in this book, and where my story might take them is why I&#8217;m sharing it.&#8221; -Paul Stanley    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/">Face the Music : A Life Exposed &#8211; Paul Stanley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing &#8211; Bob Mortimer</title>
		<link>/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Angling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fishing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV Tie-in Humour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller Two comedy greats talk life, friendship and the joys of fishing&#8230; Bob Mortimer and Paul Whitehouse have been friends for 30 years, but when life intervened, what was once a joyous and spontaneous friendship dwindled to the odd phone call or occasional catch up. Then, Glory Be! They were both diagnosed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/">Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing &#8211; Bob Mortimer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller</p>
<p>                    Two comedy greats talk life, friendship and the joys of fishing&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Bob Mortimer and Paul Whitehouse have been friends for 30 years, but when life intervened, what was once a joyous and spontaneous friendship dwindled to the odd phone call or occasional catch up. Then, Glory Be! They were both diagnosed with heart disease and realised that time is short. They&#8217;d better spend it fishing&#8230;</p>
<p>                    So they dusted off their kits, chucked on their waders and ventured into the achingly beautiful British countryside to fish, rediscover the joys of their friendship and ruminate on some of life&#8217;s most profound questions, such as: How did we get so old? Where are all the fish? What are your favourite pocket meats? What should we do if we find a corpse?   </p>
<p>                    Following the success of the BBC&#8217;s Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing series, this wonderful book by two lifelong friends is a love letter to the joys of angling, the thrill of the catch and the virtue of having a right daft laff with your mates. On the fish, the equipment, the food, and the locations, Gone Fishing is the perfect book for fans of Bob Mortimer, Paul Whitehouse and for anyone who wants to read a brilliantly written and endlessly funny joint memoir on life, friendship and joys of fishing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortimer-whitehouse-gone-fishing-bob-mortimer/">Mortimer &#038; Whitehouse: Gone Fishing &#8211; Bob Mortimer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let Love Rule &#8211; Lenny Kravitz</title>
		<link>/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I see my story as a suite of songs that have a magical connection. I never understood that connection until I sat down to write. It was then that the magic started to flow.&#8217; Let Love Rule is a work of deep reflection. Lenny Kravitz looks back at his life with candor, self-scrutiny, and humour. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/">Let Love Rule &#8211; Lenny Kravitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I see my story as a suite of songs that have a magical connection. I never understood that connection until I sat down to write. It was then that the magic started to flow.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Let Love Rule is a work of deep reflection. Lenny Kravitz looks back at his life with candor, self-scrutiny, and humour. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My life is all about opposites,&#8217; he writes. &#8216;Black and white. Jewish and Christian. The Jackson 5 and Led Zeppelin. I accepted my Gemini soul. I owned it. I adored it. Yins and yangs mingled in various parts of my heart and mind, giving me balance and fueling my curiosity and comfort.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Let Love Rule covers a vast canvas stretching from Manhattan&#8217;s Upper East Side, Brooklyn&#8217;s Bedford-Stuyvesant, Los Angeles&#8217;s Baldwin Hills, Beverly Hills, and finally to France, England and Germany. It&#8217;s the story of a wildly creative kid who, despite tough struggles at school and extreme tension at home, finds salvation in music. We see him grow as a musician and ultimately a master songwriter, producer, and performer. </p>
<p>                    We also see Lenny&#8217;s spiritual growth-and the powerful way in which spirit informs his music. The cast of characters surrounding Lenny is extraordinary: his father, Sy, a high-powered news executive; his mother, Roxie Roker, a television star; and Lisa Bonet, the young actress who becomes his muse.</p>
<p>                    The central character, of course, is Lenny, who, despite his great aspirational energy, turns down record deal after record deal until he finds his true voice.The creation of that voice, the same voice that is able to declare &#8216;Let Love Rule&#8217; to an international audience, is the very heart of this story.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Whether recording, performing, or writing a book,&#8217; says Lenny, &#8216;my art is about listening to the inspiration inside and then sharing it with people. Art must bring the world closer together.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/">Let Love Rule &#8211; Lenny Kravitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fathomless Riches : Or How I Went From Pop to Pulpit &#8211; Reverend Richard Coles</title>
		<link>/fathomless-riches-or-how-i-went-from-pop-to-pulpit-reverend-richard-coles/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anglican & Episcopalian Churches]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Church Of England]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fathomless-riches-or-how-i-went-from-pop-to-pulpit-reverend-richard-coles/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The memoir of popular BBC Radio 4 SATURDAY LIVE presenter and former member of the Communards, the Reverend Richard Coles. &#8216;I love @RevRichardColes SO MUCH&#8217; Caitlin Moran FATHOMLESS RICHES is the Reverend Richard Coles&#8217;s warm, witty and wise memoir in which he divulges with searing honesty and intimacy his pilgrimage from a rock-and-roll life of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fathomless-riches-or-how-i-went-from-pop-to-pulpit-reverend-richard-coles/">Fathomless Riches : Or How I Went From Pop to Pulpit &#8211; Reverend Richard Coles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The memoir of popular BBC Radio 4 SATURDAY LIVE presenter and former member of the Communards, the Reverend Richard Coles.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I love @RevRichardColes SO MUCH&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    FATHOMLESS RICHES is the Reverend Richard Coles&#8217;s warm, witty and wise memoir in which he divulges with searing honesty and intimacy his pilgrimage from a rock-and-roll life of sex and drugs in the Communards to one devoted to God and Christianity. The result is one of the most unusual and readable life stories of recent times, and has the power to shock as well as to console.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fathomless-riches-or-how-i-went-from-pop-to-pulpit-reverend-richard-coles/">Fathomless Riches : Or How I Went From Pop to Pulpit &#8211; Reverend Richard Coles</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Postillion Struck by Lightning : A Memoir &#8211; Dirk Bogarde</title>
		<link>/a-postillion-struck-by-lightning-a-memoir-dirk-bogarde/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-postillion-struck-by-lightning-a-memoir-dirk-bogarde/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>First published in 1977, A Postillion Struck by Lightning is volume one of Dirk Bogarde&#8217;s best-selling memoirs Following Bogarde from childhood through adolescence, to the beginnings of his budding career, A Postillion Struck by Lightning is a heartfelt memoir, offering insight into what created the drive and charisma that eventually made him a star. Dreamy, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-postillion-struck-by-lightning-a-memoir-dirk-bogarde/">A Postillion Struck by Lightning : A Memoir &#8211; Dirk Bogarde</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First published in 1977, A Postillion Struck by Lightning is volume one of Dirk Bogarde&#8217;s best-selling memoirs</p>
<p>                    Following Bogarde from childhood through adolescence, to the beginnings of his budding career, A Postillion Struck by Lightning is a heartfelt memoir, offering insight into what created the drive and charisma that eventually made him a star. Dreamy, sun-soaked summers full of freedom spent with his younger sister are mixed with holidays in France and rambling the countryside.</p>
<p>                    Writing plays instead of playing sports, Dirk&#8217;s talents lay in the creativity of painting and expression rather than in the precision of maths or science, much to the growing concern of his parents. Packed off to live with relatives in Scotland, his father hoped that a proper Scottish education would equip his son to follow in his footsteps for a career in Newspapers.</p>
<p>                    In Scotland, Dirk learned to defend himself, to sound like a native Glaswegian, and to hide his intense homesickness. In essence; he learned to act.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-postillion-struck-by-lightning-a-memoir-dirk-bogarde/">A Postillion Struck by Lightning : A Memoir &#8211; Dirk Bogarde</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Myself : A Journey &#8211; Alicia Keys</title>
		<link>/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In her intimate memoir, More Myself, Alicia Keys shares her quest for truth: about herself, her past, and her shift from sacrificing her spirit to celebrating her worth. One of the most celebrated musicians of our time, Alicia Keys has enraptured the nation with her heartfelt lyrics, extraordinary vocal range, and soul-stirring piano compositions. Yet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/">More Myself : A Journey &#8211; Alicia Keys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In her intimate memoir, More Myself, Alicia Keys shares her quest for truth: about herself, her past, and her shift from sacrificing her spirit to celebrating her worth.</p>
<p>                    One of the most celebrated musicians of our time, Alicia Keys has enraptured the nation with her heartfelt lyrics, extraordinary vocal range, and soul-stirring piano compositions. Yet away from the spotlight, Alicia has grappled with private heartache over the challenging and complex relationship with her father, the people-pleasing nature that characterized her early career, the loss of privacy surrounding her romantic relationships, and the oppressive expectations of female perfection.</p>
<p>                    Since her rise to fame, Alicia&#8217;s public persona has belied a deep personal truth: she has spent years not fully recognizing or honoring her own worth. After withholding parts of herself for so long, she is at last exploring the questions that live at the heart of her story: Who am I, really? And once I discover that truth, how can I become brave enough to embrace it?</p>
<p>                    More Myself is part autobiography, part narrative documentary. Alicia&#8217;s journey is revealed not only through her own candid recounting, but also through vivid recollections from those who have walked alongside her. The result is a 360-degree perspective on Alicia&#8217;s path: from her girlhood in Hell&#8217;s Kitchen and Harlem, to the process of self-discovery she&#8217;s still navigating.</p>
<p>                    With the raw honesty that epitomizes Alicia&#8217;s artistry, More Myself is at once a riveting account and a clarion call to readers: to define themselves in a world that rarely encourages a true and unique identity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/">More Myself : A Journey &#8211; Alicia Keys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Total Recall : My Unbelievably True Life Story &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger</title>
		<link>/total-recall-my-unbelievably-true-life-story-arnold-schwarzenegger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/total-recall-my-unbelievably-true-life-story-arnold-schwarzenegger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial, and truly unique life. The greatest immigrant success story of our time. His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. He was born in a year of famine, in a small [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-my-unbelievably-true-life-story-arnold-schwarzenegger/">Total Recall : My Unbelievably True Life Story &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial, and truly unique life. </p>
<p>                    The greatest immigrant success story of our time. </p>
<p>                     His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. </p>
<p>                     He was born in a year of famine, in a small Austrian town, the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a movie star. </p>
<p>                     By the age of twenty-one, he was living in Los Angeles and had been crowned Mr. Universe. </p>
<p>                     Within five years, he had learned English and become the greatest bodybuilder in the world. </p>
<p>                     Within ten years, he had earned his college degree and was a millionaire from his business enterprises in real estate, landscaping, and bodybuilding. He was also the winner of a Golden Globe Award for his debut as a dramatic actor in Stay Hungry. </p>
<p>                     Within twenty years, he was the world&#8217;s biggest movie star, the husband of Maria Shriver, and an emerging Republican leader who was part of the Kennedy family. </p>
<p>                     Thirty-six years after coming to America, the man once known by fellow body-builders as the Austrian Oak was elected governor of California, the seventh largest economy in the world. </p>
<p>                     He led the state through a budget crisis, natural disasters, and political turmoil, working across party lines for a better environment, election reforms, and bipartisan solutions. </p>
<p>                     With Maria Shriver, he raised four fantastic children. In the wake of a scandal he brought upon himself, he tried to keep his family together. </p>
<p>                     Until now, he has never told the full story of his life, in his own voice. </p>
<p>                     Here is Arnold, with total recall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-my-unbelievably-true-life-story-arnold-schwarzenegger/">Total Recall : My Unbelievably True Life Story &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wait : A Powerful Practice for Finding the Love of Your Life and the Life You Love &#8211; DeVon Franklin, Meagan Good, With Tim Vandehey</title>
		<link>/the-wait-a-powerful-practice-for-finding-the-love-of-your-life-and-the-life-you-love-devon-franklin-meagan-good-with-tim-vandehey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wait-a-powerful-practice-for-finding-the-love-of-your-life-and-the-life-you-love-devon-franklin-meagan-good-with-tim-vandehey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this New York Times bestseller, Hollywood power couple DeVon Franklin and Meagan Good candidly share their courtship and marriage, and the key to their success-waiting. President/CEO of Franklin Entertainment and former Sony Pictures executive DeVon Franklin and award-winning actress Meagan Good have learned firsthand that some people must wait patiently for &#8220;the one&#8221; to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wait-a-powerful-practice-for-finding-the-love-of-your-life-and-the-life-you-love-devon-franklin-meagan-good-with-tim-vandehey/">The Wait : A Powerful Practice for Finding the Love of Your Life and the Life You Love &#8211; DeVon Franklin, Meagan Good, With Tim Vandehey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this New York Times bestseller, Hollywood power couple DeVon Franklin and Meagan Good candidly share their courtship and marriage, and the key to their success-waiting.<br />
                         President/CEO of Franklin Entertainment and former Sony Pictures executive DeVon Franklin and award-winning actress Meagan Good have learned firsthand that some people must wait patiently for &#8220;the one&#8221; to come into their lives. They spent years crossing paths but it wasn&#8217;t until they were thrown together while working on the film Jumping the Broom that their storybook romance began.<br />
                         DeVon and Meagan chose to do something almost unheard of in today&#8217;s society-abstain from sex until they were married. The Wait is filled with candid his-and-hers accounts and practical advice on how waiting for everything-from dating to sex-can transform relationships.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wait-a-powerful-practice-for-finding-the-love-of-your-life-and-the-life-you-love-devon-franklin-meagan-good-with-tim-vandehey/">The Wait : A Powerful Practice for Finding the Love of Your Life and the Life You Love &#8211; DeVon Franklin, Meagan Good, With Tim Vandehey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Princess Diarist &#8211; Carrie Fisher</title>
		<link>/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Carrie Fisher discovered the journals she kept during the filming of the first Star Wars movie, she was astonished to see what they had preserved &#8211; plaintive love poems, unbridled musings with youthful naivete, and a vulnerability that she barely recognized. Now her fame as an author, actress, and pop-culture icon is indisputable, but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/">The Princess Diarist &#8211; Carrie Fisher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Carrie Fisher discovered the journals she kept during the filming of the first Star Wars movie, she was astonished to see what they had preserved &#8211; plaintive love poems, unbridled musings with youthful naivete, and a vulnerability that she barely recognized. Now her fame as an author, actress, and pop-culture icon is indisputable, but in 1977, Carrie Fisher was just a teenager with an all-consuming crush on her co-star, Harrison Ford.<br />
                     With these excerpts from her handwritten notebooks, The Princess Diarist is Fisher&#8217;s intimate and revealing recollection of what happened on one of the most famous film sets of all time &#8211; and what developed behind the scenes.  Fisher also ponders the joys and insanity of celebrity, and the absurdity of a life spawned by Hollywood royalty, only to be surpassed by her own outer-space royalty. Laugh-out-loud hilarious and endlessly quotable, The Princess Diarist brims with the candour and introspection of a diary while offering shrewd insight into the type of stardom that few will ever experience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-diarist-carrie-fisher/">The Princess Diarist &#8211; Carrie Fisher</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Privilege : Opportunity Comes to Those Who Create It &#8211; Charlamagne Tha God</title>
		<link>/black-privilege-opportunity-comes-to-those-who-create-it-charlamagne-tha-god/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Radio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-privilege-opportunity-comes-to-those-who-create-it-charlamagne-tha-god/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An instant New York Times bestseller! Charlamagne Tha God-the self-proclaimed &#8220;Prince of Pissing People Off,&#8221; cohost of Power 105.1&#8217;s The Breakfast Club, and &#8220;the most important voice in hip-hop&#8221;-shares his eight principles for unlocking your God-given privilege. In Black Privilege, Charlamagne presents his often controversial and always brutally honest insights on how living an authentic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-privilege-opportunity-comes-to-those-who-create-it-charlamagne-tha-god/">Black Privilege : Opportunity Comes to Those Who Create It &#8211; Charlamagne Tha God</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An instant New York Times bestseller! Charlamagne Tha God-the self-proclaimed &#8220;Prince of Pissing People Off,&#8221; cohost of Power 105.1&#8217;s The Breakfast Club, and &#8220;the most important voice in hip-hop&#8221;-shares his eight principles for unlocking your God-given privilege.    </p>
<p>                    In Black Privilege, Charlamagne presents his often controversial and always brutally honest insights on how living an authentic life is the quickest path to success. This journey to truth begins in the small town of Moncks Corner, South Carolina, and leads to New York and headline-grabbing interviews and insights from celebrities like Kanye West, Kevin Hart, Malcolm Gladwell, Lena Dunham, Jay Z, and Hillary Clinton.    </p>
<p>                    Black Privilege lays out all the great wisdom Charlamagne&#8217;s been given from many mentors, and tells the uncensored story of how he turned around his troubled early life by owning his (many) mistakes and refusing to give up on his dreams, even after his controversial opinions got him fired from several on-air jobs. These life-learned principles include:    </p>
<p>                    -There are no losses in life, only lessons<br />
                     -Give people the credit they deserve for being stupid-starting with yourself<br />
                     -It&#8217;s not the size of the pond but the hustle in the fish<br />
                     -When you live your truth, no one can use it against you<br />
                     -We all have privilege, we just need to access it    </p>
<p>                    By combining his own story with bold advice and his signature commitment to honesty no matter the cost, Charlamagne hopes Black Privilege will empower you to live your own truth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-privilege-opportunity-comes-to-those-who-create-it-charlamagne-tha-god/">Black Privilege : Opportunity Comes to Those Who Create It &#8211; Charlamagne Tha God</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not To Be a Boy &#8211; Robert Webb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-be-a-boy-robert-webb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-be-a-boy-robert-webb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER RULES FOR BEING A MAN Don&#8217;t Cry; Love Sport; Play Rough; Drink Beer; Don&#8217;t Talk About Feelings But Robert Webb has been wondering for some time now: are those rules actually any use? To anyone? Looking back over his life, from schoolboy crushes (on girls and boys) to discovering [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-be-a-boy-robert-webb-abridged/">How Not To Be a Boy &#8211; Robert Webb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    RULES FOR BEING A MAN<br />
                    Don&#8217;t Cry; Love Sport; Play Rough; Drink Beer; Don&#8217;t Talk About Feelings    </p>
<p>                    But Robert Webb has been wondering for some time now: are those rules actually any use? To anyone?     </p>
<p>                    Looking back over his life, from schoolboy crushes (on girls and boys) to discovering the power of making people laugh (in the Cambridge Footlights with David Mitchell), and from losing his beloved mother to becoming a husband and father, Robert Webb considers the absurd expectations boys and men have thrust upon them at every stage of life.     </p>
<p>                    Hilarious and heartbreaking, How Not To Be a Boy explores the relationships that made Robert who he is as a man, the lessons we learn as sons and daughters, and the understanding that sometimes you aren&#8217;t the Luke Skywalker of your life &#8211; you&#8217;re actually Darth Vader.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-be-a-boy-robert-webb-abridged/">How Not To Be a Boy &#8211; Robert Webb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD &#8211; Russ (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/its-all-in-your-head-russ-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rap & Hip-Hop]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/its-all-in-your-head-russ-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Instant National Bestseller! Wall Street Journal bestseller; USA Today bestseller; Publishers Weekly bestseller; international bestseller. An inspirational book by self-made musical superstar, Russ, reminding you that it starts with YOU, to believe in yourself, and to get out of your own way. Twenty-seven-year-old rapper, songwriter, and producer Russ walks his own path, at his own [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-all-in-your-head-russ-abridged/">IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD &#8211; Russ (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Instant National Bestseller! Wall Street Journal bestseller; USA Today bestseller; Publishers Weekly bestseller; international bestseller.    </p>
<p>                    An inspirational book by self-made musical superstar, Russ, reminding you that it starts with YOU, to believe in yourself, and to get out of your own way.     </p>
<p>                      Twenty-seven-year-old rapper, songwriter, and producer Russ walks his own path, at his own pace. By doing so, he proved that he didn&#8217;t need a major label to surpass over a billion streams on Spotify/Apple Music, get on Forbes&#8217; 2019 &#8220;30 Under 30,&#8221; make the Forbes&#8217; &#8220;30 Under 30 Cash Kings&#8221; at number 20 for most earned, sell out arenas across the U.S. and around the globe, and become one of the most popular and engaged rappers right now. His method was simple: love and believe in yourself absolutely and work hard no matter what. In this memoir, Russ inspires readers to walk to their individual rhythms and beat their biggest obstacles: themselves.    </p>
<p>                      With chapters named after his most powerful and popular songs, IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD will reflect on the lessons he&#8217;s learned from his career, family, and relationships. He&#8217;ll push readers to bet on themselves, take those leaps of faith, and recognize struggles as opportunities. With illustrations throughout consistent with the brand Russ has built and his fan base loves, IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD will give readers an inside-look at the man and the motivation behind the music. A lover of books like The Alchemist and The Seven Spiritual Laws of Success, Russ delivers a short, potent, inspirational, raw, and honest book that gives readers a way to find self-belief and unlock their potential. Fans already rely on Russ as an inspiration of confidence; now, he is taking it to the next level with this book, which will contain lyrics from his music and visuals that reflect his inimitable style.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-all-in-your-head-russ-abridged/">IT&#8217;S ALL IN YOUR HEAD &#8211; Russ (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Be a Bawse : A Guide to Conquering Life &#8211; Lilly Singh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-a-bawse-a-guide-to-conquering-life-lilly-singh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-a-bawse-a-guide-to-conquering-life-lilly-singh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Release your inner bawse with YouTube phenomenon Lilly Singh&#8217;s How to Be a Bawse, winner of the Goodreads Choice Awards: Non-Fiction Book of the Year &#8216;The ultimate no-nonsense manual for millennials how how to make it to the top&#8217; MARIE CLAIRE From actress, comedian and YouTube sensation Lilly Singh (aka Superwoman) comes the definitive guide [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-bawse-a-guide-to-conquering-life-lilly-singh-abridged/">How to Be a Bawse : A Guide to Conquering Life &#8211; Lilly Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Release your inner bawse with YouTube phenomenon Lilly Singh&#8217;s How to Be a Bawse, winner of the Goodreads Choice Awards: Non-Fiction Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The ultimate no-nonsense manual for millennials how how to make it to the top&#8217; MARIE CLAIRE    </p>
<p>                    From actress, comedian and YouTube sensation Lilly Singh (aka Superwoman) comes the definitive guide to being a BAWSE &#8211; a person who exudes confidence, reaches goals, gets hurt efficiently, and smiles genuinely because they&#8217;ve fought through it all and made it out the other side.    </p>
<p>                    Told in her hilarious, bold voice that&#8217;s inspired over 9 million fans, and using stories from her own life to illustrate her message, Lilly proves that there are no shortcuts to success.     </p>
<p>                    WARNING: This book does NOT include hopeful thoughts, lucky charms, and cute quotes.    </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s because success, happiness and everything else you want in life needs to be fought for &#8211; not wished for.    </p>
<p>                    With Lilly&#8217;s no-nonsense advice and first-had stories, you will learn to take your confidence to the next level and take what you want.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-bawse-a-guide-to-conquering-life-lilly-singh-abridged/">How to Be a Bawse : A Guide to Conquering Life &#8211; Lilly Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happy Fat : Taking Up Space in a World That Wants to Shrink You &#8211; Sofie Hagen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happy-fat-taking-up-space-in-a-world-that-wants-to-shrink-you-sofie-hagen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happy-fat-taking-up-space-in-a-world-that-wants-to-shrink-you-sofie-hagen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Perfect, kind, hilarious and persuasive&#8217; Lena Dunham &#8216;You need this book. Your mum needs this book. Your best friend needs this book. Everyone needs a dose of Happy Fat!&#8217; Julie Murphy In Happy Fat, comedian Sofie Hagen shares how she removed fatphobic influences from her daily life and found self-acceptance in a world where judgement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-fat-taking-up-space-in-a-world-that-wants-to-shrink-you-sofie-hagen-abridged/">Happy Fat : Taking Up Space in a World That Wants to Shrink You &#8211; Sofie Hagen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Perfect, kind, hilarious and persuasive&#8217; Lena Dunham    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;You need this book. Your mum needs this book. Your best friend needs this book. Everyone needs a dose of Happy Fat!&#8217; Julie Murphy    </p>
<p>                              In Happy Fat, comedian Sofie Hagen shares how she removed fatphobic influences from her daily life and found self-acceptance in a world where judgement and discrimination are rife. From shame and sex to airplane seats, love and getting stuck in public toilets, Sofie provides practical tips for readers.    </p>
<p>                              Part memoir, part social commentary, Happy Fat is a funny, angry and impassioned look at how taking up space can be radical, emboldening and life-changing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-fat-taking-up-space-in-a-world-that-wants-to-shrink-you-sofie-hagen-abridged/">Happy Fat : Taking Up Space in a World That Wants to Shrink You &#8211; Sofie Hagen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year. Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir. For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                A Daily Mail Book of the Year. A Mail on SundayBook of the Year.    </p>
<p>                                Famed American actress Demi Moore at last tells her own story in a surprisingly intimate and emotionally charged memoir.    </p>
<p>                              For decades, Demi Moore has been synonymous with celebrity. From iconic film roles to high-profile relationships, Moore has never been far from the spotlight &#8211; or the headlines.    </p>
<p>                              Even as Demi was becoming the highest paid actress in Hollywood, however, she was always outrunning her past, just one step ahead of the doubts and insecurities that defined her childhood. Throughout her rise to fame and during some of the most pivotal moments of her life, Demi battled addiction, body image issues, and childhood trauma that would follow her for years &#8211; all while juggling a skyrocketing career and at times negative public perception.  As her success grew, Demi found herself questioning if she belonged in Hollywood, if she was a good mother, a good actress &#8211; and, always, if she was simply good enough.    </p>
<p>                              As much as her story is about adversity, it is also about tremendous resilience. In this deeply candid and reflective memoir, Demi pulls back the curtain and opens up about her career and personal life &#8211; laying bare her tumultuous relationship with her mother, her marriages, her struggles balancing stardom with raising a family, and her journey toward open heartedness. Inside Outis a story of survival, success, and surrender &#8211; a wrenchingly honest portrayal of one woman&#8217;s at once ordinary and iconic life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inside-out-demi-moore-abridged/">Inside Out &#8211; Demi Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Fail : Everything I&#8217;Ve Ever Learned from Things Going Wrong &#8211; Elizabeth Day (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-fail-everything-ive-ever-learned-from-things-going-wrong-elizabeth-day-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-fail-everything-ive-ever-learned-from-things-going-wrong-elizabeth-day-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Inspired by her hugely popular podcast, How To Fail is Elizabeth Day&#8217;s brilliantly funny, painfully honest and insightful celebration of things going wrong. This is a book for anyone who has ever failed. Which means it&#8217;s a book for everyone. If I have learned one thing from this shockingly beautiful venture called life, it is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-everything-ive-ever-learned-from-things-going-wrong-elizabeth-day-abridged/">How to Fail : Everything I&#8217;Ve Ever Learned from Things Going Wrong &#8211; Elizabeth Day (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Inspired by her hugely popular podcast, How To Fail is Elizabeth Day&#8217;s brilliantly funny, painfully honest and insightful celebration of things going wrong.     </p>
<p>                                This is a book for anyone who has ever failed. Which means it&#8217;s a book for everyone.     </p>
<p>                                If I have learned one thing from this shockingly beautiful venture called life, it is this: failure has taught me lessons I would never otherwise have understood. I have evolved more as a result of things going wrong than when everything seemed to be going right. Out of crisis has come clarity, and sometimes even catharsis.    </p>
<p>                              Part memoir, part manifesto, and including chapters on dating, work, sport, babies, families, anger and friendship, it is based on the simple premise that understanding why we fail ultimately makes us stronger. It&#8217;s a book about learning from our mistakes and about not being afraid.    </p>
<p>                    Uplifting, inspiring and rich in stories from Elizabeth&#8217;s own life, How to Fail reveals that failure is not what defines us; rather it is how we respond to it that shapes us as individuals.    </p>
<p>                    Because learning how to fail is actually learning how to succeed better. And everyone needs a bit of that.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-everything-ive-ever-learned-from-things-going-wrong-elizabeth-day-abridged/">How to Fail : Everything I&#8217;Ve Ever Learned from Things Going Wrong &#8211; Elizabeth Day (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let Love Have the Last Word : A Memoir &#8211; Common (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/let-love-have-the-last-word-a-memoir-common-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-love-have-the-last-word-a-memoir-common-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER Common-the Grammy Award, Academy Award, and Golden Globe-winning musician, actor, and activist-follows up his New York Times bestselling memoir One Day It&#8217;ll All Make Sense with this inspiring exploration of how love and mindfulness can build communities and allow you to take better control of your life through actions [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-have-the-last-word-a-memoir-common-abridged/">Let Love Have the Last Word : A Memoir &#8211; Common (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    Common-the Grammy Award, Academy Award, and Golden Globe-winning musician, actor, and activist-follows up his New York Times bestselling memoir One Day It&#8217;ll All Make Sense with this inspiring exploration of how love and mindfulness can build communities and allow you to take better control of your life through actions and words.    </p>
<p>                    Common believes that the phrase &#8220;let love have the last word&#8221; is not just a declaration; it is a statement of purpose, a daily promise. Love is the most powerful force on the planet and ultimately, the way you love determines who you are and how you experience life.    </p>
<p>                    Touching on God, self-love, partners, children, family, and community, Common explores the core tenets of love to help others understand what it means to receive and, most important, to give love. He moves from the personal-writing about his daughter, to whom he wants to be a better father-to the universal, where he observes that our society has become fractured under issues of race and politics. He knows there&#8217;s no quick remedy for all of the hurt in the world, but love-for yourself and for others-is where the healing begins.    </p>
<p>                    Courageous, insightful, brave, and characteristically authentic, Let Love Have the Last Word shares Common&#8217;s own unique and personal stories of the people and experiences that have led to a greater understanding of love and all it has to offer. It is a powerful call to action for a new generation of open hearts and minds, one that is sure to resonate for years to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-have-the-last-word-a-memoir-common-abridged/">Let Love Have the Last Word : A Memoir &#8211; Common (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians, Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is Me &#8211; the joyously funny, honest and moving story of the most enduringly successful singer/songwriter of all time.<br />
                    ______________    </p>
<p>                    Christened Reginald Dwight, he was a shy boy with Buddy Holly glasses who grew up in the London suburb of Pinner and dreamed of becoming a pop star.  By the age of twenty-three, he was performing his first gig in America, facing an astonished audience in his bright yellow dungarees, a star-spangled T-shirt and boots with wings. Elton John had arrived and the music world would never be the same again.    </p>
<p>                    His life has been full of drama, from the early rejection of his work with songwriting partner Bernie Taupin to spinning out of control as a chart-topping superstar; from half-heartedly trying to drown himself in his LA swimming pool to disco-dancing with the Queen; from friendships with John Lennon, Freddie Mercury and George Michael to setting up his AIDS Foundation. All the while, Elton was hiding a drug addiction that would grip him for over a decade.    </p>
<p>                    In Me Elton also writes powerfully about getting clean and changing his life, about finding love with David Furnish and becoming a father.   In a voice that is warm, humble and open, this is Elton on his music and his relationships, his passions and his mistakes.  This is a story that will stay with you, by a living legend.<br />
                    ______________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Self-deprecating, funny . . . You cannot help but enjoy his company throughout, temper tantrums and all&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Racy, pacy and crammed with scurrilous anecdotes &#8211; what more could you ask from the rocket man&#8217; Guardian (Book of the Week)    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Chatty, gossipy, amusing and at times brutally candid&#8217; Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life. Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life.    </p>
<p>                     Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a movie star. By the age of 21, he was living in Los Angeles and had been crowned Mr Universe. Within five years, he had learned English and become the greatest bodybuilder in the world. Within ten years, he had earned his college degree and was a millionaire from his business enterprises in real estate, landscaping and bodybuilding. He was also the winner of a Golden Globe Award for his debut as a dramatic actor in Stay Hungry.    </p>
<p>                     But that was only the beginning. The Terminator spawned numerous sequels and made him one of Hollywood&#8217;s biggest stars, as he had a series of hit films including Predator, Total Recall, True Lies and Twins. He married Maria Shriver, becoming part of the Kennedy clan, while going on to become the Republican governor of California, where he led the state through a budget crisis, natural disasters and political turmoil.     </p>
<p>                    It is the greatest immigrant success story of our time. His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. Until now, he has never told the full story of his life, in his own voice. Here is Arnold, with total recall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
