<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Philosophy: Aesthetics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/philosophy-aesthetics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/philosophy-aesthetics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Philosophy: Aesthetics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/philosophy-aesthetics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Sexual Personae : Art &#038; Decadence from Nefertiti to Emily Dickinson &#8211; Camille Paglia</title>
		<link>/sexual-personae-art-decadence-from-nefertiti-to-emily-dickinson-camille-paglia/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sexual-personae-art-decadence-from-nefertiti-to-emily-dickinson-camille-paglia/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is the fiery, provocative, and unparalleled work of feminist art criticism that launched Camille Paglia&#8217;s exceptional career as one of our most important public intellectuals. Is Emily Dickinson &#8220;the female Sade&#8221;? Is Donatello&#8217;s David a bit of pedophile pornography? What is the secret kinship between Byron and Elvis Presley, between Medusa and Madonna? How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sexual-personae-art-decadence-from-nefertiti-to-emily-dickinson-camille-paglia/">Sexual Personae : Art &#038; Decadence from Nefertiti to Emily Dickinson &#8211; Camille Paglia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here is the fiery, provocative, and unparalleled work of feminist art criticism that launched Camille Paglia&#8217;s exceptional career as one of our most important public intellectuals. Is Emily Dickinson &#8220;the female Sade&#8221;? Is Donatello&#8217;s David a bit of pedophile pornography? What is the secret kinship between Byron and Elvis Presley, between Medusa and Madonna? How do liberals and feminists&#8211;as well as conservatives&#8211;fatally misread human nature? This audacious and omnivorously learned work of guerrilla scholarship offers nothing less than a unified-field theory of Western culture, high and low, since Egyptians invented beauty&#8211;making a persuasive case for all art as a pagan battleground between male and female, form and chaos, civilization and daemonic nature.     </p>
<p>                     47 photographs.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sexual-personae-art-decadence-from-nefertiti-to-emily-dickinson-camille-paglia/">Sexual Personae : Art &#038; Decadence from Nefertiti to Emily Dickinson &#8211; Camille Paglia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Distinction : A Social Critique of the Judgement of Taste &#8211; Pierre Bourdieu (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No judgement of taste is innocent &#8211; we are all snobs. Pierre Bourdieu&#8217;s Distinction brilliantly illuminates the social pretentions of the middle classes in the modern world, focusing on the tastes and preferences of the French bourgeoisie. First published in 1979, the book is at once a vast ethnography of contemporary France and a dissection [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/">Distinction : A Social Critique of the Judgement of Taste &#8211; Pierre Bourdieu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No judgement of taste is innocent &#8211; we are all snobs. Pierre Bourdieu&#8217;s Distinction brilliantly illuminates the social pretentions of the middle classes in the modern world, focusing on the tastes and preferences of the French bourgeoisie. First published in 1979, the book is at once a vast ethnography of contemporary France and a dissection of the bourgeois mind.     </p>
<p>                    In the course of everyday life we constantly choose between what we find aesthetically pleasing, and what we consider tacky, merely trendy, or ugly. Taste is not pure. Bourdieu demonstrates that our different aesthetic choices are all distinctions &#8211; that is, choices made in opposition to those made by other classes. This fascinating work argues that the social world functions simultaneously as a system of power relations and as a symbolic system in which minute distinctions of taste become the basis for social judgement.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/">Distinction : A Social Critique of the Judgement of Taste &#8211; Pierre Bourdieu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Aesthetic Brain : How We Evolved to Desire Beauty and Enjoy Art &#8211; Anjan Chatterjee, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-aesthetic-brain-how-we-evolved-to-desire-beauty-and-enjoy-art-anjan-chatterjee-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-aesthetic-brain-how-we-evolved-to-desire-beauty-and-enjoy-art-anjan-chatterjee-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Aesthetic Brain takes readers on an exciting journey through the world of beauty, pleasure, and art. Using the latest advances in neuroscience and evolutionary psychology, Anjan Chatterjee investigates how an aesthetic sense is etched into our minds, and explains why artistic concerns feature centrally in our lives. Along the way, Chatterjee addresses such fundamental [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-aesthetic-brain-how-we-evolved-to-desire-beauty-and-enjoy-art-anjan-chatterjee-md-abridged/">The Aesthetic Brain : How We Evolved to Desire Beauty and Enjoy Art &#8211; Anjan Chatterjee, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Aesthetic Brain takes readers on an exciting journey through the world of beauty, pleasure, and art. Using the latest advances in neuroscience and evolutionary psychology, Anjan Chatterjee investigates how an aesthetic sense is etched into our minds, and explains why artistic concerns feature centrally in our lives. Along the way, Chatterjee addresses such fundamental questions as: What is beauty? Is it universal? How is beauty related to pleasure? What<br />
                    is art? Should art be beautiful? Do we have an instinct for art?    </p>
<p>                    Early on, Chatterjee probes the reasons why we find people, places, and even numbers beautiful, highlighting the important relationship between beauty and pleasure. Examining our pleasures allows him to reveal why we enjoy things like food, sex, and money, and how these rewards relate to our aesthetic encounters. Chatterjee&#8217;s detailed discussion of beauty and pleasure equips readers to confront essential questions about the nature of art, the problems of defining it, and the challenges of<br />
                    interpreting its modern, non-traditional forms. Replete with facts, anecdotes, and analogies, this lively empirical guide to aesthetics offers scientific answers to fundamental questions without deflating the intrinsic wonders of beauty and art in an affordable paperback edition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-aesthetic-brain-how-we-evolved-to-desire-beauty-and-enjoy-art-anjan-chatterjee-md-abridged/">The Aesthetic Brain : How We Evolved to Desire Beauty and Enjoy Art &#8211; Anjan Chatterjee, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose. This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose.    </p>
<p>                    This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is among mankind&#8217;s great masterpieces-a massive work of art. As an idea, it rivals monotheism. But its cultural potential and its societal impact often elude us. In this deep and thoughtful book, Virginia Heffernan reveals the logic and aesthetics behind the Internet, just as Susan Sontag did for photography and Marshall McLuhan did for television.    </p>
<p>                    Life online, in the highly visual, social, portable, and global incarnation rewards certain virtues. The new medium favors speed, accuracy, wit, prolificacy, and versatility, and its form and functions are changing how we perceive, experience, and understand the world. In &#8220;sumptuous writing, saturated with observations that are simultaneously personal, cultural, and strikingly original&#8221; (The New Republic), Heffernan presents &#8220;a revealing look at how the Internet continues to reshape our lives emotionally, visually, and culturally&#8221; (The Smithsonian Magazine). &#8220;Magic and Loss is an illuminating guide to the Internet&#8230;it is impossible to come away from this book without sharing some of Heffernan&#8217;s awe for this brave new world&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Architecture of Happiness &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Architecture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interior Design, Decor & Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Professional Interior Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Architecture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER From one of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy and The School of Life, The Architecture of Happiness explores the fascinating hidden links between the buildings we live in and our long-term wellbeing. &#8216;Engaging and intelligent . . . Full [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Architecture of Happiness &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    From one of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy and The School of Life, The Architecture of Happiness explores the fascinating hidden links between the buildings we live in and our long-term wellbeing.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Engaging and intelligent . . . Full of splendid ideas, happily and beautifully expressed&#8217; Independent    </p>
<p>                    What makes a house truly beautiful? Why are many new houses so ugly? Why do we argue so bitterly about sofas and pictures &#8211; and can differences of taste ever be satisfactorily resolved?    </p>
<p>                    To answer these questions and many more, de Botton looks at buildings across the world, from medieval wooden huts to modern skyscrapers; he examines sofas and cathedrals, tea sets and office complexes, and teases out a host of often surprising philosophical insights. The Architecture of Happiness will take you on a beguiling tour through the history and psychology of architecture and interior design, and will change the way you look at your home.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Alain de Botton takes big, complex subjects and writes about them with thoughtful and deceptive innocence&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Clever, provocative and fresh as a daisy&#8217; Literary Review</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Architecture of Happiness &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Good and Evil : Prelude to a Philosophy of the Future &#8211; Friedrich Nietzsche (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After kicking open the doors to twentieth-century philosophy in Thus Spake Zarathustra, Friedrich Nietzsche refined his ideal of the superman with the 1886 publication of Beyond Good and Evil. Conventional morality is a sign of slavery, Nietzsche maintains, and the superman goes beyond good and evil in action, thought, and creation. Nietzsche especially targets what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/">Beyond Good and Evil : Prelude to a Philosophy of the Future &#8211; Friedrich Nietzsche (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After kicking open the doors to twentieth-century philosophy in Thus Spake Zarathustra,  Friedrich Nietzsche refined his ideal of the superman with the 1886 publication of Beyond Good and Evil. Conventional morality is a sign of slavery, Nietzsche maintains, and the superman goes beyond good and evil in action, thought, and creation. Nietzsche especially targets what he calls a slave morality that fosters herdlike quiescence and stigmatizes the highest human types.<br />
                    In this pathbreaking work, Nietzsche&#8217;s philosophical and literary powers are at their height: with devastating irony and flashing wit he gleefully dynamites centuries of accumulated conventional wisdom in metaphysics, morals, and psychology, clearing a path for such twentieth-century innovators as Thomas Mann, André Gide, Sigmund Freud, George Bernard Shaw, André Malraux, and Jean-Paul Sartre, all of whom openly acknowledged their debt to him.<br />
                    Students of philosophy and literature as well as general readers will prize this rich sampling of Nietzsche&#8217;s thought in an unabridged and inexpensive edition of one of the philosopher&#8217;s most important works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/">Beyond Good and Evil : Prelude to a Philosophy of the Future &#8211; Friedrich Nietzsche (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
