<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Immunology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/immunology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/immunology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Immunology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/immunology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8220;A valuable read that will help you understand what it takes to stop COVID-19. &#8230; A super interesting look at the science of immunity.&#8221; -Bill Gates, Gates Notes Summer Reading List The Pulitzer Prize-winning New York Times journalist &#8220;explicates for the lay reader the intricate biology of our immune system&#8221; (Jerome Groopman, MD, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/">Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable read that will help you understand what it takes to stop COVID-19. &#8230; A super interesting look at the science of immunity.&#8221; -Bill Gates, Gates Notes Summer Reading List    </p>
<p>                    The Pulitzer Prize-winning New York Times journalist &#8220;explicates for the lay reader the intricate biology of our immune system&#8221; (Jerome Groopman, MD, New York Review of Books)    </p>
<p>                    From New York Times science journalist Matt Richtel, An Elegant Defense is an acclaimed and definitive exploration of the immune system and the secrets of health. Interweaving cutting-edge science with the intimate stories of four individual patients, this epic, first-of-its-kind book &#8220;give[s] lay readers a means of understanding what&#8217;s known so far about the intricate biology of our immune systems&#8221; (The Week).    </p>
<p>                    The immune system is our body&#8217;s essential defense network, a guardian vigilantly fighting illness, healing wounds, maintaining order and balance, and keeping us alive. It has been honed by evolution over millennia to face an almost infinite array of threats. For all its astonishing complexity, however, the immune system can be easily compromised by fatigue, stress, toxins, advanced age, and poor nutrition-hallmarks of modern life-and even by excessive hygiene. Paradoxically, it is a fragile wonder weapon that can turn on our own bodies with startling results, leading today to epidemic levels of autoimmune disorders.    </p>
<p>                    An Elegant Defense effortlessly guides readers on a scientific detective tale winding from the Black Plague to twentieth-century breakthroughs in vaccination and antibiotics, to today&#8217;s laboratories that are revolutionizing immunology-perhaps the most extraordinary and consequential medical story of our time. Drawing on extensive new interviews with dozens of world-renowned scientists, Richtel has produced a landmark book, equally an investigation into the deepest riddles of survival and a profoundly human tale that is movingly brought to life through the eyes of his four main characters, each of whom illuminates an essential facet of our &#8220;elegant defense.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/">Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health    </p>
<p>                    Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, bacteria and human cells have co-existed in a relationship that has ensured the health and equilibrium of our body. But now, much like the natural world outside of us, our internal environment is being irrevocably destroyed. The culprit: some of our most revered medical advances &#8211; antibiotics &#8211; which appear to be linked to the epidemics of asthma, eczema, obesity, certain forms of cancer, and other diseases plaguing modern society.    </p>
<p>                    In a book that stands as the Silent Spring of its day, Blaser sounds a provocative alarm that we ignore at our peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A leading figure in immunology takes readers inside the remarkably powerful human immune system. Winner of the CHOICE Outstanding Academic Title of the Choice ACRL The immune system has incredible power to protect us from the ravages of infection. Boosted by vaccines, it can protect us from diseases such as measles. However, the power of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/">Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A leading figure in immunology takes readers inside the remarkably powerful human immune system.    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the CHOICE Outstanding Academic Title of the Choice ACRL    </p>
<p>                    The immune system has incredible power to protect us from the ravages of infection. Boosted by vaccines, it can protect us from diseases such as measles. However, the power of the immune system is a double-edged sword: an overactive immune system can wreak havoc, destroying normal tissue and causing diseases such as type I diabetes, rheumatoid arthritis, and multiple sclerosis. The consequences of an impaired immune system, on the other hand, are all too evident in the agonies of AIDS.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with illustrations, stories from Dr. William E. Paul&#8217;s distinguished career, and fascinating accounts of scientific discovery, Immunity presents the three laws of the human immune system-universality, tolerance, and appropriateness-and explains how the system both protects and harms us. From the tale of how smallpox was overcome and the lessons of the Ebola epidemic to the hope that the immune system can be used to treat or prevent cancer, Dr. Paul argues that we must take advantage of cutting-edge technologies and promising new tools in immunological research.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/">Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From world-renowned health expert and New York Times bestselling author of Eat to Live and Eat for Life Dr. Joel Fuhrman comes a practical nutritional plan to prevent and reverse disease&#8211;no shots, drugs or sick days required. Why do some of us get sick with greater frequency than others? What makes us more susceptible to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From world-renowned health expert and New York Times bestselling author of Eat to Live and Eat for Life Dr. Joel Fuhrman comes a practical nutritional plan to prevent and reverse disease&#8211;no shots, drugs or sick days required.    </p>
<p>                     Why do some of us get sick with greater frequency than others? What makes us more susceptible to illness? Is there a secret to staying healthy? Dr. Fuhrman doesn&#8217;t believe the secret to staying healthy lies in medical care&#8211;rather, the solution is to change the way we eat.    </p>
<p>                     With more than 85 plant-based recipes, a two-week menu plan, and lists of super foods that boost immunity, Dr. Fuhrman&#8217;s proven strategies in Super Immunity combine the latest data from clinical tests, nutritional research, and results from thousands of patients .    </p>
<p>                    Inside Super Immunity, you&#8217;ll find: The big picture&#8211;Learn everything you need to know about healthy eating for a healthy life.A 2-week meal plan&#8211;Take the guesswork out of changing your diet with planned meals for breakfast, lunch, and dinner every day of the week.85 immunity-boosting recipes&#8211;These delicious plant based recipes make eating healthy easy and crave-worthy.    </p>
<p>                     Live longer, stronger, and disease free with this proven plan to change your diet and change your life.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Super Immunity is a much needed book that contains the key to ending the cycle of sickness that plagues many of our lives. This is enlightened medicine, at last!&#8221; (Dr. Alejandro Junger, New York Times bestselling author of CLEAN)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-immunity-the-essential-nutrition-guide-for-boosting-your-bodys-defenses-to-live-longer-stronger-and-disease-free-joel-fuhrman-abridged/">Super Immunity : The Essential Nutrition Guide for Boosting Your Body&#8217;s Defenses to Live Longer, Stronger, and Disease Free &#8211; Joel Fuhrman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
