<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Urban Communities Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/urban-communities/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/urban-communities/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Urban Communities Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/urban-communities/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Gang Leader for a Day &#8211; Sudhir Venkatesh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/gang-leader-for-a-day-sudhir-venkatesh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Adolescents]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Street Crime / Gun Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/gang-leader-for-a-day-sudhir-venkatesh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sudhir Venkatesh the young sociologist who became famous in Freakonomics (Why do drug dealers still live with their moms?) describes his time living with the gangs on the Southside of Chicago and answers another question: what&#8217;s it like to live in hell? In the Robert Taylor Homes projects on Chicago&#8217;s South Side, Sudhir befriends J.T., [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gang-leader-for-a-day-sudhir-venkatesh-abridged/">Gang Leader for a Day &#8211; Sudhir Venkatesh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sudhir Venkatesh the young sociologist who became famous in Freakonomics (Why do drug dealers still live with their moms?) describes his time living with the gangs on the Southside of Chicago and answers another question: what&#8217;s it like to live in hell?    </p>
<p>                    In the Robert Taylor Homes projects on Chicago&#8217;s South Side, Sudhir befriends J.T., a gang leader for the Black Kings. As he slowly gains J.T.&#8217;s trust, one day, in order to convince Sudhir of his own CEO-like qualities, J.T. makes him leader of the gang&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    Why does J.T. make his henchmen, the &#8216;shorties&#8217;, stay in school? What is the difference between a &#8216;regular&#8217; hustler and a &#8216;hype&#8217; &#8211; and is Peanut telling him the truth about which she is? And, when the FBI finally starts cracking down on the Black Kings, is it time to get out &#8211; or is it too late?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gang-leader-for-a-day-sudhir-venkatesh-abridged/">Gang Leader for a Day &#8211; Sudhir Venkatesh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scale : The Universal Laws of Life and Death in Organisms, Cities and Companies &#8211; Geoffrey West (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/scale-the-universal-laws-of-life-and-death-in-organisms-cities-and-companies-geoffrey-west-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics Of Industrial Organisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Molecular Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/scale-the-universal-laws-of-life-and-death-in-organisms-cities-and-companies-geoffrey-west-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Geoffrey West&#8217;s research centres on a quest to find unifying principles and patterns connecting everything, from cells and ecosystems to cities, social networks and businesses. Why do organisms and ecosystems scale with size in a remarkably universal and systematic fashion? Is there a maximum size of cities? Of animals and plants? What about companies? Can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scale-the-universal-laws-of-life-and-death-in-organisms-cities-and-companies-geoffrey-west-abridged/">Scale : The Universal Laws of Life and Death in Organisms, Cities and Companies &#8211; Geoffrey West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Geoffrey West&#8217;s research centres on a quest to find unifying principles and patterns connecting everything, from cells and ecosystems to cities, social networks and businesses.    </p>
<p>                    Why do organisms and ecosystems scale with size in a remarkably universal and systematic fashion?    </p>
<p>                    Is there a maximum size of cities? Of animals and plants? What about companies?    </p>
<p>                    Can scale show us how to create a more sustainable future?    </p>
<p>                    By applying the rigour of physics to questions of biology, visionary physicist Geoffrey West found that despite the riotous diversity in the sizes of mammals, they are all, to a large degree, scaled versions of each other. This speaks to everything from how long we can expect to live to how many hours of sleep we need. He then made the even bolder move of exploring his work&#8217;s applicability to cities and to the business world. These investigations have led to powerful insights about the elemental natural laws that bind us together in profound ways, and how all complex systems are dancing to the same simple tune, however diverse and unrelated they may seem.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/scale-the-universal-laws-of-life-and-death-in-organisms-cities-and-companies-geoffrey-west-abridged/">Scale : The Universal Laws of Life and Death in Organisms, Cities and Companies &#8211; Geoffrey West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Invisible Thread : The True Story of an 11-Year-Old Panhandler, a Busy Sales Executive, and an Unlikely Meeting with Destiny &#8211; Laura Schroff, Alex Tresniowski (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This inspirational New York Times bestseller chronicles the lifelong friendship between a busy sales executive and a disadvantaged young boy, and how both of their lives were changed by what began as one small gesture of kindness. Stopping was never part of the plan&#8230; She was a successful ad sales rep in Manhattan. He was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/">An Invisible Thread : The True Story of an 11-Year-Old Panhandler, a Busy Sales Executive, and an Unlikely Meeting with Destiny &#8211; Laura Schroff, Alex Tresniowski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This inspirational New York Times bestseller chronicles the lifelong friendship between a busy sales executive and a disadvantaged young boy, and how both of their lives were changed by what began as one small gesture of kindness.     </p>
<p>                    Stopping was never part of the plan&#8230;     </p>
<p>                     She was a successful ad sales rep in Manhattan. He was a homeless, eleven-year-old panhandler on the street. He asked for spare change; she kept walking. But then something stopped her in her tracks, and she went back. And she continued to go back, again and again. They met up nearly every week for years and built an unexpected, life-changing friendship that has today spanned almost three decades.     </p>
<p>                     Whatever made me notice him on that street corner so many years ago is clearly something that cannot be extinguished, no matter how relentless the forces aligned against it. Some may call it spirit. Some may call it heart. It drew me to him, as if we were bound by some invisible, unbreakable thread. And whatever it is, it binds us still.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/">An Invisible Thread : The True Story of an 11-Year-Old Panhandler, a Busy Sales Executive, and an Unlikely Meeting with Destiny &#8211; Laura Schroff, Alex Tresniowski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happy City : Transforming Our Lives Through Urban Design &#8211; Charles Montgomery (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[City & Town Planning - Architectural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban & Municipal Planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Happy City is the story of how the solutions to this century&#8217;s problems lie in unlocking the secrets to great city living This is going to be the century of the city. But what actually makes a good city? Why are some cities a joy to live in? As Charles Montgomery reveals, it&#8217;s not how [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/">Happy City : Transforming Our Lives Through Urban Design &#8211; Charles Montgomery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Happy City is the story of how the solutions to this century&#8217;s problems lie in unlocking the secrets to great city living    </p>
<p>                    This is going to be the century of the city. But what actually makes a good city? Why are some cities a joy to live in?    </p>
<p>                    As Charles Montgomery reveals, it&#8217;s not how much money your neighbours earn, or how pleasant the climate is that makes the most difference. Journeying to dozens of cities &#8211; from Atlanta to Bogota to Vancouver &#8211; he talks to the new champions of the happy city to explore the urban innovations already transforming people&#8217;s lives. He meets the visionary Colombian mayor who turned some of the world&#8217;s most dangerous roads into an urban cycling haven; the Danish architect who brought the lessons of medieval Tuscan towns to modern-day Copenhagen; and the New York City transport commissioner who turned the gridlock of Times Square into a place to lounge in the sun.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the lessons from their stories, from brain science, and from the fascinating realm of urban experimentation, Happy City offers solutions we can all use to improve our livesandshows that simple changes can make all the difference.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Do we live in neighbourhoods that make us happy? Montgomery encourages us to ask without embarrassment, and to think intelligently about the answer&#8217; The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Excellent . . . Montgomery believes in the importance of smart town planning and Happy City is a compendium of its major ideas&#8217; Will Dean, Independent    </p>
<p>                    Charles Montgomery is a journalist and urban experimentalist from Vancouver, Canada. His writings on urban planning, psychology, culture, and history have appeared in magazines and journals on three continents. He is the author of one previous book, and was an original member of the BMW Guggenheim Lab.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happy-city-transforming-our-lives-through-urban-design-charles-montgomery-abridged/">Happy City : Transforming Our Lives Through Urban Design &#8211; Charles Montgomery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The true tale of the 1893 World&#8217;s Fair in Chicago and the cunning serial killer who used the magic and majesty of the fair to lure his victims to their death. &#8220;Relentlessly fuses history and entertainment to give this nonfiction book the dramatic effect of a novel &#8230;. It doesn&#8217;t [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/">The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The true tale of the 1893 World&#8217;s Fair in Chicago and the cunning serial killer who used the magic and majesty of the fair to lure his victims to their death.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Relentlessly fuses history and entertainment to give this nonfiction book the dramatic effect of a novel &#8230;. It doesn&#8217;t hurt that this truth is stranger than fiction.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                    Combining meticulous research with nail-biting storytelling, Erik Larson has crafted a narrative with all the wonder of newly discovered history and the thrills of the best fiction.    </p>
<p>                    Two men, each handsome and unusually adept at his chosen work, embodied an element of the great dynamic that characterized America&#8217;s rush toward the twentieth century. The architect was Daniel Hudson Burnham, the fair&#8217;s brilliant director of works and the builder of many of the country&#8217;s most important structures, including the Flatiron Building in New York and Union Station in Washington, D.C. The murderer was Henry H. Holmes, a young doctor who, in a malign parody of the White City, built his &#8220;World&#8217;s Fair Hotel&#8221; just west of the fairgrounds&#8211;a torture palace complete with dissection table, gas chamber, and 3,000-degree crematorium.     </p>
<p>                    Burnham overcame tremendous obstacles and tragedies as he organized the talents of Frederick Law Olmsted, Charles McKim, Louis Sullivan, and others to transform swampy Jackson Park into the White City, while Holmes used the attraction of the great fair and his own satanic charms to lure scores of young women to their deaths. What makes the story all the more chilling is that Holmes really lived, walking the grounds of that dream city by the lake.     </p>
<p>                    The Devil in the White City draws the reader into the enchantment of the Guilded Age, made all the more appealing by a supporting cast of real-life characters, including Buffalo Bill, Theodore Dreiser, Susan B. Anthony, Thomas Edison, Archduke Francis Ferdinand, and others. Erik Larson&#8217;s gifts as a storyteller are magnificently displayed in this rich narrative of the master builder, the killer, and the great fair that obsessed them both.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/">The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ghetto : The Invention of a Place, the History of an Idea &#8211; Professor of Sociology Mitchell Duneier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban & Municipal Planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book of 2016 Winner of the Zócalo Public Square Book Prize On March 29, 1516, the city council of Venice issued a decree forcing Jews to live in il geto&#8211;a closed quarter named for the copper foundry that once occupied the area. The term stuck. In this sweeping and original [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/">Ghetto : The Invention of a Place, the History of an Idea &#8211; Professor of Sociology Mitchell Duneier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book of 2016<br />
                    Winner of the Zócalo Public Square Book Prize     </p>
<p>                    On March 29, 1516, the city council of Venice issued a decree forcing Jews to live in il geto&#8211;a closed quarter named for the copper foundry that once occupied the area. The term stuck.     </p>
<p>                    In this sweeping and original account, Mitchell Duneier traces the idea of the ghetto from its beginnings in the sixteenth century and its revival by the Nazis to the present. As Duneier shows, we cannot comprehend the entanglements of race, poverty, and place in America today without recalling the ghettos of Europe, as well as earlier efforts to understand the problems of the American city.     </p>
<p>                    Ghetto is the story of the scholars and activists who tried to achieve that understanding. As Duneier shows, their efforts to wrestle with race and poverty cannot be divorced from their individual biographies, which often included direct encounters with prejudice and discrimination in the academy and elsewhere. Using new and forgotten sources, Duneier introduces us to Horace Cayton and St. Clair Drake, graduate students whose conception of the South Side of Chicago established a new paradigm for thinking about Northern racism and poverty in the 1940s. We learn how the psychologist Kenneth Clark subsequently linked Harlem&#8217;s slum conditions with the persistence of black powerlessness, and we follow the controversy over Daniel Patrick Moynihan&#8217;s report on the black family. We see how the sociologist William Julius Wilson redefined the debate about urban America as middle-class African Americans increasingly escaped the ghetto and the country retreated from racially specific remedies. And we trace the education reformer Geoffrey Canada&#8217;s efforts to transform the lives of inner-city children with ambitious interventions, even as other reformers sought to help families escape their neighborhoods altogether.     </p>
<p>                    Duneier offers a clear-eyed assessment of the thinkers and doers who have shaped American ideas about urban poverty&#8211;and the ghetto. The result is a valuable new estimation of an age-old concept.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/">Ghetto : The Invention of a Place, the History of an Idea &#8211; Professor of Sociology Mitchell Duneier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land *A New York Post Must-Read Book* *A Newsweek Best New Book* *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017* *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017* *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks* The Wall Street Journal: A devastating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land     </p>
<p>                    *A New York Post Must-Read Book*<br />
                    *A Newsweek Best New Book*<br />
                    *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017*<br />
                    *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017*<br />
                    *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks*     </p>
<p>                    The Wall Street Journal: A devastating portrait&#8230;For anyone wondering why swing-state America voted against the establishment in 2016, Mr. Alexander supplies plenty of answers.      </p>
<p>                    Laura Miller, Slate: This book hunts bigger game. Reads like an odd&#8211;and oddly satisfying&#8211;fusion of George Packer&#8217;s The Unwinding and one of Michael Lewis&#8217; real-life financial thrillers.     </p>
<p>                    The New Yorker: Does a remarkable job.     </p>
<p>                    Beth Macy, author of Factory Man: This book should be required reading for people trying to understand Trumpism, inequality, and the sad state of a needlessly wrecked rural America. I wish I had written it.      </p>
<p>                    In 1947, Forbes magazine declared Lancaster, Ohio the epitome of the all-American town. Today it is damaged, discouraged, and fighting for its future. In Glass House, journalist Brian Alexander uses the story of one town to show how seeds sown 35 years ago have sprouted to give us Trumpism, inequality, and an eroding national cohesion.     </p>
<p>                    The Anchor Hocking Glass Company, once the world&#8217;s largest maker of glass tableware, was the base on which Lancaster&#8217;s society was built. As Glass House unfolds, bankruptcy looms. With access to the company and its leaders, and Lancaster&#8217;s citizens, Alexander shows how financial engineering took hold in the 1980s, accelerated in the 21st Century, and wrecked the company. We follow CEO Sam Solomon, an African-American leading the nearly all-white town&#8217;s biggest private employer, as he tries to rescue the company from the New York private equity firm that hired him. Meanwhile, Alexander goes behind the scenes, entwined with the lives of residents as they wrestle with heroin, politics, high-interest lenders, low wage jobs, technology, and the new demands of American life: people like Brian Gossett, the fourth generation to work at Anchor Hocking; Joe Piccolo, first-time director of the annual music festival who discovers the town relies on him, and it, for salvation; Jason Roach, who police believed may have been Lancaster&#8217;s biggest drug dealer; and Eric Brown, a local football hero-turned-cop who comes to realize that he can never arrest Lancaster&#8217;s real problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behind the Beautiful Forevers : Life, Death and Hope in a Mumbai Slum &#8211; Katherine Boo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behind-the-beautiful-forevers-life-death-and-hope-in-a-mumbai-slum-katherine-boo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behind-the-beautiful-forevers-life-death-and-hope-in-a-mumbai-slum-katherine-boo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Annawadi is a slum at the edge of Mumbai Airport, in the shadow of shining new luxury hotels. Its residents are garbage recyclers and construction workers, economic migrants, all of them living in the hope that a small part of India&#8217;s booming future will eventually be theirs. But when a crime rocks the slum community [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behind-the-beautiful-forevers-life-death-and-hope-in-a-mumbai-slum-katherine-boo-abridged/">Behind the Beautiful Forevers : Life, Death and Hope in a Mumbai Slum &#8211; Katherine Boo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Annawadi is a slum at the edge of Mumbai Airport, in the shadow of shining new luxury hotels. Its residents are garbage recyclers and construction workers, economic migrants, all of them living in the hope that a small part of India&#8217;s booming future will eventually be theirs. But when a crime rocks the slum community and global recession and terrorism shocks the city, tensions over religion, caste, sex, power, and economic envy begin to turn brutal. As Boo gets to know those who dwell at Mumbai&#8217;s margins, she evokes an extraordinarily vivid and vigorous group of individuals flourishing against the odds amid the complications, corruptions and gross inequalities of the new India.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behind-the-beautiful-forevers-life-death-and-hope-in-a-mumbai-slum-katherine-boo-abridged/">Behind the Beautiful Forevers : Life, Death and Hope in a Mumbai Slum &#8211; Katherine Boo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
