<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Population &amp; Demography Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/population-demography/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/population-demography/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Population &amp; Demography Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/population-demography/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ghetto : The Invention of a Place, the History of an Idea &#8211; Professor of Sociology Mitchell Duneier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban & Municipal Planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book of 2016 Winner of the Zócalo Public Square Book Prize On March 29, 1516, the city council of Venice issued a decree forcing Jews to live in il geto&#8211;a closed quarter named for the copper foundry that once occupied the area. The term stuck. In this sweeping and original [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/">Ghetto : The Invention of a Place, the History of an Idea &#8211; Professor of Sociology Mitchell Duneier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book of 2016<br />
                    Winner of the Zócalo Public Square Book Prize     </p>
<p>                    On March 29, 1516, the city council of Venice issued a decree forcing Jews to live in il geto&#8211;a closed quarter named for the copper foundry that once occupied the area. The term stuck.     </p>
<p>                    In this sweeping and original account, Mitchell Duneier traces the idea of the ghetto from its beginnings in the sixteenth century and its revival by the Nazis to the present. As Duneier shows, we cannot comprehend the entanglements of race, poverty, and place in America today without recalling the ghettos of Europe, as well as earlier efforts to understand the problems of the American city.     </p>
<p>                    Ghetto is the story of the scholars and activists who tried to achieve that understanding. As Duneier shows, their efforts to wrestle with race and poverty cannot be divorced from their individual biographies, which often included direct encounters with prejudice and discrimination in the academy and elsewhere. Using new and forgotten sources, Duneier introduces us to Horace Cayton and St. Clair Drake, graduate students whose conception of the South Side of Chicago established a new paradigm for thinking about Northern racism and poverty in the 1940s. We learn how the psychologist Kenneth Clark subsequently linked Harlem&#8217;s slum conditions with the persistence of black powerlessness, and we follow the controversy over Daniel Patrick Moynihan&#8217;s report on the black family. We see how the sociologist William Julius Wilson redefined the debate about urban America as middle-class African Americans increasingly escaped the ghetto and the country retreated from racially specific remedies. And we trace the education reformer Geoffrey Canada&#8217;s efforts to transform the lives of inner-city children with ambitious interventions, even as other reformers sought to help families escape their neighborhoods altogether.     </p>
<p>                    Duneier offers a clear-eyed assessment of the thinkers and doers who have shaped American ideas about urban poverty&#8211;and the ghetto. The result is a valuable new estimation of an age-old concept.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ghetto-the-invention-of-a-place-the-history-of-an-idea-professor-of-sociology-mitchell-duneier-abridged/">Ghetto : The Invention of a Place, the History of an Idea &#8211; Professor of Sociology Mitchell Duneier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Three Women : A BBC 2 Between the Covers Book Club Pick &#8211; Lisa Taddeo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/three-women-a-bbc-2-between-the-covers-book-club-pick-lisa-taddeo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sexual Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/three-women-a-bbc-2-between-the-covers-book-club-pick-lisa-taddeo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The International No. 1 Bestseller A BBC 2 Between the Covers Book Club Pick &#8216;Cuts to the heart of who we are&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;A book that begs discussion&#8217; Vanity Fair All Lina wanted was to be desired. How did she end up in a marriage with two children and a husband who wouldn&#8217;t touch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/three-women-a-bbc-2-between-the-covers-book-club-pick-lisa-taddeo-abridged/">Three Women : A BBC 2 Between the Covers Book Club Pick &#8211; Lisa Taddeo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The International No. 1 Bestseller<br />
                    A BBC 2 Between the Covers Book Club Pick    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Cuts to the heart of who we are&#8217; Sunday Times<br />
                    &#8216;A book that begs discussion&#8217; Vanity Fair    </p>
<p>                    All Lina wanted was to be desired. How did she end up in a marriage with two children and a husband who wouldn&#8217;t touch her?    </p>
<p>                    All Maggie wanted was to be understood. How did she end up in a relationship with her teacher and then in court, a hated pariah in her small town?    </p>
<p>                    All Sloane wanted was to be admired. How did she end up a sexual object of men, including her husband, who liked to watch her have sex with other men and women?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I will probably re-read it every year of my life&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Will have millions nodding in recognition&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;As gripping as the most gripping thriller&#8217; Marian Keyes    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;When I picked it up, I felt I&#8217;d been waiting half my life to read it&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The kind of bold, timely, once-in-a-generation book that every house should have a copy of, and probably will before too long&#8217; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    The book Phoebe Waller-Bridge, Alexa Chung, Jodie Comer, Reese Witherspoon, Harry Styles, Fearne Cotton, Caitriona Balfe, Gwyneth Paltrow, Sharon Horgan, Zoe Ball, Rosie Huntington-Whiteley, Davina McCall, Gemma Chan, Christine and the Queens and Gillian Anderson are all reading</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/three-women-a-bbc-2-between-the-covers-book-club-pick-lisa-taddeo-abridged/">Three Women : A BBC 2 Between the Covers Book Club Pick &#8211; Lisa Taddeo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Where You Belong : Finding Home Wherever You Are &#8211; Melody Warnick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-where-you-belong-finding-home-wherever-you-are-melody-warnick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-where-you-belong-finding-home-wherever-you-are-melody-warnick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Gretchen Rubin&#8217;s megaseller The Happiness Project and Eric Weiner&#8217;s The Geography of Bliss, a journalist embarks on a project to discover what it takes to love where you live The average restless American will move 11.7 times in a lifetime. For Melody Warnick, it was move #6, from Austin, Texas, to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-where-you-belong-finding-home-wherever-you-are-melody-warnick-abridged/">This Is Where You Belong : Finding Home Wherever You Are &#8211; Melody Warnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Gretchen Rubin&#8217;s megaseller The Happiness Project and Eric Weiner&#8217;s The Geography of Bliss, a journalist embarks on a project to discover what it takes to love where you live    </p>
<p>                    The average restless American will move 11.7 times in a lifetime. For Melody Warnick, it was move #6, from Austin, Texas, to Blacksburg, Virginia, that threatened to unhinge her. In the lonely aftermath of unpacking, she wondered: Aren&#8217;t we supposed to put down roots at some point? How does the place we live become the place we want to stay? This time, she had an epiphany. Rather than hold her breath and hope this new town would be her family&#8217;s perfect fit, she would figure out how to fall in love with it-no matter what.<br />
                         How we come to feel at home in our towns and cities is what Warnick sets out to discover in This Is Where You Belong. She dives into the body of research around place attachment-the deep sense of connection that binds some of us to our cities and increases our physical and emotional well-being-then travels to towns across America to see it in action. Inspired by a growing movement of placemaking, she examines what its practitioners are doing to create likeable locales. She also speaks with frequent movers and loyal stayers around the country to learn what draws highly mobile Americans to a new city, and what makes us stay. The best ideas she imports to her adopted hometown of Blacksburg for a series of Love Where You Live experiments designed to make her feel more locally connected. Dining with her neighbors. Shopping Small Business Saturday. Marching in the town Christmas parade.<br />
                         Can these efforts make a halfhearted resident happier? Will Blacksburg be the place she finally stays? What Warnick learns will inspire you to embrace your own community-and perhaps discover that the place where you live right now . . . is home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-where-you-belong-finding-home-wherever-you-are-melody-warnick-abridged/">This Is Where You Belong : Finding Home Wherever You Are &#8211; Melody Warnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Hour of Eugenics&#8221; : Race, Gender, and Nation in Latin America &#8211; Nancy Leys Stepan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eugenics was a term coined in 1883 to name the scientific and social theory which advocated &#8220;race improvement&#8221; through selective human breeding. In Europe and the United States the eugenics movement found many supporters before it was finally discredited by its association with the racist ideology of Nazi Germany. Examining for the first time how [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/">The Hour of Eugenics&#8221; : Race, Gender, and Nation in Latin America &#8211; Nancy Leys Stepan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eugenics was a term coined in 1883 to name the scientific and social theory which advocated &#8220;race improvement&#8221; through selective human breeding. In Europe and the United States the eugenics movement found many supporters before it was finally discredited by its association with the racist ideology of Nazi Germany. Examining for the first time how eugenics was taken up by scientists and social reformers in Latin America, Nancy Leys Stepan compares the eugenics movements in Mexico, Brazil, and Argentina with the more familiar cases of Britain, the United States, and Germany.In this highly original account, Stepan sheds new light on the role of science in reformulating issues of race, gender, reproduction, and public health in an era when the focus on national identity was particularly intense. Drawing upon a rich body of evidence concerning the technical publications and professional meetings of Latin American eugenicists, she examines how they adapted eugenic principles to local contexts between the world wars. Stepan shows that Latin American eugenicists diverged considerably from their counterparts in Europe and the United States in their ideological approach and their interpretations of key texts concerning heredity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/">The Hour of Eugenics&#8221; : Race, Gender, and Nation in Latin America &#8211; Nancy Leys Stepan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All the Single Ladies : Unmarried Women and the Rise of an Independent Nation &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/all-the-single-ladies-unmarried-women-and-the-rise-of-an-independent-nation-rebecca-traister-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/all-the-single-ladies-unmarried-women-and-the-rise-of-an-independent-nation-rebecca-traister-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOKS OF 2016 SELECTION * BEST BOOKS OF 2016 SELECTION BY THE BOSTON GLOBE * ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY * NPR * CHICAGO PUBLIC LIBRARY * The New York Times bestselling investigation into the sexual, economic, and emotional lives of women is &#8220;an informative and thought-provoking book for anyone-not just the single [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-the-single-ladies-unmarried-women-and-the-rise-of-an-independent-nation-rebecca-traister-abridged/">All the Single Ladies : Unmarried Women and the Rise of an Independent Nation &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOKS OF 2016 SELECTION * BEST BOOKS OF 2016 SELECTION BY THE BOSTON GLOBE * ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY * NPR * CHICAGO PUBLIC LIBRARY *    </p>
<p>                     The New York Times bestselling investigation into the sexual, economic, and emotional lives of women is &#8220;an informative and thought-provoking book for anyone-not just the single ladies-who want to gain a greater understanding of this pivotal moment in the history of the United States&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review).    </p>
<p>                    In 2009, award-winning journalist Rebecca Traister started All the Single Ladies about the twenty-first century phenomenon of the American single woman. It was the year the proportion of American women who were married dropped below fifty percent; and the median age of first marriages, which had remained between twenty and twenty-two years old for nearly a century (1890-1980), had risen dramatically to twenty-seven.    </p>
<p>                    But over the course of her vast research and more than a hundred interviews with academics and social scientists and prominent single women, Traister discovered a startling truth: the phenomenon of the single woman in America is not a new one. And historically, when women were given options beyond early heterosexual marriage, the results were massive social change-temperance, abolition, secondary education, and more. Today, only twenty percent of Americans are married by age twenty-nine, compared to nearly sixty percent in 1960.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An informative and thought-provoking book for anyone-not just single ladies&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review), All the Single Ladies is a remarkable portrait of contemporary American life and how we got here, through the lens of the unmarried American woman. Covering class, race, sexual orientation, and filled with vivid anecdotes from fascinating contemporary and historical figures, &#8220;we&#8217;re better off reading Rebecca Traister on women, politics, and America than pretty much anyone else&#8221; (The Boston Globe).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-the-single-ladies-unmarried-women-and-the-rise-of-an-independent-nation-rebecca-traister-abridged/">All the Single Ladies : Unmarried Women and the Rise of an Independent Nation &#8211; Rebecca Traister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart the crucial role of violent shocks in reducing inequality over the full sweep of human history around the world. The &#8220;Four Horsemen&#8221; of leveling-mass-mobilization warfare, transformative revolutions, state collapse, and catastrophic plagues-have repeatedly destroyed the fortunes of the rich. Today, the violence that reduced inequality in the past seems to have diminished, and that is a good thing. But it casts serious doubt on the prospects for a more equal future. An essential contribution to the debate about inequality, The Great Leveler provides important new insights about why inequality is so persistent-and why it is unlikely to decline anytime soon.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
