<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Film Theory &amp; Criticism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/film-theory-criticism/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/film-theory-criticism/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Film Theory &amp; Criticism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/film-theory-criticism/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Licence to Kill : The Science of 007 &#8211; Kathryn Harkup</title>
		<link>/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Fleming&#8217;s series of novels based on the adventures of the secret service agent James Bond have thrilled and delighted readers since Casino Royale first published in 1953. And when the film of Dr No was released in 1962, Bond quickly became one of the world&#8217;s favourite secret agents. The character has been through some [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/">Licence to Kill : The Science of 007 &#8211; Kathryn Harkup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ian Fleming&#8217;s series of novels based on the adventures of the secret service agent James Bond have thrilled and delighted readers since Casino Royale first published in 1953. And when the film of Dr No was released in 1962, Bond quickly became one of the world&#8217;s favourite secret agents. The character has been through some changes and had a few ups and downs but his popularity endures, and the film franchise is currently the fifth-highest-grossing series in history. </p>
<p>                    Science and technology have always been central to the thrilling plots than make up the world of Bond, and in this book Kathryn Harkup explores this; as in some of her previous books, she takes the angle of death as a starting point to explore the science behind the story. </p>
<p>                    Naturally, there are 007 chapters, covering the full range of Bond&#8217;s exploits, and the arms, technologies, tactics and downfalls of his various foes. </p>
<p>                    In Licence to Kill, Kathryn turns her expert eye on the world&#8217;s favourite secret agent, using the hook of Bond&#8217;s enduring popularity to discuss the realities behind the silver screen. Could our favourite Bond villains actually achieve world domination? Were the huge variety of weapons and technology in Bond&#8217;s arsenal ever actually developed? And would 007 actually escape all those close shaves with his life intact? Readers will see the Bond films through new eyes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/">Licence to Kill : The Science of 007 &#8211; Kathryn Harkup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Still Just a Geek &#8211; Wil Wheaton</title>
		<link>/still-just-a-geek-wil-wheaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Acting Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diaries, Letters & Journals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV Tie-in Humour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/still-just-a-geek-wil-wheaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Celebrated actor, personality, and all-around nerd Wil Wheaton updates his memoir of collected blog posts with all new material and annotations as he reexamines one of the most interesting lives in Hollywood and fandom! Wil Wheaton grew up. Ideally, this is what everyone does. But most of us don&#8217;t do it in front of millions [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/still-just-a-geek-wil-wheaton/">Still Just a Geek &#8211; Wil Wheaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Celebrated actor, personality, and all-around nerd Wil Wheaton updates his memoir of collected blog posts with all new material and annotations as he reexamines one of the most interesting lives in Hollywood and fandom!<br />
                              Wil Wheaton grew up.    </p>
<p>                              Ideally, this is what everyone does. But most of us don&#8217;t do it in front of millions of people. Wil was a very famous kid &#8211; right up until he wasn&#8217;t. After that, he wasn&#8217;t sure who he was at all.    </p>
<p>                              So, in 2001, he started a blog. It was less about being a famous child than about being a not-so-famous grownup. He wrote about his pets and his hobbies, punk rock and parenting, board games and birthdays and (most importantly) burritos.    </p>
<p>                              He thought he was writing for an audience of one: himself. To be fair, he was only off by about 3 million people. In Still Just a Geek, an older, somewhat wiser Wil revisits Just a Geek, his 2004 collection of posts from that blog, with all-new reflections on nerd culture, fame, love, trauma, tragedy, and confronting the worst parts of yourself.    </p>
<p>                                Equal parts funny and poignant, Still Just a Geek explores the folly of youth and the pain of experience &#8211; and all the strange, awful, beautiful adventures in between.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/still-just-a-geek-wil-wheaton/">Still Just a Geek &#8211; Wil Wheaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Better Living Through Criticism: How to Think about Art, Pleasure, Beauty and Truth &#8211; A. O. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Few could explain, let alone seek out, a career in criticism. Yet what A. O. Scott shows in Better Living Through Criticism is that we are, in fact, all critics: because critical thinking informs almost every aspect of artistic creation, of civil action, of interpersonal life. With penetrating insight and humour, Scott shows that while [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/">Better Living Through Criticism: How to Think about Art, Pleasure, Beauty and Truth &#8211; A. O. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Few could explain, let alone seek out, a career in criticism. Yet what A. O. Scott shows in Better Living Through Criticism is that we are, in fact, all critics: because critical thinking informs almost every aspect of artistic creation, of civil action, of interpersonal life. With penetrating insight and humour, Scott shows that while individual critics &#8211; himself included &#8211; can make mistakes and find flaws where they shouldn&#8217;t, criticism as a discipline is one of the noblest, most creative and urgent activities.    </p>
<p>                    Using his own film criticism as a starting point &#8211; everything from an infamous dismissal of the international blockbuster The Avengers to his intense affection for Pixar&#8217;s animated Ratatouille &#8211; Scott expands outwards, easily guiding readers through the complexities of Rilke and Shelley, the origins of Chuck Berry and the Rolling Stones, the power of Marina Abramovic and &#8216;Ode on a Grecian Urn&#8217; Scott shows that real criticism was and always will be the breath of fresh air that allows true creativity to thrive. As he puts it: &#8216;The time for criticism is always now, because the imperative to think clearly, never goes away.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/">Better Living Through Criticism: How to Think about Art, Pleasure, Beauty and Truth &#8211; A. O. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FULLY REVISED &#038; UPDATED, WITH A NEW EPILOGUE &#8220;Delightful.&#8221;-The Economist There&#8217;s Santa Claus, Shakespeare, Mickey Mouse, the Bible, and then there&#8217;s Star Wars. Nothing quite compares to sitting down with a young child and hearing the sound of John Williams&#8217;s score as those beloved golden letters fill the screen. In this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/">The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    FULLY REVISED &#038; UPDATED, WITH A NEW EPILOGUE    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Delightful.&#8221;-The Economist    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s Santa Claus, Shakespeare, Mickey Mouse, the Bible, and then there&#8217;s Star Wars. Nothing quite compares to sitting down with a young child and hearing the sound of John Williams&#8217;s score as those beloved golden letters fill the screen. In this fun, erudite, and often moving book, Cass R. Sunstein explores the lessons of Star Wars as they relate to childhood, fathers, the Dark Side, rebellion, and redemption. As it turns out, Star Wars also has a lot to teach us about constitutional law, economics, and political uprisings.    </p>
<p>                              In rich detail, Sunstein tells the story of the films&#8217; wildly unanticipated success and explores why some things succeed while others fail. Ultimately, Sunstein argues, Star Wars is about freedom of choice and our never-ending ability to make the right decision when the chips are down. Written with buoyant prose and considerable heart, The World According to Star Wars shines a bright new light on the most beloved story of our time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-according-to-star-wars-cass-r-sunstein-abridged/">The World According to Star Wars &#8211; Cass R. Sunstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
