<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Terrorism, Armed Struggle Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/terrorism-armed-struggle/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/terrorism-armed-struggle/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Terrorism, Armed Struggle Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/terrorism-armed-struggle/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Isis: Inside The Army Of Terror : Updated Edition &#8211; Michael Weiß, Hassan Hassan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/isis-inside-the-army-of-terror-updated-edition-michael-weis-hassan-hassan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/isis-inside-the-army-of-terror-updated-edition-michael-weis-hassan-hassan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fully Revised &#038; Updated Edition of the New York Times Bestselling and Highly Praised Book on ISIS With newly added material and breaking news including: &#8211;Interview with a former ISIS spymaster &#8211;Why ISIS is targeting Europe and the US &#8211;What Russia wants in Syria &#8211;Revelations on the brutal ideology of ISIS With brutal attacks in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/isis-inside-the-army-of-terror-updated-edition-michael-weis-hassan-hassan-abridged/">Isis: Inside The Army Of Terror : Updated Edition &#8211; Michael Weiß, Hassan Hassan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fully Revised &#038; Updated Edition of the New York Times Bestselling and Highly Praised Book on ISIS  With newly added material and breaking news including:<br />
                     &#8211;Interview with a former ISIS spymaster<br />
                     &#8211;Why ISIS is targeting Europe and the US<br />
                     &#8211;What Russia wants in Syria<br />
                     &#8211;Revelations on the brutal ideology of ISIS With brutal attacks in last year across the globe&#8211;Brussels, Paris, Beirut, Egypt, Turkey&#8211;the Islamic State of Iraq and Syria (ISIS) has proved itself the greatest terrorist threat in the world today. They have conquered massive territories in Syria and Iraq in a bid to create a new Muslim caliphate under the strict dictates of Sharia law.  In this fully revised and updated edition of ISIS: Inside the Army of Terror, American journalist Michael Weiss and Syrian analyst Hassan Hassan explain how these violent extremists evolved from a nearly defeated Iraqi insurgent group into a jihadi army of international volunteers who, with slickly produced murder videos, are spreading violence and mayhem across the globe. Beginning with the early days of Abu Musab al-Zarqawi, the founder of ISIS&#8217;s first incarnation, Weiss and Hassan explain who the key players are&#8211;from their leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi to the former Saddam Baathists in their ranks&#8211;where they come from, how they have attracted both local and global support, and how they operate&#8211;from their social media strategy to their illicit oil revenues. As money and matériel continue to flow into the region to combat the ISIS&#8217;s spreading terror, other forces&#8211;Assad&#8217;s regime, Russian planes, Iranian Quds Forces, and other Shiite militias&#8211;are gaining power and using the fight against ISIS as a means to leverage their agenda in the region.  Political and military maneuvering by the United States, Iraq, Iran, Syria, and Russia have fueled ISIS&#8217;s explosive expansion. In five new chapters, the authors delve further into the inner workings of the Army of Terror and what it is like to live under their ever-tightening rule. With invaluable and exclusive insider information, the authors explore the Islamic State&#8217;s enigmatic recruitment and training methods, the impact of their military successes and failures, and how they structure and empower home-grown cells worldwide to carry out their terror. Drawing on original interviews with former US military officials and current ISIS fighters&#8211;and brand-new interviews with a former ISIS spy, as well as Kurdish and Yazidi survivors of the ISIS&#8217;s assault on northern Iraq&#8211;the authors reveal the internecine struggles within the movement itself, as well as ISIS&#8217;s bloody hatred of Shiite Muslims, which is generating another sectarian war in the region. A new generation of terror has dawned in the world and to understand how to stop it, we must understand who they are.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/isis-inside-the-army-of-terror-updated-edition-michael-weis-hassan-hassan-abridged/">Isis: Inside The Army Of Terror : Updated Edition &#8211; Michael Weiß, Hassan Hassan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Flags : The Rise of ISIS &#8211; Joby Warrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Fundamentalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**WINNER of the PULITZER PRIZE for NON-FICTION 2016** In a thrilling dramatic narrative, Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter Joby Warrick traces how the strain of militant Islam behind ISIS first arose in a remote Jordanian prison and spread to become the world&#8217;s greatest threat. When the government of Jordan granted amnesty to a group of political prisoners [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/">Black Flags : The Rise of ISIS &#8211; Joby Warrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**WINNER of the PULITZER PRIZE for NON-FICTION 2016**    </p>
<p>                    In a thrilling dramatic narrative, Pulitzer Prize-winning reporter  Joby Warrick traces how the strain of militant Islam behind ISIS first  arose in a remote Jordanian prison and spread to become the world&#8217;s greatest threat.    </p>
<p>                                   When the government of Jordan granted amnesty to a group of political prisoners in 1999, it little realized that among them was Abu Musab al-Zarqawi, a terrorist mastermind and soon the architect of an Islamist movement bent on dominating the Middle East. In Black Flags, an unprecedented character-driven account of the rise of ISIS, Joby Warrick shows how the zeal of this one man and the strategic mistakes of Western governments led to the banner of ISIS being raised over huge swathes of Syria and Iraq.    </p>
<p>                     Zarqawi began by directing terror attacks from a base in northern Iraq, but it was the allied invasion in 2003 that catapulted him to the head of a vast insurgency. By falsely identifying him as the link between Saddam Hussein and Osama bin Laden, Western officials inadvertently spurred like-minded radicals to rally to his cause. Their wave of brutal beheadings and suicide bombings persisted until American and Jordanian intelligence discovered clues that led to a lethal airstrike on Zarqawi&#8217;s hideout in 2006.    </p>
<p>                     His movement, however, endured. First calling themselves al-Qaeda in Iraq, then Islamic State of Iraq and Syria, or ISIS, his followers sought refuge in unstable, ungoverned pockets on the Iraq-Syria border. When the Syrian civil war broke out in 2011, and the rest of the world largely stood by, ISIS seized its chance to pursue Zarqawi&#8217;s dream of an ultra-conservative Islamic caliphate.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on unique high-level access to global intelligence sources, Warrick weaves gripping, moment-by-moment operational details with the perspectives of diplomats and spies, generals and heads of state, many of whom foresaw a menace worse than al Qaeda and tried desperately to stop it. Black Flags is a brilliant and definitive history that reveals the long arc of today&#8217;s most dangerous extremist threat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-flags-the-rise-of-isis-joby-warrick-abridged/">Black Flags : The Rise of ISIS &#8211; Joby Warrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Looming Tower : Al Qaeda&#8217;s Road to 9/11 &#8211; Lawrence Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-looming-tower-al-qaedas-road-to-9-11-lawrence-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-looming-tower-al-qaedas-road-to-9-11-lawrence-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE PULITZER PRIZE-WINNING BESTSELLER, NOW AN ACCLAIMED TV SERIES This is the definitive account of the run-up to 9/11: from the man who lit the spark of radical Islam in 1948, to those who built up a terror network, and to the FBI agent whose warnings of &#8216;something big&#8217; coming were ignored until the Twin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-looming-tower-al-qaedas-road-to-9-11-lawrence-wright-abridged/">The Looming Tower : Al Qaeda&#8217;s Road to 9/11 &#8211; Lawrence Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE PULITZER PRIZE-WINNING BESTSELLER, NOW AN ACCLAIMED TV SERIES    </p>
<p>                    This is the definitive account of the run-up to 9/11: from the man who lit the spark of radical Islam in 1948, to those who built up a terror network, and to the FBI agent whose warnings of &#8216;something big&#8217; coming were ignored until the Twin Towers fell.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The Looming Tower is a thriller. And it&#8217;s a tragedy, too&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The most detailed (and thrilling) account we have of the events that led to the destruction of the Twin Towers&#8217; Observer, Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Possibly the best book yet written on the rise of al-Qaeda &#8230; beautifully written and wonderfully compelling&#8217; William Dalrymple    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We meet some formidable schemers and killers &#8230; fabulists crazed with blood and death&#8217; Martin Amis</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-looming-tower-al-qaedas-road-to-9-11-lawrence-wright-abridged/">The Looming Tower : Al Qaeda&#8217;s Road to 9/11 &#8211; Lawrence Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave New War : The Next Stage of Terrorism and the End of Globalization &#8211; John Robb, Foreword by James Fallows (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For my money, John Robb, a former Air Force officer and tech guru, is the futurists&#8217; futurist. &#8211;Slate The counterterrorism expert John Robb reveals how the same technology that has enabled globalization also allows terrorists and criminals to join forces against larger adversaries with relative ease and to carry out small, inexpensive actions&#8211;like sabotaging an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/">Brave New War : The Next Stage of Terrorism and the End of Globalization &#8211; John Robb, Foreword by James Fallows (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For my money, John Robb, a former Air Force officer and tech guru, is the futurists&#8217; futurist.<br />
                    &#8211;Slate    </p>
<p>                    The counterterrorism expert John Robb reveals how the same technology that has enabled globalization also allows terrorists and criminals to join forces against larger adversaries with relative ease and to carry out small, inexpensive actions&#8211;like sabotaging an oil pipeline&#8211;that generate a huge return. He shows how combating the shutdown of the world&#8217;s oil, high-tech, and financial markets could cost us the thing we&#8217;ve come to value the most&#8211;worldwide economic and cultural integration&#8211;and what we must do now to safeguard against this new method of warfare.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/">Brave New War : The Next Stage of Terrorism and the End of Globalization &#8211; John Robb, Foreword by James Fallows (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terrorism And The Constitution : Sacrificing Civil Liberties in the Name of National Security &#8211; David Cole (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/terrorism-and-the-constitution-sacrificing-civil-liberties-in-the-name-of-national-security-david-cole-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/terrorism-and-the-constitution-sacrificing-civil-liberties-in-the-name-of-national-security-david-cole-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tracing the history of government intrusions on Constitutional rights in response to threats from abroad, Cole and Dempsey warn that a society in which civil liberties are sacrificed in the name of national security is in fact less secure than one in which they are upheld. A new chapter includes a discussion of domestic spying, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/terrorism-and-the-constitution-sacrificing-civil-liberties-in-the-name-of-national-security-david-cole-abridged/">Terrorism And The Constitution : Sacrificing Civil Liberties in the Name of National Security &#8211; David Cole (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tracing the history of government intrusions on Constitutional rights in response to threats from abroad, Cole and Dempsey warn that a society in which civil liberties are sacrificed in the name of national security is in fact less secure than one in which they are upheld.    </p>
<p>                    A new chapter includes a discussion of domestic spying, preventive detention, the many court challenges to post-9/11 abuses, implementation of the PATRIOT ACT, and efforts to reestablish the checks and balances left behind in the rush to strengthen governmental powers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/terrorism-and-the-constitution-sacrificing-civil-liberties-in-the-name-of-national-security-david-cole-abridged/">Terrorism And The Constitution : Sacrificing Civil Liberties in the Name of National Security &#8211; David Cole (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
