<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Software Engineering Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/software-engineering/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/software-engineering/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Software Engineering Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/software-engineering/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Programming / Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221; Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term? While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221;<br />
                     Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb    </p>
<p>                    How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term?  While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments of creation and conclusion, The Messy Middle argues that the real key to success is how you navigate the ups-and-downs after initial investment is secured. It will give you all the insights you need to build and optimize your team, improve your product and develop your own capacity to lead covering:<br />
                    *         Coping with uncertainty and conflict<br />
                    *         Playing the long game<br />
                    *         Optimising your team<br />
                    *         Problem solving through the ups and downs<br />
                    *         Adapting your strategy<br />
                    *         When to quit<br />
                    Building on seven years&#8217; of meticulous research with entrepreneurs, small agencies, start-ups and billion-dollar companies, Scott Belsky offers indispensable lessons on how to endure and thrive in the long term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Founders at Work : Stories of Startups&#8217; Early Days &#8211; Jessica Livingston (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/founders-at-work-stories-of-startups-early-days-jessica-livingston-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/founders-at-work-stories-of-startups-early-days-jessica-livingston-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now available in paperback-with a new preface and interview with Jessica Livingston about Y Combinator! Founders at Work: Stories of Startups&#8217; Early Days is a collection of interviews with founders of famous technology companies about what happened in the very earliest days. These people are celebrities now. What was it like when they were just [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/founders-at-work-stories-of-startups-early-days-jessica-livingston-abridged/">Founders at Work : Stories of Startups&#8217; Early Days &#8211; Jessica Livingston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now available in paperback-with a new preface and interview with Jessica Livingston about Y Combinator!    </p>
<p>                     Founders at Work: Stories of Startups&#8217; Early Days is a collection of interviews with founders of famous technology companies about what happened in the very earliest days. These people are celebrities now. What was it like when they were just a couple friends with an idea? Founders like Steve Wozniak (Apple), Caterina Fake (Flickr), Mitch Kapor (Lotus), Max Levchin (PayPal), and Sabeer Bhatia (Hotmail) tell you in their own words about their surprising and often very funny discoveries as they learned how to build a company.    </p>
<p>                     Where did they get the ideas that made them rich? How did they convince investors to back them? What went wrong, and how did they recover?    </p>
<p>                     Nearly all technical people have thought of one day starting or working for a startup. For them, this book is the closest you can come to being a fly on the wall at a successful startup, to learn how it&#8217;s done.    </p>
<p>                     But ultimately these interviews are required reading for anyone who wants to understand business, because startups are business reduced to its essence. The reason their founders become rich is that startups do what businesses do-create value-more intensively than almost any other part of the economy. How? What are the secrets that make successful startups so insanely productive? Read this book, and let the founders themselves tell you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/founders-at-work-stories-of-startups-early-days-jessica-livingston-abridged/">Founders at Work : Stories of Startups&#8217; Early Days &#8211; Jessica Livingston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FIRE : How Fast, Inexpensive, Restrained, and Elegant Methods Ignite Innovation &#8211; Dan Ward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Noted military technology expert Dan Ward&#8217;s manifesto for creating great products and projects using the methods of rapid innovation. Why do some programs deliver their product under cost, while others bust their budget? Why do some deliver ahead of schedule, while others experience endless delays? Which products work better-the quick and thrifty or the slow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/">FIRE : How Fast, Inexpensive, Restrained, and Elegant Methods Ignite Innovation &#8211; Dan Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Noted military technology expert Dan Ward&#8217;s manifesto for creating great products and projects using the methods of rapid innovation.  Why do some programs deliver their product under cost, while others bust their budget? Why do some deliver ahead of schedule, while others experience endless delays? Which products work better-the quick and thrifty or the slow and expensive? Which situation leads to superior equipment?  With nearly two decades as an engineering officer in the U. S. Air Force, Dan Ward explored these questions during tours of duty at military research laboratories, the Air Force Institute of Technology, an intelligence agency, the Pentagon and Afghanistan. The pattern he noticed revealed that the most successful project leaders in both the public and private sectors delivered top-shelf products with a skeleton crew, a shoestring budget, and a cannonball schedule. Excessive investment of time, money, or complexity actually reduced innovation. He concluded the secret to innovation is to be fast, inexpensive, simple, and small.  FIRE presents an entertaining and practical framework for pursuing rapid, frugal innovation.<br />
                    A story-filled blend of pop culture and engineering insight, FIRE has something for everyone: strategic concepts leaders can use as they cast a vision, actionable principles for managers as they make business decisions, and practical tools for workers as they design, build, assess and test new products.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fire-how-fast-inexpensive-restrained-and-elegant-methods-ignite-innovation-dan-ward-abridged/">FIRE : How Fast, Inexpensive, Restrained, and Elegant Methods Ignite Innovation &#8211; Dan Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Systems Analysis & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You won&#8217;t find a more honest, raw and helpful look into the trenches of founding a tech startup than this book&#8217; Nir Eyal, author of Hooked &#8216;Rand Fishkin is the real deal&#8217; Seth Godin, entrepreneur and author &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; Everyone knows how a startup story is supposed to go: a young, brilliant entrepreneur has an cool [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/">Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You won&#8217;t find a more honest, raw and helpful look into the trenches of founding a tech startup than this book&#8217; Nir Eyal, author of Hooked    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rand Fishkin is the real deal&#8217; Seth Godin, entrepreneur and author     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    Everyone knows how a startup story is supposed to go: a young, brilliant entrepreneur has an cool idea, drops out of college, defies the doubters, overcomes all odds, makes billions and becomes the envy of the technology world.     </p>
<p>                    This is not that story.    </p>
<p>                    Rand Fishkin, the founder and former CEO of Moz, is one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on SEO. Moz is now a $45 million a year business, but Fishkin&#8217;s business and reputation took 15 years to grow, and his startup began not in a Harvard dorm room but as a mother-and-son family business that fell deeply into debt.     </p>
<p>                    Now Fishkin pulls back the curtain on tech startup mythology, exposing the ups and downs of startup life that most CEOs would rather keep secret. For instance: a minimally viable product can be destructive if you launch at the wrong moment. Growth hacking may be the buzzword du jour, but initiatives to your business can fizzle quickly. Revenue and profitability won&#8217;t protect you from layoffs. And venture capital always comes with strings attached.     </p>
<p>                    In Lost and Founder Fishkin reveals the mostly awful, sometimes awesome truth about startup culture with the transparency and humour that his hundreds of thousands of blog readers have come to love. Fishkin&#8217;s hard-won lessons are applicable to any kind of business environment and this book can help solve your problems, and make you feel less alone for having them.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is a truly courageous book. It&#8217;s one part business-building guide and two parts Indiana Jones-style adventure memoir&#8217; Chris Guillebeau, author of Side Hustle and The $100 Startup    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rand Fishkin is like the industry friend we all wish we had &#8211; funny, warm, and refreshingly honest about the rollercoaster ride that is founding your own company&#8217; Julie Zhou, VP of Product Design at Facebook</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/">Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on building a product that people will actually buy and use. By rigorously following the techniques described in Running Lean, you can eliminate waste &#8211; whether it&#8217;s time, money, effort, or all of the above &#8211; and get your product to market quickly. Refined through the real-world experiences of dozens of startup companies, these techniques are part of Eric Ries&#8217; Lean Startup methodology. Principles covered in this book include: * Find a problem worth solving, then define a solution * Demo before building * Pricing is part of the product * Maximize for speed, learning, and focus * Build a continuous feedback loop with customers throughout the product development cycle * Right Action, Right Time * Build a path to customers from day one</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
