<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Industrial Or Vocational Training Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/industrial-or-vocational-training/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/industrial-or-vocational-training/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Industrial Or Vocational Training Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/industrial-or-vocational-training/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Effective SMEs : A Trainer&#8217;s Guide for Helping Subject Matter Experts Facilitate Learning &#8211; Dale Ludwig, Greg Owen-Boger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/effective-smes-a-trainers-guide-for-helping-subject-matter-experts-facilitate-learning-dale-ludwig-greg-owen-boger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/effective-smes-a-trainers-guide-for-helping-subject-matter-experts-facilitate-learning-dale-ludwig-greg-owen-boger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Content expertise isn&#8217;t enough for the training room. Partnering with subject matter experts can really pay off. SMEs (we pronounce it smees) bring credibility and relevance to live training. They enrich learning programs with their insight and depth of experience. But content expertise alone isn&#8217;t enough to deliver effective training. . . . SMEs want [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/effective-smes-a-trainers-guide-for-helping-subject-matter-experts-facilitate-learning-dale-ludwig-greg-owen-boger-abridged/">Effective SMEs : A Trainer&#8217;s Guide for Helping Subject Matter Experts Facilitate Learning &#8211; Dale Ludwig, Greg Owen-Boger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Content expertise isn&#8217;t enough for the training room.    </p>
<p>                    Partnering with subject matter experts can really pay off. SMEs (we pronounce it smees) bring credibility and relevance to live training. They enrich learning programs with their insight and depth of experience. But content expertise alone isn&#8217;t enough to deliver effective training. . . .    </p>
<p>                    SMEs want to do well in the classroom, but it&#8217;s often unfamiliar terrain. They&#8217;re authorities on content, not talent development. Without guidance, they may overshare or find themselves unable to facilitate a productive discussion&#8212;all of which frustrate learners. But, with the right approach, you can bring SMEs into the training room successfully, in a way that makes learners, instructors, and managers feel like their goals are being met.     </p>
<p>                    Effective SMEs: A Trainer&#8217;s Guide for Helping Subject Matter Experts Facilitate Learning is the blueprint to managing SME-led training. Authors Dale Ludwig and Greg Owen-Boger offer first-rate advice gleaned from decades helping presenters, instructional designers, and SMEs become better communicators. Underlying all their tips is their belief that SMEs and instructional designers must get comfortable with each other&#8217;s role. The authors lay the groundwork for you, describing the fundamental principles of a successful training event and the personal approach they contend every SME and ID bring to the training table. You&#8217;ll discover how to design learning events with the needs of SMEs in mind. And you&#8217;ll try out best practices for coaching SMEs to deliver training efficiently and effectively. The authors also share detailed and relatable workplace scenarios drawn from their vast business experience as well as job aids to assist you in a variety of learning situations.     </p>
<p>                    Effective SMEs is the rare book that addresses both designing for SMEs to deliver training and coaching them to be effective once they&#8217;re in the training room. Don&#8217;t plan your next live training event without it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/effective-smes-a-trainers-guide-for-helping-subject-matter-experts-facilitate-learning-dale-ludwig-greg-owen-boger-abridged/">Effective SMEs : A Trainer&#8217;s Guide for Helping Subject Matter Experts Facilitate Learning &#8211; Dale Ludwig, Greg Owen-Boger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traffic : Why we drive the way we do (and what it says about us) &#8211; Tom Vanderbilt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/traffic-why-we-drive-the-way-we-do-and-what-it-says-about-us-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motor Cars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Roadcraft, Driving & The Highway Code]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/traffic-why-we-drive-the-way-we-do-and-what-it-says-about-us-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Get stuck in &#8230; Why do some people become demons when they get behind a wheel? Why does the other lane always move faster? Why do New Yorkers jaywalk (and nobody does in Cophenhagen)? And why should you never drive with any beer-drinking, divorced doctors named Fred? Driving is about far more than getting from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/traffic-why-we-drive-the-way-we-do-and-what-it-says-about-us-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/">Traffic : Why we drive the way we do (and what it says about us) &#8211; Tom Vanderbilt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Get stuck in &#8230; Why do some people become demons when they get behind a wheel? Why does the other lane always move faster? Why do New Yorkers jaywalk (and nobody does in Cophenhagen)? And why should you never drive with any beer-drinking, divorced doctors named Fred?    </p>
<p>                    Driving is about far more than getting from A to B. As Tom Vanderbilt&#8217;s brilliant, curiosity-filled book shows, it&#8217;s actually the key to deciphering human nature and &#8230; well, pretty much everything. From the etiquette of horn-honking to bumper stickers you should avoid, from gridlock in ancient Rome to why getting rid of road signs actually reduces accidents, Traffic will change the way you see yourself, and other people (and not just through your windscreen).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/traffic-why-we-drive-the-way-we-do-and-what-it-says-about-us-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/">Traffic : Why we drive the way we do (and what it says about us) &#8211; Tom Vanderbilt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smart Calling : Eliminate the Fear, Failure, and Rejection from Cold Calling &#8211; Art Sobczak (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smart-calling-eliminate-the-fear-failure-and-rejection-from-cold-calling-art-sobczak-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smart-calling-eliminate-the-fear-failure-and-rejection-from-cold-calling-art-sobczak-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Master cold-calling and eliminate rejection forever In the newest edition of Smart Calling: Eliminate the Fear, Failure, and Rejection from Cold Calling, celebrated author and sales trainer, Art Sobczak packs even more powerful insight into what many people fear: prospecting by phone for new business. This best-selling guide to &#8220;never experiencing rejection again&#8221; has consistently [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smart-calling-eliminate-the-fear-failure-and-rejection-from-cold-calling-art-sobczak-abridged/">Smart Calling : Eliminate the Fear, Failure, and Rejection from Cold Calling &#8211; Art Sobczak (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Master cold-calling and eliminate rejection forever    </p>
<p>                     In the newest edition of Smart Calling: Eliminate the Fear, Failure, and Rejection from Cold Calling, celebrated author and sales trainer, Art Sobczak packs even more powerful insight into what many people fear: prospecting by phone for new business. This best-selling guide to &#8220;never experiencing rejection again&#8221; has consistently found its way into the Top 20 in Amazon&#8217;s Sales category, because its actionable sales tips and techniques have helped many minimize their fears and eliminate rejection.    </p>
<p>                     The newest edition builds upon the very successful formula of the last edition to help sales professionals take control of their strategy and get more yeses from their prospects. With new information, this info-packed release provides powerful sales insights, including:    </p>
<p>                    The foundational concepts of cold calling, featuring real-life examples you can carry with you into your sales career<br />
                    Multiple case studies and messaging from successful salespeople across the globe, providing even more insight into what works and what&#8217;s a waste of your time<br />
                    New methodologies that are proven to push you past your fear and into the world of successful prospecting<br />
                    Free access to Art Sobczak&#8217;s Smart Calling Companion Course, where he builds on the many techniques and strategies in the book, and will update it with new material and tech resources so that you will always have the current best practices and tools.    </p>
<p>                     If you&#8217;re failing to convert your prospects into dollars, Smart Calling will help you push past the obstacles holding you back until you&#8217;re an expert at taking a &#8220;no&#8221; and turning it into a &#8220;yes.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smart-calling-eliminate-the-fear-failure-and-rejection-from-cold-calling-art-sobczak-abridged/">Smart Calling : Eliminate the Fear, Failure, and Rejection from Cold Calling &#8211; Art Sobczak (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212; Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a Foreword by Jim Cora, former Chairman of Disneyland International    </p>
<p>                      &#8220;A leadership blueprint, applicable in any organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Captain D. Michael Abrashoff, U.S. Navy (Ret.), and author of It&#8217;s Your Ship    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;When I first arrived at The Walt Disney Company, I was surprised to find I had to go back to school&#8211;at Disney University! There, I learned the fundamentals of guest service that consistently gave Disney a tremendous advantage in the marketplace. Now, anyone can know these secrets of success thanks to Doug Lipp&#8217;s informative book. No matter what your business, the lessons taught at DisneyUniversity will prove invaluable.&#8221; &#8212; Michael Eisner, Former CEO and Chairman, The Walt Disney Company    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to world-class employees, few organizations rival Disney. Famous for their friendliness, knowledge, passion, and superior customer service, Disney&#8217;s employees have been fueling the iconic brand&#8217;s wild success for more than 50 years.    </p>
<p>                    How has Disney succeeded in maintaining such a powerful workforce for so many years? Why are so many corporations and executives drawn to study how Disney continues to exemplify service and leadership standards?    </p>
<p>                    The Disney University, founded by Van France, trains the supporting cast that helps create the world-famous Disney Magic. Now, for the first time, the secrets of this exemplary institution are revealed. In Disney U, Doug Lipp examines how Van perpetuated Walt Disney&#8217;s timeless company values and leadership lessons, creating a training and development dynasty. It contains never-before-told stories from numerous Disney legends. These pioneers share behind-the-scenes success stories of how they helped bring Walt Disney&#8217;s dream to life.    </p>
<p>                    Disney U reveals the heart of the Disney culture and describes the company&#8217;s values and operational philosophies that support the iconic brand. Doug Lipp lays out 13 timeless lessons Disney has used to drive profits and growth worldwide for more than half a century.    </p>
<p>                    To this day, the Disney University continues to turn out some of the most engaged, loyal, and customer-centered employees the business world has ever seen. Using the lessons outlined in Disney U will set your organization on a path of sustained success.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR Disney U:    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I highly recommend Disney U to anyone interested in building an enduring market presence and brand.&#8221; &#8212; Stephen Cannon, President and Chief Executive Officer, Mercedes-Benz USA    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lipp&#8217;s narratives reveal how Van and other Disney visionaries set the stage for a world-class organization by skillfully balancing both &#8216;people&#8217; and &#8216;technology.'&#8221; &#8212; Debi Aubee, Vice President of Sales, Bose Corporation    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every leader should have the equivalent of a Van France at his or her side. Thanks to Doug Lipp, we can now tap into the brilliance of a man who helped Walt createThe Happiest Place on Earth.&#8221; &#8212; David Overton, Founder and Chief Executive Officer, The Cheesecake Factory    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;How does Disney University create such enthusiastic, loyal, and customer-centered employees, year after year? Now, for the first time, Doug Lipp takes us on a journey backstage to answer this pivotal question.&#8221; &#8212; John G. Veres III, Ph.D., Chancellor, Auburn University at Montgomery    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Doug Lipp shares terrific stories about Disney that underscore the importance of creating an organizational culture with an unwavering dedication to superlativeservice and exceptional quality, both for employees and customers. He then takes it a step further by explaining how to bring these values to life for your organization.&#8221; &#8212;  Christine A. Morena, Executive Vice President of Human Resources, Saks Incorporated</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disney-u-how-disney-university-develops-the-worlds-most-engaged-loyal-and-customer-centric-employees-doug-lipp-abridged/">Disney U: How Disney University Develops the World&#8217;s Most Engaged, Loyal, and Customer-Centric Employees &#8211; Doug Lipp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Attention is the new commodity. Visual Storytelling is the new currency. Human brain processes visuals 60,000x faster than text.Web posts with visuals drive up to 180% more engagement than those without.Viewers spend 100% more time on web pages with videos. Filled with full-color images and thought-provoking examples from leading companies, The Power of Visual Storytelling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/">The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Attention is the new commodity. Visual Storytelling is the new currency.    </p>
<p>                    Human brain processes visuals 60,000x faster than text.Web posts with visuals drive up to 180% more engagement than those without.Viewers spend 100% more time on web pages with videos.<br />
                    Filled with full-color images and thought-provoking examples from leading companies, The Power of Visual Storytelling explains how to grow your business and strengthen your brand by leveraging photos, videos, infographics, presentations, and other rich media. The book delivers a powerful road map for getting started, while inspiring new levels of creativity within organizations of all types and sizes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book is not only a complete overview of [visual storytelling] but, most importantly, the key to doing it right, a total Right Hook!&#8221;<br />
                    -Gary Vaynerchuk, New York Times bestselling author of Crush It! and Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable guide to understanding how to develop powerful marketing programs using the art of visual storytelling.&#8221;<br />
                    -Guy Kawasaki, author of APE: Author, Publisher, Entrepreneur and former chief evangelist of Apple    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Power of Visual Storytelling is the new marketing bible!&#8221;<br />
                    -Nancy Bhagat, Vice President, Global Marketing Strategy and Campaigns, Intel    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If a picture is worth a thousand words, The Power of Visual Storytelling is worth a million.&#8221;<br />
                    -Scott Monty, Global Digital &#038; Multimedia Communications for Ford Motor Company</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/">The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that philosophy and illustrates how successful businesses have redefined themselves in the new customer universe.    </p>
<p>                    Personality Not Included is a powerhouse resource packed with bold new insights that show you how to shed the lifeless armor of your business and rediscover the soul of your brand. Sharing stories from the ethos of the world&#8217;s weirdest city, to how Manga has taken the comic book industry by storm, to showcasing brands like Intel, Boeing, ING, and Dyson, Bhargava shows you why personality matters from the inside out.    </p>
<p>                    In Part One, you&#8217;ll be introduced to the key components to building a personality and learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    Recognize the greatest myth that most marketers blindly follow, and how to get past itUse the &#8220;UAT Filter&#8221; to understand the personality of your organization and products in order to develop a communication strategy that drives your marketingCreate your company&#8217;s &#8220;marketing backstory&#8221; using techniques pioneered by Hollywood screenwritersHarness the influence of &#8220;accidental spokespeople&#8221; and use it to your advantageNavigate the roadblocks of using personality that come from bosses, peers, investors, and lawyers, without getting fired or flamedPinpoint and capitalize on the moments where personality can make a difference<br />
                    Part Two is packed with guides, tools, and techniques to help you flawlessly implement your plan. It features practical, step-by-step lessons that help you effectively move from theory to action, and includes a valuable collection of guides, checklists, question forms, printable resources, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Don&#8217;t be another faceless company-learn the new rules for succeeding in the social media era with Personality Not Included.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pitch Anything: An Innovative Method for Presenting, Persuading, and Winning the Deal &#8211; Oren Klaff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pitch-anything-an-innovative-method-for-presenting-persuading-and-winning-the-deal-oren-klaff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pitch-anything-an-innovative-method-for-presenting-persuading-and-winning-the-deal-oren-klaff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gold Medal Winner&#8211;Tops Sales World&#8217;s Best Sales and Marketing Book &#8220;Fast, fun and immensely practical.&#8221; -JOE SULLIVAN, Founder, Flextronics &#8220;Move over Neil Strauss and game theory. Pitch Anything reveals the next big thing in social dynamics: game for business.&#8221; -JOSH WHITFORD, Founder, Echelon Media &#8220;What do supermodels and venture capitalists have in common?They hear hundreds [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pitch-anything-an-innovative-method-for-presenting-persuading-and-winning-the-deal-oren-klaff-abridged/">Pitch Anything: An Innovative Method for Presenting, Persuading, and Winning the Deal &#8211; Oren Klaff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gold Medal Winner&#8211;Tops Sales World&#8217;s Best Sales and Marketing Book    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Fast, fun and immensely practical.&#8221;<br />
                    -JOE SULLIVAN, Founder, Flextronics    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Move over Neil Strauss and game theory. Pitch Anything reveals the next big thing in social dynamics: game for business.&#8221;<br />
                    -JOSH WHITFORD, Founder, Echelon Media    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What do supermodels and venture capitalists have in common?They hear hundreds of pitches a year. Pitch Anything makes sure you get the nod (or wink) you deserve.&#8221;<br />
                    -RALPH CRAM, Investor    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Pitch Anything offers a new method that will differentiate you from the rest of the pack.&#8221;<br />
                    -JASON JONES, Senior Vice President, Jones Lang LaSalle    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you want to pitch a product, raise money, or close a deal, read Pitch Anything and put its principles to work.&#8221;<br />
                    -STEVEN WALDMAN, Principal and Founder, Spectrum Capital    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Pitch Anything opened my eyes to what I had been missing in my presentations and business interactions.&#8221;<br />
                    -LOUIE UCCIFERRI, President, Regent Capital Group    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I use Oren&#8217;s unique strategies to sell deals, raise money, and handle tough situations.&#8221;<br />
                    -TAYLOR GARRETT, Vice President, White Cap    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A counter-intuitive method that works.&#8221;<br />
                    -JAY GOYAL, CEO, SumOpti    </p>
<p>                    About the Book:    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to delivering a pitch, Oren Klaff has unparalleled credentials. Over the past 13 years, he has used his one-of-a- kind method to raise more than $400 million-and now, for the fi rst time, he describes his formula to help you deliver a winning pitch in any business situation.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re selling ideas to investors, pitching a client for new business, or even negotiating for a higher salary, Pitch Anything will transform the way you position your ideas.    </p>
<p>                    According to Klaff, creating and presenting a great pitch isn&#8217;t an art-it&#8217;s a simple science. Applying the latest findings in the field of neuroeconomics, while sharing eye-opening stories of his method in action, Klaff describes how the brain makes decisions and responds to pitches. With this information, you&#8217;ll remain in complete control of every stage of the pitch process.    </p>
<p>                    Pitch Anything introduces the exclusive STRONG method of pitching, which can be put to use immediately:    </p>
<p>                    Setting the Frame<br />
                    Telling the Story<br />
                    Revealing the Intrigue<br />
                    Offering the Prize<br />
                    Nailing the Hookpoint<br />
                    Getting a Decision    </p>
<p>                    One truly great pitch can improve your career, make you a lot of money-and even change your life. Success is dependent on the method you use, not how hard you try. &#8220;Better method, more money,&#8221; Klaff says. &#8220;Much better method, much more money.&#8221; Klaff is the best in the business because his method is much better than anyone else&#8217;s. And now it&#8217;s yours.    </p>
<p>                    Apply the tactics and strategies outlined inPitch Anything to engage and persuade your audience-and you&#8217;ll have more funding and support than you ever thought possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pitch-anything-an-innovative-method-for-presenting-persuading-and-winning-the-deal-oren-klaff-abridged/">Pitch Anything: An Innovative Method for Presenting, Persuading, and Winning the Deal &#8211; Oren Klaff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Millionaire Real Estate Agent &#8211; Gary Keller, Dave Jenks, Jay Papasan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-millionaire-real-estate-agent-gary-keller-dave-jenks-jay-papasan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[English Language: Reading & Writing Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-millionaire-real-estate-agent-gary-keller-dave-jenks-jay-papasan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take your real estate career to the highest level! &#8216;Gary Keller knows the beauty of a simple path to a spectacular goal! Whether you are just getting started or a veteran in the business, &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221; is the step-by-step handbook for seeking excellence in your profession and in your life&#8217; &#8211; Mark [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-millionaire-real-estate-agent-gary-keller-dave-jenks-jay-papasan-abridged/">The Millionaire Real Estate Agent &#8211; Gary Keller, Dave Jenks, Jay Papasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take your real estate career to the highest level! &#8216;Gary Keller knows the beauty of a simple path to a spectacular goal! Whether you are just getting started or a veteran in the business, &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221; is the step-by-step handbook for seeking excellence in your profession and in your life&#8217; &#8211; Mark Victor Hansen, co-creator, number 1 &#8220;New York Times&#8221; best-selling series &#8220;Chicken Soup for the Soul&#8221;, co-author, &#8220;The One Minute Manager&#8221;. &#8216;This book presents a new paradigm for real estate and should be required reading for real estate professionals everywhere&#8217; &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki, &#8220;New York Times&#8221;, best-selling author of &#8220;Rich Dad, Poor Dad&#8221;. &#8216;In &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221;, Gary Keller&#8217;s positive influence on the careers of so many agents is encapsulated for all to enjoy and utilize&#8217; &#8211; Howard Brinton, Founder and CEO, Star Power Systems, Inc. &#8216;Gary Keller understands that to become a real millionaire, it starts with a change in your thinking. You must treat your business like a business with a focus on long-term profitability&#8217; &#8211; Brian Buffini, President and Founder, Providence Systems, Inc.Anyone who wants to turn their real estate practice into a highly successful business must understand the fundamental models that drive the best real estate agents in the industry.<br />
                    In &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221; these models are revealed and explained. This book represents the culmination of decades of real estate experience, research, and consulting, with case studies from some of the top millionaire agents in the U.S. In this revolutionary handbook you&#8217;ll learn: three key concepts that drive mega-agent production. It provides essential economic, budgetary, organizational, and lead generation models that are the foundations of any high-achiever&#8217;s business.The distinguishing characteristic of &#8220;Millionaire Real Estate Agents&#8221; &#8211; the way they think! How you can get on the real estate career path to &#8216;earn a million,&#8217; &#8216;net a million,&#8217; and then &#8216;receive a million&#8217; dollars in annual income. &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221; is not about quick fixes. It is about the innovative application of proven business techniques to the real estate industry. Isn&#8217;t it about time you put your career on the path to becoming a &#8220;Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221;.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-millionaire-real-estate-agent-gary-keller-dave-jenks-jay-papasan-abridged/">The Millionaire Real Estate Agent &#8211; Gary Keller, Dave Jenks, Jay Papasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Think Like Zuck: The Five Business Secrets of Facebook&#8217;s Improbably Brilliant CEO Mark Zuckerberg &#8211; Ekaterina Walter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/think-like-zuck-the-five-business-secrets-of-facebooks-improbably-brilliant-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-ekaterina-walter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/think-like-zuck-the-five-business-secrets-of-facebooks-improbably-brilliant-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-ekaterina-walter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal BestsellerMake Your Mark in the World with the Five Success Principles of the World-Changing Social Media Site If Facebook were a country, it would be the third largest in the world. Facebook accounts for one of every seven minutes spent online. More than one billion pieces of content are shared on Facebook. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/think-like-zuck-the-five-business-secrets-of-facebooks-improbably-brilliant-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-ekaterina-walter-abridged/">Think Like Zuck: The Five Business Secrets of Facebook&#8217;s Improbably Brilliant CEO Mark Zuckerberg &#8211; Ekaterina Walter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal BestsellerMake Your Mark in the World with the Five Success Principles of the World-Changing Social Media Site    </p>
<p>                    If Facebook were a country, it would be the third largest in the world.<br />
                    Facebook accounts for one of every seven minutes spent online.<br />
                    More than one billion pieces of content are shared on Facebook.    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s no doubt about it. Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s creation has changed the world. Literally. Facebook has singlehandedly revolutionized the way more than one-seventh of the world&#8217;s population communicates, engages, and consumes information.    </p>
<p>                    If you run a business or plan to start one, you&#8217;re probably asking yourself the same question organizational leaders worldwide are asking: What did Mark Zuckerberg do right?At long last, the answer is here. Think Like Zuck examines the five principles behind Facebook&#8217;s meteoric rise, presented in actionable lessons anyone can apply-in any organization, in any industry. Written by social business trailblazer Ekaterina Walter, this groundbreaking book reveals the five &#8220;P&#8221;s of Facebook&#8217;s success:    </p>
<p>                    PASSION-Keep your energy and commitment fully charged at all times by pursuing something you believe in<br />
                    PURPOSE-Don&#8217;t just create a great product; drive a meaningful movement<br />
                    PEOPLE-Build powerful teams that can execute your vision<br />
                    PRODUCT-Create a product that is innovative, that breaks all the rules, that changes everything<br />
                    PARTNERSHIPS-Build powerful partnerships with people who fuel imagination and energize execution    </p>
<p>                    Packed with examples of Facebook&#8217;s success principles in action-as well as those of Zappos, TOMS, Threadless, Dyson, and other companies-Think Like Zuck gives you the inspiration, knowledge, and insight to make your own mark in the world, to build a business that makes a difference, and to lead your organization to long-term profitability and growth.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Think Like Zuck is a fascinating look at how entrepreneurial vision drives success. If you want more out of work than just a job, if you have the burning desire to build something of lasting value, then this is your guide.&#8221;<br />
                    -DAVID MEERMAN SCOTT, bestselling author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned business executive or the next Mark Zuckerberg in your dorm room right now, this book is a must-read! Two likeable thumbs up!&#8221;<br />
                    -DAVE KERPEN, New York Times bestselling author of Likeable Social Media and Likeable Business    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;True success lies at the place where passion and purpose collide-this book will help you uncover yours.&#8221;<br />
                    -JOHN JANTSCH, bestselling author of Duct Tape Marketing and The Commitment Engine    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Think Like Zuck is a must-read for any innovator, social entrepreneur, or business owner looking to capitalize on the success of Facebook to propel and realize their own vision.&#8221;<br />
                    -SIMON MAINWARING, New York Times bestselling author of We First    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book takes you on the ride of a lifetime and shows you how YOU can be successful! The question is: What does it take? Ekaterina gives us the answers!&#8221;<br />
                     -JEFFREY HAYZLETT, bestselling author of Running the Gauntlet and global business celebrity    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In Think Like Zuck, you will find important principles to infuse meaning into your business strategies and inspire change. Don&#8217;t just read this book; use it.&#8221;<br />
                    -SHAWN ACHOR, author of the international bestseller The Happiness Advantage</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/think-like-zuck-the-five-business-secrets-of-facebooks-improbably-brilliant-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-ekaterina-walter-abridged/">Think Like Zuck: The Five Business Secrets of Facebook&#8217;s Improbably Brilliant CEO Mark Zuckerberg &#8211; Ekaterina Walter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Influencer: The New Science of Leading Change, Second Edition (Paperback) &#8211; Joseph Grenny, Kerry Patterson, David Maxfield, Ron McMillan, Al Switzler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/influencer-the-new-science-of-leading-change-second-edition-paperback-joseph-grenny-kerry-patterson-david-maxfield-ron-mcmillan-al-switzler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/influencer-the-new-science-of-leading-change-second-edition-paperback-joseph-grenny-kerry-patterson-david-maxfield-ron-mcmillan-al-switzler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CHANGE YOUR COMPANY. CHANGE THE LIVES OF OTHERS. CHANGE THE WORLD.An INFLUENCER leads change. An INFLUENCER replaces bad behaviorswith powerful new skills. An INFLUENCER makes things happen. This is what it takes to be an INFLUENCER. Whether you&#8217;re a CEO, a parent, or merely a person who wants to make a difference, you probably wish [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/influencer-the-new-science-of-leading-change-second-edition-paperback-joseph-grenny-kerry-patterson-david-maxfield-ron-mcmillan-al-switzler-abridged/">Influencer: The New Science of Leading Change, Second Edition (Paperback) &#8211; Joseph Grenny, Kerry Patterson, David Maxfield, Ron McMillan, Al Switzler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CHANGE YOUR COMPANY. CHANGE THE LIVES OF OTHERS. CHANGE THE WORLD.An INFLUENCER leads change.<br />
                    An INFLUENCER replaces bad behaviorswith powerful new skills.<br />
                    An INFLUENCER makes things happen.<br />
                    This is what it takes to be an INFLUENCER.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re a CEO, a parent, or merely a person who wants to make a difference, you probably wish you hadmore influence with the people in your life. But most of us stop trying to make change happen because we believe itis too difficult, if not impossible. We learn to cope rather than learning to influence.    </p>
<p>                    From the bestselling authors who taught the world how to have Crucial Conversations comes the new editionof Influencer, a thought-provoking book that combines the remarkable insights of behavioral scientists and business leaders with the astonishing stories of high-powered influencers from all walks of life. You&#8217;ll be taughteach and every step of the influence process&#8211;including robust strategies for making change inevitable in yourpersonal life, your business, and your world. You&#8217;ll learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    Identify high-leverage behaviors that lead to rapid and profound changeApply strategies for changing both thoughts and actionsMarshal six sources of influence to make change inevitable    </p>
<p>                    Influencer takes you on a fascinating journey from San Francisco to Thailand to South Africa, where you&#8217;ll see how seemingly &#8220;insignificant&#8221; people are making incredibly significant improvements in solving problems others would think impossible. You&#8217;ll learn how savvy folks make change not only achievable and sustainable, but inevitable. You&#8217;ll discover breakthrough ways of changing the key behaviors that lead to greater safety, productivity, quality, and customer service.    </p>
<p>                    No matter who you are or what you do, you&#8217;ll never learn a more valuable or important set of principles andskills. Once you tap into the power of influence, you can reach out and help others work smarter, grow faster,live, look, and feel better&#8211;and even save lives. The sky is the limit . . . for an Influencer.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR INFLUENCER:&#8221;AN INSTANT CLASSIC! Whether you&#8217;re leading change or changing your life, this book delivers.&#8221; &#8212; Stephen R. Covey, author of The 7 Habits of Highly Effective People    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ideas can change the world-but only when coupled with influence&#8211;the ability to change hearts, minds, and behavior. This book provides a practical approach to lead change and empower us all to make a difference.&#8221; &#8212; Muhammad Yunus, Nobel Peace Prize Winner    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Influencing human behavior is one of the most difficult challenges faced by leaders. This book provides powerful insight into how to make behavior change that will last.&#8221; &#8212; Sidney Taurel, Chairman and Chief Executive Officer, Eli Lilly and Company    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you are truly motivated to make productive changes in your life, don&#8217;t put down this book until you reach the last page. Whether dealing with a recalcitrant teen, doggedly resistant coworkers, or a personal frustration that &#8216;no one ever wants to hear my view,&#8217; Influencer can help guide you in making the changes that put you in the driver&#8217;s seat.&#8221; &#8212; Deborah Norville, anchor of Inside Edition and bestselling author</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/influencer-the-new-science-of-leading-change-second-edition-paperback-joseph-grenny-kerry-patterson-david-maxfield-ron-mcmillan-al-switzler-abridged/">Influencer: The New Science of Leading Change, Second Edition (Paperback) &#8211; Joseph Grenny, Kerry Patterson, David Maxfield, Ron McMillan, Al Switzler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital When you connect with the right angel [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital    </p>
<p>                    When you connect with the right angel investor, it&#8217;s like finding a new best friend&#8211;you just have to know what makes him or her happy.    </p>
<p>                    Smart funding is waiting for smart founders. Raising funds is all about connecting with the investor who&#8217;s right for you&#8211;and What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know shows you exactly how to succeed.    </p>
<p>                    Veteran early-stage investor Brian Cohen knows how to spot a great company destined for success, and in this groundbreaking book he offers soup-to-nuts guidance for anyentrepreneur seeking to launch an invention, a product, or a great new idea into a receptive marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    As chairman of the board of directors of the New York Angels, Cohen is one of the most engaged angel investors out there today. The first investor in Pinterest, he describes exactly what angels want to see, hear, and feelbefore they take out their checkbooks:    </p>
<p>                    A clear exit strategy before the startup even launchesFacts that turn &#8220;due&#8221; diligence into &#8220;do&#8221; diligenceAuthenticity&#8211;&#8220;save your spinning for the fitness center&#8221;Proof that you &#8220;live inside the customer&#8217;s head&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Cohen gives invaluable insight into how the most successful angels view due diligence, friends and family money, crowdfunding, team building, scalability, iteration, exit strategies&#8211;and much more.    </p>
<p>                    This one-of-a-kind book provides a rare look inside the minds of people who are in the business of funding businesses just like yours.    </p>
<p>                    Read What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know to get your best shot at funding for your product after your very first pitch.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR WHAT EVERY ANGEL INVESTOR WANTS YOU TO KNOW:&#8221;Brian Cohen is truly the entrepreneur&#8217;s best friend. Cohen and Kador haven distilled their first-hand experiences into an intensely personal, highly readablejourney into the mind of angels that should be kept at the bedside of every startup CEO.&#8221; &#8212; DAVID S. ROSE, founder, New York Angels, and CEO, Gust    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Meet one of the fundamental building blocks of the entrepreneurial scene. In one easy-to-read package, readers now have the wisdom of Brian Cohen, perhaps themost well-connected investor/entrepreneur in New York.&#8221; &#8212; MURAT AKTIHANOGLU, founder and managing director, Entrepreneurs Roundtable Accelerator    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know gives you an actionable checklist for success in fund-raising and entrepreneurship. Cohen and Kador provide anexhilarating ride for those who want to pilot their own business.&#8221; &#8212; REED HOLDEN, serial entrepreneur and author of Negotiating with Backbone    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Personal insights from a seasoned angel investor. An important addition to the reading list for today&#8217;s entrepreneurs.&#8221; &#8212; SCOTT CASE, CEO, Startup America Partnership    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know is a must-read for entrepreneurs and investors who want to fi nance startup dreams&#8211;an accessible, jargon-free,practical primer.&#8221; &#8212; WHITNEY JOHNSON, author of Dare, Dream, Do: Remarkable Things Happen When You Dare to Dream and cofounder, Rose Park Advisors    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;While [this] book is anecdotal, [the authors] discuss in depth how angels view a potential investment as well as how they evaluate its prospects. This is the book&#8217;s strength. Recommended. All levels of students, entrepreneurs, practitioners.&#8221; &#8212; CHOICE</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
