<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Psychological Theory &amp; Schools Of Thought Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/psychological-theory-schools-of-thought/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/psychological-theory-schools-of-thought/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Psychological Theory &amp; Schools Of Thought Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/psychological-theory-schools-of-thought/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler</title>
		<link>/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Gender]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the better &#8211; and thus we don&#8217;t like to talk or even think about the extent of our selfishness. This is &#8220;the elephant in the brain.&#8221; Such<br />
                    an introspective taboo makes it hard for us to think clearly about our nature and the explanations for our behavior. The aim of this book, then, is to confront our hidden motives directly &#8211; to track down the darker, unexamined corners of our psyches and blast them with floodlights. Then, once<br />
                    everything is clearly visible, we can work to better understand ourselves: Why do we laugh? Why are artists sexy? Why do we brag about travel? Why do we prefer to speak rather than listen?</p>
<p>                    Our unconscious motives drive more than just our private behavior; they also infect our venerated social institutions such as Art, School, Charity, Medicine, Politics, and Religion. In fact, these institutions are in many ways designed to accommodate our hidden motives, to serve covert agendas alongside their &#8220;official&#8221; ones. The existence of big hidden motives can upend the usual political debates, leading one to question the legitimacy of these social institutions, and of standard policies<br />
                    designed to favor or discourage them. You won&#8217;t see yourself &#8211; or the world &#8211; the same after confronting the elephant in the brain.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</title>
		<link>/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ego]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate, and Enlightenment Now. Believe it or not, today we may be living in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates     </p>
<p>                    A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate,  and Enlightenment Now.    </p>
<p>                    Believe it or not, today we may be living in the most peaceful moment in our species&#8217; existence. In his gripping and controversial new work, New York Times bestselling author Steven Pinker shows that despite the ceaseless news about war, crime, and terrorism, violence has actually been in decline over long stretches of history. Exploding myths about humankind&#8217;s inherent violence and the curse of modernity, this ambitious book continues Pinker&#8217;s exploration of the essence of human nature, mixing psychology and history to provide a remarkable picture of an increasingly enlightened world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</title>
		<link>/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neuro Linguistic Programming (NLP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dark Psychology Series Complete 3 Book Compilation This book includes: How to Analyze People: Dark Psychology &#8211; Dark Secrets to Analyze and Influence Anyone Using Body Language, Human Psychology, Subliminal Persuasion and NLP Persuasion: Dark Psychology &#8211; How People are Influencing You to Do What They Want Using Manipulation, NLP, and Subliminal Persuasion Dark Psychology: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/">How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dark Psychology Series Complete 3 Book Compilation    </p>
<p>                    This book includes: How to Analyze People: Dark Psychology &#8211; Dark Secrets to Analyze and Influence Anyone Using Body Language, Human Psychology, Subliminal Persuasion and NLP<br />
                    Persuasion: Dark Psychology &#8211; How People are Influencing You to Do What They Want Using Manipulation, NLP, and Subliminal Persuasion<br />
                    Dark Psychology: The Practical Uses and Best Defenses of Psychological Warfare in Everyday Life &#8211; How to Detect and Defend Against Manipulation, Deception, Dark Persuasion, and Covert NLP    </p>
<p>                    If you&#8217;re tired of being manipulated, whether you&#8217;re being tricked into doing things you don&#8217;t want, or others are taking advantage of you, there are ways to stop manipulation and persuasion in its tracks.    </p>
<p>                    In this book, you will get a groundwork for what different types of persuasion and manipulation might be. You will learn the process of how people use these tactics to their advantage.    </p>
<p>                    The first half of the book will discuss what makes up an individual. The way you use your body, the words that you choose to speak, and the way that they were raised all play important roles in what makes an individual. You will also have to look at your own self and pick out all of these unique things that make them different from everyone else as well.    </p>
<p>                    There are psychological studies that back up the idea of certain methods of persuasion, such as NLP tactics, that prove that anyone has the power to persuade others.    </p>
<p>                    Inside this book, you will discover: WhatDark Psychologyis and how it&#8217;s used to control people.How to plant different emotional seeds that will grow in people&#8217;s mindsHow to use words to steer people however you likeHow to identify and work with different types of people like contrarians and control freaks.The jobs/roles in society that you are most likely to be manipulated inThe language of the subconsciousThedirty trickslovers and family members use to control their victims.How to analyze different personality typesMind-blowing tricks for manipulationMagic words for influencing othersA step-by-step guide on influencing others with NLPForbidden secrets of dark psychologyCase studies showcasing how much damage a master manipulator can do.And much more&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Although there are many differences among people, there are also many things that make us the same. In order to better analyze and understand those around you, it&#8217;s crucial to find those things that we do connect on, and the things that bring us together rather than the things that tear us apart.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s important when reading this book to remember that not all manipulation is bad. In the first book of this boxset, it is emphasized that those who might be manipulating you might also be taking advantage of you.    </p>
<p>                    When reading this book, you should remember that manipulation is a tool, much like a hammer. You can either use that hammer to destroy everything around you, or you could alternatively use that hammer to create something organic, something new.    </p>
<p>                    This book will take you first through the discovery and analyzation of those around you, and then it will provide different ways that you can persuade them.    </p>
<p>                    The only thing you need before starting this book is the willingness to change. You might have to confront some of your darkest issues, and you might have to put yourself through future scenarios that elicit a feeling of discomfort. In the end, however, you&#8217;ll find yourself to be much more self-aware and independent.Click &#8220;Add to Cart&#8221; nowand learn how to defend against dark psychology and keep your mind and life in control.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/">How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oceanography (seas)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter? In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week<br />
                              &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian<br />
                              &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                                What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter?    </p>
<p>                              In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science and a skilled scuba diver, tells a bold new story of how nature became aware of itself &#8211; a story that largely occurs in the ocean, where animals first appeared.    </p>
<p>                              Tracking the mind&#8217;s fitful development from unruly clumps of seaborne cells to the first evolved nervous systems in ancient relatives of jellyfish, he explores the incredible evolutionary journey of the cephalopods, which began as inconspicuous molluscs who would later abandon their shells to rise above the ocean floor, searching for prey and acquiring the greater intelligence needed to do so &#8211; a journey completely independent from the route that mammals and birds would later take.    </p>
<p>                              But what kind of intelligence do cephalopods possess? How did the octopus, a solitary creature with little social life, become so smart? What is it like to have eight tentacles that are so packed with neurons that they virtually &#8216;think for themselves&#8217;? By tracing the question of inner life back to its roots and comparing human beings with our most remarkable animal relatives, Godfrey-Smith casts crucial new light on the octopus mind &#8211; and on our own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Emotions Are Made : The Secret Life of the Brain &#8211; Lisa Feldman Barrett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perception]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How Emotions Are Made did what all great books do. It took a subject I thought I understood and turned my understanding upside down&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell, author of The Tipping Point. When you feel anxious, angry, happy, or surprised, what&#8217;s really going on inside of you? Many scientists believe that emotions come from a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/">How Emotions Are Made : The Secret Life of the Brain &#8211; Lisa Feldman Barrett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How Emotions Are Made did what all great books do. It took a subject I thought I understood and turned my understanding upside down&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell, author of The Tipping Point.    </p>
<p>                    When you feel anxious, angry, happy, or surprised, what&#8217;s really going on inside of you?     </p>
<p>                    Many scientists believe that emotions come from a specific part of the brain, triggered by the world around us. The thrill of seeing an old friend, the fear of losing someone we love &#8211; each of these sensations seems to arise automatically and uncontrollably from within us, finding expression on our faces and in our behaviour, carrying us away with the experience.    </p>
<p>                    This understanding of emotion has been around since Plato. But what if it is wrong? In How Emotions Are Made, pioneering psychologist and neuroscientist Lisa Feldman Barrett draws on the latest scientific evidence to reveal that our common-sense ideas about emotions are dramatically, even dangerously, out of date &#8211; and that we have been paying the price. Emotions aren&#8217;t universally pre-programmed in our brains and bodies; rather they are psychological experiences that each of us constructs based on our unique personal history, physiology and environment.    </p>
<p>                    This new view of emotions has serious implications: when judges issue lesser sentences for crimes of passion, when police officers fire at threatening suspects, or when doctors choose between one diagnosis and another, they&#8217;re all, in some way, relying on the ancient assumption that emotions are hardwired into our brains and bodies. Revising that conception of emotion isn&#8217;t just good science, Barrett shows; it&#8217;s vital to our well-being and the health of society itself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/">How Emotions Are Made : The Secret Life of the Brain &#8211; Lisa Feldman Barrett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Brain : The Story of You &#8211; David Eagleman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-brain-the-story-of-you-david-eagleman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-brain-the-story-of-you-david-eagleman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is the story of how your life shapes your brain, and how your brain shapes your life.&#8217; Join renowned neuroscientist David Eagleman on a whistle-stop tour of the inner cosmos. It&#8217;s a journey that will take you into the world of extreme sports, criminal justice, genocide, brain surgery, robotics and the search for immortality. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-the-story-of-you-david-eagleman-abridged/">The Brain : The Story of You &#8211; David Eagleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the story of how your life shapes your brain, and how your brain shapes your life.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Join renowned neuroscientist David Eagleman on a whistle-stop tour of the inner cosmos. It&#8217;s a journey that will take you into the world of extreme sports, criminal justice, genocide, brain surgery, robotics and the search for immortality. On the way, amidst the infinitely dense tangle of brain cells and their trillions of connections, something emerges that you might not have expected to see: you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-the-story-of-you-david-eagleman-abridged/">The Brain : The Story of You &#8211; David Eagleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Why do human beings behave as they do? &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    Why do human beings behave as they do?     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm    </p>
<p>                     We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of our nature destined to win out over the other?    </p>
<p>                     Every act of human behaviour has multiple layers of causation, spiralling back seconds, minutes, hours, days, months, years, even centuries, right back to the dawn of time and the origins of our species.     </p>
<p>                     In the epic sweep of history, how does our biology affect the arc of war and peace, justice and persecution? How have our brains evolved alongside our cultures?    </p>
<p>                     This is the exhilarating story of human morality and the science underpinning the biggest question of all: what makes us human?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the best scientist-writers of our time&#8217; Oliver Sacks</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Into the Magic Shop : A neurosurgeon&#8217;s true story of the life-changing magic of mindfulness and compassion that inspired the hit K-pop band BTS &#8211; Dr James Doty (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/into-the-magic-shop-a-neurosurgeons-true-story-of-the-life-changing-magic-of-mindfulness-and-compassion-that-inspired-the-hit-k-pop-band-bts-dr-james-doty-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosurgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/into-the-magic-shop-a-neurosurgeons-true-story-of-the-life-changing-magic-of-mindfulness-and-compassion-that-inspired-the-hit-k-pop-band-bts-dr-james-doty-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The award-winning New York Times bestseller that inspired BTS&#8217;s K-pop song &#8216;Magic Shop&#8217;. The day that 12-year-old James Doty walked in to his local magic shop is the day that changed his life. Once the neglected son of an alcoholic father and a mother with chronic depression, he has gone on to become a leading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-the-magic-shop-a-neurosurgeons-true-story-of-the-life-changing-magic-of-mindfulness-and-compassion-that-inspired-the-hit-k-pop-band-bts-dr-james-doty-abridged/">Into the Magic Shop : A neurosurgeon&#8217;s true story of the life-changing magic of mindfulness and compassion that inspired the hit K-pop band BTS &#8211; Dr James Doty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The award-winning New York Times bestseller that inspired BTS&#8217;s K-pop song &#8216;Magic Shop&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    The day that 12-year-old James Doty walked in to his local magic shop is the day that changed his life.     </p>
<p>                    Once the neglected son of an alcoholic father and a mother with chronic depression, he has gone on to become a leading neurosurgeon, based at Stanford University. He credits Ruth for this incredible turnaround: the remarkable woman he met at the Cactus Rabbit Magic Shop, who devoted the summer to transforming his mind and opening his heart.    </p>
<p>                    In this uplifting memoir, Jim explains the visualisation techniques Ruth taught him that gave him the self-esteem to imagine a new future for himself. He examines the science behind mindfulness and why the skills he learned &#8211; of focus and attention &#8211; now help him to think fast and keep calm in the operating theatre. And he shows us what is possible when you start to change your brain and your heart. Into the Magic Shop imparts some powerful life lessons about how to live better, and inspires us to believe that we all have inside us the capacity to change our own destiny.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;m sure many readers will be moved by this inspiring story to open their hearts and see what they too can do for others&#8217; &#8211; His Holiness the Dalai Lama</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-the-magic-shop-a-neurosurgeons-true-story-of-the-life-changing-magic-of-mindfulness-and-compassion-that-inspired-the-hit-k-pop-band-bts-dr-james-doty-abridged/">Into the Magic Shop : A neurosurgeon&#8217;s true story of the life-changing magic of mindfulness and compassion that inspired the hit K-pop band BTS &#8211; Dr James Doty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Knowledge Illusion : The myth of individual thought and the power of collective wisdom &#8211; Steven Sloman, Philip Fernbach (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-knowledge-illusion-the-myth-of-individual-thought-and-the-power-of-collective-wisdom-steven-sloman-philip-fernbach-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-knowledge-illusion-the-myth-of-individual-thought-and-the-power-of-collective-wisdom-steven-sloman-philip-fernbach-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The human mind is both brilliant and pathetic. We have mastered fire and have stood on the moon, and yet every one of us is fundamentally ignorant, irrational and prone to making simple mistakes every day. &#8216;In The Knowledge Illusion, the cognitive scientists Steven Sloman and Philip Fernbach hammer another nail into the coffin of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-knowledge-illusion-the-myth-of-individual-thought-and-the-power-of-collective-wisdom-steven-sloman-philip-fernbach-abridged/">The Knowledge Illusion : The myth of individual thought and the power of collective wisdom &#8211; Steven Sloman, Philip Fernbach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The human mind is both brilliant and pathetic. We have mastered fire and have stood on the moon, and yet every one of us is fundamentally ignorant, irrational and prone to making simple mistakes every day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In The Knowledge Illusion, the cognitive scientists Steven Sloman and Philip Fernbach hammer another nail into the coffin of the rational individual . . . positing that not just rationality but the very idea of individual thinking is a myth.&#8217;<br />
                    Yuval Harari, bestselling author of Sapiens and Homo Deus    </p>
<p>                    In this groundbreaking book, cognitive scientists Steven Sloman and Philip Fernbach show how our success as a species is down to us living in a rich community of knowledge where we are drawing on information and expertise outside our heads. And we have no idea that we are even doing it.    </p>
<p>                    Utilizing cutting-edge research, The Knowledge Illusion explains why we think we know more than we do, why beliefs are so hard to change and why we are so prone to making mistakes. Providing a blueprint for successful ways to work in collaboration to do amazing things, it reveals why the key to human intelligence lies in the way we think and work together.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-knowledge-illusion-the-myth-of-individual-thought-and-the-power-of-collective-wisdom-steven-sloman-philip-fernbach-abridged/">The Knowledge Illusion : The myth of individual thought and the power of collective wisdom &#8211; Steven Sloman, Philip Fernbach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler, Robin Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Gender]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler, Robin Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Human beings are primates, and primates are political animals. Our brains, therefore, are designed not just to hunt and gather, but also to help us get ahead socially, often via deception and self-deception. But while we may be self-interested schemers, we benefit by pretending otherwise. The less we know about our own ugly motives, the better &#8211; and thus we don&#8217;t like to talk or even think about the extent of our selfishness. This is &#8220;the elephant in the brain.&#8221; Such<br />
                    an introspective taboo makes it hard for us to think clearly about our nature and the explanations for our behavior. The aim of this book, then, is to confront our hidden motives directly &#8211; to track down the darker, unexamined corners of our psyches and blast them with floodlights. Then, once<br />
                    everything is clearly visible, we can work to better understand ourselves: Why do we laugh? Why are artists sexy? Why do we brag about travel? Why do we prefer to speak rather than listen?    </p>
<p>                    Our unconscious motives drive more than just our private behavior; they also infect our venerated social institutions such as Art, School, Charity, Medicine, Politics, and Religion. In fact, these institutions are in many ways designed to accommodate our hidden motives, to serve covert agendas alongside their &#8220;official&#8221; ones. The existence of big hidden motives can upend the usual political debates, leading one to question the legitimacy of these social institutions, and of standard policies<br />
                    designed to favor or discourage them. You won&#8217;t see yourself &#8211; or the world &#8211; the same after confronting the elephant in the brain.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-elephant-in-the-brain-hidden-motives-in-everyday-life-kevin-simler-robin-hanson-abridged/">The Elephant in the Brain : Hidden Motives in Everyday Life &#8211; Kevin Simler, Robin Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Sleep : The New Science of Sleep and Dreams &#8211; Matthew Walker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-sleep-the-new-science-of-sleep-and-dreams-matthew-walker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Methodology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-sleep-the-new-science-of-sleep-and-dreams-matthew-walker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Astonishing . . . an amazing book . . . absolutely chocker full of things that we need to know&#8217; Chris Evans &#8216;Matthew Walker is probably one of the most influential people on the planet&#8217; Evening Standard THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER TLS, OBSERVER, SUNDAY TIMES, FT, GUARDIAN, DAILY MAIL AND EVENING STANDARD BOOKS OF [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-sleep-the-new-science-of-sleep-and-dreams-matthew-walker-abridged/">Why We Sleep : The New Science of Sleep and Dreams &#8211; Matthew Walker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Astonishing . . . an amazing book . . . absolutely chocker full of things that we need to know&#8217; Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Matthew Walker is probably one of the most influential people on the planet&#8217; Evening Standard    </p>
<p>                    THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    TLS, OBSERVER, SUNDAY TIMES, FT, GUARDIAN, DAILY MAIL AND EVENING STANDARD BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2017    </p>
<p>                    Sleep is one of the most important aspects of our life, health and longevity and yet it is increasingly neglected in twenty-first-century society, with devastating consequences: every major disease in the developed world &#8211; Alzheimer&#8217;s, cancer, obesity, diabetes &#8211; has very strong causal links to deficient sleep.    </p>
<p>                    In this book, the first of its kind written by a scientific expert, Professor Matthew Walker explores twenty years of cutting-edge research to solve the mystery of why sleep matters. Looking at creatures from across the animal kingdom as well as major human studies, Why We Sleep delves into everything from what really happens during REM sleep to how caffeine and alcohol affect sleep and why our sleep patterns change across a lifetime, transforming our appreciation of the extraordinary phenomenon that safeguards our existence.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Startling, vital &#8230; a life-raft&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A top sleep scientist argues that sleep is more important for our health than diet or exercise&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Passionate, urgent . . . it had a powerful effect on me&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-sleep-the-new-science-of-sleep-and-dreams-matthew-walker-abridged/">Why We Sleep : The New Science of Sleep and Dreams &#8211; Matthew Walker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral codes and public policies. Illustrations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans. Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests? By studying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans.      </p>
<p>                    Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests?     </p>
<p>                    By studying social behaviors in animals, such as bonding, the herd instinct, the forming of trusting alliances, expressions of consolation, and conflict resolution, Frans de Waal demonstrates that animals-and humans-are preprogrammed to reach out. He has found that chimpanzees care for mates that are wounded by leopards, elephants offer reassuring rumbles to youngsters in distress, and dolphins support sick companions near the water&#8217;s surface to prevent them from drowning. From day one humans have innate sensitivities to faces, bodies, and voices; we&#8217;ve been designed to feel for one another.     </p>
<p>                    De Waal&#8217;s theory runs counter to the assumption that humans are inherently selfish, which can be seen in the fields of politics, law, and finance. But he cites the public&#8217;s outrage at the U.S. government&#8217;s lack of empathy in the wake of Hurricane Katrina as a significant shift in perspective-one that helped Barack Obama become elected and ushered in what perhaps could become an Age of Empathy. Through a better understanding of empathy&#8217;s survival value in evolution, de Waal suggests, we can work together toward a more just society based on a more generous and accurate view of human nature.     </p>
<p>                    Written in layman&#8217;s prose with a wealth of anecdotes, wry humor, and incisive intelligence, The Age of Empathy is essential reading for our embattled times.     </p>
<p>                    An important and timely message about the biological roots of human kindness.&#8211;Desmond Morris, author of The Naked Ape</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good Reasons for Bad Feelings : Insights from the Frontier of Evolutionary Psychiatry &#8211; Randolph M. Nesse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Developmental Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new approach to mental disorder. Randolph Nesse&#8217;s insightful book suggests that conditions such as anxiety and depression have a clear evolutionary purpose &#8230; This intriguing book turns some age-old questions about the human condition upside down&#8217; Tim Adams, Observer One of the world&#8217;s most respected psychiatrists provides a much-needed new evolutionary framework for making [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/">Good Reasons for Bad Feelings : Insights from the Frontier of Evolutionary Psychiatry &#8211; Randolph M. Nesse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new approach to mental disorder. Randolph Nesse&#8217;s insightful book  suggests that conditions such as anxiety and depression have a clear  evolutionary purpose &#8230; This intriguing book turns some age-old  questions about the human condition upside down&#8217; Tim Adams, Observer    </p>
<p>                    One of the world&#8217;s most respected psychiatrists provides a much-needed new evolutionary framework for making sense of mental illness    </p>
<p>                    With his classic book Why We Get Sick, Randolph Nesse established the field of evolutionary medicine. Now he returns with a book that transforms our understanding of mental disorders by exploring a fundamentally new question. Instead of asking why certain people suffer from mental illness, Nesse asks why natural selection has left us with fragile minds at all.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on revealing stories from his own clinical practice and insights from evolutionary biology, Nesse shows how negative emotions are useful in certain situations, yet can become excessive. Anxiety protects us from harm in the face of danger, but false alarms are inevitable. Low mood prevents us from wasting effort in pursuit of unreachable goals, but it often escalates into pathological depression. Other mental disorders, such as addiction and anorexia, result from the mismatch between modern environments and our ancient human past. Taken together, these insights and many more help to explain the pervasiveness of human suffering, and show us new paths for relieving it.    </p>
<p>                    Good Reasons for Bad Feelings will fascinate anyone who wonders how our minds can be so powerful, yet so fragile, and how love and goodness came to exist in organisms shaped to maximize Darwinian fitness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/">Good Reasons for Bad Feelings : Insights from the Frontier of Evolutionary Psychiatry &#8211; Randolph M. Nesse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Your Brain On Parasites : How Tiny Creatures Manipulate Our Behavior and Shape Society &#8211; Kathleen McAuliffe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Microbiology & Virology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Parasitology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Engrossing &#8230; [An] expedition through the hidden and sometimes horrifying microbial domain.&#8221; -Wall Street Journal &#8220;Fascinating-and full of the kind of factoids you can&#8217;t wait to share.&#8221; -Scientific American Parasites can live only inside another animal and, as Kathleen McAuliffe reveals, these tiny organisms have many evolutionary motives for manipulating the behavior of their hosts. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/">This Is Your Brain On Parasites : How Tiny Creatures Manipulate Our Behavior and Shape Society &#8211; Kathleen McAuliffe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Engrossing &#8230; [An] expedition through the hidden and sometimes horrifying microbial domain.&#8221; -Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Fascinating-and full of the kind of factoids you can&#8217;t wait to share.&#8221; -Scientific American    </p>
<p>                     Parasites can live only inside another animal and, as Kathleen McAuliffe reveals, these tiny organisms have many evolutionary motives for manipulating the behavior of their hosts. With astonishing precision, parasites can coax rats to approach cats, spiders to transform the patterns of their webs, and fish to draw the attention of birds that then swoop down to feast on them. We humans are hardly immune to their influence. Organisms we pick up from our own pets are strongly suspected of changing our personality traits and contributing to recklessness and impulsivity-even suicide. Germs that cause colds and the flu may alter our behavior even before symptoms become apparent.    </p>
<p>                     Parasites influence our species on the cultural level, too. Drawing on a huge body of research, McAuliffe argues that our dread of contamination is an evolved defense against parasites. The horror and revulsion we are programmed to feel when we come in contact with people who appear diseased or dirty helped pave the way for civilization, but may also be the basis for major divisions in societies that persist to this day. This Is Your Brain on Parasites is both a journey into cutting-edge science and a revelatory examination of what it means to be human.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you&#8217;ve ever doubted the power of microbes to shape society and offer us a grander view of life, read on and find yourself duly impressed.&#8221; -Heather Havrilesky, Bookforum</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/">This Is Your Brain On Parasites : How Tiny Creatures Manipulate Our Behavior and Shape Society &#8211; Kathleen McAuliffe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flow : The Psychology of Optimal Experience &#8211; Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Csikszentmihalyi arrives at an insight that many of us can intuitively grasp, despite our insistent (and culturally supported) denial of this truth. That is, it is not what happens to us that determines our happiness, but the manner in which we make sense of that reality. . . . The manner in which Csikszentmihalyi integrates [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/">Flow : The Psychology of Optimal Experience &#8211; Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Csikszentmihalyi arrives at an insight that many of us can intuitively grasp, despite our insistent (and culturally supported) denial of this truth. That is, it is not what happens to us that determines our happiness, but the manner in which we make sense of that reality. . . . The manner in which Csikszentmihalyi integrates research on consciousness, personal psychology and spirituality is illuminating.&#8221; &#8211;Los Angeles Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    The bestselling classic that holds the key to unlocking meaning, creativity, peak performance, and true happiness.     </p>
<p>                    Legendary psychologist Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi&#8217;s famous investigations of optimal experience have revealed that what makes an experience genuinely satisfying is a state of consciousness called flow. During flow, people typically experience deep enjoyment, creativity, and a total involvement with life. In this new edition of his groundbreaking classic work, Csikszentmihalyi (the leading researcher into &#8216;flow states&#8217; &#8211;Newsweek) demonstrates the ways this positive state can be controlled, not just left to chance. Flow: The Psychology of Optimal Experience teaches how, by ordering the information that enters our consciousness, we can discover true happiness, unlock our potential, and greatly improve the quality of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/">Flow : The Psychology of Optimal Experience &#8211; Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem. We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem.      </p>
<p>                    We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider world. As the latest research in psychology and neuroscience shows, we feel empathy most for those we find attractive and who seem similar to us and not at all for those who are different, distant or anonymous. Empathy therefore biases us in favour of individuals we know while numbing us to the plight of thousands. Guiding us expertly through the experiments, case studies and arguments on all sides, Paul Bloom ultimately shows that some of our worst decisions &#8211; in charity, child-raising, criminal justice, climate change and war &#8211; are motivated by this wolf in sheep&#8217;s clothing.     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly argued, urgent and humane, Against Empathy overturns widely held assumptions to reveal one of the most profound yet overlooked sources of human conflict.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Thought it Was Just Me (but it Isn&#8217;T) : Telling the Truth About Perfectionism, Inadequacy and Power &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-thought-it-was-just-me-but-it-isnt-telling-the-truth-about-perfectionism-inadequacy-and-power-brene-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-thought-it-was-just-me-but-it-isnt-telling-the-truth-about-perfectionism-inadequacy-and-power-brene-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Researcher, thought leader, and New York Times bestselling author Bren Brown offers a liberating study on the importance of our imperfections&#8211;both to our relationships and to our own sense of self The quest for perfection is exhausting and unrelenting. There is a constant barrage of social expectations that teach us that being imperfect is synonymous [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-thought-it-was-just-me-but-it-isnt-telling-the-truth-about-perfectionism-inadequacy-and-power-brene-brown-abridged/">I Thought it Was Just Me (but it Isn&#8217;T) : Telling the Truth About Perfectionism, Inadequacy and Power &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Researcher, thought leader, and New York Times bestselling author Bren Brown offers a liberating study on the importance of our imperfections&#8211;both to our relationships and to our own sense of self     </p>
<p>                    The quest for perfection is exhausting and unrelenting. There is a constant barrage of social expectations that teach us that being imperfect is synonymous with being inadequate. Everywhere we turn, there are messages that tell us who, what and how we&#8217;re supposed to be. So, we learn to hide our struggles and protect ourselves from shame, judgment, criticism and blame by seeking safety in pretending and perfection.     </p>
<p>                    Bren Brown, PhD, LMSW, is the leading authority on the power of vulnerability, and has inspired thousands through her top-selling books Daring Greatly, Rising Strong, and The Gifts of Imperfection, her wildly popular TEDx talks, and a PBS special. Based on seven years of her ground-breaking research and hundreds of interviews, I Thought It Was Just Me shines a long-overdue light on an important truth: Our imperfections are what connect us to each other and to our humanity. Our vulnerabilities are not weaknesses; they are powerful reminders to keep our hearts and minds open to the reality that we&#8217;re all in this together.     </p>
<p>                    Brown writes, &#8220;We need our lives back. It&#8217;s time to reclaim the gifts of imperfection&#8211;the courage to be real, the compassion we need to love ourselves and others, and the connection that gives true purpose and meaning to life. These are the gifts that bring love, laughter, gratitude, empathy and joy into our lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-thought-it-was-just-me-but-it-isnt-telling-the-truth-about-perfectionism-inadequacy-and-power-brene-brown-abridged/">I Thought it Was Just Me (but it Isn&#8217;T) : Telling the Truth About Perfectionism, Inadequacy and Power &#8211; Brene Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sensemaking : What Makes Human Intelligence Essential in the Age of the Algorithm &#8211; Christian Madsbjerg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BUSINESS BOOK OF THE MONTH (APRIL 2017) Humans have become subservient to algorithms. Every day brings a new Moneyball fix &#8211; a maths whiz who will crack open an industry with clean fact-based analysis rather than human intuition and experience. As a result, we have stopped thinking. Machines do it for us. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/">Sensemaking : What Makes Human Intelligence Essential in the Age of the Algorithm &#8211; Christian Madsbjerg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BUSINESS BOOK OF THE MONTH (APRIL 2017)  Humans have become subservient to algorithms. Every day brings a new Moneyball fix &#8211; a maths whiz who will crack open an industry with clean fact-based analysis rather than human intuition and experience. As a result, we have stopped thinking. Machines do it for us. Christian Madsbjerg argues that our fixation with data often masks stunning deficiencies, and the risks for humankind are enormous. Blind devotion to number crunching imperils our businesses, our educations, our governments, and our life savings. Too many companies have lost touch with the humanity of their customers, while marginalising workers with arts-based skills. Contrary to popular thinking, Madsbjerg shows how many of today&#8217;s biggest success stories stem not from &#8216;quant&#8217; thinking but from deep, nuanced engagement with culture, language, and history. He calls his method sensemaking. In this landmark book, Madsbjerg lays out five principles for how business leaders, entrepreneurs, and individuals can use it to solve their thorniest problems.<br />
                    He profiles companies using sensemaking to connect with new customers, and takes readers inside the work process of sensemaking &#8216;connoisseurs&#8217; like investor George Soros, architect Bjarke Ingels, and others. Both practical and philosophical, Sensemaking is a powerful rejoinder to corporate groupthink and an indispensable resource for leaders and innovators who want to stand out from the pack.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/">Sensemaking : What Makes Human Intelligence Essential in the Age of the Algorithm &#8211; Christian Madsbjerg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Successful Aging : A Neuroscientist Explores the Power and Potential of Our Lives &#8211; Daniel J. Levitin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT TOP 10 BESTSELLER *New York Times *USAToday *Washington Post *LA Times Debunks the idea that aging inevitably brings infirmity and unhappiness and instead offers a trove of practical, evidence-based guidance for living longer and better. &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, author of When and Drive SUCCESSFUL AGING delivers powerful insights: &#8211; Debunking the myth that memory [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/">Successful Aging : A Neuroscientist Explores the Power and Potential of Our Lives &#8211; Daniel J. Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT TOP 10 BESTSELLER *New York Times *USAToday *Washington Post *LA Times     </p>
<p>                    Debunks the idea that aging inevitably brings infirmity and unhappiness and instead offers a trove of practical, evidence-based guidance for living longer and better.<br />
                    &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, author of When and Drive     </p>
<p>                    SUCCESSFUL AGING delivers powerful insights:<br />
                     &#8211; Debunking the myth that memory always declines with age<br />
                     &#8211; Confirming that health span&#8211;not life span&#8211;is what matters<br />
                     &#8211; Proving that sixty-plus years is a unique and newly recognized developmental stage<br />
                     &#8211; Recommending that people look forward to joy, as reminiscing doesn&#8217;t promote health     </p>
<p>                     Levitin looks at the science behind what we all can learn from those who age joyously, as well as how to adapt our culture to take full advantage of older people&#8217;s wisdom and experience. Throughout his exploration of what aging really means, using research from developmental neuroscience and the psychology of individual differences, Levitin reveals resilience strategies and practical, cognitive- enhancing tricks everyone should do as they age.     </p>
<p>                     Successful Aging inspires a powerful new approach to how readers think about our final decades, and it will revolutionize the way we plan for old age as individuals, family members, and citizens within a society where the average life expectancy continues to rise.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/">Successful Aging : A Neuroscientist Explores the Power and Potential of Our Lives &#8211; Daniel J. Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
