<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Educational Psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/educational-psychology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/educational-psychology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Educational Psychology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/educational-psychology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For centuries, experts have argued that learning was about memorizing information: You&#8217;re supposed to study facts, dates, and details; burn them into your memory; and then apply that knowledge at opportune times. But this approach to learning isn&#8217;t nearly enough for the world that we live in today, and in Learn Better journalist and education [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/">Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For centuries, experts have argued that learning was about memorizing information: You&#8217;re supposed to study facts, dates, and details; burn them into your memory; and then apply that knowledge at opportune times. But this approach to learning isn&#8217;t nearly enough for the world that we live in today, and in Learn Better journalist and education researcher Ulrich Boser demonstrates that how we learn can matter just as much as what we learn.     </p>
<p>                    In this brilliantly researched book, Boser maps out the new science of learning, showing how simple techniques like comprehension check-ins and making material personally relatable can help people gain expertise in dramatically better ways. He covers six key steps to help you &#8220;learn how to learn,&#8221; all illuminated with fascinating stories like how Jackson Pollock developed his unique painting style and why an ancient Japanese counting device allows kids to do math at superhuman speeds. Boser&#8217;s witty, engaging writing makes this book feel like a guilty pleasure, not homework.    </p>
<p>                    Learn Better will revolutionize the way students and society alike approach learning and makes the case that being smart is not an innate ability&#8211;learning is a skill everyone can master. With Boser as your guide, you will be able to fully capitalize on your brain&#8217;s remarkable ability to gain new skills and open up a whole new world of possibilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/">Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Practicing Mind : Developing Focus and Discipline in Your Life &#8211; Master Any Skill or Challenge by Learning to Love the Process &#8211; Thomas M. Sterner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-practicing-mind-developing-focus-and-discipline-in-your-life-master-any-skill-or-challenge-by-learning-to-love-the-process-thomas-m-sterner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Staff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-practicing-mind-developing-focus-and-discipline-in-your-life-master-any-skill-or-challenge-by-learning-to-love-the-process-thomas-m-sterner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In those times when we want to acquire a new skill or face a formidable challenge we hope to overcome, what we need most are patience, focus, and discipline, traits that seem elusive or difficult to maintain. In this enticing and practical book, Thomas Sterner demonstrates how to learn skills for any aspect of life, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-practicing-mind-developing-focus-and-discipline-in-your-life-master-any-skill-or-challenge-by-learning-to-love-the-process-thomas-m-sterner-abridged/">The Practicing Mind : Developing Focus and Discipline in Your Life &#8211; Master Any Skill or Challenge by Learning to Love the Process &#8211; Thomas M. Sterner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In those times when we want to acquire a new skill or face a formidable challenge we hope to overcome, what we need most are patience, focus, and discipline, traits that seem elusive or difficult to maintain. In this enticing and practical book, Thomas Sterner demonstrates how to learn skills for any aspect of life, from golfing to business to parenting, by learning to love the process. Early life is all about trial-and-error practice. If we had given up in the face of failure, repetition, and difficulty, we would never have learned to walk or tie our shoes. So why, as adults, do we often give up on a goal when at first we don&#8217;t succeed? In his study of how we learn (prompted by his pursuit of disciplines such as music and golf), Sterner has found that we have forgotten the principles of practice &#8212; the process of picking a goal and applying steady effort to reach it. The methods Sterner teaches show that practice done properly isn&#8217;t drudgery on the way to mastery but a fulfilling process in and of itself, one that builds discipline and clarity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-practicing-mind-developing-focus-and-discipline-in-your-life-master-any-skill-or-challenge-by-learning-to-love-the-process-thomas-m-sterner-abridged/">The Practicing Mind : Developing Focus and Discipline in Your Life &#8211; Master Any Skill or Challenge by Learning to Love the Process &#8211; Thomas M. Sterner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School?: A Cognitive Scientist Answers Questions About How the Mind Works and What It Means for the Classroom &#8211; Daniel T. Willingham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Research-based insights and practical advice about effective learning strategies In this new edition of the highly regarded Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School? cognitive psychologist Daniel Willingham turns his research on the biological and cognitive basis of learning into workable teaching techniques. This book will help you improve your teaching practice by explaining how you and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/">Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School?: A Cognitive Scientist Answers Questions About How the Mind Works and What It Means for the Classroom &#8211; Daniel T. Willingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Research-based insights and practical advice about effective learning strategies In this new edition of the highly regarded Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School? cognitive psychologist Daniel Willingham turns his research on the biological and cognitive basis of learning into workable teaching techniques. This book will help you improve your teaching practice by explaining how you and your students think and learn. It reveals the importance of story, emotion, memory, context, and routine in building knowledge and creating lasting learning experiences. With a treasure trove of updated material, this edition draws its themes from the most frequently asked questions in Willingham&#8217;s &#8216;Ask the Cognitive Scientist&#8217; column in the American Educator. How can you teach students the skills they need when standardized testing just requires facts? Why do students remember everything on TV, but forget everything you say? How can you adjust your teaching for different learning styles? Read this book for the answers to these questions and for practical advice on helping your learners learn better. Discover easy-to-understand, evidence-based principles with clear applications for the classroom Update yourself on the latest cognitive science research and new, teacher-tested pedagogical tools Learn about Willingham&#8217;s surprising findings, such as that you cannot develop &#8216;thinking skills&#8217; without facts Understand the brain&#8217;s workings to help you hone your teaching skills Why Students Don&#8217;t Like School is a valuable resource for both veteran and novice teachers, teachers-in-training, and for the principals, administrators, and staff development professionals who work with them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/">Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School?: A Cognitive Scientist Answers Questions About How the Mind Works and What It Means for the Classroom &#8211; Daniel T. Willingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
