<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Radio &amp; Television Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/radio-television-industry/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/radio-television-industry/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Radio &amp; Television Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/radio-television-industry/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Late Shift : Letterman, Leno, &#038; the Network Battle for the Night &#8211; Bill Carter</title>
		<link>/the-late-shift-letterman-leno-the-network-battle-for-the-night-bill-carter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Radio & Television Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-late-shift-letterman-leno-the-network-battle-for-the-night-bill-carter/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;gripping&#8221; New York Times bestseller from the host of CNN podcast Behind the Desk tells the true story-and backstage drama-of late-night comedy (Los Angeles Times). When beloved host Johnny Carson announced his retirement after thirty years on The Tonight Show, millions of Americans mourned. But inside the television industry, the news ignited a battle [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-late-shift-letterman-leno-the-network-battle-for-the-night-bill-carter/">The Late Shift : Letterman, Leno, &#038; the Network Battle for the Night &#8211; Bill Carter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;gripping&#8221; New York Times bestseller from the host of CNN podcast Behind the Desk tells the true story-and backstage drama-of late-night comedy (Los Angeles Times).</p>
<p>                     When beloved host Johnny Carson announced his retirement after thirty years on The Tonight Show, millions of Americans mourned. But inside the television industry, the news ignited a battle between two amazing talents-Jay Leno and David Letterman-who both yearned to occupy the departing legend&#8217;s chair. For NBC, it would be a decision with millions of dollars at stake. Soon these two comedians with strikingly different styles, who had once shared a friendship as they worked the clubs together, would be engaged in a fierce competition for the prize.</p>
<p>                     Based on in-depth reporting and interviews with those involved, and updated with a new introduction by the author-a producer of CNN series The Story of Late Night-The Late Shift is a &#8220;vivid, behind-the-scenes, blow-by-blow account&#8221; of the fight that ensued, as stars, agents, and executives maneuvered for control of the most profitable program in TV history (Chicago Tribune).</p>
<p>                     &#8220;Remarkably gripping . . . Takes us deep into the bizarre high-stakes world of broadcasting . . . A powerful story, and ultimately a sad one, filled with casualties as well as winners.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                     &#8220;Solid reporting, based on extensive interviews with the principals, lifts The Late Shift into a class of its own. . . . The insights into the people involved are what make [the book] a page-turner.&#8221; -Orange Country Register</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-late-shift-letterman-leno-the-network-battle-for-the-night-bill-carter/">The Late Shift : Letterman, Leno, &#038; the Network Battle for the Night &#8211; Bill Carter</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dance & Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital TV & Media Centres: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Radio & Television Industry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How big data is transforming the creative industries, and how those industries can use lessons from Netflix, Amazon, and Apple to fight back. &#8220;[The authors explain] gently yet firmly exactly how the internet threatens established ways and what can and cannot be done about it. Their book should be required for anyone who wishes to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/">Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How big data is transforming the creative industries, and how those industries can use lessons from Netflix, Amazon, and Apple to fight back.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;[The authors explain] gently yet firmly exactly how the internet threatens established ways and what can and cannot be done about it. Their book should be required for anyone who wishes to believe that nothing much has changed.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;The Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Packed with examples, from the nimble-footed who reacted quickly to adapt their businesses, to laggards who lost empires.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    Traditional network television programming has always followed the same script: executives approve a pilot, order a trial number of episodes, and broadcast them, expecting viewers to watch a given show on their television sets at the same time every week. But then came Netflix&#8217;s House of Cards. Netflix gauged the show&#8217;s potential from data it had gathered about subscribers&#8217; preferences, ordered two seasons without seeing a pilot, and uploaded the first thirteen episodes all at once for viewers to watch whenever they wanted on the devices of their choice.     </p>
<p>                    In this book, Michael Smith and Rahul Telang, experts on entertainment analytics, show how the success of House of Cards upended the film and TV industries&#8211;and how companies like Amazon and Apple are changing the rules in other entertainment industries, notably publishing and music. We&#8217;re living through a period of unprecedented technological disruption in the entertainment industries. Just about everything is affected: pricing, production, distribution, piracy. Smith and Telang discuss niche products and the long tail, product differentiation, price discrimination, and incentives for users not to steal content. To survive and succeed, businesses have to adapt rapidly and creatively. Smith and Telang explain how.    </p>
<p>                    How can companies discover who their customers are, what they want, and how much they are willing to pay for it? Data. The entertainment industries, must learn to play a little &#8220;moneyball.&#8221; The bottom line: follow the data.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/">Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
