<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Intelligence &amp; Reasoning Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/intelligence-reasoning/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/intelligence-reasoning/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Intelligence &amp; Reasoning Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/intelligence-reasoning/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oceanography (seas)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter? In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week<br />
                              &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian<br />
                              &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                                What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter?    </p>
<p>                              In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science and a skilled scuba diver, tells a bold new story of how nature became aware of itself &#8211; a story that largely occurs in the ocean, where animals first appeared.    </p>
<p>                              Tracking the mind&#8217;s fitful development from unruly clumps of seaborne cells to the first evolved nervous systems in ancient relatives of jellyfish, he explores the incredible evolutionary journey of the cephalopods, which began as inconspicuous molluscs who would later abandon their shells to rise above the ocean floor, searching for prey and acquiring the greater intelligence needed to do so &#8211; a journey completely independent from the route that mammals and birds would later take.    </p>
<p>                              But what kind of intelligence do cephalopods possess? How did the octopus, a solitary creature with little social life, become so smart? What is it like to have eight tentacles that are so packed with neurons that they virtually &#8216;think for themselves&#8217;? By tracing the question of inner life back to its roots and comparing human beings with our most remarkable animal relatives, Godfrey-Smith casts crucial new light on the octopus mind &#8211; and on our own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Upright Thinkers : The Human Journey from Living in Trees to Understanding the Cosmos &#8211; Leonard Mlodinow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-upright-thinkers-the-human-journey-from-living-in-trees-to-understanding-the-cosmos-leonard-mlodinow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-upright-thinkers-the-human-journey-from-living-in-trees-to-understanding-the-cosmos-leonard-mlodinow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of The Drunkard&#8217;s Walk and Subliminal, this is the inspiring and illuminating story of how we have come to understand the world, from the invention of the very first tools to the mind-bending theories of quantum physics. Leonard Mlodinow guides us through the critical eras and events in the development of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upright-thinkers-the-human-journey-from-living-in-trees-to-understanding-the-cosmos-leonard-mlodinow-abridged/">The Upright Thinkers : The Human Journey from Living in Trees to Understanding the Cosmos &#8211; Leonard Mlodinow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of The Drunkard&#8217;s Walk and Subliminal, this is the inspiring and illuminating story of how we have come to understand the world, from the invention of the very first tools to the mind-bending theories of quantum physics.    </p>
<p>                    Leonard Mlodinow guides us through the critical eras and events in the development of science, all of which, he demonstrates, were propelled forward by humankind&#8217;s collective struggle to know. From the birth of reasoning and culture to the formation of the studies of physics, chemistry, biology, and modern-day quantum physics, we come to see that much of our progress can be attributed to simple questions &#8211; why? how? &#8211; bravely asked. Mlodinow profiles some of the great philosophers, scientists, and thinkers who explored these questions &#8211; Aristotle, Galileo, Newton, Darwin, Einstein and Lavoisier among them &#8211; and makes clear that just as science has played a key role in shaping the patterns of human thought, human subjectivity has played a key role in the evolution of science.    </p>
<p>                    At once authoritative and accessible, and infused with the author&#8217;s trademark wit, this deeply insightful book is a stunning tribute to humanity&#8217;s intellectual curiosity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upright-thinkers-the-human-journey-from-living-in-trees-to-understanding-the-cosmos-leonard-mlodinow-abridged/">The Upright Thinkers : The Human Journey from Living in Trees to Understanding the Cosmos &#8211; Leonard Mlodinow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sensemaking : What Makes Human Intelligence Essential in the Age of the Algorithm &#8211; Christian Madsbjerg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BUSINESS BOOK OF THE MONTH (APRIL 2017) Humans have become subservient to algorithms. Every day brings a new Moneyball fix &#8211; a maths whiz who will crack open an industry with clean fact-based analysis rather than human intuition and experience. As a result, we have stopped thinking. Machines do it for us. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/">Sensemaking : What Makes Human Intelligence Essential in the Age of the Algorithm &#8211; Christian Madsbjerg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BUSINESS BOOK OF THE MONTH (APRIL 2017)  Humans have become subservient to algorithms. Every day brings a new Moneyball fix &#8211; a maths whiz who will crack open an industry with clean fact-based analysis rather than human intuition and experience. As a result, we have stopped thinking. Machines do it for us. Christian Madsbjerg argues that our fixation with data often masks stunning deficiencies, and the risks for humankind are enormous. Blind devotion to number crunching imperils our businesses, our educations, our governments, and our life savings. Too many companies have lost touch with the humanity of their customers, while marginalising workers with arts-based skills. Contrary to popular thinking, Madsbjerg shows how many of today&#8217;s biggest success stories stem not from &#8216;quant&#8217; thinking but from deep, nuanced engagement with culture, language, and history. He calls his method sensemaking. In this landmark book, Madsbjerg lays out five principles for how business leaders, entrepreneurs, and individuals can use it to solve their thorniest problems.<br />
                    He profiles companies using sensemaking to connect with new customers, and takes readers inside the work process of sensemaking &#8216;connoisseurs&#8217; like investor George Soros, architect Bjarke Ingels, and others. Both practical and philosophical, Sensemaking is a powerful rejoinder to corporate groupthink and an indispensable resource for leaders and innovators who want to stand out from the pack.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sensemaking-what-makes-human-intelligence-essential-in-the-age-of-the-algorithm-christian-madsbjerg-abridged/">Sensemaking : What Makes Human Intelligence Essential in the Age of the Algorithm &#8211; Christian Madsbjerg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decision Theory: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques in The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking, you will regularly find imaginative solutions to difficult challenges, and you will discover new ways of looking at your world and yourself&#8211;revealing previously hidden opportunities. The book offers real-life stories, explicit action items, and concrete methods that allow you to attain a deeper understanding of any issue, exploit the power of failure as a step toward success, develop a habit of creating probing questions, see the world of ideas as an ever-flowing stream of thought, and embrace the uplifting reality that we are all capable of change. No matter who you are, the practical mind-sets introduced in the book will empower you to realize any goal in a more creative, intelligent, and effective manner.<br />
                    Filled with engaging examples that unlock truths about thinking in every walk of life, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking is written for all who want to reach their fullest potential&#8211;including students, parents, teachers, businesspeople, professionals, athletes, artists, leaders, and lifelong learners. Whenever you are stuck, need a new idea, or want to learn and grow, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking will inspire and guide you on your way. To share thinking stories, go to: http://5elementsofthinking.wordpress.com/</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ungifted : Intelligence Redefined &#8211; Scott Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Ungifted , cognitive psychologist Scott Barry Kaufman,who was relegated to special education as a child,offers a new way of looking at intelligence. He explores the latest research in genetics, neuroscience, and psychology to challenge the conventional wisdom about the childhood predictors of adult success, arguing for a more holistic approach to intelligence that takes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/">Ungifted : Intelligence Redefined &#8211; Scott Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In  Ungifted , cognitive psychologist Scott Barry Kaufman,who was relegated to special education as a child,offers a new way of looking at intelligence. He explores the latest research in genetics, neuroscience, and psychology to challenge the conventional wisdom about the childhood predictors of adult success, arguing for a more holistic approach to intelligence that takes into account each individual&#8217;s abilities, engagement, and personal goals. Combining original research and a singular compassion,  Ungifted  increases our appreciation for all different kinds of minds and ways of achieving both personally meaningful and publicly recognized forms of success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/">Ungifted : Intelligence Redefined &#8211; Scott Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
