<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Time (chronology), Time Systems &amp; Standards Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/time-chronology-time-systems-standards/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/time-chronology-time-systems-standards/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Time (chronology), Time Systems &amp; Standards Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/time-chronology-time-systems-standards/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Time Paradox : Using the New Psychology of Time to Your Advantage &#8211; John Boyd, Philip Zimbardo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-time-paradox-using-the-new-psychology-of-time-to-your-advantage-john-boyd-philip-zimbardo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-time-paradox-using-the-new-psychology-of-time-to-your-advantage-john-boyd-philip-zimbardo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every significant choice, every important decision we make, is determined by our perception of time. This is the most influential force in our lives, yet we are virtually unaware of it. In this fascinating book, the award-winning past president of the American Psychological Association, Philip Zimbardo, and his co-author, John Boyd, show how: &#8211; the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-time-paradox-using-the-new-psychology-of-time-to-your-advantage-john-boyd-philip-zimbardo-abridged/">The Time Paradox : Using the New Psychology of Time to Your Advantage &#8211; John Boyd, Philip Zimbardo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every significant choice, every important decision we make, is determined by our perception of time. This is the most influential force in our lives, yet we are virtually unaware of it. In this fascinating book, the award-winning past president of the American Psychological Association, Philip Zimbardo, and his co-author, John Boyd, show how:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; the way you perceive time is as unique as your fingerprints<br />
                    &#8211; these individual time perspectives shape your life, and the world around you<br />
                    &#8211; you can change the way you perceive time, so you get the most out of every minute<br />
                    &#8211; if you don&#8217;t, the power of time in the modern world is so immense that it will take its toll on you    </p>
<p>                    The Time Paradox is a highly readable, stimulating look at a subject that absorbs us all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-time-paradox-using-the-new-psychology-of-time-to-your-advantage-john-boyd-philip-zimbardo-abridged/">The Time Paradox : Using the New Psychology of Time to Your Advantage &#8211; John Boyd, Philip Zimbardo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself. Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                              From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself.    </p>
<p>                              Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells writing and rewriting the fantastic tale that became his first book, an international sensation, The Time Machine. A host of forces were converging to transmute the human understanding of time, some philosophical and some technological &#8211; the electric telegraph, the steam railroad, the discovery of buried civilisations, and the perfection of clocks. Gleick tracks the evolution of time travel as an idea in the culture &#8211; from Marcel Proust to Doctor Who, from Woody Allen to Jorge Luis Borges. He explores the inevitable looping paradoxes and examines the porous boundary between pulp fiction and modern physics. Finally, he delves into a temporal shift that is unsettling our own moment: the instantaneous wired world, with its all-consuming present and vanishing future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Felt Time : The Science of How We Experience Time &#8211; Marc Wittmann, Translated by Erik Butler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/felt-time-the-science-of-how-we-experience-time-marc-wittmann-translated-by-erik-butler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug-induced States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/felt-time-the-science-of-how-we-experience-time-marc-wittmann-translated-by-erik-butler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An expert explores the riddle of subjective time, from why time speeds up as we grow older to the connection between time and consciousness. We have widely varying perceptions of time. Children have trouble waiting for anything. (&#8220;Are we there yet?&#8221;) Boredom is often connected to our sense of time passing (or not passing). As [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/felt-time-the-science-of-how-we-experience-time-marc-wittmann-translated-by-erik-butler-abridged/">Felt Time : The Science of How We Experience Time &#8211; Marc Wittmann, Translated by Erik Butler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An expert explores the riddle of subjective time, from why time speeds up as we grow older to the connection between time and consciousness.    </p>
<p>                    We have widely varying perceptions of time. Children have trouble waiting for anything. (&#8220;Are we there yet?&#8221;) Boredom is often connected to our sense of time passing (or not passing). As people grow older, time seems to speed up, the years flitting by without a pause. How does our sense of time come about? In Felt Time, Marc Wittmann explores the riddle of subjective time, explaining our perception of time&#8211;whether moment by moment, or in terms of life as a whole. Drawing on the latest insights from psychology and neuroscience, Wittmann offers a new answer to the question of how we experience time.    </p>
<p>                    Wittmann explains, among other things, how we choose between savoring the moment and deferring gratification; why impulsive people are bored easily, and why their boredom is often a matter of time; whether each person possesses a personal speed, a particular brain rhythm distinguishing quick people from slow people; and why the feeling of duration can serve as an &#8220;error signal,&#8221; letting us know when it is taking too long for dinner to be ready or for the bus to come. He considers the practice of mindfulness, and whether it can reduce the speed of life and help us gain more time, and he describes how, as we grow older, subjective time accelerates as routine increases; a fulfilled and varied life is a long life. Evidence shows that bodily processes&#8211;especially the heartbeat&#8211;underlie our feeling of time and act as an internal clock for our sense of time. And Wittmann points to recent research that connects time to consciousness; ongoing studies of time consciousness, he tells us, will help us to understand the conscious self.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/felt-time-the-science-of-how-we-experience-time-marc-wittmann-translated-by-erik-butler-abridged/">Felt Time : The Science of How We Experience Time &#8211; Marc Wittmann, Translated by Erik Butler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened by the traces of memory inside the connections between our neurons. We are memory. We are nostalgia. We are longing for a future that will not come&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Time is a mystery that does not cease to puzzle us. Philosophers, artists and poets have long explored its meaning while scientists have found that its structure is different from the simple intuition we have of it. From Boltzmann to quantum theory, from Einstein to loop quantum gravity, our understanding of time has been undergoing radical transformations. Time flows at a different speed in different places, the past and the future differ far less than we might think, and the very notion of the present evaporates in the vast universe.    </p>
<p>                    With his extraordinary charm and sense of wonder, bringing together science, philosophy and art, Carlo Rovelli unravels this mystery. Enlightening and consoling, The Order of Time shows that to understand ourselves we need to reflect on time &#8212; and to understand time we need to reflect on ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
