<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Coping With Illness Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/coping-with-illness/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/coping-with-illness/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Coping With Illness Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/coping-with-illness/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Wuhan Diary : Dispatches from a Quarantined City &#8211; Fang Fang</title>
		<link>/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aid & Relief Programmes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Disasters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From one of China&#8217;s most acclaimed and decorated writers comes a powerful first-person account of life in Wuhan during the COVID-19 outbreak. On January 25, 2020, after the central government imposed a lockdown in Wuhan, acclaimed Chinese writer Fang Fang began publishing an online diary. In the days and weeks that followed, Fang Fang&#8217;s nightly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/">Wuhan Diary : Dispatches from a Quarantined City &#8211; Fang Fang</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From one of China&#8217;s most acclaimed and decorated writers comes a powerful first-person account of life in Wuhan during the COVID-19 outbreak.</p>
<p>                    On January 25, 2020, after the central government imposed a lockdown in Wuhan, acclaimed Chinese writer Fang Fang began publishing an online diary. In the days and weeks that followed, Fang Fang&#8217;s nightly postings gave voice to the fears, frustrations, anger, and hope of millions of her fellow citizens, reflecting on the psychological impact of forced isolation, the role of the internet as both community lifeline and source of misinformation, and most tragically, the lives of neighbors and friends taken by the deadly virus. </p>
<p>                    A fascinating eyewitness account of events as they unfold, Wuhan Diary captures the challenges of daily life and the changing moods and emotions of being quarantined without reliable information. Fang Fang finds solace in small domestic comforts and is inspired by the courage of friends, health professionals and volunteers, as well as the resilience and perseverance of Wuhan&#8217;s nine million residents. But, by claiming the writer´s duty to record she also speaks out against social injustice, abuse of power, and other problems which impeded the response to the epidemic and gets herself embroiled in online controversies because of it.</p>
<p>                    As Fang Fang documents the beginning of the global health crisis in real time, we are able to identify patterns and mistakes that many of the countries dealing with the novel coronavirus have later repeated. She reminds us that, in the face of the new virus, the plight of the citizens of Wuhan is also that of citizens everywhere. As Fang Fang writes: &#8220;The virus is the common enemy of humankind; that is a lesson for all humanity. The only way we can conquer this virus and free ourselves from its grip is for all members of humankind to work together.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    Blending the intimate and the epic, the profound and the quotidian, Wuhan Diary is a remarkable record of an extraordinary time. </p>
<p>                    Translated from the Chinese by Michael Berry</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wuhan-diary-dispatches-from-a-quarantined-city-fang-fang/">Wuhan Diary : Dispatches from a Quarantined City &#8211; Fang Fang</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</title>
		<link>/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8211; Over five million copies sold worldwide! From renowned psychiatrist Dr. David D. Burns, the revolutionary volume that popularized Dr. Aaron T. Beck&#8217;s cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) and has helped millions combat feelings of depression and develop greater self-esteem. Anxiety and depression are the most common mental illnesses in the world, affecting 18% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/">Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8211; Over five million copies sold worldwide!</p>
<p>                    From renowned psychiatrist Dr. David D. Burns, the revolutionary volume that popularized Dr. Aaron T. Beck&#8217;s cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) and has helped millions combat feelings of depression and develop greater self-esteem.</p>
<p>                    Anxiety and depression are the most common mental illnesses in the world, affecting 18% of the U.S. population every year. But for many, the path to recovery seems daunting, endless, or completely out of reach.</p>
<p>                    The good news is that anxiety, guilt, pessimism, procrastination, low self-esteem, and other black holes of depression can be alleviated. In Feeling Good, eminent psychiatrist, David D. Burns, M.D., outlines the remarkable, scientifically proven techniques that will immediately lift your spirits and help you develop a positive outlook on life, enabling you to: Nip negative feelings in the budRecognize what causes your mood swingsDeal with guiltHandle hostility and criticismOvercome addiction to love and approvalBuild self-esteemFeel good everyday</p>
<p>                    This groundbreaking, life-changing book has helped millions overcome negative thoughts and discover joy in their daily lives. You owe it to yourself to FEEL GOOD!</p>
<p>                    I would personally evaluate David Burns&#8217; Feeling Good as one of the most significant books to come out of the last third of the Twentieth Century. ?- Dr. David F. Maas, Professor of English, Ambassador University</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feeling-good-the-new-mood-therapy-david-d-burns/">Feeling Good : The New Mood Therapy &#8211; David D Burns</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Darkness Visible : A Memoir of Madness &#8211; William Styron</title>
		<link>/darkness-visible-a-memoir-of-madness-william-styron/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/darkness-visible-a-memoir-of-madness-william-styron/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A work of great personal courage and a literary tour de force, this bestseller is Styron&#8217;s true account of his descent into a crippling and almost suicidal depression. Styron is perhaps the first writer to convey the full terror of depression&#8217;s psychic landscape, as well as the illuminating path to recovery.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkness-visible-a-memoir-of-madness-william-styron/">Darkness Visible : A Memoir of Madness &#8211; William Styron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A work of great personal courage and a literary tour de force, this bestseller is Styron&#8217;s true account of his descent into a crippling and almost suicidal depression. Styron is perhaps the first writer to convey the full terror of depression&#8217;s psychic landscape, as well as the illuminating path to recovery.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkness-visible-a-memoir-of-madness-william-styron/">Darkness Visible : A Memoir of Madness &#8211; William Styron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</title>
		<link>/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Giving Up Smoking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Respiratory Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Funding & Policy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19. Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19.    </p>
<p>                    Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns and border closings causing widespread business closures, economic collapse, and massive unemployment; and an unprecedented curtailment of civil liberties and freedoms in the name of keeping people safe by locking them up in their homes.    </p>
<p>                    We are now living in a world that is increasingly ruled, not by our democratic systems and institutions, but by public health fiat, carried out by politicians who rule by instilling fear and panic.    </p>
<p>                    In The Truth About COVID-19, Dr. Mercola and Cummins reveal new and emerging evidence that:    </p>
<p>                    The SARS-CoV-2 virus was, indeed, lab-engineered and emerged from a negligently managed bioweapons lab in Wuhan, China<br />
                    The global pandemic was long anticipated by global elites who have used it to facilitate and hide the largest upward transfer of wealth in human history<br />
                    PCR testing, case counts, morbidity, and vaccine safety and efficacy data have been widely manipulated and misrepresented<br />
                    Obesity, diabetes, and heart disease are known to worsen COVID-19 outcomes, but the junk food industry continues to push its agenda at the expense of public health<br />
                    Safe, simple, and inexpensive treatment and prevention for COVID-19 have been censored and suppressed to create a clear path for vaccine acceptance<br />
                    Effectiveness of the vaccines has been wildly exaggerated and major safety questions have gone unanswered    </p>
<p>                    The good news in all of this is that we can take control of our health and that, together, we have the power to unite and fight back for our health, democracy, and freedom. The time is now for a global awakening. As Dr. Mercola and Cummins remind us, this is the fight of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Furiously Happy &#8211; Jenny Lawson</title>
		<link>/furiously-happy-jenny-lawson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/furiously-happy-jenny-lawson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For fans of David Sedaris, Tina Fey and Caitlin Moran comes Furiously Happy from Jenny Lawson, author of the #1 New York Times bestseller Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened. In Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened, Jenny Lawson regaled readers with uproarious stories of her bizarre childhood. In Furiously Happy she explores her lifelong battle with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/furiously-happy-jenny-lawson/">Furiously Happy &#8211; Jenny Lawson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For fans of David Sedaris, Tina Fey and Caitlin Moran comes Furiously Happy from Jenny Lawson, author of the #1 New York Times bestseller Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened.    </p>
<p>                    In Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened, Jenny Lawson regaled readers with uproarious stories of her bizarre childhood. In Furiously Happy she explores her lifelong battle with mental illness. A hysterical, ridiculous book about crippling depression and anxiety? That sounds like a terrible idea. And terrible ideas are what Jenny does best.    </p>
<p>                    As Jenny says: &#8216;You can&#8217;t experience pain without also experiencing the baffling and ridiculous moments of being fiercely, unapologetically, intensely and (above all) furiously happy.&#8217;  It&#8217;s a philosophy that has &#8211; quite literally &#8211; saved her life.    </p>
<p>                    Jenny&#8217;s first book, Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened, was ostensibly about family, but deep down it was about celebrating your own weirdness. Furiously Happy is a book about mental illness, but under the surface it&#8217;s about embracing joy in fantastic and outrageous ways.  And who doesn&#8217;t need a bit more of that?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/furiously-happy-jenny-lawson/">Furiously Happy &#8211; Jenny Lawson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone struggles with sleep from time to time, but when sleepless nights and overtired days become the norm, your well-being is compromised, and frustration and worry increase-including concerns about what&#8217;s stopping you from getting the sleep you need, and what can be done about it. So, how do you stop the cycle of relentless worries [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/">End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone struggles with sleep from time to time, but when sleepless nights and overtired days become the norm, your well-being is compromised, and frustration and worry increase-including concerns about what&#8217;s stopping you from getting the sleep you need, and what can be done about it. So, how do you stop the cycle of relentless worries and restless nights?    </p>
<p>                    End the Insomnia Struggle offers a comprehensive, medication-free program that can be individually tailored for anyone who struggles with insomnia. Integrating the physiology of sleep, and proven-effective approaches from cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (CBT-I) and acceptance and commitment therapy (ACT), this book provides step-by-step guidance for developing your own treatment plan according to your particular challenges with insomnia.    </p>
<p>                    With this book, you&#8217;ll have everything you need to overcome the relentless thoughts, ruminations, and stress of insomnia. Utilizing these evidence-based strategies and easy-to-use tools, you&#8217;ll finally get to sleep, stay asleep, and wake up rested and ready to face the world as your best self, day after day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/end-the-insomnia-struggle-a-step-by-step-guide-to-help-you-get-to-sleep-and-stay-asleep-colleen-ehrnstrom-alisha-l-brosse-abridged/">End the Insomnia Struggle : A Step-by-Step Guide to Help You Get to Sleep and Stay Asleep &#8211; Colleen Ehrnstrom, Alisha L. Brosse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fight back against a modern culture that is rewiring our brains and damaging our health with this practical, doctor-approved plan for healing that includes a ten-day boot camp and forty delicious recipes. Contemporary life provides us with infinite opportunities, along with endless temptations. We can eat whatever we want, whenever we want. We can immerse [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fight back against a modern culture that is rewiring our brains and damaging our health with this practical, doctor-approved plan for healing that includes a ten-day boot camp and forty delicious recipes.<br />
                    Contemporary life provides us with infinite opportunities, along with endless temptations. We can eat whatever we want, whenever we want. We can immerse ourselves in the vast, enticing world of digital media. We can buy goods and services for rapid delivery with our fingertips or voice commands. But living in this 24/7 hyper-reality poses serious risks to our physical and mental states, our connections to others, and even to the world at large.<br />
                    Brain Wash builds from a simple premise: Our brains are being gravely manipulated, resulting in behaviors that leave us more lonely, anxious, depressed, distrustful, illness-prone, and overweight than ever before.<br />
                    Based on the latest science, the book identifies the mental hijacking that undermines each and every one of us, and presents the tools necessary to think more clearly, make better decisions, strengthen bonds with others, and develop healthier habits. Featuring a 10-day bootcamp program, including a meal plan and 40 delicious original recipes, Brain Wash is the key to cultivating a more purposeful and fulfilling life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brain-wash-detox-your-mind-for-clearer-thinking-deeper-relationships-and-lasting-happiness-david-perlmutter-austin-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Brain Wash : Detox Your Mind for Clearer Thinking, Deeper Relationships, and Lasting Happiness &#8211; David Perlmutter, Austin Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rise from Darkness : How to Overcome Depression through Cognitive Behavioral Therapy and Positive Psychology: Paths Out of Depression Toward Happiness &#8211; Kristian Hall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rise-from-darkness-how-to-overcome-depression-through-cognitive-behavioral-therapy-and-positive-psychology-paths-out-of-depression-toward-happiness-kristian-hall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rise-from-darkness-how-to-overcome-depression-through-cognitive-behavioral-therapy-and-positive-psychology-paths-out-of-depression-toward-happiness-kristian-hall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are many self-help books about overcoming depression. This one is special; it is not written by an academic, but by a person who overcame his own depression by following the techniques in this book. This means that people suffering from depression will find themselves being able to identify with the author and the text. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rise-from-darkness-how-to-overcome-depression-through-cognitive-behavioral-therapy-and-positive-psychology-paths-out-of-depression-toward-happiness-kristian-hall-abridged/">Rise from Darkness : How to Overcome Depression through Cognitive Behavioral Therapy and Positive Psychology: Paths Out of Depression Toward Happiness &#8211; Kristian Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many self-help books about overcoming depression. This one is special; it is not written by an academic, but by a person who overcame his own depression by following the techniques in this book. This means that people suffering from depression will find themselves being able to identify with the author and the text. This book was written by someone who really understands how you feel.Imagine being Administrator of NASA the day after John F. Kennedy promised to put a man on the moon by the end of the decade. It must have seemed overwhelming. You cannot complete such complex projects in a single go; you need to divide them into many small and achievable tasks. Then, just take on the individual tasks one at a time. You can follow the same strategy to overcome depression.Kristian Hall went through eleven years of deep depression as a teenager and student. He overcame his depression by practicing techniques from cognitive behavioral therapy and positive psychology. His personal development did not stop there &#8211; he used the same techniques to overcome life&#8217;s other challenges, and to become a thoroughly happy person.You can improve your life a lot &#8211; and your path may start with this book!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rise-from-darkness-how-to-overcome-depression-through-cognitive-behavioral-therapy-and-positive-psychology-paths-out-of-depression-toward-happiness-kristian-hall-abridged/">Rise from Darkness : How to Overcome Depression through Cognitive Behavioral Therapy and Positive Psychology: Paths Out of Depression Toward Happiness &#8211; Kristian Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SuperBetter : How a Gameful Life Can Make You Stronger, Happier, Braver and More Resilient &#8211; Jane McGonigal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/superbetter-how-a-gameful-life-can-make-you-stronger-happier-braver-and-more-resilient-jane-mcgonigal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games Strategy Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/superbetter-how-a-gameful-life-can-make-you-stronger-happier-braver-and-more-resilient-jane-mcgonigal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revolutionary new self-help book by top flight game designer Jane McGonigal. After suffering a brain injury, Jane McGonigal came up with a game to help aid her recovery and battle the ensuing depression she experienced. Half a million people have now played this game to astonishing results: depression gone in 6 weeks in some [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superbetter-how-a-gameful-life-can-make-you-stronger-happier-braver-and-more-resilient-jane-mcgonigal-abridged/">SuperBetter : How a Gameful Life Can Make You Stronger, Happier, Braver and More Resilient &#8211; Jane McGonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revolutionary new self-help book by top flight game designer Jane McGonigal.    </p>
<p>                              After suffering a brain injury, Jane McGonigal came up with a game to help aid her recovery and battle the ensuing depression she experienced. Half a million people have now played this game to astonishing results: depression gone in 6 weeks in some cases and even terminal cancer patients reporting that playing the game gives them a sense of control over their own health. The book shows readers how to use these techniques to find strength and create positivity: readers can look to their own &#8216;power-ups&#8217; which are little things they can do to feel better and tackle the hurdles in their own lives.    </p>
<p>                              This book provides simple step-by-step ideas that can be carried out in day-to-day life, helping you transform your life with a new flexible and reenergised mindset. In this book McGonigal uses her own story and those of others to expertly demonstrate how simple changes can result in dramatic life-affirming effects. And what&#8217;s more, she tells you how you yourself can lead a more &#8220;gameful&#8221; life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superbetter-how-a-gameful-life-can-make-you-stronger-happier-braver-and-more-resilient-jane-mcgonigal-abridged/">SuperBetter : How a Gameful Life Can Make You Stronger, Happier, Braver and More Resilient &#8211; Jane McGonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Upward Spiral : Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time &#8211; Alex Korb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Depression doesn&#8217;t happen all at once. It starts gradually and builds momentum over time. If you go through a difficult experience, you may stop taking care of yourself. You may stop exercising and eating healthy, which will end up making you feel even worse as time goes on. You are caught in a downward spiral, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/">The Upward Spiral : Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time &#8211; Alex Korb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Depression doesn&#8217;t happen all at once. It starts gradually and builds momentum over time. If you go through a difficult experience, you may stop taking care of yourself. You may stop exercising and eating healthy, which will end up making you feel even worse as time goes on. You are caught in a downward spiral, but you may feel too tired, too overwhelmed, and too scared to try and pull yourself back up. The good news is that just one small step can be a step in the right direction.    </p>
<p>                    In The Upward Spiral, neuroscientist Alex Korb demystifies the neurological processes in the brain that cause depression and offers effective ways to get better-one little step at a time. In the book, you&#8217;ll discover that there isn&#8217;t &#8220;one big solution&#8221; that will solve your depression. Instead, there are dozens of small, practical things you can do to alleviate your symptoms and start healing. Some are as simple as relaxing certain muscles to reduce feelings of anxiety, while others involve making small efforts toward more positive social interactions. Small steps in the right direction can have profound effects-giving you the power to literally &#8220;reshape&#8221; your brain.    </p>
<p>                    Like most people, you probably didn&#8217;t wake up one day and find yourself completely depressed. Instead, it probably happened over time, as a series of reactions to difficult situations and negative thinking. But if you are ready to reverse the trajectory of your depression and find lasting happiness, this book will show you how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upward-spiral-using-neuroscience-to-reverse-the-course-of-depression-one-small-change-at-a-time-alex-korb-abridged/">The Upward Spiral : Using Neuroscience to Reverse the Course of Depression, One Small Change at a Time &#8211; Alex Korb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oncology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases. Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eat your way to better health with this New York Times bestseller on food&#8217;s ability to help the body heal itself from cancer, dementia, and dozens of other avoidable diseases.      </p>
<p>                    Forget everything you think you know about your body and food, and discover the new science of how the body heals itself. Learn how to identify the strategies and dosages for using food to transform your resilience and health in Eat to Beat Disease.     </p>
<p>                    We have radically underestimated our body&#8217;s power to transform and restore our health. Pioneering physician scientist, Dr. William Li, empowers readers by showing them the evidence behind over 200 health-boosting foods that can starve cancer, reduce your risk of dementia, and beat dozens of avoidable diseases. Eat to Beat Disease isn&#8217;t about what foods to avoid, but rather is a life-changing guide to the hundreds of healing foods to add to your meals that support the body&#8217;s defense systems, including: PlumsCinnamonJasmine teaRed wine and beerBlack BeansSan Marzano tomatoesOlive oilPacific oystersCheeses like Jarlsberg, Camembert and cheddarSourdough bread<br />
                    The book&#8217;s plan shows you how to integrate the foods you already love into any diet or health plan to activate your body&#8217;s health defense systems-Angiogenesis, Regeneration, Microbiome, DNA Protection, and Immunity-to fight cancer, diabetes, cardiovascular, neurodegenerative autoimmune diseases, and other debilitating conditions.     </p>
<p>                    Both informative and practical, Eat to Beat Disease explains the science of healing and prevention, the strategies for using food to actively transform health, and points the science of wellbeing and disease prevention in an exhilarating new direction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eat-to-beat-disease-the-new-science-of-how-your-body-can-heal-itself-william-w-li-abridged/">Eat to Beat Disease : The New Science of How Your Body Can Heal Itself &#8211; William W Li (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent wake-up call about the future of emerging viruses and a gripping account of the doctors and scientists fighting to protect us, told through the story of the deadly 2013-2014 Ebola epidemic &#8220;Crisis in the Red Zone reads like a thriller. That the story it tells is all true [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/">Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent wake-up call about the future of emerging viruses and a gripping account of the doctors and scientists fighting to protect us, told through the story of the deadly 2013-2014 Ebola epidemic &#8220;Crisis in the Red Zone reads like a thriller. That the story it tells is all true makes it all more terrifying.&#8221;&#8211;Elizabeth Kolbert, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Sixth Extinction From the #1 bestselling author of The Hot Zone, now a National Geographic original miniseries . . . This time, Ebola started with a two-year-old child who likely had contact with a wild creature and whose entire family quickly fell ill and died. The ensuing global drama activated health professionals in North America, Europe, and Africa in a desperate race against time to contain the viral wildfire. By the end&#8211;as the virus mutated into its deadliest form, and spread farther and faster than ever before&#8211;30,000 people would be infected, and the dead would be spread across eight countries on three continents. In this taut and suspenseful medical drama, Richard Preston deeply chronicles the pandemic, in which we saw for the first time the specter of Ebola jumping continents, crossing the Atlantic, and infecting people in America. Rich in characters and conflict&#8211;physical, emotional, and ethical&#8211;Crisis in the Red Zone is an immersion in one of the great public health calamities of our time. Preston writes of doctors and nurses in the field putting their own lives on the line, of government bureaucrats and NGO administrators moving, often fitfully, to try to contain the outbreak, and of pharmaceutical companies racing to develop drugs to combat the virus. He also explores the charged ethical dilemma over who should and did receive the rare doses of an experimental treatment when they became available at the peak of the disaster. Crisis in the Red Zone makes clear that the outbreak of 2013-2014 is a harbinger of further, more severe outbreaks, and of emerging viruses heretofore unimagined&#8211;in any country, on any continent. In our ever more interconnected world, with roads and towns cut deep into the jungles of equatorial Africa, viruses both familiar and undiscovered are being unleashed into more densely populated areas than ever before. The more we discover about the virosphere, the more we realize its deadly potential. Crisis in the Red Zone is an exquisitely timely book, a stark warning of viral outbreaks to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/">Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dr. Gundry is a true trailblazer, always at the forefront of scientific knowledge. The Plant Paradox shows the world what pioneer thinking is about and is a must-read book for anyone interested in being as healthy as nature has designed them to be.&#8221; -Alejandro Junger MD, New York Times bestselling author of Clean, Clean Gut [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dr. Gundry is a true trailblazer, always at the forefront of scientific knowledge. The Plant Paradox shows the world what pioneer thinking is about and is a must-read book for anyone interested in being as healthy as nature has designed them to be.&#8221; -Alejandro Junger MD, New York Times bestselling author of Clean, Clean Gut and Clean Eats  &#8220;The Plant Paradox elegantly explains how plants defend themselves from being consumed by humans, and how eating the wrong ones at the wrong times immeasurably hurts our health. An eye-opening read.&#8221; -Mehmet Oz, MD, Professor of Surgery, New York Presbyterian/Columbia University  Most of us have heard of gluten-a protein found in wheat that causes widespread inflammation in the body. Americans spend billions of dollars on gluten-free diets in an effort to protect their health. But what if we&#8217;ve been missing the root of the problem? In The Plant Paradox, renowned cardiologist Dr. Steven Gundry reveals that gluten is just one variety of a common, and highly toxic, plant-based protein called lectin.<br />
                    Lectins are found not only in grains like wheat but also in the &#8220;gluten-free&#8221; foods most of us commonly regard as healthy, including many fruits, vegetables, nuts, beans, and conventional dairy products. These proteins, which are found in the seeds, grains, skins, rinds, and leaves of plants, are designed by nature to protect them from predators (including humans). Once ingested, they incite a kind of chemical warfare in our bodies, causing inflammatory reactions that can lead to weight gain and serious health conditions.  At his waitlist-only clinics in California, Dr. Gundry has successfully treated tens of thousands of patients suffering from autoimmune disorders, diabetes, leaky gut syndrome, heart disease, and neurodegenerative diseases with a protocol that detoxes the cells, repairs the gut, and nourishes the body. Now, in The Plant Paradox, he shares this clinically proven program with readers around the world.  The simple (and daunting) fact is, lectins are everywhere. Thankfully, Dr. Gundry offers simple hacks we easily can employ to avoid them, including: * Peel your veggies.<br />
                    Most of the lectins are contained in the skin and seeds of plants; simply peeling and de-seeding vegetables (like tomatoes and peppers) reduces their lectin content.* Shop for fruit in season. Fruit contain fewer lectins when ripe, so eating apples, berries, and other lectin-containing fruits at the peak of ripeness helps minimize your lectin consumption.* Swap your brown rice for white. Whole grains and seeds with hard outer coatings are designed by nature to cause digestive distress-and are full of lectins. With a full list of lectin-containing foods and simple substitutes for each, a step-by-step detox and eating plan, and delicious lectin-free recipes, The Plant Paradox illuminates the hidden dangers lurking in your salad bowl-and shows you how to eat whole foods in a whole new way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller &#8220;A valuable read that will help you understand what it takes to stop COVID-19. &#8230; A super interesting look at the science of immunity.&#8221; -Bill Gates, Gates Notes Summer Reading List The Pulitzer Prize-winning New York Times journalist &#8220;explicates for the lay reader the intricate biology of our immune system&#8221; (Jerome Groopman, MD, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/">Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable read that will help you understand what it takes to stop COVID-19. &#8230; A super interesting look at the science of immunity.&#8221; -Bill Gates, Gates Notes Summer Reading List    </p>
<p>                    The Pulitzer Prize-winning New York Times journalist &#8220;explicates for the lay reader the intricate biology of our immune system&#8221; (Jerome Groopman, MD, New York Review of Books)    </p>
<p>                    From New York Times science journalist Matt Richtel, An Elegant Defense is an acclaimed and definitive exploration of the immune system and the secrets of health. Interweaving cutting-edge science with the intimate stories of four individual patients, this epic, first-of-its-kind book &#8220;give[s] lay readers a means of understanding what&#8217;s known so far about the intricate biology of our immune systems&#8221; (The Week).    </p>
<p>                    The immune system is our body&#8217;s essential defense network, a guardian vigilantly fighting illness, healing wounds, maintaining order and balance, and keeping us alive. It has been honed by evolution over millennia to face an almost infinite array of threats. For all its astonishing complexity, however, the immune system can be easily compromised by fatigue, stress, toxins, advanced age, and poor nutrition-hallmarks of modern life-and even by excessive hygiene. Paradoxically, it is a fragile wonder weapon that can turn on our own bodies with startling results, leading today to epidemic levels of autoimmune disorders.    </p>
<p>                    An Elegant Defense effortlessly guides readers on a scientific detective tale winding from the Black Plague to twentieth-century breakthroughs in vaccination and antibiotics, to today&#8217;s laboratories that are revolutionizing immunology-perhaps the most extraordinary and consequential medical story of our time. Drawing on extensive new interviews with dozens of world-renowned scientists, Richtel has produced a landmark book, equally an investigation into the deepest riddles of survival and a profoundly human tale that is movingly brought to life through the eyes of his four main characters, each of whom illuminates an essential facet of our &#8220;elegant defense.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elegant-defense-an-the-extraordinary-new-science-of-the-immune-system-a-tale-in-four-lives-matt-richtel-abridged/">Elegant Defense, An : The Extraordinary New Science of the Immune System: A Tale in Four Lives &#8211; Matt Richtel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book. Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book.     </p>
<p>                    Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. Why suffer from disease and ill health when the right food is proven to keep you healthy, and without the side effects of drugs? We can avoid heart disease, cancer and our other biggest killers if we use food as medicine, and the How Not To Die Cookbook offers a sustainable and delicious guide to preparing and eating the foods that will prevent and reverse fatal diseases.    </p>
<p>                    Featuring over 100 easy-to-follow, beautifully photographed plant-based recipes, with plenty of recipes suitable for vegetarians and vegans, the How Not To Die Cookbook merges cutting-edge science with everyday ingredients from the supermarket to help you and your family eat your way to better health and a longer life.    </p>
<p>                    All recipes in this cookbook have been fully anglicized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm : The One Stop Guide: Practical Advice for Anybody Affected by Self-Harm &#8211; Allan House (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Self-harm is increasingly prevalent in our society. But few of us understand why, or know what to do to help ourselves, friends or family in such situations. It can be very isolating. Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm aims to fill this gap, providing practical information and advice for anyone who has an experience of self-harm. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/">Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm : The One Stop Guide: Practical Advice for Anybody Affected by Self-Harm &#8211; Allan House (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Self-harm is increasingly prevalent in our society. But few of us understand why, or know what to do to help ourselves, friends or family in such situations. It can be very isolating.    </p>
<p>                    Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm aims to fill this gap, providing practical information and advice for anyone who has an experience of self-harm.    </p>
<p>                    Showing the various forms self-harm can take, this book explores the reasons behind it, and offers advice on self-management, support to others, and what services are available. Full of clear, thoughtful advice for those who may be thinking of harming themselves, or have already done so, as well as guidance for families and friends on helpful strategies and responses &#8211; and ones to avoid &#8211; it uses evidence from research and direct experience to provide an essential resource.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/understanding-and-responding-to-self-harm-the-one-stop-guide-practical-advice-for-anybody-affected-by-self-harm-allan-house-abridged/">Understanding and Responding to Self-Harm : The One Stop Guide: Practical Advice for Anybody Affected by Self-Harm &#8211; Allan House (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep & Dreams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all. Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all.    </p>
<p>                    Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising solutions for insomnia and other sleep disturbances, empowering readers to stop taking sleeping pills and enjoy the best sleep of their lives.    </p>
<p>                    Written in a clear and entertaining way, The Sleep Solution contains tips, tricks, exercises, and illustrations throughout. Dr Winter is an international expert on sleep and has helped thousands of patients &#8211; including professional athletes &#8211; rest better at night. Now, he&#8217;s ready to help you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lost Connections : Why You&#8217;re Depressed and How to Find Hope &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Care Of The Mentally Ill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* Pre-order Johann Hari&#8217;s new book Stolen Focus now! * THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8216;A book that could actually make us happy&#8217; SIMON AMSTELL &#8216;This amazing book will change your life&#8217; ELTON JOHN &#8216;One of the most important texts of recent years&#8217; BRITISH JOURNAL OF GENERAL PRACTICE &#8216;Brilliant, stimulating, radical&#8217; MATT HAIG &#8216;The more people read [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/">Lost Connections : Why You&#8217;re Depressed and How to Find Hope &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* Pre-order Johann Hari&#8217;s new book Stolen Focus now! *    </p>
<p>                    THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book that could actually make us happy&#8217; SIMON AMSTELL<br />
                    &#8216;This amazing book will change your life&#8217; ELTON JOHN<br />
                    &#8216;One of the most important texts of recent years&#8217; BRITISH JOURNAL OF GENERAL PRACTICE<br />
                     &#8216;Brilliant, stimulating, radical&#8217; MATT HAIG<br />
                    &#8216;The more people read this book, the better off the world will be&#8217; NAOMI KLEIN<br />
                     &#8216;Wonderful&#8217; HILLARY CLINTON<br />
                    &#8216;Eye-opening&#8217; GUARDIAN<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant for anyone wanting a better understanding of mental health&#8217; ZOE BALL<br />
                     &#8216;A game-changer&#8217; DAVINA MCCALL<br />
                     &#8216;Extraordinary&#8217; DR MAX PEMBERTON<br />
                    &#8216;Beautiful&#8217; RUSSELL BRAND    </p>
<p>                    Depression and anxiety are now at epidemic levels. Why? Across the world, scientists have uncovered evidence for nine different causes. Some are in our biology, but most are in the way we are living today.    </p>
<p>                     Lost Connections offers a radical new way of thinking about this crisis. It shows that once we understand the real causes, we can begin to turn to pioneering new solutions &#8211; ones that offer real hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/">Lost Connections : Why You&#8217;re Depressed and How to Find Hope &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wheat Belly : Lose the Wheat, Lose the Weight, and Find Your Path Back to Health &#8211; William Davis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Endocrinology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every day, over 200 million Americans consume food products made of wheat. As a result, over 100 million of them experience some form of adverse health effect, ranging from minor rashes and high blood sugar to the unattractive stomach bulges that preventive cardiologist William Davis calls &#8220;wheat bellies.&#8221; According to Davis, that excess fat has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/">Wheat Belly : Lose the Wheat, Lose the Weight, and Find Your Path Back to Health &#8211; William Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every day, over 200 million Americans consume food products made of wheat. As a result, over 100 million of them experience some form of adverse health effect, ranging from minor rashes and high blood sugar to the unattractive stomach bulges that preventive cardiologist William Davis calls &#8220;wheat bellies.&#8221; According to Davis, that excess fat has nothing to do with gluttony, sloth, or too much butter: It&#8217;s due to the whole grain wraps we eat for lunch. After witnessing over 2,000 patients regain their health after giving up wheat, Davis reached the disturbing conclusion that wheat is the single largest contributor to the nationwide obesity epidemic &#8211; and its elimination is key to dramatic weight loss and optimal health. In &#8220;Wheat Belly&#8221;, Davis exposes the harmful effects of what is actually a product of genetic tinkering and agribusiness being sold to the public as &#8220;wheat&#8221; &#8211; and provides readers with a user-friendly, step-by-step plan to navigate a new, wheat-free lifestyle.<br />
                    Informed by cutting-edge science and nutrition, along with case studies from men and women who have experienced life-changing transformations in their health after waving goodbye to wheat, &#8220;Wheat Belly&#8221; is an illuminating look at what is truly making people sick and an action plan to clear our plates of this seemingly benign ingredient.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wheat-belly-lose-the-wheat-lose-the-weight-and-find-your-path-back-to-health-william-davis-abridged/">Wheat Belly : Lose the Wheat, Lose the Weight, and Find Your Path Back to Health &#8211; William Davis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Stroke of Insight &#8211; Jill Bolte Taylor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-stroke-of-insight-jill-bolte-taylor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-stroke-of-insight-jill-bolte-taylor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The astonishing international bestseller that chronicles how a brain scientist&#8217;s own stroke led to enlightenment. On the morning of the 10th December 1996, Jill Bolte Taylor, a thirty-seven-year-old Harvard-trained brain scientist experienced a massive stroke when a blood vessel exploded in the left side of her brain. A neuroanatomist by profession, she observed her own [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-stroke-of-insight-jill-bolte-taylor-abridged/">My Stroke of Insight &#8211; Jill Bolte Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The astonishing international bestseller that chronicles how a brain scientist&#8217;s own stroke led to enlightenment.    </p>
<p>                    On the morning of the 10th December 1996, Jill Bolte Taylor, a thirty-seven-year-old Harvard-trained brain scientist experienced a massive stroke when a blood vessel exploded in the left side of her brain.      </p>
<p>                    A neuroanatomist by profession, she observed her own mind completely deteriorate to the point that she lost the ability to walk, talk, read, write, or recall any of her life, all within the space of four hours. As the damaged left side of her brain &#8211; the rational, logical, detail and time-oriented side &#8211; swung in an out of function, Taylor alternated between two distinct and opposite realities: the euphoric Nirvana of the intuitive and emotional right brain, in which she felt a sense of complete well-being and peace; and the logical left brain, that realized Jill was having a stroke and enabled her to seek help before she was lost completely.     </p>
<p>                    In My Stroke of Insight: A Brain Scientist&#8217;s Personal Journey, Taylor brings to light a new perspective on the brain and its capacity for recovery that she gained through the intimate experience of awakening her own injured mind. The journey to recovery took eight years for Jill to feel completely healed. Using her knowledge of how the brain works, her respect for the cells composing her human form, and an amazing mother, Taylor completely repaired her mind and recalibrated her understanding of the world according to the insight gained from her right brain that December morning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-stroke-of-insight-jill-bolte-taylor-abridged/">My Stroke of Insight &#8211; Jill Bolte Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paediatric Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;courageous, compassionate, and rigorous every-person&#8217;s guide&#8221; (Christina Bethell, PhD, Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health) that shows the link between Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs) and diseases, and how to cope and heal from these emotional traumas. Your biography becomes your biology. The emotional trauma we suffer as children not only shapes our emotional [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/">Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;courageous, compassionate, and rigorous every-person&#8217;s guide&#8221; (Christina Bethell, PhD, Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health) that shows the link between Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs)  and diseases, and how to cope and heal from these emotional traumas.    </p>
<p>                    Your biography becomes your biology. The emotional trauma we suffer as children not only shapes our emotional lives as adults, but it also affects our physical health, longevity, and overall well-being. Scientists now know on a bio-chemical level exactly how parents&#8217; chronic fights, divorce, death in the family, being bullied or hazed, and growing up with a hypercritical, alcoholic, or mentally ill parent can leave permanent, physical &#8220;fingerprints&#8221; on our brains.    </p>
<p>                    When children encounter sudden or chronic adversity, stress hormones cause powerful changes in the body, altering the body&#8217;s chemistry. The developing immune system and brain react to this chemical barrage by permanently resetting children&#8217;s stress response to &#8220;high,&#8221; which in turn can have a devastating impact on their mental and physical health as they grow up.    </p>
<p>                    Donna Jackson Nakazawa shares stories from people who have recognized and overcome their adverse experiences, shows why some children are more immune to stress than others, and explains why women are at particular risk. &#8220;Groundbreaking&#8221; (Tara Brach, PhD, author of Radical Acceptance) in its research, inspiring in its clarity, Childhood Disrupted explains how you can reset your biology-and help your loved ones find ways to heal. &#8220;A truly important gift of understanding-illuminates the heartbreaking costs of childhood trauma and like good medicine offers the promising science of healing and prevention&#8221; (Jack Kornfield, author of A Path With Heart).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/">Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax    </p>
<p>                    Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world has become a word-of-mouth bestseller and global phenomenon. It reveals a set of simple yet powerful practices that you can incorporate into daily life to break the cycle of anxiety, stress unhappiness and exhaustion. It promotes the kind of happiness that gets into your bones and allows you to meet the worst that life throws at you with new courage.     </p>
<p>                    Mindfulness is based on mindfulness-based cognitive therapy (MBCT). Co-developed by Professor Mark Williams of Oxford University, MBCT is recommended by the UK&#8217;s National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and is as effective as drugs for preventing depression. But, equally, it works for the rest of us who aren&#8217;t depressed but who are struggling to keep up with the relentless demands of the modern world.     </p>
<p>                    By investing just a few minutes each day, this classic guide to mindfulness will put you back in control of your life once again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grain Brain : The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar&#8211;Your Brain&#8217;s Silent Killers &#8211; David Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Allergies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The devastating truth about the effects of wheat, sugar, and carbs on the brain, with a 4-week plan to achieve optimum health. In Grain Brain, renowned neurologist David Perlmutter, MD, exposes a finding that&#8217;s been buried in the medical literature for far too long: carbs are destroying your brain. Even so-called healthy carbs like whole [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Grain Brain : The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar&#8211;Your Brain&#8217;s Silent Killers &#8211; David Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The devastating truth about the effects of wheat, sugar, and carbs on the brain, with a 4-week plan to achieve optimum health.     </p>
<p>                     In Grain Brain, renowned neurologist David Perlmutter, MD, exposes a finding that&#8217;s been buried in the medical literature for far too long: carbs are destroying your brain. Even so-called healthy carbs like whole grains can cause dementia, ADHD, epilepsy, anxiety, chronic headaches, depression, decreased libido, and much more.     </p>
<p>                     Groundbreaking and timely, Grain Brain shows that the fate of your brain is not in your genes. It&#8217;s in the food you eat. The cornerstone of all degenerative conditions, including brain disorders, is inflammation, which can be triggered by carbs, especially containing gluten or high in sugar. Dr. Perlmutter explains what happens when the brain encounters common ingredients in your daily bread and fruit bowls, how statin drugs may be erasing your memory, why a diet high in good fats is ideal, and how to spur the growth of new brain cells at any age.     </p>
<p>                     Dr. Perlmutter&#8217;s revolutionary 4-week plan shows you how to keep your brain healthy, vibrant, and sharp while dramatically reducing your risk for debilitating neurological diseases as well as relieving more common, everyday conditions &#8212; without drugs. Easy-to-follow strategies, delicious recipes, and weekly goals help you to put the plan into action. With a blend of anecdotes, cutting-edge research, and accessible, practical advice, Grain Brain teaches you how to take control of your smart genes, regain wellness, and enjoy lifelong health and vitality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/grain-brain-the-surprising-truth-about-wheat-carbs-and-sugar-your-brains-silent-killers-david-perlmutter-with-kristin-loberg-abridged/">Grain Brain : The Surprising Truth about Wheat, Carbs, and Sugar&#8211;Your Brain&#8217;s Silent Killers &#8211; David Perlmutter, With Kristin Loberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Notes on a Nervous Planet &#8211; Matt Haig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Order THE COMFORT BOOK. Available now! THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The world is messing with our minds. What if there was something we could do about it? Looking at sleep, news, social media, addiction, work and play, Matt Haig invites us to feel calmer, happier and to question the habits of the digital [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/">Notes on a Nervous Planet &#8211; Matt Haig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Order THE COMFORT BOOK. Available now!    </p>
<p>                    THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The world is messing with our minds. What if there was something we could do about it?    </p>
<p>                    Looking at sleep, news, social media, addiction, work and play, Matt Haig invites us to feel calmer, happier and to question the habits of the digital age. This book might even change the way you spend your precious time on earth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notes-on-a-nervous-planet-matt-haig-abridged/">Notes on a Nervous Planet &#8211; Matt Haig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diabetes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FROM NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR DR. JASON FUNG * &#8220;The doctor who invented intermittent fasting.&#8221;-The Daily Mail &#8220;Dr. Fung reveals how [type 2 diabetes] can be prevented and also reversed using natural dietary methods instead of medications &#8230; This is an important and timely book. Highly recommended.&#8221;-Dr. Mark Hyman, author of The Pegan Diet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FROM NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR DR. JASON FUNG * &#8220;The doctor who invented intermittent fasting.&#8221;-The Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Fung reveals how [type 2 diabetes] can be prevented and also reversed using natural dietary methods instead of medications &#8230; This is an important and timely book. Highly recommended.&#8221;-Dr. Mark Hyman, author of The Pegan Diet    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Jason Fung has done it again. &#8230; Get this book!&#8221;-Dr. Steven R. Gundry, author of The Plant Paradox    </p>
<p>                    Everything you believe about treating type 2 diabetes is wrong. Today, most doctors, dietitians, and even diabetes specialists consider type 2 diabetes to be a chronic and progressive disease-a life sentence with no possibility of parole. But the truth, as Dr. Fung reveals in this groundbreaking book, is that type 2 diabetes is reversible.     </p>
<p>                    Writing with clear, persuasive language, Dr. Fung explains why conventional treatments that rely on insulin or other blood-glucose-lowering drugs can actually exacerbate the problem, leading to significant weight gain and even heart disease. The only way to treat type 2 diabetes effectively, he argues, is proper dieting and intermittent fasting-not medication.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Diabetes Code is unabashedly provocative yet practical &#8230; a clear blueprint for everyone to take control of their blood sugar, their health, and their lives.&#8221;- Dr. Will Cole, author of Intuitive Fasting</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Critical Thinking : How to Effectively Reason, Understand Irrationality, and Make Better Decisions &#8211; Stuart Vyse</title>
		<link>/critical-thinking-how-to-effectively-reason-understand-irrationality-and-make-better-decisions-stuart-vyse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/critical-thinking-how-to-effectively-reason-understand-irrationality-and-make-better-decisions-stuart-vyse/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This wide-ranging course reveals the method to our madness in everything from finances to Friday the 13th. An expert on irrational behavior, Professor Vyse discusses what it means to be rational before delving into the many reasoning errors and psychological challenges that lead us astray. In fifteen lectures, he will teach you to identify the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/critical-thinking-how-to-effectively-reason-understand-irrationality-and-make-better-decisions-stuart-vyse/">Critical Thinking : How to Effectively Reason, Understand Irrationality, and Make Better Decisions &#8211; Stuart Vyse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This wide-ranging course reveals the method to our madness in everything from finances to Friday the 13th. An expert on irrational behavior, Professor Vyse discusses what it means to be rational before delving into the many reasoning errors and psychological challenges that lead us astray. In fifteen lectures, he will teach you to identify the logical fallacies and quirks of our psychology that tempt us to make unwise decisions. While the course is based in theory, it&#8217;s also teeming with practical advice. You&#8217;ll examine several popular conspiracy theories before exploring the remarkable staying power of common &#8220;bad luck&#8221; superstitions: How did these superstitions come to be? Is it always bad to be irrational? At what point do our beliefs veer into the territory of wishful thinking or willful ignorance? Packed with fun examples and everyday pointers, this course will leave you thinking long and hard about how you think. With Professor Vyse&#8217;s guidance, you&#8217;ll learn to better understand your beliefs and make better decisions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/critical-thinking-how-to-effectively-reason-understand-irrationality-and-make-better-decisions-stuart-vyse/">Critical Thinking : How to Effectively Reason, Understand Irrationality, and Make Better Decisions &#8211; Stuart Vyse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
