<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Road Vehicle Manufacturing Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/road-vehicle-manufacturing-industry/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/road-vehicle-manufacturing-industry/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Road Vehicle Manufacturing Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/road-vehicle-manufacturing-industry/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Great Race : The Global Quest for the Car of the Future &#8211; Levi Tillemann (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-race-the-global-quest-for-the-car-of-the-future-levi-tillemann-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automotive Technology & Trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motor Cars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road & Motor Vehicles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road Vehicle Manufacturing Industry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-race-the-global-quest-for-the-car-of-the-future-levi-tillemann-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Great Race recounts the exciting story of a century-long battle among automakers for market share, profit, and technological dominance&#8211;and the thrilling race to build the car of the future. The world&#8217;s great manufacturing juggernaut&#8211;the $3 trillion automotive industry&#8211;is in the throes of a revolution. Its future will include cars Henry Ford and Karl Benz [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-race-the-global-quest-for-the-car-of-the-future-levi-tillemann-abridged/">The Great Race : The Global Quest for the Car of the Future &#8211; Levi Tillemann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Great Race recounts the exciting story of a century-long battle among automakers for market share, profit, and technological dominance&#8211;and the thrilling race to build the car of the future.     </p>
<p>                    The world&#8217;s great manufacturing juggernaut&#8211;the $3 trillion automotive industry&#8211;is in the throes of a revolution. Its future will include cars Henry Ford and Karl Benz could scarcely imagine. They will drive themselves, won&#8217;t consume oil, and will come in radical shapes and sizes. But the path to that future is fraught. The top contenders are two traditional manufacturing giants, the US and Japan, and a newcomer, China.     </p>
<p>                    Team America has a powerful and little-known weapon in its arsenal: a small group of technology buffs and regulators from California. The story of why and how these men and women could shape the future&#8211;how you move, how you work, how you live on Earth&#8211;is an unexpected tale filled with unforgettable characters: a scorned chemistry professor, a South African visionary who went for broke, an ambitious Chinese ex-pat, a quixotic Japanese nuclear engineer, and a string of billion-dollar wagers by governments and corporations.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;To explain the scramble for the next-generation auto&#8211;and the roles played in that race by governments, auto makers, venture capitalists, environmentalists, and private inventors&#8211;comes Levi Tillemann&#8217;s The Great Race&#8230;Mr. Tillemann seems ideally cast to guide us through the big ideas percolating in the world&#8217;s far-flung workshops and labs&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). His account is incisive and riveting, explaining how America bounced back in this global contest and what it will take to command the industrial future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-race-the-global-quest-for-the-car-of-the-future-levi-tillemann-abridged/">The Great Race : The Global Quest for the Car of the Future &#8211; Levi Tillemann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automotive Technology & Trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road Vehicle Manufacturing Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transport Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An automotive and tech world insider investigates the quest to develop and perfect the driverless car&#8211;an innovation that promises to be the most disruptive change to our way of life since the smartphone We stand on the brink of a technological revolution. Soon, few of us will own our own automobiles and instead will get [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/">Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An automotive and tech world insider investigates the quest to develop and perfect the driverless car&#8211;an innovation that promises to be the most disruptive change to our way of life since the smartphone    </p>
<p>                    We stand on the brink of a technological revolution. Soon, few of us will own our own automobiles and instead will get around in driverless electric vehicles that we summon with the touch of an app. We will be liberated from driving, prevent over 90% of car crashes, provide freedom of mobility to the elderly and disabled, and decrease our dependence on fossil fuels.     </p>
<p>                    Autonomy is the story of the maverick engineers and computer nerds who are creating the revolution. Longtime advisor to the Google Self-Driving Car team and former GM research and development chief Lawrence D. Burns provides the perfectly-timed history of how we arrived at this point, in a character-driven and heavily reported account of the unlikely thinkers who accomplished what billion-dollar automakers never dared.    </p>
<p>                    Beginning with the way 9/11 spurred the U.S. government to set a million-dollar prize for a series of off-road robot races in the Mojave Desert up to the early 2016 stampede to develop driverless technology, Autonomy is a page-turner that represents a chronicle of the past, diagnosis of the present, and prediction of the future&#8211;the ultimate guide to understanding the driverless car and navigating the revolution it sparks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/">Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
