<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Christian Theology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/christian-theology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/christian-theology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Christian Theology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/christian-theology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Origin of Satan : How Christians Demonized Jews, Pagans, and Heretics &#8211; Elaine Pagels</title>
		<link>/the-origin-of-satan-how-christians-demonized-jews-pagans-and-heretics-elaine-pagels/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Institutions & Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-origin-of-satan-how-christians-demonized-jews-pagans-and-heretics-elaine-pagels/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the religious historian whose The Gnostic Gospels won both the National Book Award and the National Book Critics Circle Award comes a dramatic interpretation of Satan and his role on the Christian tradition. With magisterial learning and the elan of a born storyteller, Pagels turns Satan&#8217;s story into an audacious exploration of Christianity&#8217;s shadow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-origin-of-satan-how-christians-demonized-jews-pagans-and-heretics-elaine-pagels/">The Origin of Satan : How Christians Demonized Jews, Pagans, and Heretics &#8211; Elaine Pagels</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the religious historian whose The Gnostic Gospels won both the National Book Award and the National Book Critics Circle Award comes a dramatic interpretation of Satan and his role on the Christian tradition. With magisterial learning and the elan of a born storyteller, Pagels turns Satan&#8217;s story into an audacious exploration of Christianity&#8217;s shadow side, in which the gospel of love gives way to irrational hatreds that continue to haunt Christians and non-Christians alike.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-origin-of-satan-how-christians-demonized-jews-pagans-and-heretics-elaine-pagels/">The Origin of Satan : How Christians Demonized Jews, Pagans, and Heretics &#8211; Elaine Pagels</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unmasking The Devil &#8211; John Ramirez</title>
		<link>/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Satanist-Turned-Evangelist Gives You the Inside Strategy to Defeat the Devil&#8217;s Plans! Many people, even Christians, deny the devil&#8217;s power. John Ramirez doesn&#8217;t have that luxury&#8211;he experienced the prince of darkness up close and personal. In the impoverished streets of the South Bronx, John Ramirez found &#8220;acceptance&#8221; from a family of witches and warlocks. These practitioners [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/">Unmasking The Devil &#8211; John Ramirez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Satanist-Turned-Evangelist Gives You the Inside Strategy to Defeat the Devil&#8217;s Plans!</p>
<p>                     Many people, even Christians, deny the devil&#8217;s power. John Ramirez doesn&#8217;t have that luxury&#8211;he experienced the prince of darkness up close and personal.</p>
<p>                     In the impoverished streets of the South Bronx, John Ramirez found &#8220;acceptance&#8221; from a family of witches and warlocks. These practitioners of dark arts trained him to be a high-ranking satanic priest&#8211;a story told in his first book, Out of the Devil&#8217;s Cauldron. However, everything changed when he met the living Christ.</p>
<p>                     In Unmasking the Devil, John Ramirez shares an insider view of how satan operates so you can avoid his traps and learn how to:<br />
                     discern between the voice of God that directs to victory and satan&#8217;s voice that leads to destruction.close the demonic doors satan uses to enter your life: entertainment, unhealthy relationships, greed, and false religion.activate the spiritual weapons of prayer, intercession, and Scripture to render hell powerless over your life.recognize how the spirits of Jezebel and Delilah attempt to infiltrate the church, create disunity, and render God&#8217;s people powerless.<br />
                     No army goes into battle without first knowing the tactics of their enemy. Receive behind-the-scene glimpses of satan&#8217;s strategies and equip yourself to live victoriously over the powers of darkness! </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Spiritual warfare is a must for every Christian if they are going to survive in the coming years,&#8221; says John Ramirez. &#8220;It&#8217;s time to stop playing patty-cake with the devil and learn how to put hell on notice.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmasking-the-devil-john-ramirez/">Unmasking The Devil &#8211; John Ramirez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus : How the Jewish Words of Jesus Can Change Your Life &#8211; Lois Tverberg</title>
		<link>/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aspects Of Religion (non-Christian)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus, Lois Tverberg challenges readers to follow their Rabbi more closely by reexamining his words in the light of their Jewish context. Doing so will provide a richer, deeper understanding of his ministry, compelling us to live differently, to become more Christ-like. We&#8217;ll begin to understand why his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/">Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus : How the Jewish Words of Jesus Can Change Your Life &#8211; Lois Tverberg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus, Lois Tverberg challenges readers to follow their Rabbi more closely by reexamining his words in the light of their Jewish context. Doing so will provide a richer, deeper understanding of his ministry, compelling us to live differently, to become more Christ-like. We&#8217;ll begin to understand why his first Jewish disciples abandoned everything to follow him, to live out his commands.    </p>
<p>                    Our modern society, with its individualism and materialism, is very different than the tight-knit, family-oriented setting Jesus lived and taught in. What wisdom can we glean from his Eastern, biblical attitude toward life? How can knowing Jesus within this context shed light on his teachings for us today?    </p>
<p>                    In Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus we&#8217;ll journey back in time to eavesdrop on the conversations that arose among the rabbis of Jesus&#8217; day, and consider how hearing Rabbi Jesus with the ears of a first-century disciple can bring new meaning to our faith. And we&#8217;ll listen to Jewish thinkers through the ages, discovering how ideas that germinated in Jesus&#8217; time have borne fruit. Doing so will yield fresh, practical insights for following our Rabbi&#8217;s teachings from a Jewish point of view.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walking-in-the-dust-of-rabbi-jesus-how-the-jewish-words-of-jesus-can-change-your-life-lois-tverberg/">Walking in the Dust of Rabbi Jesus : How the Jewish Words of Jesus Can Change Your Life &#8211; Lois Tverberg</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revelation Unveiled &#8211; Tim LaHaye</title>
		<link>/revelation-unveiled-tim-lahaye/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aspects Of Religion (non-Christian)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bible Readings, Selections & Meditations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/revelation-unveiled-tim-lahaye/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Biblical Foundation for the Best-selling Left Behind Series . . . In the twinkling of an eye, millions of people across the world vanish, resulting in highway catastrophes, plane crashes, utility breakdowns, and more. Chaos reigns. With the stage set, a dictator emerges who persecutes Christians horribly. But tribulation is about to give way [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revelation-unveiled-tim-lahaye/">Revelation Unveiled &#8211; Tim LaHaye</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Biblical Foundation for the Best-selling Left Behind Series . . . In the twinkling of an eye, millions of people across the world vanish, resulting in highway catastrophes, plane crashes, utility breakdowns, and more. Chaos reigns. With the stage set, a dictator emerges who persecutes Christians horribly. But tribulation is about to give way to incredible joy &#8212; for the return of the King of Kings is at hand. In Revelation Unveiled, Dr. Tim LaHaye, co-author with Jerry Jenkins of the best-selling novels Left Behind and Tribulation Force, reveals the scriptural foundation of this series. Revelation Unveiled explains such critical topics as: &#8211; The rapture of the church &#8211; The Return of Christ &#8211; The Great Tribulation &#8211; The Final Battle against Satan and His Hosts &#8211; The Seven Seals &#8211; The Millenial Reign &#8211; The Seven Trumpets &#8211; The Seven Bowls of Wrath &#8211; The Great White Throne &#8211; The Destruction of Babylon &#8211; The New Heaven and New Earth &#8212; Previously titled Revelation Illustrated and Made Plain, this revised and updated commentary includes numerous charts. With simple and accessible language, Revelation Unveiled will help you better understand this mysterious, final book of the Bible and its implications.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revelation-unveiled-tim-lahaye/">Revelation Unveiled &#8211; Tim LaHaye</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Murder of Jesus &#8211; John F. MacArthur</title>
		<link>/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bible Studies: For Individual Or Small Group Study]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The pieces are in place. The curtain rises for the final act. God is about to die. An unprecedented conspiracy of injustice, cruelty, and religious and political interests sentenced a man guilty of no crimes to the most barbaric method of execution ever devised. The victim was no mere man. Jesus was God in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/">The Murder of Jesus &#8211; John F. MacArthur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The pieces are in place. The curtain rises for the final act. God is about to die.    </p>
<p>                    An unprecedented conspiracy of injustice, cruelty, and religious and political interests sentenced a man guilty of no crimes to the most barbaric method of execution ever devised. The victim was no mere man. Jesus was God in the flesh. The Creator of life died.    </p>
<p>                    How did such a thing come to be? Who were the onlookers, the players, the fakes, frauds, and heroes? What was it like in the Upper Room that night, in the shadows of Gethsemane, or in the Praetorium awaiting Pilate&#8217;s verdict? What is the meaning of the last words Jesus uttered as He gasped for breath on the cross? What if all the facts you now so well could come alive in your ind and heart as a living story, rather than as a 2000-year-old ancient account?    </p>
<p>                    By piecing together the narrative from the perspective of the participants, John MacArthur invites you to relive the most awesome injustice in the history of man, the unparalleled triumph of the sovereignty of God, and the passion of Christ.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-murder-of-jesus-john-f-macarthur/">The Murder of Jesus &#8211; John F. MacArthur</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The More of Less: Finding the Life you Want Under Everything you Own &#8211; Joshua Becker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-more-of-less-finding-the-life-you-want-under-everything-you-own-joshua-becker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-more-of-less-finding-the-life-you-want-under-everything-you-own-joshua-becker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Don&#8217;t Settle for More Most of us know we own too much stuff. We feel the weight and burden of our clutter, and we tire of cleaning and managing and organizing. While excess consumption leads to bigger houses, faster cars, fancier technology, and cluttered homes, it never brings happiness. Rather, it results in a desire [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-more-of-less-finding-the-life-you-want-under-everything-you-own-joshua-becker-abridged/">The More of Less: Finding the Life you Want Under Everything you Own &#8211; Joshua Becker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Don&#8217;t Settle for More    </p>
<p>                     Most of us know we own too much stuff. We feel the weight and burden of our clutter, and we tire of cleaning and managing and organizing.     </p>
<p>                     While excess consumption leads to bigger houses, faster cars, fancier technology, and cluttered homes, it never brings happiness. Rather, it results in a desire for more. It redirects our greatest passions to things that can never fulfill. And it distracts us from the very life we wish we were living.     </p>
<p>                     Live a better life with less.     </p>
<p>                     In The More of Less, Joshua Becker helps you&#8230;     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Recognize the life-giving benefits of owning less<br />
                     &#8211; Realize how all the stuff you own is keeping you from pursuing your dreams<br />
                     &#8211; Craft a personal, practical approach to decluttering your home and life<br />
                     &#8211; Experience the joys of generosity<br />
                     &#8211; Learn why the best part of minimalism isn&#8217;t a clean house, it&#8217;s a full life     </p>
<p>                     The beauty of minimalism isn&#8217;t in what it takes away. It&#8217;s in what it gives.     </p>
<p>                    Make Room in Your Life for What You Really Want     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Maybe you don&#8217;t need to own all this stuff.&#8221; After a casual conversation with his neighbor on Memorial Day 2008, Joshua Becker realized he needed a change. He was spending far too much time organizing possessions, cleaning up messes, and looking for more to buy.     </p>
<p>                    So Joshua and his wife decided to remove the nonessential possessions from their home and life. Eventually, they sold, donated, or discarded over 60 percent of what they owned. In exchange, they found a life of more freedom, more contentment, more generosity, and more opportunity to pursue the things that mattered most.     </p>
<p>                    The More of Less delivers an empowering plan for living more by owning less. With practical suggestions and encouragement to personalize your own minimalist style, Joshua Becker shows you why minimizing possessions is the best way to maximize life.     </p>
<p>                    Are you ready for less cleaning, less anxiety, and less stress in your life? Simplicity isn&#8217;t as complicated as you think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-more-of-less-finding-the-life-you-want-under-everything-you-own-joshua-becker-abridged/">The More of Less: Finding the Life you Want Under Everything you Own &#8211; Joshua Becker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Now Shall We Live? &#8211; Charles Colson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-now-shall-we-live-charles-colson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Ministry & Pastoral Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Social Thought & Activity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-now-shall-we-live-charles-colson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>2000 Gold Medallion Award winner! Christianity is more than a personal relationship with Jesus Christ. It is also a worldview that not only answers life&#8217;s basic questions&#8211;Where did we come from, and who are we? What has gone wrong with the world? What can we do to fix it?&#8211;but also shows us how we should [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-now-shall-we-live-charles-colson-abridged/">How Now Shall We Live? &#8211; Charles Colson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2000 Gold Medallion Award winner!<br />
                    Christianity is more than a personal relationship with Jesus Christ. It is also a worldview that not only answers life&#8217;s basic questions&#8211;Where did we come from, and who are we? What has gone wrong with the world? What can we do to fix it?&#8211;but also shows us how we should live as a result of those answers. How Now Shall We Live? gives Christians the understanding, the confidence, and the tools to confront the world&#8217;s bankrupt worldviews and to restore and redeem every aspect of contemporary culture: family, education, ethics, work, law, politics, science, art, music. This book will change every Christian who reads it. It will change the church in the new millennium.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-now-shall-we-live-charles-colson-abridged/">How Now Shall We Live? &#8211; Charles Colson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
