<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Classic Books &amp; Novels Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/classic-books-novels/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/classic-books-novels/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 09:08:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Classic Books &amp; Novels Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/classic-books-novels/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dune (Spanish edition) &#8211; Herbert Frank</title>
		<link>/dune-spanish-edition-herbert-frank/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dune-spanish-edition-herbert-frank/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;«No conozco nada comparable, excepto El Señor de los Anillos.» Arthur C. Clarke. En el desértico planeta Arrakis, el agua es el bien más preciado y llorar a los muertos, el símbolo de máxima prodigalidad. Pero algo hace de Arrakis una pieza estratégica para los intereses del emperador, las Grandes Casas y la Cofradía, los [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dune-spanish-edition-herbert-frank/">Dune (Spanish edition) &#8211; Herbert Frank</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;«No conozco nada comparable, excepto El Señor de los Anillos.» Arthur C. Clarke. En el desértico planeta Arrakis, el agua es el bien más preciado y llorar a los muertos, el símbolo de máxima prodigalidad. Pero algo hace de Arrakis una pieza estratégica para los intereses del emperador, las Grandes Casas y la Cofradía, los tres grandes poderes de la galaxia. Arrakis es el único origen conocido de la melange, preciosa especia y uno de los bienes más codiciados del universo. Al duque Leto Atreides se le asigna el gobierno de este mundo inhóspito, habitado por los indómitos Fremen y por monstruosos gusanos de arena de centenares de metros de longitud. Sin embargo, cuando la familia es traicionada, su hijo y heredero,  Paul, emprenderá un viaje hacia un destino más grande del que jamás hubiese podido soñar. Mezcla fascinante de aventura, misticismo, intrigas políticas y ecologismo, Dune se convirtió, desde el momento de su publicación, en un fenómeno de culto y en la mayor epopeya de ciencia ficción de todos los tiempos.&#8221;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dune-spanish-edition-herbert-frank/">Dune (Spanish edition) &#8211; Herbert Frank</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Dubious Battle &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/in-dubious-battle-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-dubious-battle-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Both a fast-paced story of social unrest and strike, and the tale of one young man&#8217;s struggle for identity, IN DUBIOUS BATTLE is a novel about the apocalyptic violence that breaks out when the masses become the mob. Set in California apple country, a strike by migrant workers spirals out of control, as principled defiance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-dubious-battle-mr-john-steinbeck/">In Dubious Battle &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Both a fast-paced story of social unrest and strike, and the tale of one young man&#8217;s struggle for identity, IN DUBIOUS BATTLE is a novel about the apocalyptic violence that breaks out when the masses become the mob. Set in California apple country, a strike by migrant workers spirals out of control, as principled defiance turns into blind fanaticism. Caught in this upheaval is Jim Nolan, a once aimless man who finds himself briefly becoming the leader of the strike before being crushed in its service. IN DUBIOUS BATTLE explores and dramatises many of the ideas and themes key to Steinbeck&#8217;s writing.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-dubious-battle-mr-john-steinbeck/">In Dubious Battle &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>East of Eden &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/east-of-eden-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sci Fi Books for Kids]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/east-of-eden-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There is only one book to a man,&#8217; Steinbeck wrote of East of Eden, his most ambitious novel. Set in the rich farmland of the Salinas Valley, California, this powerful, often brutal novel, follows the intertwined destinies of two families &#8211; the Trasks and the Hamiltons &#8211; whose generations hopelessly re-enact the fall of Adam [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/east-of-eden-mr-john-steinbeck/">East of Eden &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is only one book to a man,&#8217; Steinbeck wrote of East of Eden, his most ambitious novel. Set in the rich farmland of the Salinas Valley, California, this powerful, often brutal novel, follows the intertwined destinies of two families &#8211; the Trasks and the Hamiltons &#8211; whose generations hopelessly re-enact the fall of Adam and Eve and the poisonous rivalry of Cain and Abel. Here Steinbeck created some of his most memorable characters and explored his most enduring themes: the mystery of identity; the inexplicability of love, and the murderous consequences of love&#8217;s absence.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/east-of-eden-mr-john-steinbeck/">East of Eden &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Girl With a Pearl Earring &#8211; Tracy Chevalier</title>
		<link>/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OVER FIVE MILLION COPIES SOLD WORLDWIDE &#8216;A phenomenon&#8217; Jessie Burton &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Truly magical&#8217; Guardian Those eyes are fixed on someone. But who? What is she thinking as she stares out from one of the world&#8217;s best-loved paintings? Johannes Vermeer can spot exceptional beauty. When servant girl Griet catches his eye, she soon becomes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/">Girl With a Pearl Earring &#8211; Tracy Chevalier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OVER FIVE MILLION COPIES SOLD WORLDWIDE</p>
<p>                                &#8216;A phenomenon&#8217; Jessie Burton</p>
<p>                                &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                                &#8216;Truly magical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                              Those eyes are fixed on someone. But who? What is she thinking as she stares out from one of the world&#8217;s best-loved paintings?</p>
<p>                              Johannes Vermeer can spot exceptional beauty. When servant girl Griet catches his eye, she soon becomes both student and muse. But then he gives her his wife&#8217;s pearl earrings to wear for a portrait, and a scandal erupts that could threaten Griet&#8217;s future&#8230;</p>
<p>                                Vivid and captivating, this timeless modern classic has become a successful film and an international bestseller, with over 5 million copies sold around the world; now with a new introduction by the author.</p>
<p>                              &#8216;A veritable work of art&#8230; one of those rare novels where all the decisions made by the author appear inevitable and right&#8217; Rose Tremain</p>
<p>                              &#8216;Timeless, delicate and as exquisitely measured as one of Vermeer&#8217;s paintings. Tense yet perfectly-paced and filled with the beauty of life&#8217;s colours, Girl with the Pearl Earring is a masterpiece in its own right. Just a phenomenon. I will hold this novel close for the rest of my life&#8217; Jessie Burton, author of The Minaturist</p>
<p>                              &#8216;If ever a novel rightly deserves its &#8220;five millions copies sold&#8221; achievement, it is this dazzling little masterpiece &#8230; Absolute magic&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                              &#8216;A portrait of radiance&#8230;Tracy Chevalier brings the real artist Vermeer and a fictional muse to life in a jewel of a novel&#8217; Time</p>
<p>                              &#8216;Chevalier doesn&#8217;t put a foot wrong in this triumphant work &#8230; It is a beautifully written tale that mirrors the elegance of the painting that inspired it&#8217; Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>                              &#8216;A wonderful novel, mysterious, steeped in atmosphere, deeply revealing about the process of painting&#8230;truly magical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                              &#8216;It is no wonder that this beautifully-written story has sold more than five million copies and been made into a successful film. An absolute triumph&#8217; Woman&#8217;s Weekly</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/">Girl With a Pearl Earring &#8211; Tracy Chevalier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Looking Glass War &#8211; John le Carre</title>
		<link>/the-looking-glass-war-john-le-carre-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-looking-glass-war-john-le-carre-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Cold War thriller from the master of spy fiction, John le Carre&#8217;s The Looking Glass War is a gripping novel of double-crosses, audacious bluffs and the ever-present threat of nuclear war, published in Penguin Modern Classics. When the Department &#8211; faded since the war and busy only with bureaucratic battles &#8211; hears rumour of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-looking-glass-war-john-le-carre-2/">The Looking Glass War &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Cold War thriller from the master of spy fiction, John le Carre&#8217;s The Looking Glass War is a gripping novel of double-crosses, audacious bluffs and the ever-present threat of nuclear war, published in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    When the Department &#8211; faded since the war and busy only with bureaucratic battles &#8211; hears rumour of a missile base near the West German border, it seems like the perfect opportunity to regain some political standing in the Intelligence market place. The Cold War is at its height and the Department is dying for a piece of the action.</p>
<p>                    Swiftly becoming carried away by fear and pride, the Department and her officers send deactivated agent Fred Leiser back into East Germany, armed only with some schoolboy training and his memories of the war. In the land of eloquent silence that is Communist East Germany, Leiser&#8217;s fate becomes inseparable from the Department&#8217;s.</p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed The Looking Glass War, you might like le Carre&#8217;s The Secret Pilgrim, also available in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A devastating and tragic record of human, not glamour, spies&#8217;<br />
                    New York Herald Tribune</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book of rare and great power&#8217;<br />
                    Financial Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-looking-glass-war-john-le-carre-2/">The Looking Glass War &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Murder of Quality &#8211; John le Carre</title>
		<link>/a-murder-of-quality-john-le-carre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-murder-of-quality-john-le-carre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stella Rode has twice disturbed the ancient cloisters of Carne School: firstly by being the wrong sort, with her doilies and china ducks, and secondly by being murdered. George Smiley, who has his own connection with the school, is asked by an old Service friend to investigate. Smiley knows that Stella feared her husband would [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-murder-of-quality-john-le-carre/">A Murder of Quality &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stella Rode has twice disturbed the ancient cloisters of Carne School: firstly by being the wrong sort, with her doilies and china ducks, and secondly by being murdered. George Smiley, who has his own connection with the school, is asked by an old Service friend to investigate. Smiley knows that Stella feared her husband would murder her, but as he probes further beneath Carne&#8217;s respectable veneer, he uncovers far more than a simple crime of passion. In his second novel, le Carre moves outside the world of espionage to   reveal the secrets at the heart of another particularly English   institution. The result is a pitch-perfect murder mystery, with George  Smiley  as master detective.    </p>
<p>                    THE SECOND GEORGE SMILEY NOVEL    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Beautifully intelligent, satiric and witty&#8217; Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-murder-of-quality-john-le-carre/">A Murder of Quality &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Call for the Dead &#8211; John le Carre</title>
		<link>/call-for-the-dead-john-le-carre-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spyware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/call-for-the-dead-john-le-carre-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first of his peerless novels of Cold War espionage and international intrigue, Call for the Dead is also the debut of John le Carre&#8217;s masterful creation George Smiley. After a routine security check by George Smiley, civil servant Samuel Fennan apparently kills himself. When Smiley finds Circus head Maston is trying to blame him [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-for-the-dead-john-le-carre-2/">Call for the Dead &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first of his peerless novels of Cold War espionage and international intrigue, Call for the Dead is also the debut of John le Carre&#8217;s masterful creation George Smiley. </p>
<p>                    After a routine security check by George Smiley, civil servant Samuel Fennan apparently kills himself. When Smiley finds Circus head Maston is trying to blame him for the man&#8217;s death, he begins his own investigation, meeting with Fennan&#8217;s widow to find out what could have led him to such desperation. But on the very day that Smiley is ordered off the enquiry he receives an urgent letter from the dead man. Do the East Germans &#8211; and their agents &#8211; know more about this man&#8217;s death than the Circus previously imagined? Le Carre&#8217;s first book, Call for the Dead, introduced the tenacious and retiring George Smiley in a gripping tale of espionage and deceit.</p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed Call for the Dead, you might like le Carre&#8217;s The Spy Who Came in from the Cold, also available in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Intelligent, thrilling, surprising &#8230; makes most cloak-and-dagger stuff taste of cardboard&#8217; Sunday Telegraph</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brilliant. Realistic. Constant suspense&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-for-the-dead-john-le-carre-2/">Call for the Dead &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fahrenheit 451 &#8211; Ray Bradbury</title>
		<link>/fahrenheit-451-ray-bradbury/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fahrenheit-451-ray-bradbury/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Guy Montag is a fireman. In his world, where television rules and literature is on the brink of extinction, firemen start fires rather than put them out. His job is to destroy the most illegal of commodities, the printed book, along with the houses in which they are hidden. Montag never questions the destruction and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fahrenheit-451-ray-bradbury/">Fahrenheit 451 &#8211; Ray Bradbury</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Guy Montag is a fireman. In his world, where television rules and literature is on the brink of extinction, firemen start fires rather than put them out. His job is to destroy the most illegal of commodities, the printed book, along with the houses in which they are hidden. Montag never questions the destruction and ruin his actions produce, returning each day to his bland life and wife, Mildred, who spends all day with her television “family.” But then he meets an eccentric young neighbor, Clarisse, who introduces him to a past where people didn’t live in fear and to a present where one sees the world through the ideas in books instead of the mindless chatter of television. When Mildred attempts suicide and Clarisse suddenly disappears, Montag begins to question everything he has ever known. He starts hiding books in his home, and when his pilfering is discovered, the fireman has to run for his life.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fahrenheit-451-ray-bradbury/">Fahrenheit 451 &#8211; Ray Bradbury</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Russia House &#8211; John le Carre</title>
		<link>/the-russia-house-john-le-carre-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-russia-house-john-le-carre-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>John le Carre&#8217;s first post-glasnost spy novel, The Russia House captures the effect of a slow and uncertain thaw on ordinary people and on the shadowy puppet-masters who command them Barley Blair is not a Service man: he is a small-time publisher, a self-destructive soul whose only loves are whisky and jazz. But it was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-russia-house-john-le-carre-2/">The Russia House &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John le Carre&#8217;s first post-glasnost spy novel, The Russia House captures the effect of a slow and uncertain thaw on ordinary people and on the shadowy puppet-masters who command them</p>
<p>                    Barley Blair is not a Service man: he is a small-time publisher, a self-destructive soul whose only loves are whisky and jazz. But it was Barley who, one drunken night at a dacha in Peredelkino during the Moscow Book Fair, was befriended by a high-ranking Soviet scientist who could be the greatest asset to the West since perestroika began, and made a promise. Nearly a year later, his drunken promise returns to haunt him. A reluctant Barley is quickly trained by British Intelligence and sent to Moscow to liaise with a go-between, the beautiful Katya. Both are lonely and disillusioned. Each is increasingly certain that if the human race is to have any future, all must betray their countries &#8230;</p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed The Russia House, you might like le Carre&#8217;s The Secret Pilgrim, also available in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Classic le Carre&#8217;<br />
                    Sunday Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-russia-house-john-le-carre-2/">The Russia House &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Call for the Dead &#8211; John le Carre</title>
		<link>/call-for-the-dead-john-le-carre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spyware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/call-for-the-dead-john-le-carre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The first of his peerless novels of Cold War espionage and international intrigue, Call for the Dead is also the debut of John le Carre&#8217;s masterful creation George Smiley. After a routine security check by George Smiley, civil servant Samuel Fennan apparently kills himself. When Smiley finds Circus head Maston is trying to blame him [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-for-the-dead-john-le-carre/">Call for the Dead &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first of his peerless novels of Cold War espionage and international intrigue, Call for the Dead is also the debut of John le Carre&#8217;s masterful creation George Smiley. </p>
<p>                    After a routine security check by George Smiley, civil servant Samuel Fennan apparently kills himself. When Smiley finds Circus head Maston is trying to blame him for the man&#8217;s death, he begins his own investigation, meeting with Fennan&#8217;s widow to find out what could have led him to such desperation. But on the very day that Smiley is ordered off the enquiry he receives an urgent letter from the dead man. Do the East Germans &#8211; and their agents &#8211; know more about this man&#8217;s death than the Circus previously imagined? Le Carre&#8217;s first book, Call for the Dead, introduced the tenacious and retiring George Smiley in a gripping tale of espionage and deceit.</p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed Call for the Dead, you might like le Carre&#8217;s The Spy Who Came in from the Cold, also available in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Intelligent, thrilling, surprising &#8230; makes most cloak-and-dagger stuff taste of cardboard&#8217; Sunday Telegraph</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brilliant. Realistic. Constant suspense&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/call-for-the-dead-john-le-carre/">Call for the Dead &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Small Town in Germany &#8211; John le Carre</title>
		<link>/a-small-town-in-germany-john-le-carre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-small-town-in-germany-john-le-carre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Brilliant, unforgettable &#8230; a masterpiece&#8217; New Statesman West Germany in the 1960s is a simmering cauldron of radical protests. Amid the turmoil Leo Harting, a Second Secretary in the British Embassy, has gone missing &#8211; along with more than forty Confidential embassy files. Alan Turner of the Foreign Office must travel to Bonn to recover [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-small-town-in-germany-john-le-carre/">A Small Town in Germany &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brilliant, unforgettable &#8230; a masterpiece&#8217; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    West  Germany in the 1960s is a simmering cauldron of radical protests. Amid  the turmoil Leo Harting, a Second Secretary in the British Embassy, has  gone missing &#8211; along with more than forty Confidential embassy files.  Alan Turner of the Foreign Office must travel to Bonn to recover them.  As he gets closer to the truth of Harting&#8217;s disappearance, he will  discover that the face of Cold War Europe &#8211; and the attentions of the  British Ministry itself &#8211; are far uglier that he could possibly have  imagined.    </p>
<p>                      Le Carre&#8217;s searing Cold War novel creates a world  where the lines between right and wrong, good and evil, are horribly  blurred.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Exciting, compulsively readable and brilliantly plotted&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    With an Introduction by Hari Kunzru    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-small-town-in-germany-john-le-carre/">A Small Town in Germany &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Looking Glass War &#8211; John le Carre</title>
		<link>/the-looking-glass-war-john-le-carre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-looking-glass-war-john-le-carre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Cold War thriller from the master of spy fiction, John le Carre&#8217;s The Looking Glass War is a gripping novel of double-crosses, audacious bluffs and the ever-present threat of nuclear war, published in Penguin Modern Classics. When the Department &#8211; faded since the war and busy only with bureaucratic battles &#8211; hears rumour of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-looking-glass-war-john-le-carre/">The Looking Glass War &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Cold War thriller from the master of spy fiction, John le Carre&#8217;s The Looking Glass War is a gripping novel of double-crosses, audacious bluffs and the ever-present threat of nuclear war, published in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    When the Department &#8211; faded since the war and busy only with bureaucratic battles &#8211; hears rumour of a missile base near the West German border, it seems like the perfect opportunity to regain some political standing in the Intelligence market place. The Cold War is at its height and the Department is dying for a piece of the action.</p>
<p>                    Swiftly becoming carried away by fear and pride, the Department and her officers send deactivated agent Fred Leiser back into East Germany, armed only with some schoolboy training and his memories of the war. In the land of eloquent silence that is Communist East Germany, Leiser&#8217;s fate becomes inseparable from the Department&#8217;s.</p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed The Looking Glass War, you might like le Carre&#8217;s The Secret Pilgrim, also available in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A devastating and tragic record of human, not glamour, spies&#8217;<br />
                    New York Herald Tribune</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book of rare and great power&#8217;<br />
                    Financial Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-looking-glass-war-john-le-carre/">The Looking Glass War &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Perfect Spy : A Novel &#8211; John Le Carré</title>
		<link>/a-perfect-spy-a-novel-john-le-carre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-perfect-spy-a-novel-john-le-carre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The best English novel since the war.&#8221; &#8212; Philip Roth Over the course of his seemingly irreproachable life, Magnus Pym has been all things to all people: a devoted family man, a trusted colleague, a loyal friend-and the perfect spy. But in the wake of his estranged father&#8217;s death, Magnus vanishes, and the British Secret [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-perfect-spy-a-novel-john-le-carre/">A Perfect Spy : A Novel &#8211; John Le Carré</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The best English novel since the war.&#8221; &#8212; Philip Roth    </p>
<p>                     Over the course of his seemingly irreproachable life, Magnus Pym has been all things to all people: a devoted family man, a trusted colleague, a loyal friend-and the perfect spy. But in the wake of his estranged father&#8217;s death, Magnus vanishes, and the British Secret Service is up in arms. Is it grief, or is the reason for his disappearance more sinister? And who is the mysterious man with the sad moustache who also seems to be looking for Magnus?    </p>
<p>                     In A Perfect Spy, John le Carre has crafted one of his crowning masterpieces, interweaving a moving and unusual coming-of-age story with a morally tangled chronicle of modern espionage.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-perfect-spy-a-novel-john-le-carre/">A Perfect Spy : A Novel &#8211; John Le Carré</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Russia House &#8211; John le Carre</title>
		<link>/the-russia-house-john-le-carre/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-russia-house-john-le-carre/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>John le Carre&#8217;s first post-glasnost spy novel, The Russia House captures the effect of a slow and uncertain thaw on ordinary people and on the shadowy puppet-masters who command them Barley Blair is not a Service man: he is a small-time publisher, a self-destructive soul whose only loves are whisky and jazz. But it was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-russia-house-john-le-carre/">The Russia House &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John le Carre&#8217;s first post-glasnost spy novel, The Russia House captures the effect of a slow and uncertain thaw on ordinary people and on the shadowy puppet-masters who command them</p>
<p>                    Barley Blair is not a Service man: he is a small-time publisher, a self-destructive soul whose only loves are whisky and jazz. But it was Barley who, one drunken night at a dacha in Peredelkino during the Moscow Book Fair, was befriended by a high-ranking Soviet scientist who could be the greatest asset to the West since perestroika began, and made a promise. Nearly a year later, his drunken promise returns to haunt him. A reluctant Barley is quickly trained by British Intelligence and sent to Moscow to liaise with a go-between, the beautiful Katya. Both are lonely and disillusioned. Each is increasingly certain that if the human race is to have any future, all must betray their countries &#8230;</p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed The Russia House, you might like le Carre&#8217;s The Secret Pilgrim, also available in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Classic le Carre&#8217;<br />
                    Sunday Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-russia-house-john-le-carre/">The Russia House &#8211; John le Carre</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cup of Gold : A Life of Sir Henry Morgan, Buccaneer, with Occasional Reference to History &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/cup-of-gold-a-life-of-sir-henry-morgan-buccaneer-with-occasional-reference-to-history-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cup-of-gold-a-life-of-sir-henry-morgan-buccaneer-with-occasional-reference-to-history-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck&#8217;s first novel and sole work of historical fiction&#8211;the violent, exciting story of the infamous pirate Henry Morgan A Penguin Classic From the mid-1650s through the 1660s, Henry Morgan, a pirate and outlaw of legendary viciousness, ruled the Spanish Main. He ravaged the coasts of Cuba and America, striking terror wherever he went. Morgan was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cup-of-gold-a-life-of-sir-henry-morgan-buccaneer-with-occasional-reference-to-history-john-steinbeck/">Cup of Gold : A Life of Sir Henry Morgan, Buccaneer, with Occasional Reference to History &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck&#8217;s first novel and sole work of historical fiction&#8211;the violent, exciting story of the infamous pirate Henry Morgan </p>
<p>                    A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    From the mid-1650s through the 1660s, Henry Morgan, a pirate and outlaw of legendary viciousness, ruled the Spanish Main. He ravaged the coasts of Cuba and America, striking terror wherever he went. Morgan was obsessive. He had two driving ambitions: to possess the beautiful woman called La Santa Roja and to conquer Panama, the &#8220;cup of gold.&#8221; Cup of Gold is a lush, lyrical swashbuckling pirate fantasy, and sure to add new dimensions to readers&#8217; perceptions of this all-American writer. This edition features an introduction by Susan F. Beegel. </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,800 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cup-of-gold-a-life-of-sir-henry-morgan-buccaneer-with-occasional-reference-to-history-john-steinbeck/">Cup of Gold : A Life of Sir Henry Morgan, Buccaneer, with Occasional Reference to History &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rama II &#8211; Arthur C. Clarke</title>
		<link>/rama-ii-arthur-c-clarke/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rama-ii-arthur-c-clarke/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This is a space trip that no reader will want to miss.&#8221;&#8211;Playboy Years ago, the enormous, enigmatic alien spacecraft called Rama sailed through our solar system as mind-boggling proof that life existed&#8211;or had existed&#8211;elsewhere in the universe. Now, at the dawn of the twenty-third century, another ship is discovered hurtling toward us. A crew of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rama-ii-arthur-c-clarke/">Rama II &#8211; Arthur C. Clarke</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This is a space trip that no reader will want to miss.&#8221;&#8211;Playboy     </p>
<p>                    Years ago, the enormous, enigmatic alien spacecraft called Rama sailed through our solar system as mind-boggling proof that life existed&#8211;or had existed&#8211;elsewhere in the universe. Now, at the dawn of the twenty-third century, another ship is discovered hurtling toward us.     </p>
<p>                    A crew of Earth&#8217;s best and brightest minds is assembled to rendezvous with the massive vessel. They are armed with everything we know about Raman technology and culture. But nothing can prepare them for what they are about to encounter on board Rama II cosmic secrets that are startling, sensational&#8211;and perhaps even deadly.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Offers one surprise after another.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A masterpiece . . . one of the year&#8217;s best hard SF epics.&#8221;&#8211;The Houston Post    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rama-ii-arthur-c-clarke/">Rama II &#8211; Arthur C. Clarke</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Red Pony &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-red-pony-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books for Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-red-pony-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A little masterpiece&#8217; New York Times Jody Tiflin is a ten-year-old boy, living on his father&#8217;s ranch. One day his father brings home a small pony. He&#8217;s Jody&#8217;s, if the boy will learn to feed, clean, stable and care for him. But Jody learns, through the colt, and through his other adventures on the ranch, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-red-pony-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Red Pony &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A little masterpiece&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    Jody Tiflin is a ten-year-old boy, living on his father&#8217;s ranch. One day his father brings home a small pony. He&#8217;s Jody&#8217;s, if the boy will learn to feed, clean, stable and care for him. But Jody learns, through the colt, and through his other adventures on the ranch, that with responsibility can come sacrifice and pain. Joy may swiftly turn to tragedy. And he also discover that the simplicities of childhood must eventually turn into the complications of adulthood.    </p>
<p>                    The Red Pony is Steinbeck&#8217;s brilliant, and sometimes brutal, celebration of adolescence, with a stunning new cover by renowned artist Bijou Karman.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-red-pony-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Red Pony &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Innocence &#8211; Edith Wharton</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-innocence-edith-wharton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-innocence-edith-wharton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Widely regarded as one of Edith Wharton&#8217;s greatest achievements, The Age of Innocence is not only subtly satirical, but also a sometimes dark and disturbing comedy of manners in its exploration of the &#8216;eternal triangle&#8217; of love. Set against the backdrop of upper-class New York society during the 1870s, the author&#8217;s combination of powerful prose [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-innocence-edith-wharton/">The Age of Innocence &#8211; Edith Wharton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Widely regarded as one of Edith Wharton&#8217;s greatest achievements, The Age of Innocence is not only subtly satirical, but also a sometimes dark and disturbing comedy of manners in its exploration of the &#8216;eternal triangle&#8217; of love.<br />
                     Set against the backdrop of upper-class New York society during the 1870s, the author&#8217;s combination of powerful prose combined with a thoroughly researched and meticulous evocation of the manners and style of the period, has delighted readers since the novel&#8217;s first publication in 1920.     </p>
<p>                    In 1921 The Age of Innocence achieved a double distinction &#8211; it won the Pulitzer Prize and it was the first time this prestigious award had been won by a woman author.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-innocence-edith-wharton/">The Age of Innocence &#8211; Edith Wharton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Animal Farm : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</title>
		<link>/animal-farm-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/animal-farm-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The perfect edition for any Orwell enthusiasts&#8217; collection, discover Orwell&#8217;s classic dystopian masterpiece beautifully reimagined by renowned street artist Shepard Fairey &#8216;All animals are equal. But some animals are more equal than others.&#8217; Mr Jones of Manor Farm is so lazy and drunken that one day he forgets to feed his livestock. The ensuing rebellion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/animal-farm-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/">Animal Farm : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The perfect edition for any Orwell enthusiasts&#8217; collection, discover Orwell&#8217;s classic dystopian masterpiece beautifully reimagined by renowned street artist Shepard Fairey</p>
<p>                     &#8216;All animals are equal. But some animals are more equal than others.&#8217;</p>
<p>                     Mr Jones of Manor Farm is so lazy and drunken that one day he forgets to feed his livestock. The ensuing rebellion under the leadership of the pigs Napoleon and Snowball leads to the animals taking over the farm. Vowing to eliminate the terrible inequities of the farmyard, the renamed Animal Farm is organised to benefit all who walk on four legs. But as time passes, the ideals of the rebellion are corrupted, then forgotten. And something new and unexpected emerges. . .</p>
<p>                     First published in 1945, Animal Farm &#8211; the history of a revolution that went wrong &#8211; is George Orwell&#8217;s brilliant satire on the corrupting influence of power.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Remains our great satire of the darker face of modern history&#8217; Malcolm Bradbury </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prophet who thought the unthinkable and spoke the unspeakable, even when it offended conventional thought&#8217; Daily Express</p>
<p>                    &#8216;As valid today as it was fifty years ago&#8217; Ralph Steadman</p>
<p>                    COMPLETE THE TRIO WITH SHEPARD FAIREY&#8217;S NEW-LOOK 1984 AND DOWN AND OUT IN PARIS AND LONDON.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/animal-farm-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/">Animal Farm : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Return of the King &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</title>
		<link>/the-return-of-the-king-j-r-r-tolkien/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-return-of-the-king-j-r-r-tolkien/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Classic hardback edition of the third volume of The Lord of the Rings, now featuring Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design. Includes special packaging and the definitive edition of the text, with fold-out maps. The Companions of the Ring have become involved in separate adventures as the quest continues. Aragorn, revealed as the hidden heir of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-return-of-the-king-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Return of the King &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Classic hardback edition of the third volume of The Lord of the Rings, now featuring Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design. Includes special packaging and the definitive edition of the text, with fold-out maps.</p>
<p>                              The Companions of the Ring have become involved in separate adventures as the quest continues. Aragorn, revealed as the hidden heir of the ancient Kings of the West, joined with the Riders of Rohan against the forces of Isengard, and took part in the desperate victory of the Hornburg. Merry and Pippin, captured by orcs, escaped into Fangorn Forest and there encountered the Ents.</p>
<p>                              Gandalf returned, miraculously, and defeated the evil wizard, Saruman. Meanwhile, Sam and Frodo progressed towards Mordor to destroy the Ring, accompanied by Smeagol &#8211; Gollum, still obsessed by his &#8216;preciouss&#8217;. After a battle with the giant spider, Shelob, Sam left his master for dead; but Frodo is still alive &#8211; in the hands of the orcs. And all the time the armies of the Dark Lord are massing.</p>
<p>                              This classic hardback features Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design, and its text has been fully restored with almost 400 corrections &#8211; with the full co-operation of Christopher Tolkien &#8211; making it the definitive version, and as close as possible to the version that J.R.R. Tolkien intended. Also included are the original red and black maps as fold-out sheets, and &#8211; for the first time &#8211; a fully revised and enlarged index.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-return-of-the-king-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Return of the King &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lord of the Flies : with an introduction by Stephen King &#8211; William Golding</title>
		<link>/lord-of-the-flies-with-an-introduction-by-stephen-king-william-golding/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books for Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books for Children]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lord-of-the-flies-with-an-introduction-by-stephen-king-william-golding/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>William Golding&#8217;s Lord of the Flies is a dystopian classic: &#8216;exciting, relevant and thought-provoking&#8217; (Stephen King). When a group of schoolboys are stranded on a desert island, what could go wrong? &#8216;One of my favorite books &#8211; I read it every couple of years.&#8217; (Suzanne Collins, author of The Hunger Games) A plane crashes on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lord-of-the-flies-with-an-introduction-by-stephen-king-william-golding/">Lord of the Flies : with an introduction by Stephen King &#8211; William Golding</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>William Golding&#8217;s Lord of the Flies is a dystopian classic: &#8216;exciting, relevant and thought-provoking&#8217; (Stephen King). When a group of schoolboys are stranded on a desert island, what could go wrong?</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of my favorite books &#8211; I read it every couple of years.&#8217; (Suzanne Collins, author of The Hunger Games)</p>
<p>                    A plane crashes on a desert island. The only survivors are a group of schoolboys. By day, they discover fantastic wildlife and dazzling beaches, learning to survive; at night, they are haunted by nightmares of a primitive beast. Orphaned by society, it isn&#8217;t long before their innocent childhood games devolve into a savage, murderous hunt &#8230; </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Stands out mightily in my memory &#8230; Such a strong statement about the human heart.&#8217; (Patricia Cornwell)</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Terrifying and haunting.&#8217; (Kingsley Amis)</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Beautifully written, tragic and provocative.&#8217; (E. M. Forster)</p>
<p>                    ONE OF THE BBC&#8217;S ICONIC &#8216;NOVELS THAT SHAPED OUR WORLD&#8217;</p>
<p>                    What readers are saying:</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Every real human being should read this &#8230; This is what we are.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s brilliant, it&#8217;s captivating, it&#8217;s thought provoking and brutal and for some, its truly terrifying.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It can be read and re-read many times, and every time something new will appear.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;There is a reason why this is studied at school &#8230; Excellent read.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is one of the few books I&#8217;ve read that I keep on my Kindle to read again.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;I revisit this every few years and it&#8217;s always fresh and impressive &#8230; One of the best books I&#8217;ve ever read.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lord-of-the-flies-with-an-introduction-by-stephen-king-william-golding/">Lord of the Flies : with an introduction by Stephen King &#8211; William Golding</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cannery Row &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/cannery-row-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cannery-row-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the BBC&#8217;s &#8216;100 Novels That Shaped Our World&#8217; &#8216;Cannery Row in Monterey in California is a poem, a stink, a grating noise, a quality of light, a tone, a habit, a nostalgia, a dream.&#8217; Meet the gamblers, whores, drunks, bums and artists of Cannery Row in Monterey, California, during the Great Depression. They [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cannery-row-mr-john-steinbeck/">Cannery Row &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the BBC&#8217;s &#8216;100 Novels That Shaped Our World&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Cannery  Row in Monterey in California is a poem, a stink, a grating noise, a  quality of light, a tone, a habit, a nostalgia, a dream.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    Meet  the gamblers, whores, drunks, bums and artists of Cannery Row in  Monterey, California, during the Great Depression. They want to throw a  party for their friend Doc, so Mack and the boys set about, in their own  inimitable way, recruiting everyone in the neighbourhood to the cause.  But along the way they can&#8217;t help but get involved in a little mischief  and misadventure. It wouldn&#8217;t be Cannery Row if it was otherwise, now  would it?    </p>
<p>                    Packed with a ramshackle joi de vivre, Cannery Row is Steinback&#8217;s high-spirited tribute to his native California.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Uninhibited, bawdy, compassionate, inquisitive, deeply intelligent&#8217;  Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cannery-row-mr-john-steinbeck/">Cannery Row &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chapterhouse: Dune &#8211; Frank Herbert</title>
		<link>/chapterhouse-dune-frank-herbert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space Opera]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chapterhouse-dune-frank-herbert/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Frank Herbert&#8217;s Final Novel in the Magnificent Dune Chronicles&#8211;the Bestselling Science Fiction Adventure of All Time The desert planet Arrakis, called Dune, has been destroyed. The remnants of the Old Empire have been consumed by the violent matriarchal cult known as the Honored Matres. Only one faction remains a viable threat to their total conquest&#8211;the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chapterhouse-dune-frank-herbert/">Chapterhouse: Dune &#8211; Frank Herbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Frank Herbert&#8217;s Final Novel in the Magnificent Dune Chronicles&#8211;the Bestselling Science Fiction Adventure of All Time     </p>
<p>                    The desert planet Arrakis, called Dune, has been destroyed. The remnants of the Old Empire have been consumed by the violent matriarchal cult known as the Honored Matres. Only one faction remains a viable threat to their total conquest&#8211;the Bene Gesserit, heirs to Dune&#8217;s power.     </p>
<p>                    Under the leadership of Mother Superior Darwi Odrade, the Bene Gesserit have colonized a green world on the planet Chapterhouse and are turning it into a desert, mile by scorched mile. And once they&#8217;ve mastered breeding sandworms, the Sisterhood will control the production of the greatest commodity in the known galaxy&#8211;the spice melange. But their true weapon remains a man who has lived countless lifetimes&#8211;a man who served under the God Emperor Paul Muad&#8217;Dib&#8230;.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chapterhouse-dune-frank-herbert/">Chapterhouse: Dune &#8211; Frank Herbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Burning Bright : A Play in Story Form &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/burning-bright-a-play-in-story-form-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/burning-bright-a-play-in-story-form-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The last of John Steinbeck&#8217;s play-novelettes and his final attempt, after 1937&#8217;s Of Mice and Men and 1942&#8217;s The Moon is Down, to create what he saw as a new, experimental literary form A Penguin Classic Four scenes, four people: the husband who yearns for a son, ignorant of his own sterility; the wife who [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/burning-bright-a-play-in-story-form-john-steinbeck/">Burning Bright : A Play in Story Form &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The last of John Steinbeck&#8217;s play-novelettes and his final attempt, after 1937&#8217;s Of Mice and Men and 1942&#8217;s The Moon is Down, to create what he saw as a new, experimental literary form A Penguin Classic Four scenes, four people: the husband who yearns for a son, ignorant of his own sterility; the wife who commits adultery to fulfill her husband&#8217;s wish; the father of the child; and the outsider whose actions will affect them all. In this turn on a medieval morality play, Nobel Prize winner John Steinbeck casts an unwavering light on these four intertwined lives, revealing in their finely drawn circumstances the universal contours of vulnerability and passion, desperation and desire. This edition features an introduction and notes for further reading by Steinbeck scholar John Ditsky. For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,800 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/burning-bright-a-play-in-story-form-john-steinbeck/">Burning Bright : A Play in Story Form &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flush &#8211; Virginia Woolf</title>
		<link>/flush-virginia-woolf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flush-virginia-woolf/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Things are not simple but complex. If he bit Mr. Browning he bit her too. Hatred is not hatred; hatred is also love.&#8217; Virginia Woolf&#8217;s delightful biography of the poet Elizabeth Barrett Browning&#8217;s spaniel, which asks what it means to be human &#8211; and to be dog. One of 46 new books in the bestselling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flush-virginia-woolf/">Flush &#8211; Virginia Woolf</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Things are not simple but complex. If he bit Mr. Browning he bit her too. Hatred is not hatred; hatred is also love.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Virginia Woolf&#8217;s delightful biography of the poet Elizabeth Barrett Browning&#8217;s spaniel, which asks what it means to be human &#8211; and to be dog.    </p>
<p>                    One of 46 new books in the bestselling Little Black Classics series, to celebrate the first ever Penguin Classic in 1946. Each book gives readers a taste of the Classics&#8217; huge range and diversity, with works from around the world and across the centuries &#8211; including fables, decadence, heartbreak, tall tales, satire, ghosts, battles and elephants.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flush-virginia-woolf/">Flush &#8211; Virginia Woolf</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave New World &#8211; Aldous Huxley</title>
		<link>/brave-new-world-aldous-huxley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-new-world-aldous-huxley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With introductions by Margaret Atwood and David Bradshaw. Far in the future, the World Controllers have created the ideal society. Through clever use of genetic engineering, brainwashing and recreational sex and drugs all its members are happy consumers. Bernard Marx seems alone harbouring an ill-defined longing to break free. A visit to one of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-world-aldous-huxley/">Brave New World &#8211; Aldous Huxley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With introductions by Margaret Atwood and David Bradshaw. Far in the future, the World Controllers have created the ideal society. Through clever use of genetic engineering, brainwashing and recreational sex and drugs all its members are happy consumers. Bernard Marx seems alone harbouring an ill-defined longing to break free. A visit to one of the few remaining Savage Reservations where the old, imperfect life still continues, may be the cure for his distress&#8230;Huxley&#8217;s ingenious fantasy of the future sheds a blazing light on the present and is considered to be his most enduring masterpiece.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-world-aldous-huxley/">Brave New World &#8211; Aldous Huxley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sweet Thursday &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/sweet-thursday-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sweet-thursday-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Monterey, on the California Coast, Sweet Thursday is what they call the day after Lousy Wednesday &#8211; one of those days that&#8217;s just bad from the start. But Sweet Thursday is sunny and clear, a day when anything can happen. Returning to the scene of Cannery Row, Steinbeck brilliantly creates its bawdy, high-spirited world [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sweet-thursday-mr-john-steinbeck/">Sweet Thursday &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Monterey, on the California Coast, Sweet Thursday is what they call the day after Lousy Wednesday &#8211; one of those days that&#8217;s just bad from the start. But Sweet Thursday is sunny and clear, a day when anything can happen. Returning to the scene of Cannery Row, Steinbeck brilliantly creates its bawdy, high-spirited world of bums, drunks and hookers, telling the story of what happened to everyone after the war. There are colourful characters old and new, all united by love, laughter and tears: Fauna, the latest madam at the Bear Flag brothel, Doc, still there for everyone else but feeling strangely sad himself, and Suzy, the new hustler in town who might just be the girl to save him.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sweet-thursday-mr-john-steinbeck/">Sweet Thursday &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rama Revealed &#8211; Arthur C. Clarke</title>
		<link>/rama-revealed-arthur-c-clarke/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rama-revealed-arthur-c-clarke/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On its mysterious voyage through interstellar space, a massive alien starship carries its human passengers to the end of a generations-long odyssey. But the great experiment designed by the Ramans has failed, and Rama III has become a battleground. Fleeing a tyrant, a band of humans ventures into the nether regions of the ship, where [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rama-revealed-arthur-c-clarke/">Rama Revealed &#8211; Arthur C. Clarke</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On its mysterious voyage through interstellar space, a massive alien starship carries its human passengers to the end of a generations-long odyssey.     </p>
<p>                    But the great experiment designed by the Ramans has failed, and Rama III has become a battleground. Fleeing a tyrant, a band of humans ventures into the nether regions of the ship, where they encounter an emerald-doomed lair ruled by the fabulously advanced octospiders.     </p>
<p>                    As the octospiders lure the humans deeper into their domain, the humans must decide whether the creatures are their allies of enemies. All the while, Rama III continues its in-explorable journey towards the node, where the climax of their voyage awaits the stunning revelation of the true identity of the beings behind this glittering trek across the cosmos.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rama-revealed-arthur-c-clarke/">Rama Revealed &#8211; Arthur C. Clarke</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>By the Pricking of My Thumbs : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</title>
		<link>/by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vintage Crime]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An old woman in a nursing home speaks of a child buried behind the fireplace&#8230; When Tommy and Tuppence visited an elderly aunt in her gothic nursing home, they thought nothing of her mistrust of the doctors; after all, Ada was a very difficult old lady. But when Mrs Lockett mentioned a poisoned mushroom stew [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/">By the Pricking of My Thumbs : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An old woman in a nursing home speaks of a child buried behind the fireplace&#8230;    </p>
<p>                              When Tommy and Tuppence visited an elderly aunt in her gothic nursing home, they thought nothing of her mistrust of the doctors; after all, Ada was a very difficult old lady.    </p>
<p>                              But when Mrs Lockett mentioned a poisoned mushroom stew and Mrs Lancaster talked about &#8216;something behind the fireplace&#8217;, Tommy and Tuppence found themselves caught up in an unexpected adventure involving possible black magic&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/by-the-pricking-of-my-thumbs-a-tommy-tuppence-mystery-agatha-christie/">By the Pricking of My Thumbs : A Tommy &#038; Tuppence Mystery &#8211; Agatha Christie</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Once There Was a War &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic &#8220;Age can never dull this kind of writing,&#8221; writes the Chicago Tribune of John Steinbeck&#8217;s dispatches from World War II, filed for the New York Herald Tribune in 1943, which vividly captured the human side of war. Writing from England in the midst of the London blitz, North Africa, and Italy, Steinbeck [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/">Once There Was a War &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Age can never dull this kind of writing,&#8221; writes the Chicago Tribune of John Steinbeck&#8217;s dispatches from World War II, filed for the New York Herald Tribune in 1943, which vividly captured the human side of war. Writing from England in the midst of the London blitz, North Africa, and Italy, Steinbeck focuses on the people as opposed to the battles, portraying everyone from the guys in the bomber crew to Bob Hope on his USO tour. He eats and drinks with soldiers behind enemy lines, talks with them, and fights beside them. First published in book form in 1958, these writings, now with a new introduction by Mark Bowden, create an unforgettable portrait of life in wartime that continues to resonate with truth and humanity.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/">Once There Was a War &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tortilla Flat &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/tortilla-flat-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tortilla-flat-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck&#8217;s first major critical and commercial success, TORTILLA FLAT is also his funniest novel. Danny is a paisano, descended from the original Spanish settlers who arrived in Monterey, California, centuries before. He values friendship abovemoney and possessions, so that when he suddently inherits two houses, Danny is quick to offer shelter to his fellow gentlemen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tortilla-flat-mr-john-steinbeck/">Tortilla Flat &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck&#8217;s first major critical and commercial success, TORTILLA FLAT is also his funniest novel. Danny is a paisano, descended from the original Spanish settlers who arrived in Monterey, California, centuries before. He values friendship abovemoney and possessions, so that when he suddently inherits two houses, Danny is quick to offer shelter to his fellow gentlemen of the road. Their love of freedom and scorn for material things draw them into daring and often hilarious adventures. Until Danny, tiring of his new reponsibilities, suddenly disappears&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tortilla-flat-mr-john-steinbeck/">Tortilla Flat &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Winter of Our Discontent &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-winter-of-our-discontent-mr-john-steinbeck-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-winter-of-our-discontent-mr-john-steinbeck-2/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethan Allen Hawley has lost the acquisitive spirit of his wealthy and enterprising forebears, a long line of proud New England sea captains and Pilgrims. Scarred by failure, Ethan works as a grocery clerk in a store his family once owned. But his wife is restless and his teenage children troubled and hungry for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-winter-of-our-discontent-mr-john-steinbeck-2/">The Winter of Our Discontent &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethan Allen Hawley has lost the acquisitive spirit of his wealthy and enterprising forebears, a long line of proud New England sea captains and Pilgrims. Scarred by failure, Ethan works as a grocery clerk in a store his family once owned. But his wife is restless and his teenage children troubled and hungry for the material comforts he cannot provide. Then a series of unusual events reignites Ethan&#8217;s ambition, and he is pitched on to a bold course, where all scruples are put aside. Steinbeck&#8217;s searing examination of the evil influences of money, immorality, greed and ambition on America drew acclaim from the Nobel Committee who hailed him as an &#8216;independent expounder of the truth&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Returns to the high standards of The Grapes of Wrath and to the social themes that made his early work &#8230; so powerful&#8217;<br />
                    Saul Bellow, author of Herzog    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-winter-of-our-discontent-mr-john-steinbeck-2/">The Winter of Our Discontent &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>1984 : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</title>
		<link>/1984-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/1984-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The perfect edition for any Orwell enthusiasts&#8217; collection, discover the classic dystopian masterpiece beautifully reimagined by renowned street artist Shepard Fairey Winston Smith works for the Ministry of Truth in London, chief city of Airstrip One. Big Brother stares out from every poster, the Thought Police uncover every act of betrayal. When Winston finds love [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/1984-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/">1984 : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The perfect edition for any Orwell enthusiasts&#8217; collection, discover the classic dystopian masterpiece beautifully reimagined by renowned street artist Shepard Fairey</p>
<p>                     Winston Smith works for the Ministry of Truth in London, chief city of Airstrip One. Big Brother stares out from every poster, the Thought Police uncover every act of betrayal. When Winston finds love with Julia, he discovers that life does not have to be dull and deadening, and awakens to new possibilities. Despite the police helicopters that hover and circle overhead, Winston and Julia begin to question the Party; they are drawn towards conspiracy. Yet Big Brother will not tolerate dissent &#8211; even in the mind. For those with original thoughts they invented Room 101. . .</p>
<p>                     First published in 1949, 1984 is George Orwell&#8217;s terrifying vision of a totalitarian future in which everything and everyone is slave to a tyrannical regime.</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Right up there among my favourite books . . . I read it again and again&#8217; Margaret Atwood</p>
<p>                     &#8216;More relevant to today than almost any other book that you can think of&#8217; Jo Brand</p>
<p>                    COMPLETE THE TRIO WITH SHEPARD FAIREY&#8217;S NEW-LOOK ANIMAL FARM AND DOWN AND OUT IN PARIS AND LONDON.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/1984-the-dystopian-classic-reimagined-with-cover-art-by-shepard-fairey-george-orwell/">1984 : The dystopian classic reimagined with cover art by Shepard Fairey &#8211; George Orwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Pearl &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-pearl-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books for Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-pearl-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE PEARL is Steinbeck&#8217;s flawless parable about wealth and the evil it can bring. When Kino, an Indian pearl-diver, finds &#8216;the Pearl of the world&#8217; he believes that his life will be magically transformed. He will marry Juana in church and their little boy, Coyotito, will be able to attend school. Obsessed by his dreams, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-pearl-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Pearl &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE PEARL is Steinbeck&#8217;s flawless parable about wealth and the evil it can bring. When Kino, an Indian pearl-diver, finds &#8216;the Pearl of the world&#8217; he believes that his life will be magically transformed. He will marry Juana in church and their little boy, Coyotito, will be able to attend school. Obsessed by his dreams, Kino is blind to the greed, fear and even violence the pearl arouses in him and his neighbours. Haunting and lyrical, THE PEARL sets the values of the civilized world against those of the primitive and finds them tragically inadequate.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-pearl-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Pearl &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Long Valley &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-long-valley-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-long-valley-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This classic collection of short stories serves as the ideal introduction to Steinbeck&#8217;s work. Set in the idyllic Salinas Valley in California, where simple people farm the land and struggle to find a place for themeselves in the world, these stories reflect many of the concerns key to Steinbeck as a writer; the tensions between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-long-valley-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Long Valley &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This classic collection of short stories serves as the ideal introduction to Steinbeck&#8217;s work. Set in the idyllic Salinas Valley in California, where simple people farm the land and struggle to find a place for themeselves in the world, these stories reflect many of the concerns key to Steinbeck as a writer; the tensions between town and city, labourers and owners, past and present. Included here are the celebrated tales, THE MURDERER and THE CHRYSANTHEMUMS.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-long-valley-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Long Valley &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man in the High Castle &#8211; Philip K. Dick</title>
		<link>/the-man-in-the-high-castle-philip-k-dick/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-in-the-high-castle-philip-k-dick/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A dazzling speculative novel of &#8216;counterfactual history&#8217; from one of America&#8217;s most highly-regarded science fiction authors, Philip K. Dick&#8217;s The Man in the High Castle includes an introduction by Eric Brown in Penguin Modern Classics. Philip K. Dick&#8217;s acclaimed cult novel gives us a horrifying glimpse of an alternative world &#8211; one where the Allies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-in-the-high-castle-philip-k-dick/">The Man in the High Castle &#8211; Philip K. Dick</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A dazzling speculative novel of &#8216;counterfactual history&#8217; from one of America&#8217;s most highly-regarded science fiction authors, Philip K. Dick&#8217;s The Man in the High Castle includes an introduction by Eric Brown in Penguin Modern Classics.</p>
<p>                    Philip K. Dick&#8217;s acclaimed cult novel gives us a horrifying glimpse of an alternative world &#8211; one where the Allies have lost the Second World War. In this nightmare dystopia the Nazis have taken over New York, the Japanese control California and the African continent is virtually wiped out. In a neutral buffer zone in America that divides the world&#8217;s new rival superpowers, lives the author of an underground bestseller. His book offers a new vision of reality &#8211; an alternative theory of world history in which the Axis powers were defeated &#8211; giving hope to the disenchanted. Does &#8216;reality&#8217; lie with him, or is his world just one among many others?</p>
<p>                    Philip Kindred Dick (1928-82) was born in Chicago in 1928. His career as a science fiction writer comprised an early burst of short stories followed by a stream of novels, typically character studies incorporating androids, drugs, and hallucinations. His best works are generally agreed to be The Man in the High Castle and Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep?, the inspiration for the movie Blade Runner.</p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed The Man in the High Castle, you might like Yevgeny Zamyatin&#8217;s We, also available in Penguin Classics.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The most brilliant science fiction mind on any planet&#8217;<br />
                    Rolling Stone</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Dick&#8217;s finest book, and one of the very best science fiction novels ever published&#8217;<br />
                    Eric Brown</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-in-the-high-castle-philip-k-dick/">The Man in the High Castle &#8211; Philip K. Dick</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Two Towers &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</title>
		<link>/the-two-towers-j-r-r-tolkien/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-two-towers-j-r-r-tolkien/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Classic hardback edition of the second volume of The Lord of the Rings, featuring Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design. Includes special packaging and the definitive edition of the text, with fold-out map. Frodo and the Companions of the Ring have been beset by danger during their quest to prevent the Ruling Ring from falling into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-two-towers-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Two Towers &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Classic hardback edition of the second volume of The Lord of the Rings, featuring Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design. Includes special packaging and the definitive edition of the text, with fold-out map. Frodo and the Companions of the Ring have been beset by danger during their quest to prevent the Ruling Ring from falling into the hands of the Dark Lord by destroying it in the Cracks of Doom. They have lost the wizard, Gandalf, in the battle with an evil spirit in the Mines of Moria; and at the Falls of Rauros, Boromir, seduced by the power of the Ring, tried to seize it by force. While Frodo and Sam made their escape the rest of the company were attacked by Orcs. Now they continue their journey alone down the great River Anduin &#8211; alone, that is, save for the mysterious creeping figure that follows wherever they go. This classic hardback features Tolkien&#8217;s original unused dust-jacket design, and its text has been fully restored with almost 400 corrections &#8211; with the full co-operation of Christopher Tolkien &#8211; making it the definitive version, and as close as possible to the version that J.R.R. Tolkien intended.Also included is the original red and black map of the Shire as a foldout sheet.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-two-towers-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Two Towers &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>To a God Unknown &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/to-a-god-unknown-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/to-a-god-unknown-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic Ancient pagan beliefs, the great Greek epics, and the Bible all inform this extraordinary novel by Nobel Prize winner John Steinbeck, which occupied him for more than five difficult years. While fulfilling his dead father&#8217;s dream of creating a prosperous farm in California, Joseph Wayne comes to believe that a magnificent tree [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-a-god-unknown-john-steinbeck/">To a God Unknown &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    Ancient pagan beliefs, the great Greek epics, and the Bible all inform this extraordinary novel by Nobel Prize winner John Steinbeck, which occupied him for more than five difficult years. While fulfilling his dead father&#8217;s dream of creating a prosperous farm in California, Joseph Wayne comes to believe that a magnificent tree on the farm embodies his father&#8217;s spirit. His brothers and their families share in Joseph&#8217;s prosperity, and the farm flourishes&#8211;until one brother, frightened by Joseph&#8217;s pagan belief, kills the tree, allowing disease and famine to descend on the farm. Set in familiar Steinbeck country, To a God Unknown is a mystical tale, exploring one man&#8217;s attempt to control the forces of nature and, ultimately, to understand the ways of God and the forces of the unconscious within. This edition features an introduction and notes by Steinbeck scholar Robert DeMott. </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-a-god-unknown-john-steinbeck/">To a God Unknown &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Grapes of Wrath &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-grapes-of-wrath-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-grapes-of-wrath-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shocking and controversial when it was first published in 1939, Steinbeck&#8217;s Pulitzer prize-winning epic remains his undisputed masterpiece. Set against the background of dust bowl Oklahoma and Californian migrant life, it tells of the Joad family, who, like thousands of others, are forced to travel West in search of the promised land. Their story is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grapes-of-wrath-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Grapes of Wrath &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shocking and controversial when it was first published in 1939, Steinbeck&#8217;s Pulitzer prize-winning epic remains his undisputed masterpiece. Set against the background of dust bowl Oklahoma and Californian migrant life, it tells of the Joad family, who, like thousands of others, are forced to travel West in search of the promised land. Their story is one of false hopes, thwarted desires and broken dreams, yet out of their suffering Steinbeck created a drama that is intensely human, yet majestic in its scale and moral vision; an eloquent tribute to the endurance and dignity of the human spirit.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grapes-of-wrath-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Grapes of Wrath &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Moon is Down &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-moon-is-down-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-moon-is-down-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Originally published at the zenith of Nazi Germany&#8217;s power, The Moon Is Down explores the effects of invasion on both the conquered and the conquerors. Occupied by enemy troops, a small, peaceable town comes face-to-face with evil imposed from the outside and betrayal from within the close-knit community. As he delves into the motivations and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moon-is-down-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Moon is Down &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Originally published at the zenith of Nazi Germany&#8217;s power, The Moon Is Down explores the effects of invasion on both the conquered and the conquerors. Occupied by enemy troops, a small, peaceable town comes face-to-face with evil imposed from the outside and betrayal from within the close-knit community. As he delves into the motivations and emotions of the enemy, Steinbeck uncovers profound and often unsettling truths both about war and human nature.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moon-is-down-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Moon is Down &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Winter of Our Discontent &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-winter-of-our-discontent-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-winter-of-our-discontent-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ethan Allen Hawley has lost the acquisitive spirit of his wealthy and enterprising forebears, a long line of proud New England sea captains and Pilgrims. Scarred by failure, Ethan works as a grocery clerk in a store his family once owned. But his wife is restless and his teenage children troubled and hungry for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-winter-of-our-discontent-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Winter of Our Discontent &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethan Allen Hawley has lost the acquisitive spirit of his wealthy and enterprising forebears, a long line of proud New England sea captains and Pilgrims. Scarred by failure, Ethan works as a grocery clerk in a store his family once owned. But his wife is restless and his teenage children troubled and hungry for the material comforts he cannot provide. Then a series of unusual events reignites Ethan&#8217;s ambition, and he is pitched on to a bold course, where all scruples are put aside. Steinbeck&#8217;s searing examination of the evil influences of money, immorality, greed and ambition on America drew acclaim from the Nobel Committee who hailed him as an &#8216;independent expounder of the truth&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Returns to the high standards of The Grapes of Wrath and to the social themes that made his early work &#8230; so powerful&#8217;<br />
                    Saul Bellow, author of Herzog    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-winter-of-our-discontent-mr-john-steinbeck/">The Winter of Our Discontent &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Garden of Rama &#8211; Arthur C. Clarke</title>
		<link>/the-garden-of-rama-arthur-c-clarke/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-garden-of-rama-arthur-c-clarke/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the spellbinding Arthur C. Clarke tradition, here is an exhilarating adventure into the hearts of both the Universe and mankind . . . By the twenty-third century Earth has already had two encounters with massive, mysterious robotic spacecraft from beyond our solar system&#8211;the incontestable proof of an alien technology that far exceeds our own. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-garden-of-rama-arthur-c-clarke/">The Garden of Rama &#8211; Arthur C. Clarke</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the spellbinding Arthur C. Clarke tradition, here is an exhilarating adventure into the hearts of both the Universe and mankind . . .      </p>
<p>                    By the twenty-third century Earth has already had two encounters with massive, mysterious robotic spacecraft from beyond our solar system&#8211;the incontestable proof of an alien technology that far exceeds our own. Now three human cosmonauts are trapped aboard a labyrinthine Raman vessel, where it will take all of their physical and mental resources to survive.     </p>
<p>                    Only twelve years into their journey do these intrepid travelers learn their destination and face their ultimate challenge: a rendezvous with a Raman base&#8211;and the unseen architects of their galactic home. The cosmonauts have given up family, friends, and possessions to live a new kind of life. But the answers that await them at the Raman Node will require an even greater sacrifice&#8211;if humanity is indeed ready to learn the awe-inspiring truth.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-garden-of-rama-arthur-c-clarke/">The Garden of Rama &#8211; Arthur C. Clarke</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Pastures of Heaven &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-pastures-of-heaven-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry & Drama]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-pastures-of-heaven-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic In Nobel Prize winner John Steinbeck&#8217;s beautifully rendered depictions of small yet fateful moments that transform ordinary lives, these twelve early stories introduce both the subject and style of artistic expression that recur in the most important works of his career. Each of these self-contained stories is linked to the others by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-pastures-of-heaven-john-steinbeck/">The Pastures of Heaven &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    In Nobel Prize winner John Steinbeck&#8217;s beautifully rendered depictions of small yet fateful moments that transform ordinary lives, these twelve early stories introduce both the subject and style of artistic expression that recur in the most important works of his career. Each of these self-contained stories is linked to the others by the presence of the Munroes, a family whose misguided behavior and lack of sensitivity precipitate disasters and tragedies. As the individual dramas unfold, Steinbeck reveals the self-deceptions, intellectual limitations, and emotional vulnerabilities that shape the characters&#8217; reactions and gradually erode the harmony and dreams that once formed the foundation of the community. This edition includes an introduction and notes by James Nagel. </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-pastures-of-heaven-john-steinbeck/">The Pastures of Heaven &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Prefect&#8217;s Uncle &#8211; P.G. Wodehouse</title>
		<link>/a-prefects-uncle-p-g-wodehouse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-prefects-uncle-p-g-wodehouse/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The action of the novel takes place at the fictional &#8220;Beckford College&#8221;, a private school for boys; the title alludes to the arrival at the school of a mischievous young boy called Farnie, who turns out to be the uncle of the older &#8220;Bishop&#8221; Gethryn, a prefect, cricketer and popular figure in the school. His [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-prefects-uncle-p-g-wodehouse/">A Prefect&#8217;s Uncle &#8211; P.G. Wodehouse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The action of the novel takes place at the fictional &#8220;Beckford College&#8221;, a private school for boys; the title alludes to the arrival at the school of a mischievous young boy called Farnie, who turns out to be the uncle of the older &#8220;Bishop&#8221; Gethryn, a prefect, cricketer and popular figure in the school. His arrival, along with that of another youngster who becomes fag to Gethryn, leads to much excitement and scandal in the school, and the disruption of some important cricket matches.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-prefects-uncle-p-g-wodehouse/">A Prefect&#8217;s Uncle &#8211; P.G. Wodehouse</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Una visita inesperada &#8211; Irenea Morales</title>
		<link>/una-visita-inesperada-irenea-morales/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/una-visita-inesperada-irenea-morales/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Londres, 1913 Los planes de la joven viuda Florence Morland de presentar a su hermana pequeña, Daisy, en sociedad y disfrutar de la temporada londinense se ven truncados cuando recibe una tentadora invitación: la nueva propietaria de Des Bienheureux, la idílica finca del norte de Francia que antaño perteneció a la familia, desea que ambas [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/una-visita-inesperada-irenea-morales/">Una visita inesperada &#8211; Irenea Morales</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Londres, 1913<br />
                    Los planes de la joven viuda Florence Morland de presentar a su hermana pequeña, Daisy, en sociedad y disfrutar de la temporada londinense se ven truncados cuando recibe una tentadora invitación: la nueva propietaria de Des Bienheureux, la idílica finca del norte de Francia que antaño perteneció a la familia, desea que ambas se unan al resto de sus invitados para pasar el verano entre sus bucólicos jardines.<br />
                    El recuerdo de antiguos amores, así como el anhelo de los nuevos, florecerá nada más traspasar su mágico umbral, y las dos hermanas descubrirán, entre sesiones de espiritismo y escapadas a la luz de la luna, que no todo es joie de vivre y que los secretos que se esconden la una a la otra no son nada comparados con los que atesora la antigua mansión familiar.<br />
                    Un mal ancestral acecha aletargado entre raíces y sombras, esperando la oportunidad de ser liberado.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/una-visita-inesperada-irenea-morales/">Una visita inesperada &#8211; Irenea Morales</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rabbit Hunter &#8211; Lars Kepler</title>
		<link>/the-rabbit-hunter-lars-kepler/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rabbit-hunter-lars-kepler/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The sixth gripping thriller in Lars Kepler&#8217;s bestselling series featuring Joona Linna. Perfect for fans of Stieg Larsson and Jo Nesbo. There&#8217;s a face at the window. A stranger wearing a mask stands in the shadow of a garden. He&#8217;s watching his first victim through the window. He will kill him slowly, make it last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rabbit-hunter-lars-kepler/">The Rabbit Hunter &#8211; Lars Kepler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The sixth gripping thriller in Lars Kepler&#8217;s bestselling series featuring Joona Linna. Perfect for fans of Stieg Larsson and Jo Nesbo.</p>
<p>                              There&#8217;s a face at the window.<br />
                    A stranger wearing a mask stands in the shadow of a garden. He&#8217;s watching his first victim through the window. He will kill him slowly, make it last &#8211; play him a nursery rhyme &#8211; make him pay.</p>
<p>                              A killer in your house.<br />
                    There&#8217;s only one person the police can turn to &#8211; ex-Detective Joona Linna &#8211; but he&#8217;s serving time in a high-security prison. So they offer him a chance to secure his freedom: help Superintendent Saga Bauer track down the vicious killer known as the Rabbit Hunter, before he strikes again.</p>
<p>                              Only one man can stop him.<br />
                    Soon another three victims have been murdered and Stockholm is in the grip of terror. Joona Linna must catch a disturbed predator, whose trail of destruction leads back to one horrific night of violence &#8211; with consequences more terrifying than anyone could have imagined&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rabbit-hunter-lars-kepler/">The Rabbit Hunter &#8211; Lars Kepler</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fellowship of the Ring &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</title>
		<link>/the-fellowship-of-the-ring-j-r-r-tolkien/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fellowship-of-the-ring-j-r-r-tolkien/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Continuing the story begun in The Hobbit, this is the first part of Tolkien&#8217;s epic masterpiece, The Lord of the Rings, featuring a striking black cover based on Tolkien&#8217;s own design, the definitive text, and a detailed map of Middle-earth. Sauron, the Dark Lord, has gathered to him all the Rings of Power &#8211; the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fellowship-of-the-ring-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Fellowship of the Ring &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Continuing the story begun in The Hobbit, this is the first part of Tolkien&#8217;s epic masterpiece, The Lord of the Rings, featuring a striking black cover based on Tolkien&#8217;s own design, the definitive text, and a detailed map of Middle-earth.</p>
<p>                              Sauron, the Dark Lord, has gathered to him all the Rings of Power &#8211; the means by which he intends to rule Middle-earth. All he lacks in his plans for dominion is the One Ring &#8211; the ring that rules them all &#8211; which has fallen into the hands of the hobbit, Bilbo Baggins.</p>
<p>                              In a sleepy village in the Shire, young Frodo Baggins finds himself faced with an immense task, as his elderly cousin Bilbo entrusts the Ring to his care. Frodo must leave his home and make a perilous journey across Middle-earth to the Cracks of Doom, there to destroy the Ring and foil the Dark Lord in his evil purpose.</p>
<p>                              Part of a set of three paperbacks, this popular edition is once again available in its classic black livery designed by Tolkien himself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fellowship-of-the-ring-j-r-r-tolkien/">The Fellowship of the Ring &#8211; J. R. R. Tolkien</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Stranger &#8211; Albert Camus</title>
		<link>/the-stranger-albert-camus/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-stranger-albert-camus/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With the intrigue of a psychological thriller, The Stranger&#8211;Camus&#8217;s masterpiece&#8211;gives us the story of an ordinary man unwittingly drawn into a senseless murder on an Algerian beach. With an Introduction by Peter Dunwoodie; translated by Matthew Ward. Behind the subterfuge, Camus explores what he termed the nakedness of man faced with the absurd and describes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stranger-albert-camus/">The Stranger &#8211; Albert Camus</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the intrigue of a psychological thriller, The Stranger&#8211;Camus&#8217;s masterpiece&#8211;gives us the story of an ordinary man unwittingly drawn into a senseless murder on an Algerian beach. With an Introduction by Peter Dunwoodie; translated by Matthew Ward.     </p>
<p>                    Behind the subterfuge, Camus explores what he termed the nakedness of man faced with the absurd and describes the condition of reckless alienation and spiritual exhaustion that characterized so much of twentieth-century life.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Stranger is a strikingly modern text and Matthew Ward&#8217;s translation will enable readers to appreciate why Camus&#8217;s stoical anti-hero and ­devious narrator remains one of the key expressions of a postwar Western malaise, and one of the cleverest exponents of a literature of ambiguity.&#8221; -from the Introduction by Peter Dunwoodie     </p>
<p>                    First published in 1946; now in translation by Matthew Ward.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-stranger-albert-camus/">The Stranger &#8211; Albert Camus</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Short Reign of Pippin IV : A Fabrication &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-short-reign-of-pippin-iv-a-fabrication-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-short-reign-of-pippin-iv-a-fabrication-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic In his only work of political satire, The Short Reign of Pippin IV, John Steinbeck turns the French Revolution upside down as amateur astronomer Pippin Héristal is drafted to rule the unruly French. Steinbeck creates around the infamous Pippin the most hilarious royal court ever: Pippin&#8217;s wife, Queen Marie, who &#8220;might have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-short-reign-of-pippin-iv-a-fabrication-john-steinbeck/">The Short Reign of Pippin IV : A Fabrication &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic     </p>
<p>                    In his only work of political satire, The Short Reign of Pippin IV, John Steinbeck turns the French Revolution upside down as amateur astronomer Pippin Héristal is drafted to rule the unruly French. Steinbeck creates around the infamous Pippin the most hilarious royal court ever: Pippin&#8217;s wife, Queen Marie, who &#8220;might have taken her place at the bar of a very good restaurant&#8221;; his uncle, a man of dubious virtue; his glamour-struck daughter and her beau, the son of the so-called &#8220;egg king&#8221; of Petaluma, California; and a motley crew of courtiers and politicians, guards and gardeners. This edition includes an introduction by Robert Morsberger and Katharine Morsberger.     </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-short-reign-of-pippin-iv-a-fabrication-john-steinbeck/">The Short Reign of Pippin IV : A Fabrication &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Of Mice and Men &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/of-mice-and-men-mr-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/of-mice-and-men-mr-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Drifters in search of work, George and his childlike friend Lennie, have nothing in the world except the clothes on their back &#8211; and a dream that one day they will have some land of their own. Eventually they find work on a ranch in California&#8217;s Salinas Valley, but their hopes are dashed as Lennie [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/of-mice-and-men-mr-john-steinbeck/">Of Mice and Men &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Drifters in search of work, George and his childlike friend Lennie, have  nothing in the world except the clothes on their back &#8211; and a dream  that one day they will have some land of their own. Eventually they find  work on a ranch in California&#8217;s Salinas Valley, but their hopes are  dashed as Lennie &#8211; struggling against extreme cruelty, misunderstanding  and feelings of jealousy &#8211; becomes a victim of his own strength.  Tackling universal themes of friendship and shared vision, and giving a  voice to America&#8217;s lonely and dispossessed, Of Mice and Men remains Steinbeck&#8217;s most popular work, achieving success as a novel, Broadway play and three acclaimed films.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/of-mice-and-men-mr-john-steinbeck/">Of Mice and Men &#8211; Mr John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</title>
		<link>/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER A RICHARD AND JUDY BOOKCLUB PICK &#8216;Utterly engrossing&#8217; Guardian It is wash-day for the housemaids at Longbourn House, and Sarah&#8217;s hands are chapped and raw. Domestic life below stairs, ruled with a tender heart and an iron will by Mrs Hill the housekeeper, is about to be disturbed by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/">Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER<br />
                    A RICHARD AND JUDY BOOKCLUB PICK<br />
                    &#8216;Utterly engrossing&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    It is wash-day for the housemaids at Longbourn House, and Sarah&#8217;s hands are chapped and raw. Domestic life below stairs, ruled with a tender heart and an iron will by Mrs Hill the housekeeper, is about to be disturbed by the arrival of a new footman, bearing secrets and the scent of the sea.    </p>
<p>                    What readers are saying:    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A novel to be savoured&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;Highly recommended&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;Very enjoyable exploration of the background to Pride and Prejudice&#8217;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/">Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
