<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Anthologies (non-poetry) Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/anthologies-non-poetry/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/anthologies-non-poetry/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Anthologies (non-poetry) Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/anthologies-non-poetry/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Masons Of Lowell, Massachusetts, Monday Evening, September 26, 1881 : In Memoriam, The President Of The United States, James A. Garfield (1881) &#8211; Lowell Masonic Association</title>
		<link>/the-masons-of-lowell-massachusetts-monday-evening-september-26-1881-in-memoriam-the-president-of-the-united-states-james-a-garfield-1881-lowell-masonic-association/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-masons-of-lowell-massachusetts-monday-evening-september-26-1881-in-memoriam-the-president-of-the-united-states-james-a-garfield-1881-lowell-masonic-association/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book is a facsimile reprint and may contain imperfections such as marks, notations, marginalia and flawed pages. This scarce antiquarian book is a facsimile reprint of the original. Due to its age, it may contain imperfections such as marks, notations, marginalia and flawed pages. Because we believe this work is culturally important, we have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-masons-of-lowell-massachusetts-monday-evening-september-26-1881-in-memoriam-the-president-of-the-united-states-james-a-garfield-1881-lowell-masonic-association/">The Masons Of Lowell, Massachusetts, Monday Evening, September 26, 1881 : In Memoriam, The President Of The United States, James A. Garfield (1881) &#8211; Lowell Masonic Association</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book is a facsimile reprint and may contain imperfections such as marks, notations, marginalia and flawed pages. This scarce antiquarian book is a facsimile reprint of the original. Due to its age, it may contain imperfections such as marks, notations, marginalia and flawed pages. Because we believe this work is culturally important, we have made it available as part of our commitment for protecting, preserving, and promoting the world&#8217;s literature in affordable, high quality, modern editions that are true to the original work.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-masons-of-lowell-massachusetts-monday-evening-september-26-1881-in-memoriam-the-president-of-the-united-states-james-a-garfield-1881-lowell-masonic-association/">The Masons Of Lowell, Massachusetts, Monday Evening, September 26, 1881 : In Memoriam, The President Of The United States, James A. Garfield (1881) &#8211; Lowell Masonic Association</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Distrust that Particular Flavor &#8211; William Gibson</title>
		<link>/distrust-that-particular-flavor-william-gibson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/distrust-that-particular-flavor-william-gibson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Distrust That Particular Flavor &#8211; an acclaimed nonfiction collection by William Gibson, bestselling author of Neuromancer &#8216;The future&#8217;s already here: it&#8217;s just not evenly distributed&#8217; William Gibson was writing fiction when he predicted the internet. And as his stories bled into reality so he became one of the first to report on the real-world consequences [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/distrust-that-particular-flavor-william-gibson/">Distrust that Particular Flavor &#8211; William Gibson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Distrust That Particular Flavor &#8211; an acclaimed nonfiction collection by William Gibson, bestselling author of Neuromancer</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The future&#8217;s already here: it&#8217;s just not evenly distributed&#8217;</p>
<p>                    William Gibson was writing fiction when he predicted the internet. And as his stories bled into reality so he became one of the first to report on the real-world consequences of cyberspace&#8217;s growth and development.</p>
<p>                    Now, with the dust settling on the first internet revolution, comes Gibson&#8217;s first collection of non-fiction &#8211; essays from the technological and cultural frontiers of this new world. </p>
<p>                    Covering a variety of subjects, they include:</p>
<p>                    &#8211; Metrophagy &#8211; the Art and Science of Digesting Great Cities<br />
                    &#8211; An account of obsession in &#8216;the world&#8217;s attic&#8217; &#8211; eBay<br />
                    &#8211; Reasons why &#8216;The Net is a Waste of Time&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Singapore as &#8216;Disneyland with the Death Penalty&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; A primer on Japan, our default setting for the future </p>
<p>                    These and many other pieces, collected for the first time in Distrust that Particular Flavour, are studded with revealing autobiographical fragments and map the development of Gibson&#8217;s acute perceptions about modern life. Readers of Neal Stephenson, Ray Bradbury and Iain M. Banks will love this book.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Gibson is a prophet and a satirist, a black comedian and an astounding architect of cool. He&#8217;s also responsible for much of the world we live in&#8217; Spectator</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Part-detective story, part-cultural snapshot &#8230; all bound by Gibson&#8217;s pin-sharp prose&#8217; Arena</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/distrust-that-particular-flavor-william-gibson/">Distrust that Particular Flavor &#8211; William Gibson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deacon King Kong : Barack Obama Favourite Read &#038; Oprah&#8217;s Book Club Pick &#8211; James McBride</title>
		<link>/deacon-king-kong-barack-obama-favourite-read-oprahs-book-club-pick-james-mcbride/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deacon-king-kong-barack-obama-favourite-read-oprahs-book-club-pick-james-mcbride/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND OPRAH&#8217;S BOOK CLUB PICK CHOSEN BY BARACK OBAMA AS A FAVOURITE READ TOP TEN BOOKS OF THE YEAR, NEW YORK TIMES &#038; WASHINGTON POST &#8216;Brilliantly imagined, larger than life, a tragicomedic epic of intertwined lives.&#8217; JOYCE CAROL OATES &#8216;Deeply felt, beautifully written and profoundly humane.&#8217; JUNOT DIAZ, New York Times [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deacon-king-kong-barack-obama-favourite-read-oprahs-book-club-pick-james-mcbride/">Deacon King Kong : Barack Obama Favourite Read &#038; Oprah&#8217;s Book Club Pick &#8211; James McBride</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND OPRAH&#8217;S BOOK CLUB PICK<br />
                      CHOSEN BY BARACK OBAMA AS A FAVOURITE READ<br />
                      TOP TEN BOOKS OF THE YEAR, NEW YORK TIMES &#038; WASHINGTON POST</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brilliantly imagined, larger than life, a tragicomedic epic of intertwined lives.&#8217; JOYCE CAROL OATES</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Deeply felt, beautifully written and profoundly humane.&#8217; JUNOT DIAZ, New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                    The year is 1969. In a housing project in south Brooklyn, a shambling old church deacon called Sportcoat shoots &#8211; for no apparent reason &#8211; the local drug-dealer who used to be part of the church&#8217;s baseball team. The repercussions of that moment draw in the whole community, from Sportcoat&#8217;s best friend &#8211; Hot Sausage &#8211; to the local Italian mobsters, the police (corrupt and otherwise), and the stalwart ladies of the Five Ends Baptist Church.</p>
<p>                    DEACON KING KONG is a book about a community under threat, about the ways people pull together in an age when the old rules are being rewritten. It is very funny in places, and heartbreaking in others. From a prize-winning storyteller, this New York Times bestseller shows us that not all secrets are meant to be hidden, and that the communities we build are fragile but vital.<br />
                    ______________________<br />
                    From the winner of a National Book Award and author of the bestselling memoir,The Color of Water, and The Good Lord Bird, a TV series starring Ethan Hawke</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A hilarious, pitch-perfect comedy set in the Brooklyn projects of the late 1960s. This alone may qualify it as one of the year&#8217;s best novels.&#8217; The Washington Post</p>
<p>                    What Goodreads readers are saying:</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;Deacon King Kong is one of those novels whose brilliance sneaks up on you. I haven&#8217;t been this pleasantly surprised by a book in a while.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;I do believe I just finished one of my all time favorite books. I loved every minute spent with Sportcoat and his community. A good old fashioned yarn shot through with truth, spirit, and humor. I LOVED it!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;This book was a balm for my soul, a portrait of a black church community circa 1969 with sweet characters (well, most of them), interconnections that stretch back decades, and a plot with more than one mystery at its heart.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;&#8221;Deacon&#8221; has the texture of folk lore and fable mixed with the unexpected rhythms of jazz and the noisy streets of late 1960s Brooklyn.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;The ending was one of those where you clutch your heart and want to hug the book (or your Kindle).&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deacon-king-kong-barack-obama-favourite-read-oprahs-book-club-pick-james-mcbride/">Deacon King Kong : Barack Obama Favourite Read &#038; Oprah&#8217;s Book Club Pick &#8211; James McBride</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wastelands : Stories of the Apocalypse &#8211; John Joseph Adams</title>
		<link>/wastelands-stories-of-the-apocalypse-john-joseph-adams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wastelands-stories-of-the-apocalypse-john-joseph-adams/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Famine, Death, War, and Pestilence&#8211;the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse, the harbingers of Armageddon&#8211;these are our guides through the Wastelands.From the Book of Revelation to The Road Warrior, from A Canticle for Leibowitz to The Road, storytellers have long imagined the end of the world, weaving eschatological tales of catastrophe, chaos, and calamity. In doing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wastelands-stories-of-the-apocalypse-john-joseph-adams/">Wastelands : Stories of the Apocalypse &#8211; John Joseph Adams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Famine, Death, War, and Pestilence&#8211;the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse, the harbingers of Armageddon&#8211;these are our guides through the Wastelands.From the Book of Revelation to The Road Warrior, from A Canticle for Leibowitz to The Road, storytellers have long imagined the end of the world, weaving eschatological tales of catastrophe, chaos, and calamity. In doing so, these visionary authors have addressed one of the most challenging and enduring themes of imaginative fiction: the nature of life in the aftermath of total societal collapse.Gathering together the best postapocalyptic literature of the last two decades from many of today&#8217;s most renowned authors of speculative fiction&#8211;including George R. R. Martin, Gene Wolfe, Orson Scott Card, Carol Emshwiller, Jonathan Lethem, Octavia E. Butler, and Stephen King&#8211;Wastelands explores the scientific, psychological, and philosophical questions of what it means to remain human in the wake of Armageddon. Whether the end of the world comes through nuclear war, ecological disaster, or cosmological cataclysm, these are tales of survivors, in some cases struggling to rebuild the society that was, in others, merely surviving, scrounging for food in depopulated ruins and defending themselves against monsters, mutants, and marauders.Wastelands delves into this bleak landscape, uncovering the raw human emotion and heart-pounding thrills at the genre&#8217;s core.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wastelands-stories-of-the-apocalypse-john-joseph-adams/">Wastelands : Stories of the Apocalypse &#8211; John Joseph Adams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Somehow, Some Way : A Billionaire Builders Novella &#8211; Madeleine Maby, Lance Greenfield, Jennifer Probst</title>
		<link>/somehow-some-way-a-billionaire-builders-novella-madeleine-maby-lance-greenfield-jennifer-probst/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult & Contemporary Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/somehow-some-way-a-billionaire-builders-novella-madeleine-maby-lance-greenfield-jennifer-probst/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bolivar Randy Heart (a.k.a. Brady) knows exactly what he wants next in life: the perfect wife. Raised in a strict traditional family household, he seeks a woman who is sweet, conservative, and eager to settle down. With his well-known protective and dominant streak, he needs a woman to offer him balance in a world where [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/somehow-some-way-a-billionaire-builders-novella-madeleine-maby-lance-greenfield-jennifer-probst/">Somehow, Some Way : A Billionaire Builders Novella &#8211; Madeleine Maby, Lance Greenfield, Jennifer Probst</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bolivar Randy Heart (a.k.a. Brady) knows exactly what he wants next in life: the perfect wife. Raised in a strict traditional family household, he seeks a woman who is sweet, conservative, and eager to settle down. With his well-known protective and dominant streak, he needs a woman to offer him balance in a world where he relishes control.     </p>
<p>                    Too bad the newly hired, gorgeous, rehab addict is blasting through all his preconceptions and wrecking his ideals&#8230;one nail at a time&#8230;.     </p>
<p>                    Charlotte Grayson knows who she is and refuses to apologize. Growing up poor made her appreciate the simple things in life, and her new job at Pierce Brothers Construction is perfect to help her carve out a career in renovating houses. When an opportunity to transform a dilapidated house in a dangerous neighborhood pops up, she goes in full throttle. Unfortunately, she&#8217;s forced to work with the firm&#8217;s sexy architect who&#8217;s driving her crazy with his archaic views on women. Too bad he&#8217;s beginning to tempt her to take a chance on more than just work&#8230;one stroke at a time&#8230;.     </p>
<p>                    Somehow, some way, they need to work together to renovate a house without killing each other&#8230;or surrendering to the white-hot chemistry knocking at the front door.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/somehow-some-way-a-billionaire-builders-novella-madeleine-maby-lance-greenfield-jennifer-probst/">Somehow, Some Way : A Billionaire Builders Novella &#8211; Madeleine Maby, Lance Greenfield, Jennifer Probst</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pensions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface* Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time? Many of us have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface*    </p>
<p>                    Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time?     </p>
<p>                    Many of us have been raised on the traditional notion of a three-stage approach to our working lives: education, followed by work and then retirement.  But this well-established pathway is already beginning to collapse &#8211; life expectancy is rising, final-salary pensions are vanishing, and increasing numbers of people are juggling multiple careers. Whether you are 18, 45 or 60, you will need to do things very differently from previous generations and learn to structure your life in completely new ways.    </p>
<p>                    The 100-Year Life is here to help.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the unique pairing of their experience in psychology and economics, Lynda Gratton and Andrew J. Scott offer a broad-ranging analysis as well as a raft of solutions, showing how to rethink your finances, your education, your career and your relationships and create a fulfilling 100-year life.     </p>
<p>                    * How can you fashion a career and life path that defines you and your values and creates a shifting balance between work and leisure?    </p>
<p>                    * What are the most effective ways of boosting your physical and mental health over a longer and more dynamic lifespan?    </p>
<p>                    * How can you make the most of your intangible assets &#8211; such as family and friends &#8211; as you build a productive, longer life?    </p>
<p>                    * In a multiple-stage life how can you learn to make the transitions that will be so crucial and experiment with new ways of living, working and learning?    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award and featuring a new preface, The 100-Year Life is a wake-up call that describes what to expect and considers the choices and options that you will face. It is also fundamentally a call to action for individuals, politicians, firms and governments and offers the clearest demonstration that a 100-year life can be a wonderful and inspiring one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nothing To Envy : Real Lives In North Korea &#8211; Barbara Demick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nothing-to-envy-real-lives-in-north-korea-barbara-demick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nothing-to-envy-real-lives-in-north-korea-barbara-demick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE BBC SAMUEL JOHNSON PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2010 A spectacularly revealing and harrowing portrait of ordinary lives in the world&#8217;s least ordinary country, North Korea North Korea is Orwell&#8217;s 1984 made reality: it is the only country in the world not connected to the internet; Gone with the Wind is a dangerous, banned [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nothing-to-envy-real-lives-in-north-korea-barbara-demick-abridged/">Nothing To Envy : Real Lives In North Korea &#8211; Barbara Demick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE BBC SAMUEL JOHNSON PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2010    </p>
<p>                    A spectacularly revealing and harrowing portrait of ordinary lives in the world&#8217;s least ordinary country, North Korea    </p>
<p>                    North Korea is Orwell&#8217;s 1984 made reality: it is the only country in the world not connected to the internet; Gone with the Wind is a dangerous, banned book; during political rallies, spies study your expression to check your sincerity. After the death of the country&#8217;s great leader Kim Il Sung in 1994, famine descended, and Nothing to Envy &#8211; winner of the 2010 BBC Samuel Johnson Prize for Non-Fiction &#8211; weaves together the stories of adversity and resilience of six residents of Chongin, North Korea&#8217;s third-largest city. From extensive interviews and with tenacious investigative work, Barbara Demick has recreated the concerns, culture and lifestyles of North Korean citizens in a gripping narrative, and vividly reconstructed the inner workings of this extraordinary and secretive country.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nothing-to-envy-real-lives-in-north-korea-barbara-demick-abridged/">Nothing To Envy : Real Lives In North Korea &#8211; Barbara Demick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover Wollstonecraft&#8217;s classic feminist text in an abridged, digestible form. WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY ZOE WILLIAMS The term feminism did not yet exist when Mary Wollstonecraft wrote this book, but it was the first great piece of feminist writing. In these pages you will find the essence of her argument &#8211; for the education of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/">A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover Wollstonecraft&#8217;s classic feminist text in an abridged, digestible form.    </p>
<p>                    WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY ZOE WILLIAMS     </p>
<p>                    The term feminism did not yet exist when Mary Wollstonecraft wrote this book, but it was the first great piece of feminist writing. In these pages you will find the essence of her argument &#8211; for the education of women and for an increased female contribution to society. Her work made the first ripples of what would later become the tidal wave of the women&#8217;s rights movement. Rationalist but revolutionary, Wollstonecraft changed the world for women.    </p>
<p>                    Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/">A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walden: Or, Life in the Woods &#8211; Henry David Thoreau (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nature was a form of religion for naturalist, essayist, and early environmentalist Henry David Thoreau (1817-62). In communing with the natural world, he wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and &#8230; learn what it had to teach. Toward that end Thoreau built a cabin in the spring of 1845 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/">Walden: Or, Life in the Woods &#8211; Henry David Thoreau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nature was a form of religion for naturalist, essayist, and early environmentalist Henry David Thoreau (1817-62). In communing with the natural world, he wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and &#8230; learn what it had to teach. Toward that end Thoreau built a cabin in the spring of 1845 on the shores of Walden Pond &#8212; on land owned by Ralph Waldo Emerson &#8212; outside Concord, Massachusetts. There he observed nature, farmed, built fences, surveyed, and wrote in his journal.<br />
                    One product of his two-year sojourn was this book &#8212; a great classic of American letters. Interwoven with accounts of Thoreau&#8217;s daily life (he received visitors and almost daily walked into Concord) are mediations on human existence, society, government, and other topics, expressed with wisdom and beauty of style.<br />
                    Walden offers abundant evidence of Thoreau&#8217;s ability to begin with observations on a mundane incident or the minutiae of nature and then develop these observations into profound ruminations on the most fundamental human concerns. Credited with influencing Tolstoy, Gandhi, and other thinkers, the volume remains a masterpiece of philosophical reflection.<br />
                    A selection of the Common Core State Standards Initiative.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/">Walden: Or, Life in the Woods &#8211; Henry David Thoreau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thick And Other Essays &#8211; Tressie McMillan Cottom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thick-and-other-essays-tressie-mcmillan-cottom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thick-and-other-essays-tressie-mcmillan-cottom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In eight highly praised treatises on beauty, media, money, and more, Tressie McMillan Cottom &#8211; award-winning professor and acclaimed author of Lower Ed &#8211; is unapologetically &#8216;thick&#8217;: deemed &#8216;thick where I should have been thin, more where I should have been less,&#8217; McMillan Cottom refuses to shy away from blending the personal with the political, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thick-and-other-essays-tressie-mcmillan-cottom-abridged/">Thick And Other Essays &#8211; Tressie McMillan Cottom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In eight highly praised treatises on beauty, media, money, and more, Tressie McMillan Cottom &#8211; award-winning professor and acclaimed author of Lower Ed &#8211; is unapologetically &#8216;thick&#8217;: deemed &#8216;thick where I should have been thin, more where I should have been less,&#8217; McMillan Cottom refuses to shy away from blending the personal with the political, from bringing her full self and voice to the fore of her analytical work.In eight highly praised treatises on beauty, media, money, and more, Tressie McMillan Cottom &#8211; award-winning professor and acclaimed author of Lower Ed &#8211; is unapologetically &#8216;thick&#8217;: deemed &#8216;thick where I should have been thin, more where I should have been less,&#8217; McMillan Cottom refuses to shy away from blending the personal with the political, from bringing her full self and voice to the fore of her analytical work. Collected in an indispensable volume that speaks to the everywoman and the erudite alike, these unforgettable essays never fail to be &#8216;painfully honest and</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thick-and-other-essays-tressie-mcmillan-cottom-abridged/">Thick And Other Essays &#8211; Tressie McMillan Cottom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Story of My Life &#8211; Helen Keller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When she was 19 months old, Helen Keller (1880-1968) suffered a severe illness that left her blind and deaf. Not long after, she also became mute. Her tenacious struggle to overcome these handicaps &#8212; with the help of her inspired teacher, Anne Sullivan &#8212; is one of the great stories of human courage and dedication. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/">The Story of My Life &#8211; Helen Keller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When she was 19 months old, Helen Keller (1880-1968) suffered a severe illness that left her blind and deaf. Not long after, she also became mute. Her tenacious struggle to overcome these handicaps &#8212; with the help of her inspired teacher, Anne Sullivan &#8212; is one of the great stories of human courage and dedication. In this classic autobiography, first published in 1903, Miss Keller recounts the first 22 years of her life, including the magical moment at the water pump when, recognizing the connection between the word &#8220;water&#8221; and the cold liquid flowing over her hand, she realized that objects had names. Subsequent experiences were equally noteworthy: her joy at eventually learning to speak, her friendships with Oliver Wendell Holmes, Edward Everett Hale and other notables, her education at Radcliffe (from which she graduated cum laude), and-underlying all-her extraordinary relationship with Miss Sullivan, who showed a remarkable genius for communicating with her eager and quick-to-learn pupil. These and many other aspects of Helen Keller&#8217;s life are presented here in clear, straightforward prose full of wonderful descriptions and imagery that would do credit to a sighted writer. Completely devoid of self-pity, yet full of love and compassion for others, this deeply moving memoir offers an unforgettable portrait of one of the outstanding women of the twentieth century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/">The Story of My Life &#8211; Helen Keller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Among the most influential authors and reformers of his age, Thomas Paine (1737-1809) was born in England but went on to play an important role in both the American and French Revolutions. In 1774, he emigrated to America where, for a time, he helped to edit the Pennsylvania Magazine. On January 10, 1776, he published [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/">Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Among the most influential authors and reformers of his age, Thomas Paine (1737-1809) was born in England but went on to play an important role in both the American and French Revolutions. In 1774, he emigrated to America where, for a time, he helped to edit the Pennsylvania Magazine. On January 10, 1776, he published his pamphlet Common Sense,  a persuasive argument for the colonies&#8217; political and economic separation from Britain.<br />
                    Common Sense cites the evils of monarchy, accuses the British government of inflicting economic and social injustices upon the colonies, and points to the absurdity of an island attempting to rule a continent. Credited by George Washington as having changed the minds of many of his countrymen, the document sold over 500,000 copies within a few months.<br />
                    Today, Common Sense remains a landmark document in the struggle for freedom, distinguished not only by Paine&#8217;s ideas but also by its clear and passionate presentation. Designed to ignite public opinion against autocratic rule, the pamphlet offered a careful balance between imagination and judgment, and appropriate language and expression to fit the subject. It immediately found a receptive audience, heartened Washington&#8217;s despondent army, and foreshadowed much of the phrasing and substance of the Declaration of Independence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/">Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Good and Evil : Prelude to a Philosophy of the Future &#8211; Friedrich Nietzsche (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After kicking open the doors to twentieth-century philosophy in Thus Spake Zarathustra, Friedrich Nietzsche refined his ideal of the superman with the 1886 publication of Beyond Good and Evil. Conventional morality is a sign of slavery, Nietzsche maintains, and the superman goes beyond good and evil in action, thought, and creation. Nietzsche especially targets what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/">Beyond Good and Evil : Prelude to a Philosophy of the Future &#8211; Friedrich Nietzsche (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After kicking open the doors to twentieth-century philosophy in Thus Spake Zarathustra,  Friedrich Nietzsche refined his ideal of the superman with the 1886 publication of Beyond Good and Evil. Conventional morality is a sign of slavery, Nietzsche maintains, and the superman goes beyond good and evil in action, thought, and creation. Nietzsche especially targets what he calls a slave morality that fosters herdlike quiescence and stigmatizes the highest human types.<br />
                    In this pathbreaking work, Nietzsche&#8217;s philosophical and literary powers are at their height: with devastating irony and flashing wit he gleefully dynamites centuries of accumulated conventional wisdom in metaphysics, morals, and psychology, clearing a path for such twentieth-century innovators as Thomas Mann, André Gide, Sigmund Freud, George Bernard Shaw, André Malraux, and Jean-Paul Sartre, all of whom openly acknowledged their debt to him.<br />
                    Students of philosophy and literature as well as general readers will prize this rich sampling of Nietzsche&#8217;s thought in an unabridged and inexpensive edition of one of the philosopher&#8217;s most important works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/">Beyond Good and Evil : Prelude to a Philosophy of the Future &#8211; Friedrich Nietzsche (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
