<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Teaching Resources &amp; Education Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/teaching-resources-education/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/teaching-resources-education/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Teaching Resources &amp; Education Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/teaching-resources-education/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads</title>
		<link>/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are You Ready To Get The Most Out Of Yourself And Out Of Life?When it comes to getting fit, a lot of us find excuses. We&#8217;re too busy; we sleep in, we don&#8217;t feel like it. But what happens when we stop making excuses? David Goggins stopped making excuses and started giving life 100%. If [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads/">Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are You Ready To Get The Most Out Of Yourself And Out Of Life?When it comes to getting fit, a lot of us find excuses. We&#8217;re too busy; we sleep in, we don&#8217;t feel like it. But what happens when we stop making excuses? </p>
<p>                    David Goggins stopped making excuses and started giving life 100%. If you&#8217;ve heard his name, it&#8217;s probably because this former Air Force serviceman and Navy SEAL is also an ultra-endurance athlete and once held a world record for the most pull-ups in 24 hours. He is one of the toughest people alive. </p>
<p>                    His success wasn&#8217;t handed to him, though. Goggins had a terribly hard life. After surviving an abusive and traumatic childhood, he faced poverty and became overweight in his twenties. As a result of the trauma from his childhood, he was nearly illiterate as a teen. None of this stopped him, though. </p>
<p>                    Now he&#8217;s here to help you stop backing away from challenges, too. In his book &#8220;Can&#8217;t Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds,&#8221; he teaches that the difficult things in life make you the strongest. </p>
<p>                    If you are ready to get the most out of yourself and out of life, then you need this summary by Quick Reads. After reading this summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me, you&#8217;ll discover: What it takes to master your mind from someone who has overcome huge obstacles and become one of the toughest people on earth.How to break your mental roadblocks and take control of your success.How you can always come out stronger from any condition no matter how much trauma you&#8217;ve experiencedHow to work hard and push yourself to be your best self instead of believing in overnight successHow to be ready to dump your excuses and do and become better than ever before. And most importantly, how to become the master of your mind and achieve more than you thought possible using the 40% rule and much more&#8230; See the Table of Contents to find out by clicking on &#8220;Look inside.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    So, if you want a concise yet very informative summary book on Can&#8217;t Hurt Me that can help you grasp the insights, key ideas, and main points within minutes, simply scroll up and click the &#8220;BUY NOW&#8221; button for instant access! </p>
<p>                    DISCLAIMER:  </p>
<p>                    This is not the official book, but an unofficial summary and analysis of the book &#8220;Can&#8217;t Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds by David Goggins bringing you the main points, concise and easy to consume. It is a way to get you the key ideas from great books and bestsellers in minutes, not hours. More knowledge in less time! </p>
<p>                    QUICK READS = Learn Faster &#038; Get Smarter!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads/">Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockade Billy : Contains the chilling bonus story &#8216;Morality&#8217; &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/blockade-billy-contains-the-chilling-bonus-story-morality-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blockade-billy-contains-the-chilling-bonus-story-morality-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Even the most diehard baseball fans don&#8217;t know the true story of William &#8216;Blockade Billy&#8217; Blakely. He may have been the greatest player the game has ever seen, but today no one remembers his name. He was the first &#8211; and only &#8211; player to have his existence completely removed from the record books. Even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blockade-billy-contains-the-chilling-bonus-story-morality-stephen-king/">Blockade Billy : Contains the chilling bonus story &#8216;Morality&#8217; &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even the most diehard baseball fans don&#8217;t know the true story of William &#8216;Blockade Billy&#8217; Blakely. He may have been the greatest player the game has ever seen, but today no one remembers his name. He was the first &#8211; and only &#8211; player to have his existence completely removed from the record books. Even his team is long forgotten, barely a footnote in the game&#8217;s history.    </p>
<p>                    Every effort was made to erase any evidence that William Blakely played professional baseball, and with good reason. Blockade Billy had a secret darker than any pill or injection that might cause a scandal in sports today. His secret was much, much worse . . . and only Stephen King, the most gifted storyteller of our age, can reveal the truth about the world, once and for all.     </p>
<p>                    The bonus story in MORALITY is a riveting short about Chad, an aspiring writer who is teaching in a school until he lands a publishing contract. His wife Nora is working as a home nurse for a retired minister. Like most people these days, they are struggling financially. And then Nora is approached by her employer with a proposition that could make their dream of a home in Vermont a reality. But will it be worth the moral consequences?    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blockade-billy-contains-the-chilling-bonus-story-morality-stephen-king/">Blockade Billy : Contains the chilling bonus story &#8216;Morality&#8217; &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year A Guardian book of the year &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year<br />
                              A Guardian book of the year<br />
                              &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times<br />
                              &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman<br />
                              &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith<br />
                              What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation?    </p>
<p>                              Offering nuanced and witty reflections on feminism, reality TV, the internet, drugs, identity and more, Trick Mirror is a multifaceted, thought-provoking and entertaining response to our zeitgeist &#8211; a must-read for anyone interested in the way we live and think today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teacher Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Staff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching    </p>
<p>                     Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically and mentally ill, things have gone too far. Unsurprisingly, these effects are highest in difficult-to-fill positions such as math, science, and foreign languages, and in urban areas and secondary classrooms-places where we need our teachers to be especially motivated and engaged. This book offers a path to resiliency to help teachers weather the storms and bounce back-and work toward banishing the rain for good.    </p>
<p>                     This actionable framework gives you concrete steps toward rediscovering yourself, your energy, and your passion for teaching. You&#8217;ll learn how a simple shift in mindset can affect your outlook, and how taking care of yourself physically, mentally, and emotionally is one of the most important things you can do. The companion workbook helps you put the framework into action, streamlining your way toward renewal and strength.    </p>
<p>                    Cultivate resilience with a four-part framework based on 12 key habits<br />
                    Uncover your true self, understand emotions, and use your energy where it counts<br />
                    Adopt a mindful, story-telling approach to communication and community building<br />
                    Keep learning, playing, and creating to create an environment of collective celebration    </p>
<p>                     By cultivating resilience in schools, we help ensure that we are working in, teaching in, and leading organizations where every child thrives, and where the potential of every child is recognized and nurtured. Onward provides a step-by-step plan for reigniting that spark.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smartest Kids in the World : And How They Got That Way &#8211; Amanda Ripley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Examinations & Assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secondary Schools]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Students & Student Organisations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of Gifted Students]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>America has long compared its students to top-performing kids of other nations. But how do the world&#8217;s education superpowers look through the eyes of an American high school student? Author Amanda Ripley follows three teenagers who chose to spend one school year living and learning in Finland, South Korea, and Poland. Through their adventures, Ripley [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/">The Smartest Kids in the World : And How They Got That Way &#8211; Amanda Ripley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>America has long compared its students to top-performing kids of other nations. But how do the world&#8217;s education superpowers look through the eyes of an American high school student? Author Amanda Ripley follows three teenagers who chose to spend one school year living and learning in Finland, South Korea, and Poland. Through their adventures, Ripley discovers startling truths about how attitudes, parenting, and rigorous teaching have revolutionized these countries&#8217; education results.     </p>
<p>                    In The Smartest Kids in the World, Ripley&#8217;s astonishing new insights reveal that top-performing countries have achieved greatness only in the past several decades; that the kids who live there are learning to think for themselves, partly through failing early and often; and that persistence, hard work, and resilience matter more to our children&#8217;s life chances than self-esteem or sports.     </p>
<p>                    Ripley&#8217;s investigative work seamlessly weaves narrative and research, providing in-depth analysis and gripping details that will keep you turning the pages. Written in a clear and engaging style, The Smartest Kids in the World will enliven public as well as dinner table debates over what makes for brighter and better students.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-kids-in-the-world-and-how-they-got-that-way-amanda-ripley-abridged/">The Smartest Kids in the World : And How They Got That Way &#8211; Amanda Ripley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are You Ready To Get The Most Out Of Yourself And Out Of Life?When it comes to getting fit, a lot of us find excuses. We&#8217;re too busy; we sleep in, we don&#8217;t feel like it. But what happens when we stop making excuses? David Goggins stopped making excuses and started giving life 100%. If [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads-abridged/">Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are You Ready To Get The Most Out Of Yourself And Out Of Life?When it comes to getting fit, a lot of us find excuses. We&#8217;re too busy; we sleep in, we don&#8217;t feel like it. But what happens when we stop making excuses?     </p>
<p>                    David Goggins stopped making excuses and started giving life 100%. If you&#8217;ve heard his name, it&#8217;s probably because this former Air Force serviceman and Navy SEAL is also an ultra-endurance athlete and once held a world record for the most pull-ups in 24 hours. He is one of the toughest people alive.     </p>
<p>                    His success wasn&#8217;t handed to him, though. Goggins had a terribly hard life. After surviving an abusive and traumatic childhood, he faced poverty and became overweight in his twenties. As a result of the trauma from his childhood, he was nearly illiterate as a teen. None of this stopped him, though.     </p>
<p>                    Now he&#8217;s here to help you stop backing away from challenges, too. In his book &#8220;Can&#8217;t Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds,&#8221; he teaches that the difficult things in life make you the strongest.     </p>
<p>                    If you are ready to get the most out of yourself and out of life, then you need this summary by Quick Reads. After reading this summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me, you&#8217;ll discover: What it takes to master your mind from someone who has overcome huge obstacles and become one of the toughest people on earth.How to break your mental roadblocks and take control of your success.How you can always come out stronger from any condition no matter how much trauma you&#8217;ve experiencedHow to work hard and push yourself to be your best self instead of believing in overnight successHow to be ready to dump your excuses and do and become better than ever before. And most importantly, how to become the master of your mind and achieve more than you thought possible using the 40% rule and much more&#8230; See the Table of Contents to find out by clicking on &#8220;Look inside.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    So, if you want a concise yet very informative summary book on Can&#8217;t Hurt Me that can help you grasp the insights, key ideas, and main points within minutes, simply scroll up and click the &#8220;BUY NOW&#8221; button for instant access!     </p>
<p>                    DISCLAIMER:      </p>
<p>                    This is not the official book, but an unofficial summary and analysis of the book &#8220;Can&#8217;t Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds by David Goggins bringing you the main points, concise and easy to consume. It is a way to get you the key ideas from great books and bestsellers in minutes, not hours. More knowledge in less time!     </p>
<p>                    QUICK READS = Learn Faster &#038; Get Smarter!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads-abridged/">Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decision Theory: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques in The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking, you will regularly find imaginative solutions to difficult challenges, and you will discover new ways of looking at your world and yourself&#8211;revealing previously hidden opportunities. The book offers real-life stories, explicit action items, and concrete methods that allow you to attain a deeper understanding of any issue, exploit the power of failure as a step toward success, develop a habit of creating probing questions, see the world of ideas as an ever-flowing stream of thought, and embrace the uplifting reality that we are all capable of change. No matter who you are, the practical mind-sets introduced in the book will empower you to realize any goal in a more creative, intelligent, and effective manner.<br />
                    Filled with engaging examples that unlock truths about thinking in every walk of life, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking is written for all who want to reach their fullest potential&#8211;including students, parents, teachers, businesspeople, professionals, athletes, artists, leaders, and lifelong learners. Whenever you are stuck, need a new idea, or want to learn and grow, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking will inspire and guide you on your way. To share thinking stories, go to: http://5elementsofthinking.wordpress.com/</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaving Microsoft To Change the World &#8211; John Wood (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leaving-microsoft-to-change-the-world-john-wood-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-profitmaking Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leaving-microsoft-to-change-the-world-john-wood-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>John Wood discovered his passion, his greatest success, and his life&#8217;s work not at business school or helping lead Microsoft&#8217;s charge into Asia in the 1990s but on a soul-searching trip to the Himalayas. He made the difficult decision to walk away from his lucrative career to create Room to Read, a nonprofit organization that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaving-microsoft-to-change-the-world-john-wood-abridged/">Leaving Microsoft To Change the World &#8211; John Wood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John Wood discovered his passion, his greatest success, and his life&#8217;s work not at business school or helping lead Microsoft&#8217;s charge into Asia in the 1990s but on a soul-searching trip to the Himalayas. He made the difficult decision to walk away from his lucrative career to create Room to Read, a nonprofit organization that promotes education across the developing world. By the end of 2007, the organization will have established over 5,000 libraries and 400 schools, and awarded long-term scholarships to more than 3,000 girls, giving more than one million children the lifelong gift of education.     </p>
<p>                    If you have ever pondered abandoning your desk job for an adventure and an opportunity to give back, Wood&#8217;s story will inspire you. He offers a vivid, emotional, and absorbing tale of how to take the lessons learned at a hard-charging company like Microsoft and apply them to the world&#8217;s most pressing social problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaving-microsoft-to-change-the-world-john-wood-abridged/">Leaving Microsoft To Change the World &#8211; John Wood (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Open Learning, Home Learning, Distance Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned education writer comes a fascinating examination of the rapidly shifting world of college that every parent, student and educator needs to understand. In 2011-2012, some of the world&#8217;s most famous universities and technology entrepreneurs began a revolution in higher education. College courses that had been kept from all but an elite few [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/">The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned education writer comes a fascinating examination of the rapidly shifting world of college that every parent, student and educator needs to understand.    </p>
<p>                    In 2011-2012, some of the world&#8217;s most famous universities and technology entrepreneurs began a revolution in higher education. College courses that had been kept from all but an elite few were released to students around the world &#8212; for free. And thanks to exploding tuition prices, a volatile global economy and some high-tech innovations, we&#8217;re now poised for a total rethinking of what college is and should be. In the NEW YORK TIMES-bestselling THE END OF COLLEGE, Kevin Carey draws on new research to paint an exciting portrait of the near future of education. He explains how the college experience is being radically altered now and how it will emancipate millions of people around the world. Insightful and readable, THE END OF COLLEGE is an innovative roadmap to understanding tomorrow&#8217;s higher education today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-college-creating-the-future-of-learning-and-the-university-of-everywhere-kevin-carey-abridged/">The End Of College : Creating the Future of Learning and the University of Everywhere &#8211; Kevin Carey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School?: A Cognitive Scientist Answers Questions About How the Mind Works and What It Means for the Classroom &#8211; Daniel T. Willingham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Research-based insights and practical advice about effective learning strategies In this new edition of the highly regarded Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School? cognitive psychologist Daniel Willingham turns his research on the biological and cognitive basis of learning into workable teaching techniques. This book will help you improve your teaching practice by explaining how you and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/">Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School?: A Cognitive Scientist Answers Questions About How the Mind Works and What It Means for the Classroom &#8211; Daniel T. Willingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Research-based insights and practical advice about effective learning strategies In this new edition of the highly regarded Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School? cognitive psychologist Daniel Willingham turns his research on the biological and cognitive basis of learning into workable teaching techniques. This book will help you improve your teaching practice by explaining how you and your students think and learn. It reveals the importance of story, emotion, memory, context, and routine in building knowledge and creating lasting learning experiences. With a treasure trove of updated material, this edition draws its themes from the most frequently asked questions in Willingham&#8217;s &#8216;Ask the Cognitive Scientist&#8217; column in the American Educator. How can you teach students the skills they need when standardized testing just requires facts? Why do students remember everything on TV, but forget everything you say? How can you adjust your teaching for different learning styles? Read this book for the answers to these questions and for practical advice on helping your learners learn better. Discover easy-to-understand, evidence-based principles with clear applications for the classroom Update yourself on the latest cognitive science research and new, teacher-tested pedagogical tools Learn about Willingham&#8217;s surprising findings, such as that you cannot develop &#8216;thinking skills&#8217; without facts Understand the brain&#8217;s workings to help you hone your teaching skills Why Students Don&#8217;t Like School is a valuable resource for both veteran and novice teachers, teachers-in-training, and for the principals, administrators, and staff development professionals who work with them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/">Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School?: A Cognitive Scientist Answers Questions About How the Mind Works and What It Means for the Classroom &#8211; Daniel T. Willingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
