<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Biochemistry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/biochemistry/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/biochemistry/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Biochemistry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/biochemistry/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</title>
		<link>/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Break the rules, not the fast with world-renowned biohacker and New York Times bestselling author Dave Asprey. For more than a decade, the Bulletproof founder Dave Asprey has shared his unique point of view and expertise to help fans become the best versions of themselves. From living longer to getting smarter, maximising performance to practising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/">Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Break the rules, not the fast with world-renowned biohacker and New York Times bestselling author Dave Asprey.</p>
<p>                              For more than a decade, the Bulletproof founder Dave Asprey has shared his unique point of view and expertise to help fans become the best versions of themselves. From living longer to getting smarter, maximising performance to practising mindfulness, Dave&#8217;s followers look to him for his take on the most effective techniques to become healthier and more powerful than most doctors think is possible.</p>
<p>                              Asprey has been fasting for years, long before it gained widespread popularity, and if you&#8217;re a fan of The Bulletproof Diet, you have been enjoying some of the benefits of Intermittent Fasting too.</p>
<p>                              In Fast This Way, Dave asks readers to forget everything they think they know about the ancient practice and takes them on a journey through cutting-edge science to examine the ways novice fasters and Intermittent Fasting loyalists can up-end their relationship with food and upgrade their fasting game beyond calorie restriction.  </p>
<p>                     What IF eating the right foods at the right time can actually enhance your fast?<br />
                     What IF how you work out and sleep could trick your body into thinking you are fasting?<br />
                     What IF it were easy to skip a meal, or two, or three?<br />
                     What IF fasting is different for women, can be personalised to your genes, and can impact your mental health?<br />
                     What IF all fasts could be created equal?</p>
<p>                              Fast This Way is a compelling read through the latest thinking on fasting and gives readers the manual and toolkit to make the most of their fasts and their personal biology.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fast-this-way-burn-fat-heal-inflammation-and-eat-like-the-high-performing-human-you-were-meant-to-be-dave-asprey/">Fast This Way : Burn Fat, Heal Inflammation and Eat Like the High-Performing Human You Were Meant to be &#8211; Dave Asprey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life. Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211; probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life.     </p>
<p>                    Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of<br />
                    nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211;<br />
                    probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine rock formations and fossil charcoals<br />
                    all tell the same story. High oxygen levels may also explain the global firestorm that contributed to the<br />
                    demise of the dinosaurs after the asteroid impact.    </p>
<p>                    The strange and profound effects that oxygen has had on the evolution of life pose a riddle, which this book<br />
                    sets out to answer. Oxygen is a toxic gas. Divers breathing pure oxygen at depth suffer from convulsions<br />
                    and lung injury. Fruit flies raised at twice normal atmospheric levels of oxygen live half as long as their<br />
                    siblings. Reactive forms of oxygen, known as free radicals, are thought to cause ageing in people. Yet if<br />
                    atmospheric oxygen reached 35 per cent in the Carboniferous, why did it promote exuberant growth,<br />
                    instead of rapid ageing and death?    </p>
<p>                    Oxygen takes the reader on an enthralling journey, as gripping as a thriller, as it unravels the unexpected<br />
                    ways in which oxygen spurred the evolution of life and death. The book explains far more than the size of<br />
                    ancient insects: it shows how oxygen underpins the origin of biological complexity, the birth of photosynthesis, the sudden evolution of animals, the need for two sexes, the accelerated ageing of cloned animals like Dolly the sheep, and the surprisingly long lives of bats and birds.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on this grand evolutionary canvas, Oxygen offers fresh perspectives on our own lives and deaths,<br />
                    explaining modern killer diseases, why we age, and what we can do about it. Advancing revelatory new ideas,<br />
                    following chains of evidence, the book ranges through many disciplines, from environmental sciences to<br />
                    molecular medicine. The result is a captivating vision of contemporary science and a humane synthesis of our<br />
                    place in nature. This remarkable book might just redefine the way we think about the world.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bio-ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Ethics & Professional Conduct]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Her name was Henrietta Lacks, but scientists know her as HeLa. Born a poor black tobacco farmer, her cancer cells &#8211; taken without her knowledge &#8211; became a multimillion-dollar industry and one of the most important tools in medicine. Yet Henrietta&#8217;s family did not learn of her &#8216;immortality&#8217; until more than twenty years after her [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/">The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Her name was Henrietta Lacks, but scientists know her as HeLa. Born a poor black tobacco farmer, her cancer cells &#8211; taken without her knowledge &#8211; became a multimillion-dollar industry and one of the most important tools in medicine. Yet Henrietta&#8217;s family did not learn of her &#8216;immortality&#8217; until more than twenty years after her death, with devastating consequences . . .     </p>
<p>                    Rebecca Skloot&#8217;s fascinating account is the story of the life, and afterlife, of one woman who changed the medical world forever. Balancing the beauty and drama of scientific discovery with dark questions about who owns the stuff our bodies are made of, The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks is an extraordinary journey in search of the soul and story of a real woman, whose cells live on today in all four corners of the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/">The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
